<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing on Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 02:02:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[A crash course on what changing the US bond rate means, and why it is considered such an important factor for US and global markets and economies]]></title><description><![CDATA[INTRO

Yesterday, somebody in the comments of some thread asked for an ELI5 on why US
bond rates matter and what their relationship is with markets and economies.
What I wrote ended up being more like an ELI12, and also ended up being quite
long; in any case, I have decided to modify it a bit and…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxoj2i/a_crash_course_on_what_changing_the_us_bond_rate/?score=493&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxoj2i%2Fa_crash_course_on_what_changing_the_us_bond_rate%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxoj2i%2Fa_crash_course_on_what_changing_the_us_bond_rate%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxoj2i/a_crash_course_on_what_changing_the_us_bond_rate/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 01:08:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Intro&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Yesterday, somebody in the comments of some thread asked for an ELI5 on why US bond rates matter and what their relationship is with markets and economies. What I wrote ended up being more like an ELI12, and also ended up being quite long; in any case, I have decided to modify it a bit and turn it into its own post.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;What are bonds&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;First, an introduction on what bonds actually are. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Simply put, a bond is the &amp;amp;quot;asset side&amp;amp;quot; of governmental or corporate debt. When a government or corporation borrows money, the borrower now holds a liability, and the lender holds an asset, which is expected to return them their original investment (the money they lent) plus profit (interest) at some later date. A bond is basically a token that says some government or company owes you some amount of principal by some date known as the maturity date (usually 3 months to 30 years, depending on the type of bond), plus interest. Because bonds are a tokenization of debt, they can be easily traded in a liquid, open market, just like stocks. This means that the original lender does not need to be the person who is repaid when the bond matures; the repayment and interest simply goes to whomever holds the bond at the time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are two main types of bonds: corporate bonds, and government bonds. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Corporate bonds are the main way companies raise money, apart from selling shares. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Government bonds are how the government raises money to cover budget deficits (ie: when the government spends more than they have the tax revenue to spend, they borrow the remainder by selling bonds to whomever will buy them). If nobody is buying the government bonds, the interest will go up organically due to supply and demand until people are willing to buy them. Government bonds are often known as &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;treasuries&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, and are broken down into three categories: treasury notes (short-term maturity), treasury bills (mid-term maturity), and treasury bonds (long-term maturity).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One of the main buyers of US government bonds is the Federal Reserve, which is the name of America&amp;amp;#39;s central bank. This is the entity that is able to actually print US dollars. Everyone has heard of things like how the US government recently ran huge deficits due to &amp;amp;quot;stimulus spending&amp;amp;quot;, and that it printed the money it needed for that spending. Well, this is a slightly inaccurate picture of how it works. The government chooses fiscal policy, which means they build the budget and they set the tax rates. They are the ones who choose to overspend and run a deficit. However, they don&amp;amp;#39;t choose monetary policy: they cannot print money. This power was delegated by congress to the Federal Reserve over 100 years ago. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, when the government runs a deficit, they sell bonds to borrow the money. If the FED chooses to, it can print a whole bunch of money and then lend that money to the government (ie: the taxpayer) by buying the government bonds with it. That is how newly printed money actually gets into the economy: the FED prints it and then lends it out to companies and to the government by buying corporate and government bonds. When the FED buys a bunch of treasuries (government bonds), it is really lending out freshly-printed cash to the American people (since the government&amp;amp;#39;s liabilities are really the taxpayers&amp;amp;#39; liabilities), and the people then owe that money, with interest, back to the FED by the time the treasury matures. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When the FED decides to buy up the government&amp;amp;#39;s bonds in order to lend to the taxpayers the money that congress is spending, they are also putting downward pressure on the bond interest rate. This is because, if the FED decided &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;not&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; to lend a bunch of money to the government to cover its deficits, the bond interest would organically rise through supply &amp;amp;amp; demand until other buyers (individuals, companies, foreign investors, whatever) are willing to buy those bonds.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, when the FED wants to keep bond interest low, they achieve this indirectly by creating what is basically artificial demand for US bonds by buying a ton of them with money that they printed at no cost to themselves. Due to how supply &amp;amp;amp; demand works with debt, the more demand there is for bonds, the lower the interest those bonds offer.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, the Federal Reserve executes its main task of managing the US bond rate by choosing how much government debt it buys. If they want bond rates to go up, they will print less cash and buy fewer bonds. If they want it to go down, they will print more cash and buy more bonds.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The FED is essentially a whale with the power to print money, who uses said printed money to manipulate the US bond market, ostensibly for the good of everybody.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;The risk-free rate&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The interest rate on American government bonds is considered one of the most important variables in the American (and even worldwide) economy. This is because the American gov is considered the de-facto safest borrower of all borrowers in the world. In other words, if I buy an American government bond, I am lending my money to the entity that is considered to have the smallest risk of defaulting in the world (maybe this is arguable, but regardless this is a premise that is at the core of the world economy; what&amp;amp;#39;s important is that people believe it).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There is a concept in economics called the &amp;amp;quot;risk-free rate&amp;amp;quot;. This is the interest you can get for lending your money to a 0-risk borrower, and should logically be the lowest interest rate you see anywhere in that economy. Of course, there is always technically some risk when you lend money, so the risk-free rate is technically imaginary. However, in practice, just about everybody considers the US bond rate (specifically, treasury bills, the US bond with the shortest maturity) to be the risk-free rate, as the risk is considered to be so low as to be negligible. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, if buying American gov bonds is the safest way to lend money, it means that every single other form of loan must pay higher interest. Why? Because every other borrower is considered higher risk, and for me as a lender, I will not accept less interest for greater risk. So, if American bond interest goes up, all other loan interest (corporate bonds, bank loans, mortgages, credit cards, whatever) will organically go up, because everything must pay greater interest than American bonds to compensate for greater risk. This is simply a matter of supply &amp;amp;amp; demand mechanics.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, American bond interest is kind of like the baseline or the &amp;amp;quot;sea level&amp;amp;quot; for all interest rates in the entire economy. This even stretches to other countries, because anyone can buy a bond from the US gov, and they are considered the safest borrower in the world, so nobody will ever lend money to anybody else unless they are compensated with greater interest than US bond interest.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;The cost of capital&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, if US bond rates go up, and therefore all interest in the economy goes up, that means money itself has gotten more expensive. Loan interest is literally just the cost of money (known as the cost of capital). The lesser the interest, the cheaper it is for me to acquire money right now. When you realize that the entire world runs mainly on debt, it becomes clear how significant this phenomenon is.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, when US bond rates go up, the price of capital itself goes up. That means it becomes more costly for businesses to raise money, more costly to mortgage a house, more costly to open a line of credit to buy investments, more costly to spend with credit cards, more costly to use leverage in securities markets, etc.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This means that growth goes down, spending goes down, wages go down, etc. It also means the prices of goods go down (or at least climb slower), because people aren&amp;amp;#39;t willing to pay as much, since capital itself is more expensive to acquire.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What happens when prices go down? Well, that&amp;amp;#39;s a reduction in inflation. So, when inflation is getting too high, the FED (central bank) will make bond interest go up to apply recessive forces on the economy to curb said inflation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If inflation is low, the FED might reduce bond interest in order to make the cost of capital lower to juice the economy, prop up securities markets, and incentivize growth. Too much growth though, and we end up with inflation again, meaning the FED might increase rates again. This causes a sort of wave-like dance between bond rates and the heat of the economy.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, the FED influences bond rates ostensibly to keep the economy balanced: not too hot and inflationary (can be very bad) and not too cold and deflationary (also can be very bad).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is also worth noting that the FED wields a couple other levers it can use to increase or decrease the cost of capital (ie: the general interest rates in the economy) that are separate from bond rates. They can change the reserve requirements of banks (what percentage of total assets a bank must hold in reserve). If banks need to hold more in reserve, then they have less liquid money to lend out, so the supply of capital goes down, so market interest (cost of capital) rises. Also, the FED can change the discount rate, which is the amount of interest they charge banks for short-term loans (24 hours less) from the FED itself.  When these rates go up, banks are disincentivized from borrowing from the FED, so the bank&amp;amp;#39;s end up with less liquid capital, which means they need to be more conservative about the loans they themselves give out, which makes the supply of capital go down and thus the cost of capital go up.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;What does this mean for markets?&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now, when bond rates go up, most investment markets go down. Why? Well, the higher bond rates go, the more I can make by investing in bonds, without the risk going up. So, as bond rates go up, it becomes more and more attractive to move my wealth out of riskier markets like stocks and into what is considered the safest investment market in the world: US bonds. Since rates going up means I get greater returns on my bond investments, but the risk doesn&amp;amp;#39;t change, US gov bonds become more and more sensible to an investor as the rates increase.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Of course, bonds rates going up a smidgen doesn&amp;amp;#39;t actually suddenly make bonds a strategically more sound investment than riskier things like stocks. In fact, US bond rates have been so comically low for so long that it hasn&amp;amp;#39;t made much sense to buy bonds in years (decades, really). However, when people hear that the FED is going to increase bond rates, they think &amp;amp;quot;bond rates going up means people will sell stocks to buy bonds, so I better sell now to front-run that&amp;amp;quot;, which is the main thing that &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;actually&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; causes stocks to fall when bond rates increase.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How crypto will fare with increasing bond rates is unknown, because rates have been declining ever since BTC was born, until very recently. Personally, I imagine crypto will follow stocks down if rates go up too much, but nobody knows for sure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Some historical context&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;US bond rates hit an ATH in 1981 around 15%. Unsurprisingly, the stock market hit a low at the same time (like I said before, you should expect an inverse relationship between bond rates and most securities markets). Think about how ridiculous 15% bond rates are. That would mean you could buy what is definitionally the safest investment available and get 15% returns each year. By contrast, the safest stock ETFs (still way riskier than US bonds) average like 7% a year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, in the 80s, you could double your money every 5 years while accepting what is usually considered 0 risk. Ever wonder why boomers seemed to get wealthy so easily? This is one of the reasons.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Since the ATH in 1981, the treasury note rate has fallen continuously until Covid hit, at which point it pivoted at a low of about 0.5%. Since then, it has been going back up, but is still extremely low, at around 1.5%.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Since bond rates going down means stocks go up, the stock market has been in a tremendous and arguably unnatural bull run for about 40 years, only pausing twice very briefly for &amp;amp;quot;corrections&amp;amp;quot; circa 1999 and 2008.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Since US bond rates have gotten so close to 0%, they can&amp;amp;#39;t really lower them any further without going negative (which is actually a thing, and some countries are trying negative interest now. This is related to Modern Monetary Theory, and is an extremely weird rabbit hole that nobody really knows the true consequences of yet. Imagine getting paid to borrow money. Some countries have been experimenting with this over the last 7 years). The chair of the FED (Jerome Powell) said a few months back that they have no intention of going to negative interest rates, so that means these past 40 years of propping up markets by reducing bond rates has probably come to an end. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You could think of the continuous lowering of rates for the last 40 years as the FED spending its ammunition to prop up markets and propel economic growth, but now that rates are barely above 0% and the FED isn&amp;amp;#39;t willing to go negative, they are out of ammo. Not only are they out of ammo when it comes to lowering the rates, but they are also currently incentivized to &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;increase&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; rates to combat rising inflation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is why there is fear. The FED has been sticking its hands in for 40 years to prop up markets, and now it seems they are going to stop, at least for now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I hope this &amp;lt;del&amp;gt;ELI5&amp;lt;/del&amp;gt; &amp;lt;del&amp;gt;ELI12&amp;lt;/del&amp;gt; ELI-an-Intro-to-Econ student about why US gov bond rates are such an important concept for understanding global economics has been enlightening!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MATIC brought down by some flowers?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I was bullish on MATIC since I got into crypto, a few days ago I decided to
actually use their network to mint some NFTs my brother and I came up with and
oh man has my view on MATIC changed fast!

Not only was it a pain just getting into and established on the network, some
damn sunflower game…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxmjwh/matic_brought_down_by_some_flowers/?score=309&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxmjwh%2Fmatic_brought_down_by_some_flowers%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxmjwh%2Fmatic_brought_down_by_some_flowers%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxmjwh/matic_brought_down_by_some_flowers/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 01:08:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I was bullish on MATIC since I got into crypto, a few days ago I decided to actually use their network to mint some NFTs my brother and I came up with and oh man has my view on MATIC changed fast!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Not only was it a pain just getting into and established on the network, some damn sunflower game came along and brought the network down! We’re talking increased fees and while still cheaper then ETH I’m hear talking of tx’s costing up to a few MATIC from fractions of one per tx. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And now the MATIC mainnet is down so like yeaaaa gonna go ahead and not be as bullish on this one.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Technical analysis: the Camel Theory. This bullrun is not over yet. I'm 100% sure.]]></title><description><![CDATA[So as you may already know... Bitcoin dipped a little, which of course isn't the
first time in cryptocurrency history. As a crypto veteran (hodling since
November 2021) I'm still very bullish right so I figured doing some technical
analysis for my fellow r/cryptocurrency [/r/cryptocurrency]…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxbtwh/technical_analysis_the_camel_theory_this_bullrun/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxbtwh%2Ftechnical_analysis_the_camel_theory_this_bullrun%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxbtwh%2Ftechnical_analysis_the_camel_theory_this_bullrun%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxbtwh/technical_analysis_the_camel_theory_this_bullrun/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 23:40:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So as you may already know... Bitcoin dipped a little, which of course isn&amp;amp;#39;t the first time in cryptocurrency history. As a crypto veteran (hodling since November 2021) I&amp;amp;#39;m still very bullish right so I figured doing some technical analysis for my fellow &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/r/cryptocurrency&quot;&amp;gt;r/cryptocurrency&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; members. I came up with the &amp;amp;#39;Camel Theory&amp;amp;#39;. Bear with me (no pun intended).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;The 1 day chart&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/d3yzzt5eq1a81.jpg?width=1530&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=3c2a63be9fd6bd04dec4585f00599b61cd25c54d&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/d3yzzt5eq1a81.jpg?width=1530&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=3c2a63be9fd6bd04dec4585f00599b61cd25c54d&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As you can see here, these were critical support points for the last few days.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;The 1 week chart&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/5uld34moq1a81.jpg?width=1528&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=4269814696faac50152ca408b3191fd04d18ec15&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/5uld34moq1a81.jpg?width=1528&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=4269814696faac50152ca408b3191fd04d18ec15&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At this point you can&amp;amp;#39;t really tell what a resistance or support zone is anymore. I drew some lines to pretend to know what I&amp;amp;#39;m doing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;The 1 month chart&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/3bxl7e95r1a81.jpg?width=1522&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=3f3191010ae205a92e98adff7ba72652784eeedb&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/3bxl7e95r1a81.jpg?width=1522&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=3f3191010ae205a92e98adff7ba72652784eeedb&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;OK so these two horizontal lines clearly are resistance points. Cool huh. Bitcoin seems to go up and down.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;The 1 year chart&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ttrxfv0fr1a81.jpg?width=1526&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=b65f0dd44aa9806140e68e94203bec69c8ee7ea8&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/ttrxfv0fr1a81.jpg?width=1526&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=b65f0dd44aa9806140e68e94203bec69c8ee7ea8&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So this is the Camel Theory I was talking about. Please note: this is still just a theory I am working on. I am not sure if it will work out. But according to this theory, Bitcoin will go up again anytime this year. The 1 year chart has two peaks. The two humps on the camel&amp;amp;#39;s back resembles these two peaks. It&amp;amp;#39;s not rocket science.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Feel free to ask me any questions about this theory and I&amp;amp;#39;ll do my best to answer them. Bottomline is that this isn&amp;amp;#39;t the first time Bitcoin is dipping and we shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t panic. Some of you asked for a dip... well... here it is. And if people are in for the long haul... this dip shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t worry you at all.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What causes both Crypto and Stock market to drop like it did?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I hear many reasons like Covid or other factors, such as regulations but what
about this time? It affects both markets so it doesn't have anything to do with
only crypto, which we could blame on regulations being implemented or being
considered.

And it definitely isn't whales since stocks dropped…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxlcm5/what_causes_both_crypto_and_stock_market_to_drop/?score=335&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxlcm5%2Fwhat_causes_both_crypto_and_stock_market_to_drop%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxlcm5%2Fwhat_causes_both_crypto_and_stock_market_to_drop%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxlcm5/what_causes_both_crypto_and_stock_market_to_drop/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 23:40:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I hear many reasons like Covid or other factors, such as regulations but what about this time? It affects both markets so it doesn&amp;amp;#39;t have anything to do with only crypto, which we could blame on regulations being implemented or being considered.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And it definitely isn&amp;amp;#39;t whales since stocks dropped too, so how does it make sense for everything to drop? Very curious to know the answer, maybe it really is because of the new variants of the disease but people still aren&amp;amp;#39;t certain about it to sell their investments.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lawyer question: what if the Trias Politica in a hypothetical country is broken? When executive power grants itself eternal emergency powers. When legislative power is bamboozled or bribed into passing emergency laws. When judiciary power is thus bypassed. Is there a legal fix? https://t.co/b8ZPnG3aFu]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1479217211617198088/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1479217211617198088/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 22:44:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1.6.22: UK infection rates among fully vaxxed now HIGHER &amp; RISING FASTER than among unvaxxed in ALL adult cohorts. Vaxxed &amp; unvaxxed of all ages continue to get infected &amp; spread - and in most age groups, the vaxxed much more so - rendering vaxx passports &amp; mandates pointless. https://t.co/wLXWLkurlf]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1479205638223933446/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1479205638223933446/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 21:46:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Yesterday a scammer/shiller who masqueraded as an investor with a “discovery” made a post that shot straight to the top of this sub]]></title><description><![CDATA[On January 5, a user made a post here on cryptocurrency about a new NFT game
they “discovered”. The game has its own token on the Binance Smart Chain.


THE POST WAS SWIFTFULLY AND RIGHTFULLY DELETED BY THE MODS BEFORE IT COULD DO
MUCH DAMAGE, BUT NOT BEFORE IT GOT TO THE FRONTPAGE OF THIS SUB.

In…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxfs5n/yesterday_a_scammershiller_who_masqueraded_as_an/?score=307&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxfs5n%2Fyesterday_a_scammershiller_who_masqueraded_as_an%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxfs5n%2Fyesterday_a_scammershiller_who_masqueraded_as_an%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxfs5n/yesterday_a_scammershiller_who_masqueraded_as_an/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 21:45:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On January 5, a user made a post here on cryptocurrency about a new NFT game they “discovered”. The game has its own token on the Binance Smart Chain.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;The post was swiftfully and rightfully deleted by the mods before it could do much damage, but not before it got to the frontpage of this sub.&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In fact, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/fEuukUf.png&quot;&amp;gt;the post made it to the top&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Right off the bat, this was extremely suspicious because:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Upvotes are still hidden which means it’s a very new post&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;It got to the top 8 posts of the sub when it was half an hour old then quickly kept going up from there&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;It only had a few comments and more than ⅓  of them were from the OP&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Normally when a very young post makes it to the top of the frontpage, it has an insane level of engagement and high variety comments from other users gained in a super short time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But this was not the case here.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;I come from a marketing background and know firsthand how easy it is to “hack” social media platforms like reddit to make something go viral artificially.&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Coincidentally a few months ago, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/pqnd3s/i_did_a_little_digging_on_the_latest_shitcoin/&quot;&amp;gt;I also found a network of paid accounts&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and bot accounts on reddit that crypto scammers use to boost their rugpull posts of new coins (you know the ones with titles like 🚀🚀 Anal Inu Coin 🚀🚀🌕 🌕).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So just from the points above, I was 95% sure it was just a lost rugpuller who probably meant to post it on the other less-moderated crypto subreddits.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But no.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This rugpuller had the audacity to pretend to be a new investor who had just “discovered” an amazing gem, so I wanted to dig a little more.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Checking the user behind the post sealed the deal as a bought-for shiller&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here’s a screenshot of their &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/SkkTfjr&quot;&amp;gt;post history&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/cblIPdB&quot;&amp;gt;comment history&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;More suspicious things pop up here that says: this is 100% not a genuine person and this was not a genuine post:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Account had 0 post activity in 3 years&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Also 0 comment activity in 1 year&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Absolutely no crypto-related content in any comments of posts in the history of the account&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Despite all that, the account comes out of the shadows and suddenly starts making posts about a new crypto game in multiple places.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Let&amp;amp;#39;s look at their post and how they masqueraded as an innocent user who just wanted to share their discovery&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here are &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/TfhgkgH.png&quot;&amp;gt;direct quotes from the post&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; before it was deleted:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;“Hey guys, just wanted to let you all know about this new Crypto Game called &amp;amp;quot;Moonscape&amp;amp;quot;.”&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This first sentence of the post is not the language of someone who just discovered a game. This is the script of someone making a promotional video.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;“It is the first game launched on the Seascape Lighthouse IDO project, but made by a very successful team. Definitely worth checking out and for sure can 100X very quickly.”&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve read a lot of DDs and research pieces on this sub, and the only posts that compliment the devs but don’t give names or examples of what the devs actually accomplished are scam posts.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you look at how genuine newbies post and talk here, they all ask if a project is legit. They don’t confidently guarantee lambos.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;“Moonscape is a resource strategy management #DeFi NFT Game that takes place on a futuristic moon. Players scramble for limited resources to develop their burgeoning cities.”&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The only people who use hashtags in new coin posts are the rugpullers behind the new coin.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;*“The game will be brower based, with phone apps coming later in the year. Direct payment to moonscape token will also be availble in the game at a later date the devs have stated. Please keep an eye out for this one, its going to be masive.”
*
More marketing-derived language.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Besides, if the game hasn’t launched yet how did the user discover it? Lmao&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;“MSCP Token is a BSC token and availble on Pancake swap, but i think the native token is on the Moonriver network. You can use the meter.passport to swap fro m BSC to moonriver which will enable you to stake the coins. I believe staking is around 70% at the moment, and you can take your coins out whenever you want without penalty. Moonriver is part of the Moonbeam network on Kusama I belive.”&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;More language that looks lifted from a brochure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This time they added “I think” and “I believe” because they’re a third party and totally not affiliated with it. They’re 100% impartial and are just guessing things. Sure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;“Id be happy to answer any questions if you have any as well :)”*&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They got their message mixed up here in the end.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What kind of new investor who just discovered a “massive” project is confident enough to take questions? If they know so much, why did they talk about the specifics in the previous section with such uncertainty?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;They also kept up the charade in the comments and had lots of replies to innocent users&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do these sound like they came from someone who’s impartial to the completely new not launched yet project they just discovered?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/9qblSaW.png&quot;&amp;gt;OP sure knows a lot about this game&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; that hasn’t launched yet for someone who’s not involved in it&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Telling people to &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/5k07B43.png&quot;&amp;gt;send you PMs&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; is always a sure fire way to convince them you’re not a scammer yes&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Apparently &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gCtmbMc.png&quot;&amp;gt;100x returns is realistic and genuine&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It’s honestly hilarious.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It’s like they started with a genius idea to pretend to be a normal person, but abandoned it halfway through their post then went all in on shilling in the comments.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;TLDR&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Scammers, shillers, rugpullers have a network of accounts to boost their posts to the top of subreddits, including here on /cryptocurrency.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Be mindful of the language in the post and look into the user before you believe anything.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Red days are the true FOMO but you need to control yourselves.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Prices are down, and you can't buy?

Do you feel the fear of missing out a good buying opportunity?

Yeah, then you should control yourselves. People will tell you to buy the dip
and they may be right BUT your investments shouldn't be driven by FOMO.

If you have a plan, stick to your plan. If you…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxb7hg/red_days_are_the_true_fomo_but_you_need_to/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxb7hg%2Fred_days_are_the_true_fomo_but_you_need_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxb7hg%2Fred_days_are_the_true_fomo_but_you_need_to%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxb7hg/red_days_are_the_true_fomo_but_you_need_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 20:45:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Prices are down, and you can&amp;amp;#39;t buy? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do you feel the fear of missing out a good buying opportunity? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Yeah, then you should control yourselves. People will tell you to buy the dip and they may be right BUT your investments shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t be driven by FOMO. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you have a plan, stick to your plan. If you have money to invest in red times, spread the sell orders and don&amp;amp;#39;t throw too much at the market. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Don&amp;amp;#39;t invest more than you can afford to lose. This is even more true during red days. The opportunity seems very good but you never know the bottom of the dip. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please act rationally and not with your emotions. DCAing doesn&amp;amp;#39;t mean throwing money at dips in hope that the market goes back up. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You don&amp;amp;#39;t need to buy every dip, in the end consistency is more rewarded. Good luck out there!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wtf is going on?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ive watched the stock market, crypto market, and precious metal market for a the
past 5ish years. One thing I always found fascinating is the way the markets
move together, most common example, one going up while another goes down and the
third not doing anything noteworthy.

Since this whole GME…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxefap/wtf_is_going_on/?score=367&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxefap%2Fwtf_is_going_on%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxefap%2Fwtf_is_going_on%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxefap/wtf_is_going_on/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 20:45:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Ive watched the stock market, crypto market, and precious metal market for a the past 5ish years. One thing I always found fascinating is the way the markets move together, most common example, one going up while another goes down and the third not doing anything noteworthy.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Since this whole GME thing last year, I’ve watch the crypto and stock markets move almost in tandem with each other, but metals markets still did their independent thing…until lately. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;All three markets are down and look like they are starting to Synchronize and start moving in tandem. And I will tell you I don’t know what it means but it scares the hell out of me.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My goal for 2022 is to get to 0.1 BTC]]></title><description><![CDATA[It ain't much but it's an honest goal. Gonna stack!]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rx2ekf/my_goal_for_2022_is_to_get_to_01_btc/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frx2ekf%2Fmy_goal_for_2022_is_to_get_to_01_btc%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frx2ekf%2Fmy_goal_for_2022_is_to_get_to_01_btc%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rx2ekf/my_goal_for_2022_is_to_get_to_01_btc/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 19:34:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It ain&amp;amp;#39;t much but it&amp;amp;#39;s an honest goal. Gonna stack!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Great Readjustment: understanding where we are and where we're headed]]></title><description><![CDATA[On November 10th, 2021, Bitcoin reached a high around $69,000. As I type this,
the current price is $42,948. But this post isn't about the price. It's about
where we are and where we're headed, in terms of the 4 year halving-to-halving
cycle.

We're almost halfway to the next Halving.

You probably…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rx4tt1/the_great_readjustment_understanding_where_we_are/?score=315&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frx4tt1%2Fthe_great_readjustment_understanding_where_we_are%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frx4tt1%2Fthe_great_readjustment_understanding_where_we_are%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rx4tt1/the_great_readjustment_understanding_where_we_are/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 19:34:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On November 10th, 2021, Bitcoin reached a high around $69,000.  As I type this, the current price is $42,948.  But this post isn&amp;amp;#39;t about the price.  It&amp;amp;#39;s about where we are and where we&amp;amp;#39;re headed, in terms of the 4 year halving-to-halving cycle.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;We&amp;amp;#39;re almost halfway to the next Halving.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You probably know what the halving is.  Let&amp;amp;#39;s talk about the effect the halving has.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Every ten minutes, a miner wins a block reward, and that&amp;amp;#39;s a big deal because block rewards are the only way new Bitcoin is created.  Right now, the block reward is 6.25 BTC.  Thus, every ten minutes, 6.25 BTC is created and awarded to a miner.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In May 2024, the block reward will be cut in half, to 3.125 BTC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That doesn&amp;amp;#39;t sound like a big change unless you&amp;amp;#39;re a miner, but add up the block rewards over time and you&amp;amp;#39;ll see how much of a difference the halving makes on the supply of newly mined coins hitting the market:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;6.25 BTC are mined every ten minutes (roughly).  This is the current block reward.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;6.25 X 6 = 37.5 BTC are mined every hour.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;37.5 X 24 = 900 BTC are mined every day.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;900 X 30 = 27,000 BTC are mined every month.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;27,000 X 4 = 108,000 BTC are mined every four months.  I use four months as a reference point here because it takes around four months for the halving to cause an imbalance of supply and demand, better known as a supply shock.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;The Supply Shock Of 2024:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In May 2024, the halving will cut the block reward in half, from 6.25 BTC down to 3.125 BTC.  Price is where supply meets demand, and the halving cuts the supply of new coins in half.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;By the beginning of fall, 2024, instead of having 108,000 BTC added to the supply since May, only 54,000 will have been added (because The Halving cut the block reward in half).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That decrease is what causes a supply shock.  The supply drops, which means there won&amp;amp;#39;t be enough supply to meet the demand, which means the price will keep rising until demand drops enough to put supply and demand in balance again.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here&amp;amp;#39;s an easy way to understand a supply shock:  Imagine that you have to attend a huge meeting every morning for a week.  Luckily, they provide enough coffee for everybody.  But one day, there&amp;amp;#39;s only half as much coffee.  The supply of coffee was cut in half but the demand is still the same, so there&amp;amp;#39;s not enough.  People are getting pissed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the marketplace, price is set by demand.  When the supply of BTC being sold goes down, the price keeps going up until there isn&amp;amp;#39;t enough demand to buy it at a higher price.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Price is where supply meets demand:  how much is being sold and how much are buyers willing to pay.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But we all know it isn&amp;amp;#39;t that simple in reality.  In 2024, miners will start hoarding coins instead of selling them, because they anticipate higher prices.  This will make the supply shock worse because it will drop the supply of coins being sold even lower.  And rising prices causes hype, which will drive demand even higher, which will push prices even higher.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;But It Ain&amp;amp;#39;t 2024 Yet!&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A typical halving-to-halving four year cycle looks like this:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Halving, followed by around 4 months of hoarding, where people hold on to their coins rather than sell them, anticipating higher prices.  This is followed by a bull run of around a year and a crash that goes on for a few months, which is followed by a roughly 2 year period of readjustment that lasts until the next halving.  I think we&amp;amp;#39;re somewhere between the crash and readjustment phase now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Maybe we&amp;amp;#39;ll see a crash, maybe we won&amp;amp;#39;t.  Institutional money may have disrupted the usual post-bull-run crash, or at least lessened it.  Or not.  Only time will tell.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s easy to feel despair as the price of Bitcoin drops, but I view this as an opportunity.  I think you should too.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just as the last 4 year cycle was the last chance to buy at 4 digit prices, this 4 year cycle may be the last chance to buy at 5 digit prices.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is the time to accumulate.  Buy while you can and hold, because 2024 will be here before you know it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Secure your coins, preferably in a hardware wallet.  Make sure your seed phrase is secured for the long haul.  Have a plan in place for passing on your coins if you die...  just in case.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;P.S.:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If declining prices are causing you anguish, walk away for a while.  Don&amp;amp;#39;t sell, but DO stop checking the price and reading forums and the news if doing so causes you more pain than pleasure.  Take care of your mental health.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;KEEP CALM&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
AND&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
HODL ON&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(Sorry for the edit.  I wrote this rather quickly &amp;amp;amp; I found a typo)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This guy has a magical skill to predict where you should go and buy more Bitcoin. Go on and HODL]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rxi8g3/this_guy_has_a_magical_skill_to_predict_where_you/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frxi8g3%2Fthis_guy_has_a_magical_skill_to_predict_where_you%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frxi8g3%2Fthis_guy_has_a_magical_skill_to_predict_where_you%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rxi8g3/this_guy_has_a_magical_skill_to_predict_where_you/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 19:34:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[💠French Pres. Macron: 5 million fellow unvaccinated citizens are "non-citizens." 
💠Canadian PM Trudeau: the unvaxxed are “misogynistic &amp; racist” extremists
💠Pres. Biden: the epidemic is a pandemic of the unvaccinated

Does progressive leadership require demonizing the other?]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1479094775475179520/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1479094775475179520/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:47:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Het interview met @100trillionUSD  gaat nu in premiere! 🚀🚨
Over:
- het S2F-model
- het falen van modellen
- zijn controversiële tweets
- blocks op Twitter
- de economische oorlog
- nieuwe welvaart
- het verlaten van Nederland.

Check hem hier 👉🏻 https://t.co/nWRrUDuGNl https://t.co/YgMZlFjOLN]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1479118366837149697/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1479118366837149697/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:47:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bio security surveillance regime, Dutch edition 2022.  https://t.co/tcXIgIJznV]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1479116640566476803/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1479116640566476803/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:47:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Are you ready to hodl everything you have for the entirety of 2022 regardless of outcome? If not you might want to rethink your position.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Personal antidote; in April I asked my older brother if he held any crypto. He
said yes, that he sold some Eth and made a few hundred. I told him no sell only
hold. He said he was 'opportunistic' and 'didn't have diamond hands'. - Just
last week we were driving in the car together and he said 'All…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxa8er/are_you_ready_to_hodl_everything_you_have_for_the/?score=558&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxa8er%2Fare_you_ready_to_hodl_everything_you_have_for_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxa8er%2Fare_you_ready_to_hodl_everything_you_have_for_the%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxa8er/are_you_ready_to_hodl_everything_you_have_for_the/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:47:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Personal antidote; in April I asked my older brother if he held any crypto. He said yes, that he sold some Eth and made a few hundred. I told him no sell only hold. He said he was &amp;amp;#39;opportunistic&amp;amp;#39; and &amp;amp;#39;didn&amp;amp;#39;t have diamond hands&amp;amp;#39;.  - Just last week we were driving in the car together and he said &amp;amp;#39;All my crypto now are ten year holds&amp;amp;#39; and I could have cried out of happiness.       &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Volatility scares people, and we all have to respect that. It will take time for people to come around and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://thumbs.dreamstime.com/b/bitcoin-cryptocurrency-import-big-data-animation-abstract-rainbow-spot-light-background-223802827.jpg&quot;&amp;gt;see this space for all that it holds&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;; from opportunistic cash grabs to apex dollar hedges, from over leveraged scams to the true start of DAOs that one-day might replace Apple.        &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Nuance is key! Consistency requires you to be as ignorant today as you were a year ago (historian Bernard Berenson said that). Are you still the same hodler you were a year ago?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The 4th largest BTC address just added a massive 43,000 BTC! This wallet has never sold a single BTC in its history and now holds almost $5BN worth]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxdehv/the_4th_largest_btc_address_just_added_a_massive/?score=501&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxdehv%2Fthe_4th_largest_btc_address_just_added_a_massive%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxdehv%2Fthe_4th_largest_btc_address_just_added_a_massive%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxdehv/the_4th_largest_btc_address_just_added_a_massive/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:47:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The closer you look the less you see]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rxcip4/the_closer_you_look_the_less_you_see/?score=1267&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frxcip4%2Fthe_closer_you_look_the_less_you_see%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frxcip4%2Fthe_closer_you_look_the_less_you_see%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rxcip4/the_closer_you_look_the_less_you_see/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:47:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The 3rd largest Bitcoin whale wallet added 179 more BTC today at $43.5k for a total of $7.8M. The whale has bought each day BTC is under $47k since the Dec correction. Since Nov, the whale has bought 13,594 BTC in total and sold 0.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx5yq5/the_3rd_largest_bitcoin_whale_wallet_added_179/?score=382&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx5yq5%2Fthe_3rd_largest_bitcoin_whale_wallet_added_179%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx5yq5%2Fthe_3rd_largest_bitcoin_whale_wallet_added_179%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx5yq5/the_3rd_largest_bitcoin_whale_wallet_added_179/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 10:32:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin is down 10 percent this year in the first 5 days]]></title><description><![CDATA[Every 4 years there’s a nasty bear market. Looking to stack some cheap sats end
of the year time 💰💰💰]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwyn1x/bitcoin_is_down_10_percent_this_year_in_the_first/?score=364&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwyn1x%2Fbitcoin_is_down_10_percent_this_year_in_the_first%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwyn1x%2Fbitcoin_is_down_10_percent_this_year_in_the_first%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwyn1x/bitcoin_is_down_10_percent_this_year_in_the_first/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 08:44:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Every 4 years there’s a nasty bear market.  Looking to stack some cheap sats end of the year time 💰💰💰&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I can't be the only one who thinks that most of the "Buy the dip" dudes are full of shit.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Before you say OP is just mad because he is in the red: I am well in the green
and I don't care even if there is a 90% flash crash, I only invest what I can
afford to lose.

Every single time there there is a small correction this sub gets bombarded with
"Did you buy the dip? Oh man you better buy…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx6zdf/i_cant_be_the_only_one_who_thinks_that_most_of/?score=419&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx6zdf%2Fi_cant_be_the_only_one_who_thinks_that_most_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx6zdf%2Fi_cant_be_the_only_one_who_thinks_that_most_of%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx6zdf/i_cant_be_the_only_one_who_thinks_that_most_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 08:44:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Before you say OP is just mad because he is in the red: I am well in the green and I don&amp;amp;#39;t care even if there is a 90% flash crash, I only invest what I can afford to lose.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Every single time there there is a small correction this sub gets bombarded with &amp;amp;quot;Did you buy the dip? Oh man you better buy the dip!&amp;amp;quot;, &amp;amp;quot;What coins are you guys buying this dip?&amp;amp;quot;, &amp;amp;quot;Yo, bro I wish the dip was 50% so I could buy more&amp;amp;quot;.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If people in this sub bought the dip as much as they claim to in their posts I am pretty positive we would have ran out of some coins in the market. To me these posts are no different than someone commenting &amp;amp;quot;To the moon&amp;amp;quot;,&amp;amp;quot;When Lambo?&amp;amp;quot; or &amp;amp;quot;Nobody knows shit about fuck&amp;amp;quot;. Low effort bullshit that gets spammed over and over again.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just buy whatever the fuck you want, at whatever price you want.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$725 Million in Crypto Liquidation in last 24 Hours!]]></title><description><![CDATA[In last 24 hours while we all are waiting for a breakout, $725 million US
Dollars have been liquidated.

Last week were in 'extreme fear' at 48k. Today, if we reach the same price
point, we all will be bullish.

In my honest opinion, I know this is quite a rough start to the year, but 42,500
price…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx4fje/725_million_in_crypto_liquidation_in_last_24_hours/?score=449&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx4fje%2F725_million_in_crypto_liquidation_in_last_24_hours%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx4fje%2F725_million_in_crypto_liquidation_in_last_24_hours%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx4fje/725_million_in_crypto_liquidation_in_last_24_hours/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 06:48:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In last 24 hours while we all are waiting for a breakout, $725 million US Dollars have been liquidated. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Last week were in &amp;amp;#39;extreme fear&amp;amp;#39; at 48k. 
Today, if we reach the same price point, we all will be bullish.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In my honest opinion,
I know this is quite a rough start to the year, but 42,500 price point might be our bottom. 
For long term, its always going to go up. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This recent acceleration in sell-side momentum is getting BTC closer to a bullish trend reversal.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On days like this one,
When you cant buy a dip, 
Just keep your phone away from you, eyes off your red candle screens, and do something else today.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Come a back after a day or two. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Have a good day everyone!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto has made me obsessed about money and changed my life for the better. This being with a red portfolio too.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I always planned on going through life being a decent man making a decent living
and playing by the rules. Making sure everything I did was safe and calculated
and non stressful. Just meander through and die. Such is life and what can you
do about it.

Then enter crypto.

I’m 29 and have been semi…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwvpye/crypto_has_made_me_obsessed_about_money_and/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwvpye%2Fcrypto_has_made_me_obsessed_about_money_and%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwvpye%2Fcrypto_has_made_me_obsessed_about_money_and%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwvpye/crypto_has_made_me_obsessed_about_money_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 06:48:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I always planned on going through life being a decent man making a decent living and playing by the rules. Making sure everything I did was safe and calculated and non stressful. Just meander through and die. Such is life and what can you do about it. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then enter crypto. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m 29 and have been semi successful. I’ve always been happy with where I was and never super stressed out about anything. Get the 8-5 M-F job. Log off at 5 every day. Go to the gym. Play some videogames. Got married. Was happy. Figured everything would work out as long as I played by the system. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But man has crypto lit a fire under my ass. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve never been super on top of money. Spent it wisely, got a house early. Been ok with it. But after crypto I researched everything constantly. I consolidated old 401ks. Opened an IRA, maxed out my current 401k match. Sold my house because I had a place to be rent free for as long as I needed for a new house and it wasn’t the best neighborhood to be in. Made a nice return on proceeds. Was able to have a dream wedding from it. Invested a good amount of safe money into crypto. Got a crypto.com card for rewards. Got another simple credit card. Boosted my credit from 680 to 720. Did much better at work since I had new motivation and got raises and promotions from. Love working OT because thats more money to have and invest. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Is my portfolio in the red? Again, yes lol. But I don’t care. Playing the long game and getting all my other finances in order has been part of the journey. Couldn’t be happier with where I am at in life now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Would you still buy crypto if you couldn't exchange it back to fiat?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Earlier today, I saw someone on here commenting that they would never sell some
coin they held - nothing too unusual, there are people saying that every day.
But it got me thinking: if you could never sell your crypto for fiat, would
people still buy it?

This is a thought experiment. In this…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwq3mg/would_you_still_buy_crypto_if_you_couldnt/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwq3mg%2Fwould_you_still_buy_crypto_if_you_couldnt%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwq3mg%2Fwould_you_still_buy_crypto_if_you_couldnt%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwq3mg/would_you_still_buy_crypto_if_you_couldnt/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 05:33:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Earlier today, I saw someone on here commenting that they would &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;never&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; sell some coin they held - nothing too unusual, there are people saying that every day. But it got me thinking: if you &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;could&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; never sell your crypto for fiat, would people still buy it?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;This is a thought experiment.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; In this scenario, you couldn&amp;amp;#39;t exchange crypto for fiat, ever - but it&amp;amp;#39;s not just that exchanges wouldn&amp;amp;#39;t offer it, there would be no loophole (&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;edit: so also no crypto credit/debit cards&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;) for it. You, for some reason, could not find someone to privately sell your coin to for fiat. In this hypothetical world, everything would be the same as now - you could buy crypto with fiat, you could use crypto for their use cases, and you could even use crypto to buy stuff in the few places that enable it - but you could not get fiat for it. This means, you would either have to have a use case for crypto that isn&amp;amp;#39;t &amp;amp;quot;getting more money&amp;amp;quot;, or you would have to speculate on more adoption and more merchants accepting crypto in the future.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Would you still invest in crypto? I&amp;amp;#39;ll be honest: I&amp;amp;#39;m in this to make more fiat, if I couldn&amp;amp;#39;t exhange crypto for fiat I would not invest. What about you?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Yet again over 666,000,000 worth of positions were wiped from the market.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Yet again over $650,000,000 worth of positions were wiped from the market.

Most of them were long positions.

In the past 24 hours, 175,705 traders were liquidated.

The largest single liquidation order happened on Bitmex - XBTUSD value $10.00M
(damn!)

Interestingly this time around majority of…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwyti0/yet_again_over_666000000_worth_of_positions_were/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwyti0%2Fyet_again_over_666000000_worth_of_positions_were%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwyti0%2Fyet_again_over_666000000_worth_of_positions_were%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwyti0/yet_again_over_666000000_worth_of_positions_were/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 05:33:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Yet again over $650,000,000 worth of positions were wiped from the market.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Most of them were long positions.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the past 24 hours, 175,705 traders were liquidated.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The largest single liquidation order happened on Bitmex - XBTUSD value $10.00M (damn!)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Interestingly this time around majority of positions wiped were on Okex and not on Binance. Are Binance users getting smarter?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please remember that trading with leverage is extremely risky and you should not do it unless you are extremely experienced.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/9huz09mq5y981.png?width=1533&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=a58d01efc98a99199a3c047a63732de07661e413&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/9huz09mq5y981.png?width=1533&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=a58d01efc98a99199a3c047a63732de07661e413&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["Anybody else excited!?" No. I'm not. This sucks and I have no problem saying it.]]></title><description><![CDATA[It takes weeks upon weeks to slowly climb in the charts, then within a few hours
it we're right back to where we were months ago? Yeah, that blows. The fact that
crypto is just some game for rich people to dip out of the microsecond something
threatening from the Fed happens sucks. The fact that…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwywij/anybody_else_excited_no_im_not_this_sucks_and_i/?score=466&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwywij%2Fanybody_else_excited_no_im_not_this_sucks_and_i%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwywij%2Fanybody_else_excited_no_im_not_this_sucks_and_i%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwywij/anybody_else_excited_no_im_not_this_sucks_and_i/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It takes weeks upon weeks to slowly climb in the charts, then within a few hours it we&amp;amp;#39;re right back to where we were months ago?  Yeah, that blows.  The fact that crypto is just some game for rich people to dip out of the microsecond something threatening from the Fed happens sucks.  The fact that people bought only to see things dip like crazy sucks.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And most importantly - all the people who are curious about crypto, and want to learn more and get in, but then see the prospect of losing 15% of their investment in a couple of hours and avoid crypto like the plague, THAT FUCKIN SUCKS.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sure, buy the dip if you&amp;amp;#39;ve got money, make your trades, come here and make your post assuring everyone everything will be ok and act like we&amp;amp;#39;re all idiots who can&amp;amp;#39;t see you&amp;amp;#39;re just assuring yourself more than anyone.  I&amp;amp;#39;m not impressed anymore.  It&amp;amp;#39;s fine for all of us to be bummed about this, and it would be great if this subreddit was a place that didn&amp;amp;#39;t make anyone who felt that way feel like some kind of stupid investor for having those feelings.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;edit&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;:  alright I&amp;amp;#39;m disabling inbox replies now.  Nothing new being said, my responses are clear, and there&amp;amp;#39;s now countless comments doing exactly the very thing I called out.  All I&amp;amp;#39;ll say is if you&amp;amp;#39;re feeling bummed today, you&amp;amp;#39;re not stupid, you&amp;amp;#39;re not a bad investor, and it &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;absolutely does not mean you should leave crypto.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;  It&amp;amp;#39;s a normal reaction and having that feeling isn&amp;amp;#39;t the same as throwing in the towel and giving up.  Peace&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["Banks in Germany Tell Customers to Take Their Money Elsewhere as Customers have to Pay Negative Interest": No Problem, Guess we will take our Money to Crypto then]]></title><description><![CDATA[Banks in Germany have started charging customers negative interest, meaning that
they want you to pay them in exchange for you storing your money in an account.

No joke, they literally tell their customers to take their money elsewhere
[https://www.wsj.com/articles/banks-in-germany-tell-customers…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwvac8/banks_in_germany_tell_customers_to_take_their/?score=362&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwvac8%2Fbanks_in_germany_tell_customers_to_take_their%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwvac8%2Fbanks_in_germany_tell_customers_to_take_their%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwvac8/banks_in_germany_tell_customers_to_take_their/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Banks in Germany have started charging customers negative interest, meaning that they want you to pay them in exchange for you storing your money in an account.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;No joke, they literally &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/banks-in-germany-tell-customers-to-take-deposits-elsewhere-11614594601&quot;&amp;gt;tell their customers to take their money elsewhere&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Of course, in reality they still want to be in control of your money, but now even charge you for giving them this privilege.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;No problem, guess we take our money somewhere else. You can earn more than 10% interest on holding some stablecoin, or you hold any other Crypto, like Ethereum, which has outperformed even the highest rallying traditional markets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If banks really want to be in control of our money, they better be ready to pay for it, or we move our money to Crypto (or literally anywhere else). This basically a scam on older people who are not aware where to store their money elsewhere.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[If you can’t handle the 50% dump you don’t deserve the 500% pump…]]></title><description><![CDATA[If you can’t handle the 50% dump you don’t deserve the 500% pump…

Words (insert eg x% )that was used years ago as the go to for panic posts-

Since we are seeing a bit of volatility today and I’m starting to see panic
posts some words from veterans here from years ago to keep the chin up and…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx0ati/if_you_cant_handle_the_50_dump_you_dont_deserve/?score=773&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx0ati%2Fif_you_cant_handle_the_50_dump_you_dont_deserve%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx0ati%2Fif_you_cant_handle_the_50_dump_you_dont_deserve%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx0ati/if_you_cant_handle_the_50_dump_you_dont_deserve/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you can’t handle the 50% dump you don’t deserve the 500% pump…&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Words (insert eg x% )that was used years ago as the go to for panic posts- &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Since we are seeing a bit of volatility today and I’m starting to see panic posts some words from veterans here from years ago to keep the chin up and HODL strong. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The market tend to have a bullwhip effect vs normal stock market nowadays so any move is exponentially larger. Part of the risk and excitement of being in the crypt. If you haven’t been here long (most people here have got into the crypt the last 4 months) this is part of the game and likely will be for a time. This is good as this also gives the gainz over time more than traditional markets. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The market is more mature than years gone by but the volatility is still there albeit less pronounced eg 80% drop in 2hrs - keep it simple (dont over trade)and HODL in what you believe in and may the gwei be with you….&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;PS this is something that has been part of crypto since the early days that hardens one to a new level of apathy and diamond hands the real test comes in when suicide lines come in at the post 30% drops to 80% drops. Again only have skin in the game in what you believe and make sure it’s quality bags!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Selling when your coin crashes is plain stupid]]></title><description><![CDATA[With the recent crash I'm sure there are a lot of people selling, but it doesn't
make any sense to me as if you've bought reliable coins, and not some low
marketcap coin that came out yesterday, they will all climb back up and you'll
forget about this crash.

Bitcoin crashed to 28k but climbed back…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwyvgy/selling_when_your_coin_crashes_is_plain_stupid/?score=442&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwyvgy%2Fselling_when_your_coin_crashes_is_plain_stupid%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwyvgy%2Fselling_when_your_coin_crashes_is_plain_stupid%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwyvgy/selling_when_your_coin_crashes_is_plain_stupid/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With the recent crash I&amp;amp;#39;m sure there are a lot of people selling, but it doesn&amp;amp;#39;t make any sense to me as if you&amp;amp;#39;ve bought reliable coins, and not some low marketcap coin that came out yesterday, they will all climb back up and you&amp;amp;#39;ll forget about this crash.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin crashed to 28k but climbed back up to 69K, isn&amp;amp;#39;t that a proof that it always does? There have been so many crashes like this one and it will pass and everyone will forget about it. Not only that but Bitcoin will break its ATH again this year, that much is obvious.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The reason you&amp;amp;#39;re down is not because your coin failed, the whole market failed so why sell if you believe in it? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So if you&amp;amp;#39;re thinking about selling, especially at a loss, I&amp;amp;#39;d advise you to be patient and hold as there&amp;amp;#39;s no point to it and you&amp;amp;#39;ll only lose money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Silvio Micali, founder of Algorand, won the Turing Award for inventing Zero Knowledge (ZK) Proofs]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwwx6x/silvio_micali_founder_of_algorand_won_the_turing/?score=417&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwwx6x%2Fsilvio_micali_founder_of_algorand_won_the_turing%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwwx6x%2Fsilvio_micali_founder_of_algorand_won_the_turing%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwwx6x/silvio_micali_founder_of_algorand_won_the_turing/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wahoo... New Years BTC Sale!]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwy1jn/wahoo_new_years_btc_sale/?score=490&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwy1jn%2Fwahoo_new_years_btc_sale%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwy1jn%2Fwahoo_new_years_btc_sale%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwy1jn/wahoo_new_years_btc_sale/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cryptoland, this is real, it’s disgusting, and it’s a physical manifestation of everything wrong with Cryptocurrency.]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is cryptoland, just be warned you won’t get the 10 minutes back after
watching this video.

https://youtu.be/jf3ajS5me78

For those who did not want to watch the video here is the rub. Cryptoland is the
physical manifestation of the metaverse. Created by two brain dead visionaries
to sell you…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwj21h/cryptoland_this_is_real_its_disgusting_and_its_a/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwj21h%2Fcryptoland_this_is_real_its_disgusting_and_its_a%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwj21h%2Fcryptoland_this_is_real_its_disgusting_and_its_a%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwj21h/cryptoland_this_is_real_its_disgusting_and_its_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:48:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is cryptoland, just be warned you won’t get the 10 minutes back after watching this video. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/jf3ajS5me78&quot;&amp;gt;https://youtu.be/jf3ajS5me78&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For those who did not want to watch the video here is the rub. Cryptoland is the physical manifestation of the metaverse. Created by two brain dead visionaries to sell you yet again more worthless NFTs and tokens to equate to real land on a private island only for crypto visionaries to work, live, and play.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can buy a 1 acre plot of real land to build a real house on, workout on a beachside crypto themed gym, eat at a crypto themed restaurant and bar. But what else? A ultra exclusive night club that is a members only club on a members only island than only special NFT holders can get into.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cryptoland is designed for the new lifestyle of “digital nomads” who spend their lives in hotels and glued to charts on their phones then create content with quality TA about how what coin can go up, down, or sideways. The best part is there is a whole island of these assholes!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I think I’m going to be sick…&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I just threw all my savings into bitcoin and idk how to feel.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Some background information, im from a newly 3rd world country ( Lebanon) and
ive saved 730$, dont have a job and im 23, i just threw a 700$ into btc and im
excited yet nervous, i would never sell at a loss, I'd kill my self before
taking a loss but idk i have butterflies in my stomach.

Insert…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwnj33/i_just_threw_all_my_savings_into_bitcoin_and_idk/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwnj33%2Fi_just_threw_all_my_savings_into_bitcoin_and_idk%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwnj33%2Fi_just_threw_all_my_savings_into_bitcoin_and_idk%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwnj33/i_just_threw_all_my_savings_into_bitcoin_and_idk/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:33:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some background information, im from a newly 3rd world country ( Lebanon) and ive saved 730$, dont have a job and im 23, i just threw a 700$ into btc and im excited yet nervous, i would never sell at a loss, I&amp;amp;#39;d kill my self before taking a loss but idk i have butterflies in my stomach.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Insert motivational quotes here xD.
What do you think? Is it foolish from me? But i had to buy this dip...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Looping Smart Wallet is now free to activate on L2 on iOS.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Update your iOS app, it will let you activate the L2 wallet completely free as
the fee gets passed onto Loopring.

You can then add funds via L2 networked friends or buy via the RAMP fiat on-ramp
to fund the L2 Wallet.

To have full functionality (social recovery, L1 funds etc) you’ll need…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwluuk/looping_smart_wallet_is_now_free_to_activate_on/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwluuk%2Flooping_smart_wallet_is_now_free_to_activate_on%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwluuk%2Flooping_smart_wallet_is_now_free_to_activate_on%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwluuk/looping_smart_wallet_is_now_free_to_activate_on/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:33:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Update your iOS app, it will let you activate the L2 wallet completely free as the fee gets passed onto Loopring.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can then add funds via L2 networked friends or buy via the RAMP fiat on-ramp to fund the L2 Wallet.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To have full functionality (social recovery, L1 funds etc) you’ll need to activate the L1 wallet which will of course incur a gas fee so be cautious of the current Eth gas fee. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The main draw of the L2 Wallet atm is access to DEX/AMM on L2 w/very cheap transfer fees. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Apparently the Android free L2 Wallet deploy will come soon, I assume in the next day as they can push it to Android basically any time whereas iOS has to get approved.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What's the best bitcoin quote you have ever heard?]]></title><description><![CDATA["Their ignorance is your opportunity." -Michael Saylor

That one is my favorite- surely an homage to Bezos famous quote]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rweo0a/whats_the_best_bitcoin_quote_you_have_ever_heard/?score=318&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frweo0a%2Fwhats_the_best_bitcoin_quote_you_have_ever_heard%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frweo0a%2Fwhats_the_best_bitcoin_quote_you_have_ever_heard%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rweo0a/whats_the_best_bitcoin_quote_you_have_ever_heard/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:33:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Their ignorance is your opportunity.&amp;amp;quot; -Michael Saylor&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That one is my favorite- surely an homage to Bezos famous quote&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wives &amp; Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[In another post, I read countless users saying that if crypto all of a sudden
went to $0, their wives would divorce them, take the kids, etc etc. How does
that work?

If you have some business that you invested in, and it goes to crap, does the
family give up on you?

Are you using you wife's money…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwo2sy/wives_crypto/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwo2sy%2Fwives_crypto%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwo2sy%2Fwives_crypto%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwo2sy/wives_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:33:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In another post, I read countless users saying that if crypto all of a sudden went to $0, their wives would divorce them, take the kids, etc etc. How does that work? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you have some business that you invested in, and it goes to crap, does the family give up on you? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Are you using you wife&amp;amp;#39;s money to buy crypto and your kids aren&amp;amp;#39;t eating because of it?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Well, not at all like that here at home. I invested in Crypto, but I invested in crypto with MY OWN MONEY, if it goes to zero, it&amp;amp;#39;s my bad, not hers. She works and earns her money too, buys her shoes and dresses and I don&amp;amp;#39;t stick my nose in, it&amp;amp;#39;s her money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As long as our house expenses are covered where each one pays half of them, then the spare money we can do whatever we want because it&amp;amp;#39;s our money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For context, I live in Portugal (Europe), for cultural reasons, things might work differently in your country. Not saying I&amp;amp;#39;m right and you are wrong, just putting different lifestyles in perspective.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How does it work at your place? Does your family have a say in your personal expenses?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zero-knowledge proof explained like you are 5 years old]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi kids!

So, you're interested in cryptocurrencies, and you've heard about those
so-called "zero-knowledge proofs" (ZK) used by projects such as Loopring, zkSync
and StarkWare.

Now you're wondering : what are zero-knowledge proofs and why are they so
important? Good news, champ, I am here for…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwpfkx/zeroknowledge_proof_explained_like_you_are_5/?score=358&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwpfkx%2Fzeroknowledge_proof_explained_like_you_are_5%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwpfkx%2Fzeroknowledge_proof_explained_like_you_are_5%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwpfkx/zeroknowledge_proof_explained_like_you_are_5/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:33:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hi kids!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, you&amp;amp;#39;re interested in cryptocurrencies, and you&amp;amp;#39;ve heard about those so-called &amp;amp;quot;zero-knowledge proofs&amp;amp;quot; (ZK) used by projects such as Loopring, zkSync and StarkWare.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now you&amp;amp;#39;re wondering : what are zero-knowledge proofs and why are they so important? Good news, champ, I am here for you!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let&amp;amp;#39;s say I found a cave with two distinct entrances, Left and Right. The two entrances are connected by a corridor, but a dragon prevents anyone from passing through the corridor. To make the dragon let you through, you need a magic stone. I have this magic stone, and I want to prove to you that I have it, but I don&amp;amp;#39;t want to show it to you, and I don&amp;amp;#39;t want to tell my secret to anyone but you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is how it works. You close your eyes while I enter the cave, without telling you if I chose the Left or Right entrance. You open your eyes again, then ask me to come out on a particular side and I do so. You close your eyes, I go back into the cave, and we repeat the experience 100 times.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If I have the magic stone, the dragon will let me through everytime and I can leave the cave through the entrance you tell me, 100 times out of 100. But if I don&amp;amp;#39;t have the stone, every other time I won&amp;amp;#39;t be able to get out through the chosen entrance - statistically, I will only have the good answer 50% of the time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;So by using this method, I will prove to you that I have the magic stone, without ever showing it to you&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Moreover, you will not be able to prove to anyone else that I have the stone, since an outside observer could always think that we have arranged it together in advance.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is what is called a zero-knowledge proof. In cryptocurrencies, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;the magic stone is the private key&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Zero-knowledge proofs are used to show to a validator that you are indeed in possession of the private key, without revealing said private keys to the validator, and without letting the rest of the world know you have the key.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thank you for listening to my story. I hope you had fun today, my little friends!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anyone else experience this? Told my friend at work about Bitcoin, he was really fascinated by it as an inflation hedge. Came back the next day with a bunch of shitcoins but no Bitcoin.]]></title><description><![CDATA[He said he downloaded Coinbase and bought a bunch of random coins some youtuber
suggested. I asked him if he bought any Bitcoin, he said "nope, it was too
expensive".

🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rws5ye/anyone_else_experience_this_told_my_friend_at/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frws5ye%2Fanyone_else_experience_this_told_my_friend_at%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frws5ye%2Fanyone_else_experience_this_told_my_friend_at%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rws5ye/anyone_else_experience_this_told_my_friend_at/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 21:32:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He said he downloaded Coinbase and bought a bunch of random coins some youtuber suggested. I asked him if he bought any Bitcoin, he said &amp;amp;quot;nope, it was too expensive&amp;amp;quot;. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Heads up and be safe: I just lost BTC because of Malware that highjacks my clipboard [Windows]]]></title><description><![CDATA[I just lost a significant amount of BTC (to me at least, I can only save
~100$/month). I had my last BTC (sats, really) purchases sitting in my exchange
and wanted to move them to my (software) wallet that I use on my phone. So I
copied/pasted it the address on a secure notepad app that syncs with…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwlkd0/heads_up_and_be_safe_i_just_lost_btc_because_of/?score=331&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwlkd0%2Fheads_up_and_be_safe_i_just_lost_btc_because_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwlkd0%2Fheads_up_and_be_safe_i_just_lost_btc_because_of%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwlkd0/heads_up_and_be_safe_i_just_lost_btc_because_of/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 21:32:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I just lost a significant amount of BTC (to me at least, I can only save ~100$/month). I had my last BTC (sats, really) purchases sitting in my exchange and wanted to move them to my (software) wallet that I use on my phone. So I copied/pasted it the address on a secure notepad app that syncs with PC, then checked that the address shown on my PC matched the wallet address. It did, so that&amp;amp;#39;s cool.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So on the PC I copied/pasted it on the address box for the withdrawal at my exchange, it was shown as a valid address and I proceeded with the transaction. WRONG!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I sat there waiting for my funds to appear on my wallet but they never did. Transaction was shown as completed on the exchange and then I got alarmed. Started to write an email to my exchange&amp;amp;#39;s support team and then it clicked.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I wanted to say that the destination address was &amp;amp;#39;X&amp;amp;#39; but somehow it was being shown as &amp;amp;#39;Y&amp;amp;#39; on the transaction history. But every time I tried to paste my address it was changing right before my eyes. So my email was looking like &amp;amp;lt;&amp;amp;lt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;This is mi destination address: &amp;amp;#39;Y&amp;amp;#39; // This is the address shown on the transacion history: &amp;amp;#39;Y&amp;amp;#39;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;gt;&amp;amp;gt;. Now, my notepad app was clearly showing that the adddress I was trying to copy was most definitely not &amp;amp;#39;Y&amp;amp;#39;, so something was up.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyway, at that point I deleted the email, no need to bother some support dude because of something that was looking more and more like a royal fuck up.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And then there it is, there was some malware on my PC that was actively seeking BTC addresses and switching them to something similar but a different address alltoghether from whoever scammer made the damned thing. I clearly fucked up by not realizing that, and now&amp;amp;#39;s too late.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Malwarebytes was quick to find and delete the thing and now the computer&amp;amp;#39;s clean again (just like my exchange account, haha. FUCK.)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Be safe out there and double check or triple check everything when doing a transaction. I didn&amp;amp;#39;t realize  at the time so I&amp;amp;#39;m an idiot, but maybe you won&amp;amp;#39;t have to be.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;---&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TL;DR&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s malware out there reading your clipboard to find BTC addresses, and when you try to copy/paste it will paste a similar address from the scammer. I didn&amp;amp;#39;t realize so I&amp;amp;#39;m an idiot, but maybe you won&amp;amp;#39;t have to be.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;---&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: Okay, thanks for the awards and all. I read the comments but was lazy to reply to each one individually.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;1- My PC wasn&amp;amp;#39;t as infested as some of you may think, I actually clean installed windows 11 like 3 weeks ago FFS. I will reformat it again on the weekend, no worries there. The fucking antivirus did find the culprit, though. After deleting the files and restarting the PC, clipboard was behaving correctly again (I checked a shit ton of times).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;2- &amp;amp;#39;A secure notepad app that syncs&amp;amp;#39; was just to make it easier to explain. It was Bitwarden, using the note entry options. It&amp;amp;#39;s a password manager so it is indeed secure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;3- Mac / Linux people... Let&amp;amp;#39;s just not go there, I don&amp;amp;#39;t care about OS master race. Windows is a great fit for what I use it and all other OS have their flaws too.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;4- Hardware wallet option is something that I&amp;amp;#39;m always considering, I just fear loosing it, TBH. 2-stage transactions seems like a good enough compromise to me for the time being.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;5- Software wallet on my phone gets uninstalled after each deposit, because I agree that it&amp;amp;#39;s not a great thing to carry around. Then whenever I want to transfer again I re-download it and use the seed phrase to access my stuff.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;6- Now let&amp;amp;#39;s be clear, I know that evrything&amp;amp;#39;s my fault, here. For what is worth, the address was very similar (first letters were the exact same), and was given as a valid address by the exchange so i trusted it more than I should have, but i did not check the complete string and that&amp;amp;#39;s on me. I&amp;amp;#39;m a bit of a newbie, but not a complete idiot, it&amp;amp;#39;s just that I plain hadn&amp;amp;#39;t heard about this particular scam before (hence why I wrote it to alert any other newbie that could find the info useful).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;7- To the people thinking that this was an ad and I didn&amp;amp;#39;t just lose my money... I wish it was so, I truly truly do. Imagine if those fuckers were paying me, too. Ah... Wouldn&amp;amp;#39;t that be nice? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyway, you can&amp;amp;#39;t trust your clipboard, there&amp;amp;#39;s a lesson learned.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m a few steps back and it kinda sucks, but I&amp;amp;#39;ll go back to stacking sats.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Airbnb To Implement Crypto Payments]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwn5a8/airbnb_to_implement_crypto_payments/?score=399&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwn5a8%2Fairbnb_to_implement_crypto_payments%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwn5a8%2Fairbnb_to_implement_crypto_payments%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwn5a8/airbnb_to_implement_crypto_payments/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 20:37:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Things I Wish I Did Earlier When Investing In Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi everyone! Today marks the anniversary of my first ever crypto transaction! My
first purchase was of Ethereum, and since then it has been nothing else but a
learning journey.

There were a lot of things I learnt later than what I wished, so here are a few
of the things I wish I did earlier when…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwjwly/things_i_wish_i_did_earlier_when_investing_in/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwjwly%2Fthings_i_wish_i_did_earlier_when_investing_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwjwly%2Fthings_i_wish_i_did_earlier_when_investing_in%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwjwly/things_i_wish_i_did_earlier_when_investing_in/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 18:47:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hi everyone! Today marks the anniversary of my first ever crypto transaction! My first purchase was of Ethereum, and since then it has been nothing else but a learning journey.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There were a lot of things I learnt later than what I wished, so here are a few of the things I wish I did earlier when investing in crypto:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Keeping track of transactions&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: when I first bought crypto, I invested X amount of fiat without keeping track of how much I have put into it. Later, I discovered the portfolio trackers. Some good examples are the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://delta.app/en&quot;&amp;gt;Delta App&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coinmarketcap.com/&quot;&amp;gt;CoinMarketCap&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; portfolio tool. I rather input the transaction manually after making them, as I don&amp;amp;#39;t really like giving API keys to 3rd parties.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Opening a Vault for Moons&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: easily the worst mistake I have ever done. I never knew the existence of moons until they, well, mooned. I always use my PC or laptop for Reddit and never seen the Vault menu, and when I found out about I felt so stupid as I was quite active in this sub when I first started. Open your Vault!! It is literally free crypto for your posts - please focus on quality!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Having Native Wallets&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: this isn&amp;amp;#39;t a mistake, but more of a &amp;amp;quot;help the ecosystem&amp;amp;quot; kind of thing. What I must recommend though is to keep all your assets away from exchanges. A system failure, hacking attack or just bankruptcy can be the end of your funds, so keep your coins in an external wallet. I started with &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.exodus.com/&quot;&amp;gt;Exodus Wallet&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, as it has the most assets and allows staking for interest rewards. With time, I migrated to native wallets (wallets made for a single network in particular) and around 80% of my assets are secured with a Ledger Nano X (hardware wallet, not hackable!).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Don&amp;amp;#39;t stick to one exchange&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: not all exchanges have all the coins you will want. Not all exchanges have the same features and most importantly, not all have the same fees. what exchanges do I recommend? I personally use &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://Crypto.com&quot;&amp;gt;Crypto.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kraken.com/&quot;&amp;gt;Kraken&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. Of course, each one to their own and geographical restrictions may apply to some exchanges.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Don&amp;amp;#39;t do stupid things that can cause you headaches&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: what I mean with this is, do not add 5 bank accounts to your fiat withdrawal addresses, don&amp;amp;#39;t deposit fiat from 4 different banks in 3 different countries, 2 credit cards and 4 debit cards. Focus on 1 and 1. One card. One bank account. Work yourself around that and it will help you massively. I have seen so many issues with people with locked accounts due to having to verify details etc. that can just be solved by this. I never had a single issue using &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.revolut.com/&quot;&amp;gt;Revolut&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; as my bank account and the virtual card as my means of payment if i use this. Also, all bank deposits are allowed to exchanges from them (EU Customer). KYC! Just do it. The government knows all about you anyways, so don&amp;amp;#39;t worry. You are happy to give your bank details, name, surname, card number away but not a selfie of yourself? The big exchanges have great privacy and security measures, don&amp;amp;#39;t worry!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Find Rewards. There are A LOT OF THEM!&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: Crypto is a baby. A volatile baby, but a baby nonetheless. Everything is new! DeFi projects can offer 100%+ APY by staking your coins, projects with PoS networks offer some really good interest by just hodling their coin and a lot of platforms offer interest in stablecoins and other tokens. Personally, I use one of the VISA Cards that CDC offer. It earns me cashback, free services and lets be honest, looks cool af!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Lastly but most importantly, ENJOY&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: Don&amp;amp;#39;t look at the chart every day and worry. Yes I look at my portfolio every day but just to see if it is a good moment to buy or not. I never worry. If you are a day trader, then yes. A hodler, then hodl. You are here for the long run. Enjoy the experience, the learning and the communities (apart from &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/r/bitcoin&quot;&amp;gt;r/bitcoin&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; - that&amp;amp;#39;s a cult). &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hopefully this helps newbies a bit more, and makes it easier to start up! Have a great year everyone.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Did your altcoin just moon? Great! Now sell 15% of the bag. Hodl the rest for the next liftoff, or buy the next dip with your new gains. It's an easy rule of thumb to make sure you're always taking profits]]></title><description><![CDATA[It's so easy to get stuck on, "oh no, I shouldn't sell the whole bag because
what if it goes up more!" And dammit, you're right to wanna hold.

But this is a game of making money, and if that's your goal you need to sell
into euphoria

When you're seeing double digit percent gains on your coin,…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwcosl/did_your_altcoin_just_moon_great_now_sell_15_of/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwcosl%2Fdid_your_altcoin_just_moon_great_now_sell_15_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwcosl%2Fdid_your_altcoin_just_moon_great_now_sell_15_of%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwcosl/did_your_altcoin_just_moon_great_now_sell_15_of/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 16:38:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s so easy to get stuck on, &amp;amp;quot;oh no, I shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t sell the whole bag because what if it goes up more!&amp;amp;quot; And dammit, you&amp;amp;#39;re right to wanna hold. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But this is a game of making money, and if that&amp;amp;#39;s your goal you need to &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;sell into euphoria&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When you&amp;amp;#39;re seeing double digit percent gains on your coin, it&amp;amp;#39;s time to make that trade and sell a little bit of the bag. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s usually a nice dip afterwards and you&amp;amp;#39;ll be glad you&amp;amp;#39;ve got the powder to burn. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And if there&amp;amp;#39;s not a dip afterwards, you&amp;amp;#39;ve got 85% of your original bag to decide to hold or sell. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Finally, if the coin truly tanks afterwards then, you have some USDC that&amp;amp;#39;s much more tradable than your ElonCumRocket. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s truly a win-win-win&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NFTs won't ruin computer games, greedy game companies will ruin computer games using NFTs]]></title><description><![CDATA[As the title says, there was a post recently in the gaming subreddit that was
claiming that NFTs will ruin computer gaming further just like microtransactions
did.

However, I disagree with that statement. If NFTs were in DnD they would be a
lawful neutral force, they are not good or evil they are…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwlo57/nfts_wont_ruin_computer_games_greedy_game/?score=505&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwlo57%2Fnfts_wont_ruin_computer_games_greedy_game%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwlo57%2Fnfts_wont_ruin_computer_games_greedy_game%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwlo57/nfts_wont_ruin_computer_games_greedy_game/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 14:33:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As the title says, there was a post recently in the gaming subreddit that was claiming that NFTs will ruin computer gaming further just like microtransactions did.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, I disagree with that statement. If NFTs were in DnD they would be a lawful neutral force, they are not good or evil they are just a tool and being a transparent and open tool it makes them more easy to keep track of.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If anything NFTs should provide more consumer protection for digital game downloads than the present model of Microsoft being all like &amp;amp;quot;trust me bra, we got this&amp;amp;quot; until one day they just remove the game from the store and leave no public evidence that you ever owned it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, I also 100% guarantee that game companies are going to use this to further monetise the market for pointless crap cosmetics and strip even more out of a game to sell back to the player later.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But people shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t hate the technology, that&amp;amp;#39;s like hating the internet because game companies use the internet to download microtransactions, it really makes no sense. Hate the companies and hate the people buying their garbage.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Be honest. Which coin(s) did you buy just because it is being shilled here or twitter or anywhere else, without doing researching on it?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Have you ever seen coins that are being or have been shilled nonstop? Ehem ERG
ALGO LRC

Everyone always say DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH, but we all know that there are times
when we are too lazy to do this tedious part of investment and we're like ahh
fuck it, what could possibly go wrong and just put in…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwhxvb/be_honest_which_coins_did_you_buy_just_because_it/?score=362&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwhxvb%2Fbe_honest_which_coins_did_you_buy_just_because_it%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwhxvb%2Fbe_honest_which_coins_did_you_buy_just_because_it%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwhxvb/be_honest_which_coins_did_you_buy_just_because_it/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 13:37:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Have you ever seen coins that are being or have been shilled nonstop? &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Ehem&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; ERG ALGO LRC&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Everyone always say DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH, but we all know that there are times when we are too lazy to do this tedious part of investment and we&amp;amp;#39;re like &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;ahh fuck it, what could possibly go wrong&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; and just put in money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So which projects or coins have you bought without doing prior research and just went in head first? Was it successful? Did it fail horribly? How were you convinced to buy it just because? Was it the sheer volume of the people shilling? Did you read something informative that enticed you to buy it?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: ok that&amp;amp;#39;s a lot of people&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Assets lined up by their S2F ratio and market value, just coincidence or meaningful pattern? Note that current BTC cluster (2020-2024, upper right blue dots) is half-filled. https://t.co/2A05HERwoY]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1478701553800335363/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1478701553800335363/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 12:48:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Happening Now: Airbnb Could Soon Add Support for Cryptocurrency Payments]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwgmna/happening_now_airbnb_could_soon_add_support_for/?score=357&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwgmna%2Fhappening_now_airbnb_could_soon_add_support_for%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwgmna%2Fhappening_now_airbnb_could_soon_add_support_for%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwgmna/happening_now_airbnb_could_soon_add_support_for/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 12:48:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[human progress is measured on the Kardashev scale; #bitcoin accelerates the building of energy grids to power the future. https://t.co/hLe9XLp8IW]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1478656462947762177/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1478656462947762177/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Am I the only one that has never had a problem with Coinbase?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I see countless posts everyday about how Coinbase has been terrible for people.
Their Coinbase account got hacked, they got scammed, Coinbase support won’t get
back to them, etc…

I started with Coinbase early last year. I did lumpsum investments, weekly
recurring investments, monthly recurring,…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwcou2/am_i_the_only_one_that_has_never_had_a_problem/?score=333&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwcou2%2Fam_i_the_only_one_that_has_never_had_a_problem%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwcou2%2Fam_i_the_only_one_that_has_never_had_a_problem%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwcou2/am_i_the_only_one_that_has_never_had_a_problem/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 11:37:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I see countless posts everyday about how Coinbase has been terrible for people. Their Coinbase account got hacked, they got scammed, Coinbase support won’t get back to them, etc…&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I started with Coinbase early last year. I did lumpsum investments, weekly recurring investments, monthly recurring, staking, Coinbase earn, conversions, literally everything you can do on Coinbase (besides sell) and have never ever had one issue. I mean, I’m not out here throwing money at memecoins but I’d say I’m using Coinbase the way it is supposed to be used and what they promise. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve more than tripled what I put in, and do not have a single complaint about it. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Is there anyone else that is completely satisfied with Coinbase? I can’t help but think, looking at all these posts, that a lot of the problems people are running into are user error, but maybe I’m the exception?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[It takes a brave man to tell the truth. @bobscartoons is a brave and deeply compassionate man.
https://t.co/NRfaqmIzAr]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1478662379005259776/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1478662379005259776/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 10:36:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Could Reach $100K And Overtake Gold's Market Share: Goldman Sachs]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwbnby/bitcoin_could_reach_100k_and_overtake_golds/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwbnby%2Fbitcoin_could_reach_100k_and_overtake_golds%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwbnby%2Fbitcoin_could_reach_100k_and_overtake_golds%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwbnby/bitcoin_could_reach_100k_and_overtake_golds/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 10:36:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>