<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing on Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 08:45:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[$725 Million in Crypto Liquidation in last 24 Hours!]]></title><description><![CDATA[In last 24 hours while we all are waiting for a breakout, $725 million US
Dollars have been liquidated.

Last week were in 'extreme fear' at 48k. Today, if we reach the same price
point, we all will be bullish.

In my honest opinion, I know this is quite a rough start to the year, but 42,500
price…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx4fje/725_million_in_crypto_liquidation_in_last_24_hours/?score=449&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx4fje%2F725_million_in_crypto_liquidation_in_last_24_hours%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx4fje%2F725_million_in_crypto_liquidation_in_last_24_hours%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx4fje/725_million_in_crypto_liquidation_in_last_24_hours/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 06:48:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In last 24 hours while we all are waiting for a breakout, $725 million US Dollars have been liquidated. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Last week were in &amp;amp;#39;extreme fear&amp;amp;#39; at 48k. 
Today, if we reach the same price point, we all will be bullish.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In my honest opinion,
I know this is quite a rough start to the year, but 42,500 price point might be our bottom. 
For long term, its always going to go up. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This recent acceleration in sell-side momentum is getting BTC closer to a bullish trend reversal.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On days like this one,
When you cant buy a dip, 
Just keep your phone away from you, eyes off your red candle screens, and do something else today.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Come a back after a day or two. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Have a good day everyone!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto has made me obsessed about money and changed my life for the better. This being with a red portfolio too.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I always planned on going through life being a decent man making a decent living
and playing by the rules. Making sure everything I did was safe and calculated
and non stressful. Just meander through and die. Such is life and what can you
do about it.

Then enter crypto.

I’m 29 and have been semi…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwvpye/crypto_has_made_me_obsessed_about_money_and/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwvpye%2Fcrypto_has_made_me_obsessed_about_money_and%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwvpye%2Fcrypto_has_made_me_obsessed_about_money_and%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwvpye/crypto_has_made_me_obsessed_about_money_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 06:48:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I always planned on going through life being a decent man making a decent living and playing by the rules. Making sure everything I did was safe and calculated and non stressful. Just meander through and die. Such is life and what can you do about it. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then enter crypto. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m 29 and have been semi successful. I’ve always been happy with where I was and never super stressed out about anything. Get the 8-5 M-F job. Log off at 5 every day. Go to the gym. Play some videogames. Got married. Was happy. Figured everything would work out as long as I played by the system. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But man has crypto lit a fire under my ass. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve never been super on top of money. Spent it wisely, got a house early. Been ok with it. But after crypto I researched everything constantly. I consolidated old 401ks. Opened an IRA, maxed out my current 401k match. Sold my house because I had a place to be rent free for as long as I needed for a new house and it wasn’t the best neighborhood to be in. Made a nice return on proceeds. Was able to have a dream wedding from it. Invested a good amount of safe money into crypto. Got a crypto.com card for rewards. Got another simple credit card. Boosted my credit from 680 to 720. Did much better at work since I had new motivation and got raises and promotions from. Love working OT because thats more money to have and invest. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Is my portfolio in the red? Again, yes lol. But I don’t care. Playing the long game and getting all my other finances in order has been part of the journey. Couldn’t be happier with where I am at in life now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Would you still buy crypto if you couldn't exchange it back to fiat?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Earlier today, I saw someone on here commenting that they would never sell some
coin they held - nothing too unusual, there are people saying that every day.
But it got me thinking: if you could never sell your crypto for fiat, would
people still buy it?

This is a thought experiment. In this…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwq3mg/would_you_still_buy_crypto_if_you_couldnt/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwq3mg%2Fwould_you_still_buy_crypto_if_you_couldnt%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwq3mg%2Fwould_you_still_buy_crypto_if_you_couldnt%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwq3mg/would_you_still_buy_crypto_if_you_couldnt/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 05:33:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Earlier today, I saw someone on here commenting that they would &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;never&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; sell some coin they held - nothing too unusual, there are people saying that every day. But it got me thinking: if you &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;could&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; never sell your crypto for fiat, would people still buy it?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;This is a thought experiment.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; In this scenario, you couldn&amp;amp;#39;t exchange crypto for fiat, ever - but it&amp;amp;#39;s not just that exchanges wouldn&amp;amp;#39;t offer it, there would be no loophole (&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;edit: so also no crypto credit/debit cards&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;) for it. You, for some reason, could not find someone to privately sell your coin to for fiat. In this hypothetical world, everything would be the same as now - you could buy crypto with fiat, you could use crypto for their use cases, and you could even use crypto to buy stuff in the few places that enable it - but you could not get fiat for it. This means, you would either have to have a use case for crypto that isn&amp;amp;#39;t &amp;amp;quot;getting more money&amp;amp;quot;, or you would have to speculate on more adoption and more merchants accepting crypto in the future.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Would you still invest in crypto? I&amp;amp;#39;ll be honest: I&amp;amp;#39;m in this to make more fiat, if I couldn&amp;amp;#39;t exhange crypto for fiat I would not invest. What about you?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Yet again over 666,000,000 worth of positions were wiped from the market.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Yet again over $650,000,000 worth of positions were wiped from the market.

Most of them were long positions.

In the past 24 hours, 175,705 traders were liquidated.

The largest single liquidation order happened on Bitmex - XBTUSD value $10.00M
(damn!)

Interestingly this time around majority of…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwyti0/yet_again_over_666000000_worth_of_positions_were/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwyti0%2Fyet_again_over_666000000_worth_of_positions_were%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwyti0%2Fyet_again_over_666000000_worth_of_positions_were%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwyti0/yet_again_over_666000000_worth_of_positions_were/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 05:33:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Yet again over $650,000,000 worth of positions were wiped from the market.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Most of them were long positions.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the past 24 hours, 175,705 traders were liquidated.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The largest single liquidation order happened on Bitmex - XBTUSD value $10.00M (damn!)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Interestingly this time around majority of positions wiped were on Okex and not on Binance. Are Binance users getting smarter?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please remember that trading with leverage is extremely risky and you should not do it unless you are extremely experienced.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/9huz09mq5y981.png?width=1533&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=a58d01efc98a99199a3c047a63732de07661e413&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/9huz09mq5y981.png?width=1533&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=a58d01efc98a99199a3c047a63732de07661e413&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["Anybody else excited!?" No. I'm not. This sucks and I have no problem saying it.]]></title><description><![CDATA[It takes weeks upon weeks to slowly climb in the charts, then within a few hours
it we're right back to where we were months ago? Yeah, that blows. The fact that
crypto is just some game for rich people to dip out of the microsecond something
threatening from the Fed happens sucks. The fact that…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwywij/anybody_else_excited_no_im_not_this_sucks_and_i/?score=466&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwywij%2Fanybody_else_excited_no_im_not_this_sucks_and_i%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwywij%2Fanybody_else_excited_no_im_not_this_sucks_and_i%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwywij/anybody_else_excited_no_im_not_this_sucks_and_i/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It takes weeks upon weeks to slowly climb in the charts, then within a few hours it we&amp;amp;#39;re right back to where we were months ago?  Yeah, that blows.  The fact that crypto is just some game for rich people to dip out of the microsecond something threatening from the Fed happens sucks.  The fact that people bought only to see things dip like crazy sucks.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And most importantly - all the people who are curious about crypto, and want to learn more and get in, but then see the prospect of losing 15% of their investment in a couple of hours and avoid crypto like the plague, THAT FUCKIN SUCKS.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sure, buy the dip if you&amp;amp;#39;ve got money, make your trades, come here and make your post assuring everyone everything will be ok and act like we&amp;amp;#39;re all idiots who can&amp;amp;#39;t see you&amp;amp;#39;re just assuring yourself more than anyone.  I&amp;amp;#39;m not impressed anymore.  It&amp;amp;#39;s fine for all of us to be bummed about this, and it would be great if this subreddit was a place that didn&amp;amp;#39;t make anyone who felt that way feel like some kind of stupid investor for having those feelings.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;edit&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;:  alright I&amp;amp;#39;m disabling inbox replies now.  Nothing new being said, my responses are clear, and there&amp;amp;#39;s now countless comments doing exactly the very thing I called out.  All I&amp;amp;#39;ll say is if you&amp;amp;#39;re feeling bummed today, you&amp;amp;#39;re not stupid, you&amp;amp;#39;re not a bad investor, and it &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;absolutely does not mean you should leave crypto.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;  It&amp;amp;#39;s a normal reaction and having that feeling isn&amp;amp;#39;t the same as throwing in the towel and giving up.  Peace&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["Banks in Germany Tell Customers to Take Their Money Elsewhere as Customers have to Pay Negative Interest": No Problem, Guess we will take our Money to Crypto then]]></title><description><![CDATA[Banks in Germany have started charging customers negative interest, meaning that
they want you to pay them in exchange for you storing your money in an account.

No joke, they literally tell their customers to take their money elsewhere
[https://www.wsj.com/articles/banks-in-germany-tell-customers…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwvac8/banks_in_germany_tell_customers_to_take_their/?score=362&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwvac8%2Fbanks_in_germany_tell_customers_to_take_their%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwvac8%2Fbanks_in_germany_tell_customers_to_take_their%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwvac8/banks_in_germany_tell_customers_to_take_their/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Banks in Germany have started charging customers negative interest, meaning that they want you to pay them in exchange for you storing your money in an account.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;No joke, they literally &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/banks-in-germany-tell-customers-to-take-deposits-elsewhere-11614594601&quot;&amp;gt;tell their customers to take their money elsewhere&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Of course, in reality they still want to be in control of your money, but now even charge you for giving them this privilege.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;No problem, guess we take our money somewhere else. You can earn more than 10% interest on holding some stablecoin, or you hold any other Crypto, like Ethereum, which has outperformed even the highest rallying traditional markets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If banks really want to be in control of our money, they better be ready to pay for it, or we move our money to Crypto (or literally anywhere else). This basically a scam on older people who are not aware where to store their money elsewhere.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[If you can’t handle the 50% dump you don’t deserve the 500% pump…]]></title><description><![CDATA[If you can’t handle the 50% dump you don’t deserve the 500% pump…

Words (insert eg x% )that was used years ago as the go to for panic posts-

Since we are seeing a bit of volatility today and I’m starting to see panic
posts some words from veterans here from years ago to keep the chin up and…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx0ati/if_you_cant_handle_the_50_dump_you_dont_deserve/?score=773&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx0ati%2Fif_you_cant_handle_the_50_dump_you_dont_deserve%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx0ati%2Fif_you_cant_handle_the_50_dump_you_dont_deserve%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx0ati/if_you_cant_handle_the_50_dump_you_dont_deserve/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you can’t handle the 50% dump you don’t deserve the 500% pump…&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Words (insert eg x% )that was used years ago as the go to for panic posts- &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Since we are seeing a bit of volatility today and I’m starting to see panic posts some words from veterans here from years ago to keep the chin up and HODL strong. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The market tend to have a bullwhip effect vs normal stock market nowadays so any move is exponentially larger. Part of the risk and excitement of being in the crypt. If you haven’t been here long (most people here have got into the crypt the last 4 months) this is part of the game and likely will be for a time. This is good as this also gives the gainz over time more than traditional markets. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The market is more mature than years gone by but the volatility is still there albeit less pronounced eg 80% drop in 2hrs - keep it simple (dont over trade)and HODL in what you believe in and may the gwei be with you….&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;PS this is something that has been part of crypto since the early days that hardens one to a new level of apathy and diamond hands the real test comes in when suicide lines come in at the post 30% drops to 80% drops. Again only have skin in the game in what you believe and make sure it’s quality bags!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Selling when your coin crashes is plain stupid]]></title><description><![CDATA[With the recent crash I'm sure there are a lot of people selling, but it doesn't
make any sense to me as if you've bought reliable coins, and not some low
marketcap coin that came out yesterday, they will all climb back up and you'll
forget about this crash.

Bitcoin crashed to 28k but climbed back…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwyvgy/selling_when_your_coin_crashes_is_plain_stupid/?score=442&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwyvgy%2Fselling_when_your_coin_crashes_is_plain_stupid%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwyvgy%2Fselling_when_your_coin_crashes_is_plain_stupid%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwyvgy/selling_when_your_coin_crashes_is_plain_stupid/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With the recent crash I&amp;amp;#39;m sure there are a lot of people selling, but it doesn&amp;amp;#39;t make any sense to me as if you&amp;amp;#39;ve bought reliable coins, and not some low marketcap coin that came out yesterday, they will all climb back up and you&amp;amp;#39;ll forget about this crash.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin crashed to 28k but climbed back up to 69K, isn&amp;amp;#39;t that a proof that it always does? There have been so many crashes like this one and it will pass and everyone will forget about it. Not only that but Bitcoin will break its ATH again this year, that much is obvious.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The reason you&amp;amp;#39;re down is not because your coin failed, the whole market failed so why sell if you believe in it? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So if you&amp;amp;#39;re thinking about selling, especially at a loss, I&amp;amp;#39;d advise you to be patient and hold as there&amp;amp;#39;s no point to it and you&amp;amp;#39;ll only lose money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Silvio Micali, founder of Algorand, won the Turing Award for inventing Zero Knowledge (ZK) Proofs]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwwx6x/silvio_micali_founder_of_algorand_won_the_turing/?score=417&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwwx6x%2Fsilvio_micali_founder_of_algorand_won_the_turing%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwwx6x%2Fsilvio_micali_founder_of_algorand_won_the_turing%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwwx6x/silvio_micali_founder_of_algorand_won_the_turing/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wahoo... New Years BTC Sale!]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwy1jn/wahoo_new_years_btc_sale/?score=490&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwy1jn%2Fwahoo_new_years_btc_sale%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwy1jn%2Fwahoo_new_years_btc_sale%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwy1jn/wahoo_new_years_btc_sale/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cryptoland, this is real, it’s disgusting, and it’s a physical manifestation of everything wrong with Cryptocurrency.]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is cryptoland, just be warned you won’t get the 10 minutes back after
watching this video.

https://youtu.be/jf3ajS5me78

For those who did not want to watch the video here is the rub. Cryptoland is the
physical manifestation of the metaverse. Created by two brain dead visionaries
to sell you…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwj21h/cryptoland_this_is_real_its_disgusting_and_its_a/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwj21h%2Fcryptoland_this_is_real_its_disgusting_and_its_a%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwj21h%2Fcryptoland_this_is_real_its_disgusting_and_its_a%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwj21h/cryptoland_this_is_real_its_disgusting_and_its_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:48:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is cryptoland, just be warned you won’t get the 10 minutes back after watching this video. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/jf3ajS5me78&quot;&amp;gt;https://youtu.be/jf3ajS5me78&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For those who did not want to watch the video here is the rub. Cryptoland is the physical manifestation of the metaverse. Created by two brain dead visionaries to sell you yet again more worthless NFTs and tokens to equate to real land on a private island only for crypto visionaries to work, live, and play.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can buy a 1 acre plot of real land to build a real house on, workout on a beachside crypto themed gym, eat at a crypto themed restaurant and bar. But what else? A ultra exclusive night club that is a members only club on a members only island than only special NFT holders can get into.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cryptoland is designed for the new lifestyle of “digital nomads” who spend their lives in hotels and glued to charts on their phones then create content with quality TA about how what coin can go up, down, or sideways. The best part is there is a whole island of these assholes!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I think I’m going to be sick…&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I just threw all my savings into bitcoin and idk how to feel.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Some background information, im from a newly 3rd world country ( Lebanon) and
ive saved 730$, dont have a job and im 23, i just threw a 700$ into btc and im
excited yet nervous, i would never sell at a loss, I'd kill my self before
taking a loss but idk i have butterflies in my stomach.

Insert…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwnj33/i_just_threw_all_my_savings_into_bitcoin_and_idk/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwnj33%2Fi_just_threw_all_my_savings_into_bitcoin_and_idk%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwnj33%2Fi_just_threw_all_my_savings_into_bitcoin_and_idk%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwnj33/i_just_threw_all_my_savings_into_bitcoin_and_idk/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:33:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some background information, im from a newly 3rd world country ( Lebanon) and ive saved 730$, dont have a job and im 23, i just threw a 700$ into btc and im excited yet nervous, i would never sell at a loss, I&amp;amp;#39;d kill my self before taking a loss but idk i have butterflies in my stomach.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Insert motivational quotes here xD.
What do you think? Is it foolish from me? But i had to buy this dip...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Looping Smart Wallet is now free to activate on L2 on iOS.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Update your iOS app, it will let you activate the L2 wallet completely free as
the fee gets passed onto Loopring.

You can then add funds via L2 networked friends or buy via the RAMP fiat on-ramp
to fund the L2 Wallet.

To have full functionality (social recovery, L1 funds etc) you’ll need…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwluuk/looping_smart_wallet_is_now_free_to_activate_on/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwluuk%2Flooping_smart_wallet_is_now_free_to_activate_on%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwluuk%2Flooping_smart_wallet_is_now_free_to_activate_on%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwluuk/looping_smart_wallet_is_now_free_to_activate_on/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:33:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Update your iOS app, it will let you activate the L2 wallet completely free as the fee gets passed onto Loopring.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can then add funds via L2 networked friends or buy via the RAMP fiat on-ramp to fund the L2 Wallet.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To have full functionality (social recovery, L1 funds etc) you’ll need to activate the L1 wallet which will of course incur a gas fee so be cautious of the current Eth gas fee. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The main draw of the L2 Wallet atm is access to DEX/AMM on L2 w/very cheap transfer fees. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Apparently the Android free L2 Wallet deploy will come soon, I assume in the next day as they can push it to Android basically any time whereas iOS has to get approved.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What's the best bitcoin quote you have ever heard?]]></title><description><![CDATA["Their ignorance is your opportunity." -Michael Saylor

That one is my favorite- surely an homage to Bezos famous quote]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rweo0a/whats_the_best_bitcoin_quote_you_have_ever_heard/?score=318&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frweo0a%2Fwhats_the_best_bitcoin_quote_you_have_ever_heard%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frweo0a%2Fwhats_the_best_bitcoin_quote_you_have_ever_heard%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rweo0a/whats_the_best_bitcoin_quote_you_have_ever_heard/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:33:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Their ignorance is your opportunity.&amp;amp;quot; -Michael Saylor&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That one is my favorite- surely an homage to Bezos famous quote&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wives &amp; Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[In another post, I read countless users saying that if crypto all of a sudden
went to $0, their wives would divorce them, take the kids, etc etc. How does
that work?

If you have some business that you invested in, and it goes to crap, does the
family give up on you?

Are you using you wife's money…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwo2sy/wives_crypto/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwo2sy%2Fwives_crypto%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwo2sy%2Fwives_crypto%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwo2sy/wives_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:33:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In another post, I read countless users saying that if crypto all of a sudden went to $0, their wives would divorce them, take the kids, etc etc. How does that work? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you have some business that you invested in, and it goes to crap, does the family give up on you? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Are you using you wife&amp;amp;#39;s money to buy crypto and your kids aren&amp;amp;#39;t eating because of it?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Well, not at all like that here at home. I invested in Crypto, but I invested in crypto with MY OWN MONEY, if it goes to zero, it&amp;amp;#39;s my bad, not hers. She works and earns her money too, buys her shoes and dresses and I don&amp;amp;#39;t stick my nose in, it&amp;amp;#39;s her money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As long as our house expenses are covered where each one pays half of them, then the spare money we can do whatever we want because it&amp;amp;#39;s our money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For context, I live in Portugal (Europe), for cultural reasons, things might work differently in your country. Not saying I&amp;amp;#39;m right and you are wrong, just putting different lifestyles in perspective.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How does it work at your place? Does your family have a say in your personal expenses?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zero-knowledge proof explained like you are 5 years old]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi kids!

So, you're interested in cryptocurrencies, and you've heard about those
so-called "zero-knowledge proofs" (ZK) used by projects such as Loopring, zkSync
and StarkWare.

Now you're wondering : what are zero-knowledge proofs and why are they so
important? Good news, champ, I am here for…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwpfkx/zeroknowledge_proof_explained_like_you_are_5/?score=358&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwpfkx%2Fzeroknowledge_proof_explained_like_you_are_5%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwpfkx%2Fzeroknowledge_proof_explained_like_you_are_5%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwpfkx/zeroknowledge_proof_explained_like_you_are_5/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:33:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hi kids!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, you&amp;amp;#39;re interested in cryptocurrencies, and you&amp;amp;#39;ve heard about those so-called &amp;amp;quot;zero-knowledge proofs&amp;amp;quot; (ZK) used by projects such as Loopring, zkSync and StarkWare.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now you&amp;amp;#39;re wondering : what are zero-knowledge proofs and why are they so important? Good news, champ, I am here for you!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let&amp;amp;#39;s say I found a cave with two distinct entrances, Left and Right. The two entrances are connected by a corridor, but a dragon prevents anyone from passing through the corridor. To make the dragon let you through, you need a magic stone. I have this magic stone, and I want to prove to you that I have it, but I don&amp;amp;#39;t want to show it to you, and I don&amp;amp;#39;t want to tell my secret to anyone but you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is how it works. You close your eyes while I enter the cave, without telling you if I chose the Left or Right entrance. You open your eyes again, then ask me to come out on a particular side and I do so. You close your eyes, I go back into the cave, and we repeat the experience 100 times.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If I have the magic stone, the dragon will let me through everytime and I can leave the cave through the entrance you tell me, 100 times out of 100. But if I don&amp;amp;#39;t have the stone, every other time I won&amp;amp;#39;t be able to get out through the chosen entrance - statistically, I will only have the good answer 50% of the time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;So by using this method, I will prove to you that I have the magic stone, without ever showing it to you&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Moreover, you will not be able to prove to anyone else that I have the stone, since an outside observer could always think that we have arranged it together in advance.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is what is called a zero-knowledge proof. In cryptocurrencies, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;the magic stone is the private key&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Zero-knowledge proofs are used to show to a validator that you are indeed in possession of the private key, without revealing said private keys to the validator, and without letting the rest of the world know you have the key.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thank you for listening to my story. I hope you had fun today, my little friends!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anyone else experience this? Told my friend at work about Bitcoin, he was really fascinated by it as an inflation hedge. Came back the next day with a bunch of shitcoins but no Bitcoin.]]></title><description><![CDATA[He said he downloaded Coinbase and bought a bunch of random coins some youtuber
suggested. I asked him if he bought any Bitcoin, he said "nope, it was too
expensive".

🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rws5ye/anyone_else_experience_this_told_my_friend_at/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frws5ye%2Fanyone_else_experience_this_told_my_friend_at%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frws5ye%2Fanyone_else_experience_this_told_my_friend_at%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rws5ye/anyone_else_experience_this_told_my_friend_at/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 21:32:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He said he downloaded Coinbase and bought a bunch of random coins some youtuber suggested. I asked him if he bought any Bitcoin, he said &amp;amp;quot;nope, it was too expensive&amp;amp;quot;. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Heads up and be safe: I just lost BTC because of Malware that highjacks my clipboard [Windows]]]></title><description><![CDATA[I just lost a significant amount of BTC (to me at least, I can only save
~100$/month). I had my last BTC (sats, really) purchases sitting in my exchange
and wanted to move them to my (software) wallet that I use on my phone. So I
copied/pasted it the address on a secure notepad app that syncs with…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwlkd0/heads_up_and_be_safe_i_just_lost_btc_because_of/?score=331&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwlkd0%2Fheads_up_and_be_safe_i_just_lost_btc_because_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwlkd0%2Fheads_up_and_be_safe_i_just_lost_btc_because_of%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwlkd0/heads_up_and_be_safe_i_just_lost_btc_because_of/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 21:32:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I just lost a significant amount of BTC (to me at least, I can only save ~100$/month). I had my last BTC (sats, really) purchases sitting in my exchange and wanted to move them to my (software) wallet that I use on my phone. So I copied/pasted it the address on a secure notepad app that syncs with PC, then checked that the address shown on my PC matched the wallet address. It did, so that&amp;amp;#39;s cool.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So on the PC I copied/pasted it on the address box for the withdrawal at my exchange, it was shown as a valid address and I proceeded with the transaction. WRONG!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I sat there waiting for my funds to appear on my wallet but they never did. Transaction was shown as completed on the exchange and then I got alarmed. Started to write an email to my exchange&amp;amp;#39;s support team and then it clicked.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I wanted to say that the destination address was &amp;amp;#39;X&amp;amp;#39; but somehow it was being shown as &amp;amp;#39;Y&amp;amp;#39; on the transaction history. But every time I tried to paste my address it was changing right before my eyes. So my email was looking like &amp;amp;lt;&amp;amp;lt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;This is mi destination address: &amp;amp;#39;Y&amp;amp;#39; // This is the address shown on the transacion history: &amp;amp;#39;Y&amp;amp;#39;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;gt;&amp;amp;gt;. Now, my notepad app was clearly showing that the adddress I was trying to copy was most definitely not &amp;amp;#39;Y&amp;amp;#39;, so something was up.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyway, at that point I deleted the email, no need to bother some support dude because of something that was looking more and more like a royal fuck up.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And then there it is, there was some malware on my PC that was actively seeking BTC addresses and switching them to something similar but a different address alltoghether from whoever scammer made the damned thing. I clearly fucked up by not realizing that, and now&amp;amp;#39;s too late.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Malwarebytes was quick to find and delete the thing and now the computer&amp;amp;#39;s clean again (just like my exchange account, haha. FUCK.)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Be safe out there and double check or triple check everything when doing a transaction. I didn&amp;amp;#39;t realize  at the time so I&amp;amp;#39;m an idiot, but maybe you won&amp;amp;#39;t have to be.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;---&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TL;DR&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s malware out there reading your clipboard to find BTC addresses, and when you try to copy/paste it will paste a similar address from the scammer. I didn&amp;amp;#39;t realize so I&amp;amp;#39;m an idiot, but maybe you won&amp;amp;#39;t have to be.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;---&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: Okay, thanks for the awards and all. I read the comments but was lazy to reply to each one individually.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;1- My PC wasn&amp;amp;#39;t as infested as some of you may think, I actually clean installed windows 11 like 3 weeks ago FFS. I will reformat it again on the weekend, no worries there. The fucking antivirus did find the culprit, though. After deleting the files and restarting the PC, clipboard was behaving correctly again (I checked a shit ton of times).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;2- &amp;amp;#39;A secure notepad app that syncs&amp;amp;#39; was just to make it easier to explain. It was Bitwarden, using the note entry options. It&amp;amp;#39;s a password manager so it is indeed secure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;3- Mac / Linux people... Let&amp;amp;#39;s just not go there, I don&amp;amp;#39;t care about OS master race. Windows is a great fit for what I use it and all other OS have their flaws too.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;4- Hardware wallet option is something that I&amp;amp;#39;m always considering, I just fear loosing it, TBH. 2-stage transactions seems like a good enough compromise to me for the time being.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;5- Software wallet on my phone gets uninstalled after each deposit, because I agree that it&amp;amp;#39;s not a great thing to carry around. Then whenever I want to transfer again I re-download it and use the seed phrase to access my stuff.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;6- Now let&amp;amp;#39;s be clear, I know that evrything&amp;amp;#39;s my fault, here. For what is worth, the address was very similar (first letters were the exact same), and was given as a valid address by the exchange so i trusted it more than I should have, but i did not check the complete string and that&amp;amp;#39;s on me. I&amp;amp;#39;m a bit of a newbie, but not a complete idiot, it&amp;amp;#39;s just that I plain hadn&amp;amp;#39;t heard about this particular scam before (hence why I wrote it to alert any other newbie that could find the info useful).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;7- To the people thinking that this was an ad and I didn&amp;amp;#39;t just lose my money... I wish it was so, I truly truly do. Imagine if those fuckers were paying me, too. Ah... Wouldn&amp;amp;#39;t that be nice? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyway, you can&amp;amp;#39;t trust your clipboard, there&amp;amp;#39;s a lesson learned.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m a few steps back and it kinda sucks, but I&amp;amp;#39;ll go back to stacking sats.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Airbnb To Implement Crypto Payments]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwn5a8/airbnb_to_implement_crypto_payments/?score=399&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwn5a8%2Fairbnb_to_implement_crypto_payments%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwn5a8%2Fairbnb_to_implement_crypto_payments%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwn5a8/airbnb_to_implement_crypto_payments/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 20:37:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Things I Wish I Did Earlier When Investing In Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi everyone! Today marks the anniversary of my first ever crypto transaction! My
first purchase was of Ethereum, and since then it has been nothing else but a
learning journey.

There were a lot of things I learnt later than what I wished, so here are a few
of the things I wish I did earlier when…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwjwly/things_i_wish_i_did_earlier_when_investing_in/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwjwly%2Fthings_i_wish_i_did_earlier_when_investing_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwjwly%2Fthings_i_wish_i_did_earlier_when_investing_in%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwjwly/things_i_wish_i_did_earlier_when_investing_in/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 18:47:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hi everyone! Today marks the anniversary of my first ever crypto transaction! My first purchase was of Ethereum, and since then it has been nothing else but a learning journey.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There were a lot of things I learnt later than what I wished, so here are a few of the things I wish I did earlier when investing in crypto:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Keeping track of transactions&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: when I first bought crypto, I invested X amount of fiat without keeping track of how much I have put into it. Later, I discovered the portfolio trackers. Some good examples are the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://delta.app/en&quot;&amp;gt;Delta App&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coinmarketcap.com/&quot;&amp;gt;CoinMarketCap&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; portfolio tool. I rather input the transaction manually after making them, as I don&amp;amp;#39;t really like giving API keys to 3rd parties.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Opening a Vault for Moons&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: easily the worst mistake I have ever done. I never knew the existence of moons until they, well, mooned. I always use my PC or laptop for Reddit and never seen the Vault menu, and when I found out about I felt so stupid as I was quite active in this sub when I first started. Open your Vault!! It is literally free crypto for your posts - please focus on quality!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Having Native Wallets&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: this isn&amp;amp;#39;t a mistake, but more of a &amp;amp;quot;help the ecosystem&amp;amp;quot; kind of thing. What I must recommend though is to keep all your assets away from exchanges. A system failure, hacking attack or just bankruptcy can be the end of your funds, so keep your coins in an external wallet. I started with &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.exodus.com/&quot;&amp;gt;Exodus Wallet&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, as it has the most assets and allows staking for interest rewards. With time, I migrated to native wallets (wallets made for a single network in particular) and around 80% of my assets are secured with a Ledger Nano X (hardware wallet, not hackable!).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Don&amp;amp;#39;t stick to one exchange&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: not all exchanges have all the coins you will want. Not all exchanges have the same features and most importantly, not all have the same fees. what exchanges do I recommend? I personally use &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://Crypto.com&quot;&amp;gt;Crypto.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kraken.com/&quot;&amp;gt;Kraken&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. Of course, each one to their own and geographical restrictions may apply to some exchanges.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Don&amp;amp;#39;t do stupid things that can cause you headaches&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: what I mean with this is, do not add 5 bank accounts to your fiat withdrawal addresses, don&amp;amp;#39;t deposit fiat from 4 different banks in 3 different countries, 2 credit cards and 4 debit cards. Focus on 1 and 1. One card. One bank account. Work yourself around that and it will help you massively. I have seen so many issues with people with locked accounts due to having to verify details etc. that can just be solved by this. I never had a single issue using &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.revolut.com/&quot;&amp;gt;Revolut&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; as my bank account and the virtual card as my means of payment if i use this. Also, all bank deposits are allowed to exchanges from them (EU Customer). KYC! Just do it. The government knows all about you anyways, so don&amp;amp;#39;t worry. You are happy to give your bank details, name, surname, card number away but not a selfie of yourself? The big exchanges have great privacy and security measures, don&amp;amp;#39;t worry!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Find Rewards. There are A LOT OF THEM!&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: Crypto is a baby. A volatile baby, but a baby nonetheless. Everything is new! DeFi projects can offer 100%+ APY by staking your coins, projects with PoS networks offer some really good interest by just hodling their coin and a lot of platforms offer interest in stablecoins and other tokens. Personally, I use one of the VISA Cards that CDC offer. It earns me cashback, free services and lets be honest, looks cool af!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Lastly but most importantly, ENJOY&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: Don&amp;amp;#39;t look at the chart every day and worry. Yes I look at my portfolio every day but just to see if it is a good moment to buy or not. I never worry. If you are a day trader, then yes. A hodler, then hodl. You are here for the long run. Enjoy the experience, the learning and the communities (apart from &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/r/bitcoin&quot;&amp;gt;r/bitcoin&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; - that&amp;amp;#39;s a cult). &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hopefully this helps newbies a bit more, and makes it easier to start up! Have a great year everyone.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Did your altcoin just moon? Great! Now sell 15% of the bag. Hodl the rest for the next liftoff, or buy the next dip with your new gains. It's an easy rule of thumb to make sure you're always taking profits]]></title><description><![CDATA[It's so easy to get stuck on, "oh no, I shouldn't sell the whole bag because
what if it goes up more!" And dammit, you're right to wanna hold.

But this is a game of making money, and if that's your goal you need to sell
into euphoria

When you're seeing double digit percent gains on your coin,…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwcosl/did_your_altcoin_just_moon_great_now_sell_15_of/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwcosl%2Fdid_your_altcoin_just_moon_great_now_sell_15_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwcosl%2Fdid_your_altcoin_just_moon_great_now_sell_15_of%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwcosl/did_your_altcoin_just_moon_great_now_sell_15_of/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 16:38:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s so easy to get stuck on, &amp;amp;quot;oh no, I shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t sell the whole bag because what if it goes up more!&amp;amp;quot; And dammit, you&amp;amp;#39;re right to wanna hold. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But this is a game of making money, and if that&amp;amp;#39;s your goal you need to &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;sell into euphoria&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When you&amp;amp;#39;re seeing double digit percent gains on your coin, it&amp;amp;#39;s time to make that trade and sell a little bit of the bag. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s usually a nice dip afterwards and you&amp;amp;#39;ll be glad you&amp;amp;#39;ve got the powder to burn. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And if there&amp;amp;#39;s not a dip afterwards, you&amp;amp;#39;ve got 85% of your original bag to decide to hold or sell. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Finally, if the coin truly tanks afterwards then, you have some USDC that&amp;amp;#39;s much more tradable than your ElonCumRocket. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s truly a win-win-win&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NFTs won't ruin computer games, greedy game companies will ruin computer games using NFTs]]></title><description><![CDATA[As the title says, there was a post recently in the gaming subreddit that was
claiming that NFTs will ruin computer gaming further just like microtransactions
did.

However, I disagree with that statement. If NFTs were in DnD they would be a
lawful neutral force, they are not good or evil they are…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwlo57/nfts_wont_ruin_computer_games_greedy_game/?score=505&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwlo57%2Fnfts_wont_ruin_computer_games_greedy_game%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwlo57%2Fnfts_wont_ruin_computer_games_greedy_game%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwlo57/nfts_wont_ruin_computer_games_greedy_game/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 14:33:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As the title says, there was a post recently in the gaming subreddit that was claiming that NFTs will ruin computer gaming further just like microtransactions did.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, I disagree with that statement. If NFTs were in DnD they would be a lawful neutral force, they are not good or evil they are just a tool and being a transparent and open tool it makes them more easy to keep track of.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If anything NFTs should provide more consumer protection for digital game downloads than the present model of Microsoft being all like &amp;amp;quot;trust me bra, we got this&amp;amp;quot; until one day they just remove the game from the store and leave no public evidence that you ever owned it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, I also 100% guarantee that game companies are going to use this to further monetise the market for pointless crap cosmetics and strip even more out of a game to sell back to the player later.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But people shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t hate the technology, that&amp;amp;#39;s like hating the internet because game companies use the internet to download microtransactions, it really makes no sense. Hate the companies and hate the people buying their garbage.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Be honest. Which coin(s) did you buy just because it is being shilled here or twitter or anywhere else, without doing researching on it?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Have you ever seen coins that are being or have been shilled nonstop? Ehem ERG
ALGO LRC

Everyone always say DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH, but we all know that there are times
when we are too lazy to do this tedious part of investment and we're like ahh
fuck it, what could possibly go wrong and just put in…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwhxvb/be_honest_which_coins_did_you_buy_just_because_it/?score=362&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwhxvb%2Fbe_honest_which_coins_did_you_buy_just_because_it%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwhxvb%2Fbe_honest_which_coins_did_you_buy_just_because_it%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwhxvb/be_honest_which_coins_did_you_buy_just_because_it/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 13:37:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Have you ever seen coins that are being or have been shilled nonstop? &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Ehem&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; ERG ALGO LRC&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Everyone always say DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH, but we all know that there are times when we are too lazy to do this tedious part of investment and we&amp;amp;#39;re like &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;ahh fuck it, what could possibly go wrong&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; and just put in money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So which projects or coins have you bought without doing prior research and just went in head first? Was it successful? Did it fail horribly? How were you convinced to buy it just because? Was it the sheer volume of the people shilling? Did you read something informative that enticed you to buy it?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: ok that&amp;amp;#39;s a lot of people&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Assets lined up by their S2F ratio and market value, just coincidence or meaningful pattern? Note that current BTC cluster (2020-2024, upper right blue dots) is half-filled. https://t.co/2A05HERwoY]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1478701553800335363/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1478701553800335363/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 12:48:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Happening Now: Airbnb Could Soon Add Support for Cryptocurrency Payments]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwgmna/happening_now_airbnb_could_soon_add_support_for/?score=357&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwgmna%2Fhappening_now_airbnb_could_soon_add_support_for%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwgmna%2Fhappening_now_airbnb_could_soon_add_support_for%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwgmna/happening_now_airbnb_could_soon_add_support_for/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 12:48:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[human progress is measured on the Kardashev scale; #bitcoin accelerates the building of energy grids to power the future. https://t.co/hLe9XLp8IW]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1478656462947762177/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1478656462947762177/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Am I the only one that has never had a problem with Coinbase?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I see countless posts everyday about how Coinbase has been terrible for people.
Their Coinbase account got hacked, they got scammed, Coinbase support won’t get
back to them, etc…

I started with Coinbase early last year. I did lumpsum investments, weekly
recurring investments, monthly recurring,…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwcou2/am_i_the_only_one_that_has_never_had_a_problem/?score=333&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwcou2%2Fam_i_the_only_one_that_has_never_had_a_problem%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwcou2%2Fam_i_the_only_one_that_has_never_had_a_problem%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwcou2/am_i_the_only_one_that_has_never_had_a_problem/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 11:37:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I see countless posts everyday about how Coinbase has been terrible for people. Their Coinbase account got hacked, they got scammed, Coinbase support won’t get back to them, etc…&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I started with Coinbase early last year. I did lumpsum investments, weekly recurring investments, monthly recurring, staking, Coinbase earn, conversions, literally everything you can do on Coinbase (besides sell) and have never ever had one issue. I mean, I’m not out here throwing money at memecoins but I’d say I’m using Coinbase the way it is supposed to be used and what they promise. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve more than tripled what I put in, and do not have a single complaint about it. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Is there anyone else that is completely satisfied with Coinbase? I can’t help but think, looking at all these posts, that a lot of the problems people are running into are user error, but maybe I’m the exception?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[It takes a brave man to tell the truth. @bobscartoons is a brave and deeply compassionate man.
https://t.co/NRfaqmIzAr]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1478662379005259776/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1478662379005259776/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 10:36:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Could Reach $100K And Overtake Gold's Market Share: Goldman Sachs]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwbnby/bitcoin_could_reach_100k_and_overtake_golds/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwbnby%2Fbitcoin_could_reach_100k_and_overtake_golds%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwbnby%2Fbitcoin_could_reach_100k_and_overtake_golds%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwbnby/bitcoin_could_reach_100k_and_overtake_golds/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 10:36:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[dont be like your parents.. INVEST NOW, so your kids can grow up with money and become the douche bags you always hated]]></title><description><![CDATA[I've been in crypto for a while and no im not rich yet. but what i been noticing
besides the price flux lol, is the amount of people that is getting into crypto
as a whole. if its not investing its NFT games, or using it to buy something at
a discount at somewhere like the Dallas Mavericks stadium,…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw3vsz/dont_be_like_your_parents_invest_now_so_your_kids/?score=307&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw3vsz%2Fdont_be_like_your_parents_invest_now_so_your_kids%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw3vsz%2Fdont_be_like_your_parents_invest_now_so_your_kids%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw3vsz/dont_be_like_your_parents_invest_now_so_your_kids/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 08:38:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ve been in crypto for a while and no im not rich yet. but what i been noticing besides the price flux lol, is the amount of people that is getting into crypto as a whole. if its not investing its NFT games, or using it to buy something at a discount at somewhere like the Dallas Mavericks stadium, or people are just seeing ads or companies that produce products they use, get into it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;the other day on the train i seen many train carts with AVAX (Avalanche blockchain) ads all over the inside of the train cart in NYC ( you can imagine the excitement i felt lol) , i also seen ads for Upland ( a crypto real estate game)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;this is our chance to really get invested and wait for things to get better. I know there&amp;amp;#39;s a chance the market will collapse in a spectacle of people pulling their hair out and jumping out windows, but with the amount of institutions and big companies getting involved, i doubt it. the amount of users they will bring on to what ever networks they decide to work with will def help the case.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;every time the internet upgrades a good handful of people get rich, and yes alot of people lose money also ( but those are the impatient people or the people who put in too much and end up having to pull out )&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;even look at this video from after skool is all about crypto. ( mainly ether and bitcoin ) but they are a youtube channel that makes videos about mental health and life&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;VIDEO: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qGHMyxYSa58&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qGHMyxYSa58&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;if they are making videos about it, i know this is def not going anywhere and who ever chooses the best chains to invest in will change their life for the better or worse if you only want hookers and cocaine... your choice and youre money&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;So for the love of MONEY,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; just DYOR and Invest&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;HODEL&amp;amp;gt; PROFIT&amp;amp;gt; CREATE&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Samsung to plant 2 million trees with climate solutions platform, Veritree that uses Cardano to verify and track every step of the reforestation process.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rvvt2w/samsung_to_plant_2_million_trees_with_climate/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frvvt2w%2Fsamsung_to_plant_2_million_trees_with_climate%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frvvt2w%2Fsamsung_to_plant_2_million_trees_with_climate%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rvvt2w/samsung_to_plant_2_million_trees_with_climate/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 07:38:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[After being on the air for months, the Matt Damon crypto commercial is all of a sudden getting a bunch of negative attention. Twitter trolls seem to be upset they missed the gains]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw5s4p/after_being_on_the_air_for_months_the_matt_damon/?score=314&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw5s4p%2Fafter_being_on_the_air_for_months_the_matt_damon%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw5s4p%2Fafter_being_on_the_air_for_months_the_matt_damon%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw5s4p/after_being_on_the_air_for_months_the_matt_damon/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 05:38:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Algorand Governance Distribution Breakdown - 50,000 transactions costing just 50 ALGO]]></title><description><![CDATA[Those that signed up for the first round of governance will have received their
rewards now.

50,000 transactions took just 20 minutes, with $100 million worth of ALGO
distributed. The total transaction fee costing 50 ALGO.

Now whether you have a bag of ALGO or not, its good to see what is…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw4j5a/algorand_governance_distribution_breakdown_50000/?score=313&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw4j5a%2Falgorand_governance_distribution_breakdown_50000%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw4j5a%2Falgorand_governance_distribution_breakdown_50000%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw4j5a/algorand_governance_distribution_breakdown_50000/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 05:38:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Those that signed up for the first round of governance will have received their rewards now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;50,000 transactions took just 20 minutes, with $100 million worth of ALGO distributed. The total transaction fee costing 50 ALGO. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now whether you have a bag of ALGO or not, its good to see what is possible with crypto and can only be seen as a positive for us all.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For those that aren&amp;amp;#39;t aware, the rewards were around 3.5% for the 3 month locked period - that&amp;amp;#39;s 14.75%APR. Again, this is only another positive for us all. Its well above inflation and considerably more than any bank would offer in a standard savings account. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The deadline for the second round of Governance is the 6th January, so if you&amp;amp;#39;re thinking about locking it in until the end of March you&amp;amp;#39;ve got a couple of days left (depending where you are in the world).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Bored Ape NFT craze is all about ego and money, not art | Art and design]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rvy6gm/the_bored_ape_nft_craze_is_all_about_ego_and/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frvy6gm%2Fthe_bored_ape_nft_craze_is_all_about_ego_and%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frvy6gm%2Fthe_bored_ape_nft_craze_is_all_about_ego_and%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rvy6gm/the_bored_ape_nft_craze_is_all_about_ego_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 05:38:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin is monetary integrity.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rw7t66/bitcoin_is_monetary_integrity/?score=424&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frw7t66%2Fbitcoin_is_monetary_integrity%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frw7t66%2Fbitcoin_is_monetary_integrity%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rw7t66/bitcoin_is_monetary_integrity/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 04:52:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Learning how to invest in crypto has been absolutely empowering as a woman.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have been working in digital for over twenty years, and the first time I heard
about crypto was from one of my fellow devs who was mining Doge in 2014. I
bought about $50 worth of it back then and ended up losing access to wherever it
was stored at the time. No big deal, it was my first lesson in…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw9smd/learning_how_to_invest_in_crypto_has_been/?score=349&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw9smd%2Flearning_how_to_invest_in_crypto_has_been%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw9smd%2Flearning_how_to_invest_in_crypto_has_been%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw9smd/learning_how_to_invest_in_crypto_has_been/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 04:52:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I have been working in digital for over twenty years, and the first time I heard about crypto was from one of my fellow devs who was mining Doge in 2014. I bought about $50 worth of it back then and ended up losing access to wherever it was stored at the time. No big deal, it was my first lesson in this crypto journey, one of many. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After years of not paying much attention to crypto and working on other investments; stocks, real estate, retirement funds, etc. I came back to the space in 2019 with a renewed passion and drive. Stocks had always bored me, I never felt like it was a market I related with, and since I work in digital, crypto makes sense to me. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So I got back into Doge because that&amp;amp;#39;s where I started. And then BTC and then ETH all around the same time in 2019. Then came alts, and with them came tons of research and discovery, buying projects I believe in. The crypto world&amp;amp;#39;s volatility didn&amp;amp;#39;t scare me then, and it doesn&amp;amp;#39;t scare me now because I think it&amp;amp;#39;s the future, and I refuse to sit on fiat that isn&amp;amp;#39;t working for me.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Fast forward to this fine new year, and I am so proud to have grown my portfolio to what it is today. To be a woman in this space, understand the fundamentals, and withstand the fear is very empowering. So to all the women out there who are either veterans in the crypto space or newbies, keep going!! It&amp;amp;#39;s an honor to invest alongside all of you! And cheers to the men out there crushing it too!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: this is absolutely not an anti-man post! Yeesh! Men rock! This is more about women having confidence to invest, learn, grow and become financially independent. Ultimately being able to build an empire with their crypto loving mate!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Only 1% of the world owns Crypto, it is silly to say we aren't early.]]></title><description><![CDATA[There are currently approximately 100 million blockchain wallets out there. This
is an extremely small amount considering that is only 1.28% of the 7.8 Billion
people we have on earth. The $2.2 Trillion Crypto market is extremely
undervalued. In the future when digital currencies start gaining…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw2atb/only_1_of_the_world_owns_crypto_it_is_silly_to/?score=313&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw2atb%2Fonly_1_of_the_world_owns_crypto_it_is_silly_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw2atb%2Fonly_1_of_the_world_owns_crypto_it_is_silly_to%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw2atb/only_1_of_the_world_owns_crypto_it_is_silly_to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 04:52:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are currently approximately 100 million blockchain wallets out there. This is an extremely small amount considering that is only 1.28% of the 7.8 Billion people we have on earth. The $2.2 Trillion Crypto market is extremely undervalued. In the future when digital currencies start gaining ground and you count inflation, tens of trillions in market cap are completely feasible.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Remember, market cap doesn&amp;amp;#39;t reflect the amount of money invested in Crypto, it just multiplies the current market price with circulating coins. Just because the market cap is high, does not mean Crypto does not have more room to grow.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let&amp;amp;#39;s say someone tries to acquire $10 Billion in Bitcoin, exchanges feel the pinch and start raising the prices accordingly, the new raised price for each Bitcoin is going to multiplied by the entire circulating amount and raise the market cap by hundreds of billions, if not more.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A good explanation would be Fiat, according to estimates, all the U.S money in circulation is worth &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;6.6 trillion U.S. dollars.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Yet, the USD market cap exceeds 21 Trillion dollars.  The market cap of all Fiat in the world is over &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://fiatmarketcap.com/&quot;&amp;gt;123 Trillion USD&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. Crypto has huge potential, and a 2.2 Trillion market cap for Crypto is still very undervalued.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TLDR&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: Yes, we might not be early compared to people in 2010, but being the first 1% to adopt Crypto is still very early. Crypto still has the untapped potential of the 99%, and in that sense we are indeed early as we have tens, if not hundreds of trillions to go.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is anyone else terrified of CBDC's and their potential to enslave humanity?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Look into CBDCs and the amount of control they give to central banks.

 * they are fully centralized
 * transparent, every transaction is subject to surveillance.
 * transactions are directly taxable.
 * endless money printing ie. inflation.
 * negative interest rates.
 * expiry dates on money…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rw2een/is_anyone_else_terrified_of_cbdcs_and_their/?score=315&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frw2een%2Fis_anyone_else_terrified_of_cbdcs_and_their%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frw2een%2Fis_anyone_else_terrified_of_cbdcs_and_their%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rw2een/is_anyone_else_terrified_of_cbdcs_and_their/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 03:42:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Look into CBDCs and the amount of control they give to central banks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;they are fully centralized&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;transparent, every transaction is subject to surveillance.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;transactions are directly taxable.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;endless money printing ie. inflation.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;negative interest rates.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;expiry dates on money (literally you have 3 months to spend your salary or it is gone).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;control over what you can and cannot spend your money on.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;easily restrict where you can spend your money, at what time you can spend your money, or even turn off bankaccounts/people.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Look into social credit systems, how effectively they oppress populations. They are already a reality in parts of China.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;a point system that determines your social status.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;virtue points for stuff the government likes&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;penalty points for stuff the government doesnt like.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;your &amp;amp;quot;citizen privileges&amp;amp;quot; are determined by this point system.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;want access to restaurants? your score needs to be over 100 or your QR doesnt work.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;went to the wrong protest?, talked to a dissident?&amp;amp;gt;&amp;amp;gt;&amp;amp;gt; no traveling for you, no supermarket for you... no school for your kids.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;sucked off the balls of the government? &amp;amp;gt;&amp;amp;gt;&amp;amp;gt; maybe youre allowed to buy better food or even some alcohol this month, sucked hard enough?? maybe your kids get to go to a better school.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now combine CBDC&amp;amp;#39;s and social credit...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;CBDCs are every totalitarians wet dream. An airtight tool for oppression.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The QR code system that they&amp;amp;#39;ve been trying to introduce though the covid pandemic is the perfect trojan horse. (I happen to think that is not a coincidence, but then again I am also a crazy conspiracy theorist.)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know one thing though:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If CBDC&amp;amp;#39;s ever get widely implemented we will forever be cattle to whoever controls them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ergo (ERG) is a prime example of why you shouldn’t listen to this sub for financial advice.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Around 4-5 months ago, this subs favorite low market cap coin was Ergo (ERG).

During its hype it was hovering around $14-$18, a few months later and it’s down
at $4 - down more than 70% from its ATH.

This is an even better post about this…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw3924/ergo_erg_is_a_prime_example_of_why_you_shouldnt/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw3924%2Fergo_erg_is_a_prime_example_of_why_you_shouldnt%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw3924%2Fergo_erg_is_a_prime_example_of_why_you_shouldnt%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw3924/ergo_erg_is_a_prime_example_of_why_you_shouldnt/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 02:49:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Around 4-5 months ago, this subs favorite low market cap coin was Ergo (ERG). &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;During its hype it was hovering around $14-$18, a few months later and it’s down at $4 - down more than 70% from its ATH.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/qbyq2i/unpopular_as_heck_if_this_sub_is_shilling_a_coin/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=ios_app&amp;amp;amp;utm_name=iossmf&quot;&amp;gt;This is an even better post about this topic.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;As&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;you&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;can&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;see,&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;when&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;OP&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;made&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;the&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;post&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;Ergo&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;was&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;at&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;$9.99,&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;it’s&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;down&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;even&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;more&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;now!&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/q563f2/ergo_deep_dive/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=ios_app&amp;amp;amp;utm_name=iossmf&quot;&amp;gt;An Ergo shill post, a really good one tbh!&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;Down&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;54%&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;since&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;this&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;post.&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/pn1drc/erg_ergo_is_getting_popular_dont_miss_out_just/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=ios_app&amp;amp;amp;utm_name=iossmf&quot;&amp;gt;Don’t miss out on Ergo!&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;Don’t&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;miss&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;out&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;on&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;a&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;way&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;to&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;lose&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;67%&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;in&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;4&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;months.&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/p9g8v4/whats_your_favorite_project_outside_the_top_100/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=ios_app&amp;amp;amp;utm_name=iossmf&quot;&amp;gt;What’s the top comment in a post asking about the best project outside top 100 market cap? Guess?&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;Ergo&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;everywhere.&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Don’t make my mistake. If a coin is shilled way to much here don’t buy it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto is ‘not a fad’ says Morgan Stanley CEO Gorman, ‘It’s not going away’]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rvj2hk/crypto_is_not_a_fad_says_morgan_stanley_ceo/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frvj2hk%2Fcrypto_is_not_a_fad_says_morgan_stanley_ceo%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frvj2hk%2Fcrypto_is_not_a_fad_says_morgan_stanley_ceo%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rvj2hk/crypto_is_not_a_fad_says_morgan_stanley_ceo/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 01:01:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stop being A$$holes]]></title><description><![CDATA[This needs to be said here. Bashing people for not understanding or adopting BTC
like you might doesn’t help to turn them in your corner.

More BTC people need to think about this as getting people “over to your team”
and realize people will have vastly different reasons than yours on why…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rvszor/stop_being_aholes/?score=316&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frvszor%2Fstop_being_aholes%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frvszor%2Fstop_being_aholes%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rvszor/stop_being_aholes/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 01:01:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This needs to be said here. Bashing people for not understanding or adopting BTC like you might doesn’t help to turn them in your corner. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;More BTC people need to think about this as getting people “over to your team” and realize people will have vastly different reasons than yours on why they adopt BTC. And that’s a good thing. It only strengthens BTC. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So cheers to getting more people orange pilled for whatever damn reason they choose and just wish them luck on their journey!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MATIC is sweating like a pig with over 580 GWEI right now]]></title><description><![CDATA[ZK rollup solution to reduce the gas fees and improve transactions is something
that I'm really bullish on. I've been in MATIC since it was worth only a quarter
of a dollar and I support the project wholeheartedly.

Right now, MATIC Polygon is sweating like a pig on a roast, because one one
small…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw0mky/matic_is_sweating_like_a_pig_with_over_580_gwei/?score=333&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw0mky%2Fmatic_is_sweating_like_a_pig_with_over_580_gwei%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw0mky%2Fmatic_is_sweating_like_a_pig_with_over_580_gwei%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw0mky/matic_is_sweating_like_a_pig_with_over_580_gwei/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 23:31:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;ZK rollup solution to reduce the gas fees and improve transactions is something that I&amp;amp;#39;m really bullish on. I&amp;amp;#39;ve been in MATIC since it was worth only a quarter of a dollar and I support the project wholeheartedly.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Right now, MATIC Polygon is sweating like a pig on a roast, because one one small blockchain game. People are farming pixel sunflowers and the gas fees went up over 580 GWEI and keeps rising! I don&amp;amp;#39;t think this should happen from such a small bump in activity on blockchain. Right now the gas fees are getting pretty damn high on MATIC almost 0.4 MATIC to get a transaction through and that is a big if.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Quite crazy what one little event did. I wonder if they can learn from this and improve the network.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[If all cryptocurrency fell to 0$ tomorrow, how fucked are you ?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello fellow crypto enjoyers.

We all know the rules of crypto investments. One of those rules, for the new
people around here, is « You shall only invest what you are not afraid to
loose ».

But realistically, we all know there’s a lot of people that invest a lot more
than what they can afford to…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw0v99/if_all_cryptocurrency_fell_to_0_tomorrow_how/?score=358&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw0v99%2Fif_all_cryptocurrency_fell_to_0_tomorrow_how%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw0v99%2Fif_all_cryptocurrency_fell_to_0_tomorrow_how%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw0v99/if_all_cryptocurrency_fell_to_0_tomorrow_how/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 22:37:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hello fellow crypto enjoyers.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We all know the rules of crypto investments. One of those rules, for the new people around here, is « You shall only invest what you are not afraid to loose ».&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But realistically, we all know there’s a lot of people that invest a lot more than what they can afford to loose. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Personally, I’m a pretty broke student, and 70% of my capital is in crypto. If I happened to loose that, I would be basically homeless pretty soon !&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, if all crypto fell to 0$ or something close to that, how deep in the mud are you ? This can also serve as a reminder to be careful about the projects you invest in.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Many experts have started predicting two or three more countries will make Bitcoin legal tender this year in 2022. Here is why I believe Dubai and the UAE will be next.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dubai has to be the next top contender for making Bitcoin legal tender. Here are
a few reasons I could think of as to why.

1) Their currency is stuck pegged to the US dollar which with inflation rising
is horrible for them, they need an alternative to use along side their existing
currency.

2)…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rvyxw9/many_experts_have_started_predicting_two_or_three/?score=358&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frvyxw9%2Fmany_experts_have_started_predicting_two_or_three%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frvyxw9%2Fmany_experts_have_started_predicting_two_or_three%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rvyxw9/many_experts_have_started_predicting_two_or_three/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 22:37:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Dubai has to be the next top contender for making Bitcoin legal tender. Here are a few reasons I could think of as to why.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;1) Their currency is stuck pegged to the US dollar which with inflation rising is horrible for them, they need an alternative to use along side their existing currency.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;2) They have no capital gains tax or income taxes so no friction in terms of adopting Bitcoin. They are not losing any tax revenue by making it legal tender.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;3) Dubai loves PR and marketing itself and this would be the best PR stunt they could possibly do. The entire world would be talking about them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;4) Their population is 95% immigrant expats, and of those expats most send remittances home to their families overseas, Bitcoin would make remitting money far easier for their residents and their residents families.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;5) Dubai is a tourism based economy so allowing tourists to travel there without having to worry about cash or travel cards or currency exchange desks or credit cards would make life easier for tourists who would need nothing but a lightning wallet to be able to pay for everything in the country.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;6) Dubai has proclaimed themselves as being the city of the world so they should then adopt the worlds one truly global currency.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;7) They have an efficient government that could roll out lightning wallet support for merchants and residents extremely fast. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;8) Dubai wants to be the worlds most futuristic city so they should therefore adopt the worlds most futuristic currency.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;9) Making Bitcoin legal tender would attract the worlds fintech entrepreneurs and they want Dubai to become a technology hub where businesses headqarter their operations.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;10) Their Sovereign Wealth Fund already invests in Bitcoin and the crypto ecosystem.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;11) Solar powered miners in the middle of the desert with sun 360 days of the year could be a fantastic revenue generator for their government.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;12) Dubai has ubiquitous usage of wifi and 4G data everywhere and every single resident has a smartphone so there&amp;amp;#39;s no technological barrier to adoption.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;13) Bitcoin as legal tender would attract the crypto rich crowd looking for a pro Bitcoin country to live in, and Dubai always wants more wealthy residents to move there.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;14) Dubai has a culture that loves Gold meaning they have a culture that truly appreciates sound money principles, so bitcoin fits in perfectly with their existing cultural ideals.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;15) Dubai has a small and extremely efficient government which they are always looking to make even more efficient and more automated. Bitcoin allows instant money flows between all government departments and staff in a programmatic manner.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;16) They have a value added tax and VAT collection could be completely automated with Bitcoin. Merchant terminals could be programmed to automatically send VAT to the government in real time as each transaction happens, effectively automating tax collection making life far easier for both the government and businesses.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;17) Dubai loves being the first to adopt new tech and they take pride in doing everything bigger and better than anyone else. The same will be true of Bitcoin.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I don&amp;amp;#39;t think Dubai would let this opportunity pass them up while places like El Salvador and other central and south American countries take all the benefits of tourism immigration and business creation. If Dubai doesnt make Bitcoin legal tender this year they are letting other countries get a huge head start on them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I believe for all these reasons and more Dubai will announce bitcoin as legal tender before the end of 2022.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Quite good Forbes article without any FUD - How Bitcoin Is Giving Elderly El Salvadorians A Reason To Smile]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rvprtq/quite_good_forbes_article_without_any_fud_how/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frvprtq%2Fquite_good_forbes_article_without_any_fud_how%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frvprtq%2Fquite_good_forbes_article_without_any_fud_how%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rvprtq/quite_good_forbes_article_without_any_fud_how/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 20:31:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Signing bonus paid in Bitcoin for professional disc golfer Ricky Wysocky ($4 million dollar contract)]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rvyefo/signing_bonus_paid_in_bitcoin_for_professional/?score=340&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frvyefo%2Fsigning_bonus_paid_in_bitcoin_for_professional%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frvyefo%2Fsigning_bonus_paid_in_bitcoin_for_professional%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rvyefo/signing_bonus_paid_in_bitcoin_for_professional/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 20:31:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Joe Rogan has completely disrupted the legacy media. https://t.co/rBLCYweag0]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1478436200713179142/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1478436200713179142/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 19:38:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Many people believe that cryptocurrency will "kill" banks, but it might also be a compliance opportunity for them.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I just saw this article
[https://www.newsbtc.com/news/company/could-crypto-adoption-represent-a-compliance-opportunity-for-banks/]
and I was thinking about how banks and crypto can work together.

Since the first merchants in history, banks have existed in some form. They
became the religious…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rvq7d5/many_people_believe_that_cryptocurrency_will_kill/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frvq7d5%2Fmany_people_believe_that_cryptocurrency_will_kill%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frvq7d5%2Fmany_people_believe_that_cryptocurrency_will_kill%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rvq7d5/many_people_believe_that_cryptocurrency_will_kill/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 19:32:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I just saw this &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newsbtc.com/news/company/could-crypto-adoption-represent-a-compliance-opportunity-for-banks/&quot;&amp;gt;article&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and I was thinking about how banks and crypto can work together. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Since the first merchants in history, banks have existed in some form. They became the religious ruling elite, which evolved into the privately owned and government-subsidized enterprises that we see now today. And as we all know, banks have monopolies over people&amp;amp;#39;s money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And they&amp;amp;#39;re doing a great job at it too. This is a record profit every year, paid for with your money. Banks have unlimited cash at their disposal. Nobody is a crypto expert, but everyone has money in a bank, and it&amp;amp;#39;s generating bank record profits quarter after quarter. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Meanwhile, crypto is providing people with a new source of income. Banks despise this since it has a direct impact on their company, affects their enormous monopoly, and reduces their profit margins, among other things.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cryptocurrency and DeFi are not intended to destabilize existing banking, but rather to drive banks and established financial institutions to adapt and compete in an ever changing market. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This can assist banks in escaping the dark ages, dismantling monopolies, and attaining financial independence and knowledge.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The way I see it, Banks will never go out of business. Cryptocurrency has the potential to revolutionize the way banks work.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Solana did not go down yesterday. It was still processing more than Ethereum and Bitcoin.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm not sure what is up with the modding here but it allows completely incorrect
FUD to persist here. Solana never went down yesterday but did suffer from being
a lot slower than normal, with bot spam of high compute transactions crowding
blockspace. Blocks included votes as usual and less…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rvxoyk/solana_did_not_go_down_yesterday_it_was_still/?score=331&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frvxoyk%2Fsolana_did_not_go_down_yesterday_it_was_still%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frvxoyk%2Fsolana_did_not_go_down_yesterday_it_was_still%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rvxoyk/solana_did_not_go_down_yesterday_it_was_still/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 19:32:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m not sure what is up with the modding here but it allows completely incorrect FUD to persist here. Solana never went down yesterday but did suffer from being a lot slower than normal, with bot spam of high compute transactions crowding blockspace. Blocks included votes as usual and less transactions than normal but tps also doesn&amp;amp;#39;t have much nuance since a Raydium transaction requires over 100x the compute of many Serum transactions, which means bots spamming Raydium transaction take up a lot of compute. The transaction fee model that they are moving to will take into account compute which will hopefully disincentivize spamming better. There are inefficiencies related to processing these more complex transactions which Solana Labs and contributors are working on addressing. Solana still does nearly 100k tps on testnet ddos tests but with transfer type transactions. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you want to explore the actual blocks during the supposed outage yesterday you can use Solana Explorer to do so. Blocks included votes and a lesser amount of transactions -- &amp;amp;quot;failed&amp;amp;quot; transactions are not transactions which are in Solana&amp;amp;#39;s version of a mempool, which sometimes has over a million transactions waiting. A failed transaction can occur due a person not having required balance for example -- and failed transactions still pay a fee. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://explorer.solana.com/block/114782725&quot;&amp;gt;https://explorer.solana.com/block/114782725&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Lastly, Solana never &amp;amp;quot;turned off&amp;amp;quot; the network in September. If you think so you have been badly misinformed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://jumpcrypto.com/reflections-on-the-sept-14-solana-outage/&quot;&amp;gt;https://jumpcrypto.com/reflections-on-the-sept-14-solana-outage/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Solana Network Suffers Another Reported DDoS Attack]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rvu5dc/solana_network_suffers_another_reported_ddos/?score=371&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frvu5dc%2Fsolana_network_suffers_another_reported_ddos%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frvu5dc%2Fsolana_network_suffers_another_reported_ddos%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rvu5dc/solana_network_suffers_another_reported_ddos/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 18:38:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>