<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing on Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 16:28:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Anyone else get overwhelmed by how many cryptocurrencies there are?]]></title><description><![CDATA[There are thousands. And yes, most are crap - but there are still hundreds once
you've subtracted the memes and the down-and-outers that you could quite
reasonably argue have potential. And then within those, there are 10s of
different angles being played. Privacy? Yep, here's 15 coins/ tokens that…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgluia/anyone_else_get_overwhelmed_by_how_many/?score=323&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgluia%2Fanyone_else_get_overwhelmed_by_how_many%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgluia%2Fanyone_else_get_overwhelmed_by_how_many%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgluia/anyone_else_get_overwhelmed_by_how_many/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 15:32:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are thousands. And yes, most are crap - but there are still hundreds once you&amp;amp;#39;ve subtracted the memes and the down-and-outers that you could quite reasonably argue have potential. And then within those, there are 10s of different angles being played. Privacy? Yep, here&amp;amp;#39;s 15 coins/ tokens that offer it in some way. NFTs? Yep, here are 150 projects with dApps. Dex tokens? Staking? How much APR!? That&amp;amp;#39;s too good to be true, isn&amp;amp;#39;t it? &amp;amp;#39;Ecosystems&amp;amp;#39;? What the hell is interoperability? Why are there 5 different coins with Bitcoin in the name in the top 100?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How the hell do you decide what to invest in? How do you limit yourself to just a select few? It&amp;amp;#39;s great that there&amp;amp;#39;s so much choice, but it&amp;amp;#39;s a bloody minefield at times.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meeting with @IndiraKempis, the Mexican senator working to bring #Bitcoin and financial freedom to the people of Mexico. Probably nothing. 🇲🇽😁 https://t.co/OnmitsNMVr]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1488135452737650691/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1488135452737650691/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 14:40:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is the difference between a shitcoin and an altcoin? If my shitcoin becomes popular does it become an altcoin?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey guys,

Happy Sunday by the way!

I'm pretty new to everything and googled my question and most, if not all
articles tell me it's because they are meme based and don't have any
functionality other than making money.

At first I though fair enough, but after googling some of the top 20 "alt…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgj68s/what_is_the_difference_between_a_shitcoin_and_an/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgj68s%2Fwhat_is_the_difference_between_a_shitcoin_and_an%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgj68s%2Fwhat_is_the_difference_between_a_shitcoin_and_an%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgj68s/what_is_the_difference_between_a_shitcoin_and_an/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 12:45:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hey guys,&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Happy Sunday by the way! &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m pretty new to everything and googled my question and most, if not all articles tell me it&amp;amp;#39;s because they are meme based and don&amp;amp;#39;t have any functionality other than making money. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At first I though fair enough, but after googling some of the top 20 &amp;amp;quot;alt coins&amp;amp;quot; ADA for instance, I can&amp;amp;#39;t seem to see any use case function for this at all? If it was called a funny name, would it be a shitcoin or is it because it&amp;amp;#39;s not meme based it&amp;amp;#39;s an alt? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Monero for instance, I can see why this is popular due to its privacy and as far as I can see I&amp;amp;#39;d the only coin that has this feature, however quite a few alt coins I&amp;amp;#39;ve checked out don&amp;amp;#39;t seem to be any different than shitcoins. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Very confusing. Or is it all just a matter of opinon?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: 6 people have told me I&amp;amp;#39;m an idiot because of my ADA comment, yet not one ahs explained to me it&amp;amp;#39;s use case. Calling me an idiot or a troll isn&amp;amp;#39;t helping your case is it? I read their website and it&amp;amp;#39;s nothing but vague roadmaps.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It wasn&amp;amp;#39;t a dig just a mere observation, please teach me if I&amp;amp;#39;m wrong.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT 2: Wow some of you are so angry and bitchy, are y&amp;amp;#39;all ok in here?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Who is just waiting for the market to crash already?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Don't get me wrong. If I could go back in time to November ATHs and sell
everything, I definitely would. But obviously that is impossible.

What's frustrating is how the market has dropped quite a bit to the point where
it's not feasible to take profits, but the uncertainty also makes buying the…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgsmvg/who_is_just_waiting_for_the_market_to_crash/?score=335&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgsmvg%2Fwho_is_just_waiting_for_the_market_to_crash%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgsmvg%2Fwho_is_just_waiting_for_the_market_to_crash%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgsmvg/who_is_just_waiting_for_the_market_to_crash/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 12:45:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Don&amp;amp;#39;t get me wrong. If I could go back in time to November ATHs and sell everything, I definitely would. But obviously that is impossible. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What&amp;amp;#39;s frustrating is how the market has dropped quite a bit to the point where it&amp;amp;#39;s not feasible to take profits, but the uncertainty also makes buying the dip foolish. If the market could just fully crash and get over with it, I would feel much better about buying. But currently, I think it&amp;amp;#39;s very possible for BTC to tank down to 20k right after I get tired of waiting and buy this dip.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;These types of highly unpredictable and abnormally volatile markets are throwing me off, and I&amp;amp;#39;m waiting for some more predictability, whether it&amp;amp;#39;s positive or negative price action.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Elon Musk Posts a Meme About Hitler: 'Hitler Inu' token up 5500%]]></title><description><![CDATA[Elon Musk recently made a (fairly average) meme
[https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1487861173626101760?cxt=HHwWgICjkdf2-KUpAAAA]
about how people say that anyone who disagrees with them politically is Hitler.

Since then, a new token 'Hitler Inu', is up over 5000%.



Hitler Inu is up over…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgvote/elon_musk_posts_a_meme_about_hitler_hitler_inu/?score=392&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgvote%2Felon_musk_posts_a_meme_about_hitler_hitler_inu%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgvote%2Felon_musk_posts_a_meme_about_hitler_hitler_inu%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgvote/elon_musk_posts_a_meme_about_hitler_hitler_inu/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 10:41:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1487861173626101760?cxt=HHwWgICjkdf2-KUpAAAA&quot;&amp;gt;Elon Musk recently made a (fairly average) meme&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; about how people say that anyone who disagrees with them politically is Hitler. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Since then, a new token &amp;amp;#39;Hitler Inu&amp;amp;#39;, is up over 5000%.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/uwnlb1tl9ze81.jpg?width=632&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=fa0a40d0cfcee37fcf3aa8b08ebbf701922256a9&quot;&amp;gt;Hitler Inu is up over 5500&amp;amp;#37;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Jokes aside, I think this is terrible for crypto. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Firstly, one man can indirectly control the markets without even meaning to (at least, he didn&amp;amp;#39;t mean to in this case). Secondly, it is projects like this that makes the average retail investor think that crypto is a pyramid scheme/scam. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As an asset class, crypto needs to move away from these sort of projects and focus on fundamentals etc. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Tl;dr Hitler Inu token is up over 5500% based off an average meme.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why the Lightning Network is the most important thing in Bitcoin right now.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Here are five reasons for the title´s claim, ordered from most the significant
to the least.

1. Increases decentralization

To run a Lightning Node, you have to also be running a fully synced Bitcoin Core
node. This simple technical requirement means that the number of full Bitcoin
nodes is going…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sgb4si/why_the_lightning_network_is_the_most_important/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsgb4si%2Fwhy_the_lightning_network_is_the_most_important%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsgb4si%2Fwhy_the_lightning_network_is_the_most_important%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sgb4si/why_the_lightning_network_is_the_most_important/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 10:41:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here are five reasons for the title´s claim, ordered from most the significant to the least.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;1.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Increases decentralization&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To run a Lightning Node, you have to also be running a fully synced Bitcoin Core node. This simple technical requirement means that the number of full Bitcoin nodes is going to explode. Bitcoin  nodes are the most important part of the network since they enforce the consensus rules. Therefore, the more nodes, the better level of the decentralization and the more immune the Bitcoin Network will be to consensus rules change as we saw during the Blocksize war. For example, if someone wanted to change our beloved 21 million fixed supply, they would have to convince a substantial majority of people. The more nodes and the more spread out they are across the globe, the more impossible this tasks becomes.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, I&amp;amp;#39;ve always felt that the incentives for an individual running a Bitcoin Node were never that strong. It was always sold as “&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;having full sovereignty over your transactions by not needing to be trust any third party&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;.” But this is only going to convince a small group of people. A second argument that does have a bit more reach is the altruistic argument, “&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;you should run a bitcoin node to help out the network&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;.” Many hardcore bitcoiners probably run their nodes for this reason, but it is not a sustainable value proposition for the long term and won´t allow us to reach the insanely high level of decentralization mandated by a global trustless currency.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I believe the incentives for running a Lightning Node, which implies running a Bitcoin Node under the hood, are far far stronger. First of all, if you are an individual or medium to large business that is going to be making and/or receiving a lot of transactions, you can use your own lightning node to make sure you&amp;amp;#39;ll always be playing lowest possible fees. As a merchant with your own node, you can make sure your customers will pay the minimum fees for buying one of your products or if you are paying suppliers you can ensure that your node will search for the shortest route and minimize your fees paid. You can of course use a free custodial third party that avoids the hassle of installing your own lightning node but you will end up paying higher fees over the long run, that&amp;amp;#39;s how they make their money of course. So a very simple and selfish incentive emerges: people will run lightning nodes so that they can save money. A time tried incentive that is pretty effective.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But an even stronger incentive than saving money is making money. Many people already run what are called routing nodes, with the only purpose of routing payments and taking a small fee every time. This is in fact the main reason why people are interested in running a Lightning node in order to generate a small secondary income stream.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Finally, the third selfish incentive is that for some sad nerdy people, like myself, running a node actually is fun! There is a growing group of hobbyists that enjoy maintaining their nodes and participating in the network as a whole, just check out &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://plebnet.wiki/wiki/Welcome_to_Plebnet&quot;&amp;gt;PlebNet &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;for proof of this. Unlike running a simple Bitcoin node where you simply get it up and running and then just watch it sit there, running a Lightning Network involves active maintanance by rebalancing channels or figuring which nodes to connect to. This community involvement effect has definitely been a driver for adoption.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;These three incentives are much stronger than anything preceding them, and it simply means that many more people will want to run a Lightning note and therefore as a by-product they will also be running a Bitcoin node, whether they want to or not and whether they even know it or not. The end result is a far more decentralized network which will take Bitcoin´s most valuable attribute, decentralization, to a whole new level.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;2. Solves the privacy tradeoff&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The criticism that both Edward Snowden and Eric Weinstein have made of Bitcoin, which is for me the only reasonable criticism of the protocol I have heard, is its lack of privacy on the base layer. The issue is that there needs to be a public record for every transaction as a by-product of having a decentralized blockchain. Buying Bitcoin without KYC is becoming increasingly a legal grey area, and the ability for people to track transactions threatens one of Bitcoin&amp;amp;#39;s most important features: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;fungibility&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. If certain coins have a shady history, they might be worth less, while freshly mined coins can be sold at a premium. This is not good.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But the Lightning Network comes to the rescue.  When you open a Lightning channel, you are sending funds to a 2 of 2 multisig address and from there they do not move, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ever&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, until the channel is closed. With taproot now deployed, we will be able to able to hide that it&amp;amp;#39;s a a multisig, so therefore hide that´s it&amp;amp;#39;s problably a channel opening transaction. Lightning should be integrating this in the next few years &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You transact on the Lightning network by exchanging and updating IOUs with your channel peer, as many times as required. This is 100% private, these transactions are fully within your custody and nobody can ever know how or what you spent your money on. Even nodes re-routing payments cannot know the sender and the receiver.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Lightning Network does not increase the privacy of payment, it makes payments &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;100% private&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Absolutely and unequivocally private&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. End of.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is an insane innovation when you think about it, not only are payments still permissionless and uncensorable, they are now also uncompromisingly private, no longer suffering from the trade-off of having to transact on a public ledger like the base Bitcoin layer does.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And my favourite part of this is that when you take your funds back onto the Bitcoin network, their traceability have also almost been entirely eliminated. Imagine that you buy 1m Satoshis from a fully KYC´ed exchange and then move your Sats from the exchange to your wallet and then from there you open a Lightning channel with a well-connected node in order to spend your Bitcoin. Let&amp;amp;#39;s say you go on a bit of a shopping spree and you end up spending around 800K Satoshis. You decide that it would be wiser to save your remaining 200,000 sats by sending to your cold storage, so you close your Lightning channel, which means you move that amount from the multisig address to your cold wallet address. If you use a fresh address (which wallets will almost always generate automatically even if you are sending back to the same wallet), then there is absolutely no way on-chain analysis can know which UXTO is yours and which belongs to the other channel peer. They will see two transactions on the Blockchain with no idea which belongs to who. And funnily enough, if you spent the entire amount you put in to channel, when closing it there would only be one transaction on the blockchain and again nobody will know if those Sats are going back to you in or to the other owner of the node,  and so nobody knows if you spent the entirety o none of your coins. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;What in essence you have done is an ad hoc CoinJoin which severs the relationship between your KYC account and your Bitcoin&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. (As along as you do not use the same address as you opened the channel with, it goes without saying).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Even if the chain analysis makes the assumption that you spent all your Bitcoin,it is impossible for them to know what you spent it on and where those Satoshis now are.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Privacy solved.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;3.  Makes every altcoin irrelevant&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One way of understanding s*** coins  is to think of them as being a counterfeit copy of the Bitcoin protocole and token, pretending to offer a better or more specialized version of it when in reality they only dillute the value of Bitcoin´s market cap and serve as a very pesky distraction for many newcomers. This is an unfortunate consequence of Bitcoin´s open source nature, and the threat posed by s*** coins in the short to medium term is far larger than what many think.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, the traction already garnered by the Lightning network and it&amp;amp;#39;s capabilities really do put the shame all other coins that supposedly are solving Bitcoins scalability limitations. Many s*** coins sacrifice decentralization for more transactional efficiency. Meanwhile, the Lightning network achieves the highest speed of transaction at a ridiculously low costs without sacrificing in any shape or form the decentralized and secure properties of the underlying Bitcoin network. This makes other sh**coins completely irrelevant. And the number of users between both is an undeniable proof of this. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Millions&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; of people use the Lightning network to make transactions &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;everyday&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;And when I say millions I am not exaggerating&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. No other s*** coin even comes close to this number.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Another subset of sh** coins claim to use blockchain technologies for non-monetary use cases such as messaging or logistics or art. The whole Web 3.0 blurb. However, every single one of these ideas can be built far more easily on the Lightning network, and they already are. They are known as LAPPS. These are considered as layer 3 solutions and tackle specific problems. Of course many of these will fail just like in any free market but at least they won´t be stealing people&amp;amp;#39;s money when doing so, since investing in these solutions will go through the traditional private market. There is no publicly available token for people to be swindled into buying.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sphinx and Zion are a great example of this. Again I&amp;amp;#39;m not saying that these are going to be successful, but they are proof that we do not need to be creating completely new chains and pouring capital into them in order to try use cases that by definition are aimed at a small niche of users. I really hope the Lightning Network exposes the Altcoin ecosystem for the inefficient capital draining and overhyped speculation that it really is. Smart entrepreneurs will soon understand that it is far cheaper and efficient to build and fail and iterate on the Lightning network. And in the long term, only smart entrepreneurs win.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;4. Offers a Proof-of-Stake Alternative&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This rarely gets mentioned, but it&amp;amp;#39;s simple enough to understand. Imagine you could lock up your Bitcoin and get rewarded on a percentage basis for processing transactions. Sounds very much like proof of stake, right?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Well, the Lightning network offers you that option. Nodes can charge a small transaction fee for routing payments between unconnected nodes. This means you get a small financial reward for providing the liquidity the network needs. This offers pretty clear competition to what Ethereum is trying so hard and yet failing so far to implement. And unlike Ethereum, the Lightning´s network equivalent of staking is available today.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Imagine you were a large whale, and you wanted to earn a predictable yield on your Bitcoin &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;while retaining custody&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; (this last bit is key). The Lightning Network, unlike anything else in the ecosystem, would allow you to do this. Right now the fees a node can obtain for routing are very low, but this is because for now supply outstrips demand, but if the Lightning Network´s adoption continues at the rate it&amp;amp;#39;s at, then this will soon change.I can envision a near future where there are staking pools which groups together people&amp;amp;#39;s liquidity to create a very well-connected routing node and collect fees, redistributing them out to their clients after taking a small commission for managing the node.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;5. Makes price volatility irrelevant.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin&amp;amp;#39;s critics cite volatility as an unsurmountable problem which means it will never become a viable currency , when in fact its volatility is just a temporary feature caused by its insanely fast monetization.But anyway, I understand the frustration of making an on-chain transaction and having to wait 6 confirmations (roughly 1 hour) during which Bitcoin´s fiat price could have drastically shifted. This is not great for international transactions or any circumstance where you are using Bitcoin as a bridge between two fiat currencies. (Far better than anything the legacy financial system can offer, mind you).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Again problem solved with the Lightning Network, the instantaneous nature of its transactions mean that you convert instantly in fiat, locking in your agreed price. Strike and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.opennode.com/&quot;&amp;gt;OpenNode&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; have shown that this is a key advantage of using the Lightning Network around which they are building their business models.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;How you can help&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So to close out, if this little post has got you more curious about the Lightning network, here are a few things you can do to help out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Run your own node&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; (it´s fun I promise)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Show friends, families, local business how the Lightning Network works &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;and give them a demonstration&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Most people are genuinely impressed by its speed and low transaction cost when they see it with their own eyes.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Contribute to open source code or &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;create services for the growing community of node runners&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. There is so much still to build.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Reimagine how existing services could be improved when powered by the Lightning Network&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Pay-Per-Second Podcasting, Reddit comment tipping with microSats, Fully custodial online poker… So many fun things to launch!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[mfw after reading the bitcoin standard]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sgh4f6/mfw_after_reading_the_bitcoin_standard/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsgh4f6%2Fmfw_after_reading_the_bitcoin_standard%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsgh4f6%2Fmfw_after_reading_the_bitcoin_standard%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sgh4f6/mfw_after_reading_the_bitcoin_standard/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 09:31:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[51k btc just moved onto Binance today. Are we about to get dumped on?]]></title><description><![CDATA[51k BTC were just moved onto Binance today. Are we about to get dumped on?

That’s a lot of fucken btc. I was hoping for a little pumpy wumpy after all the
dumpy we’ve been handed…but, something tells me whicer moved these btc aren’t
using these for a leveraged longs, they’re going to dump on the…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgqfrc/51k_btc_just_moved_onto_binance_today_are_we/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgqfrc%2F51k_btc_just_moved_onto_binance_today_are_we%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgqfrc%2F51k_btc_just_moved_onto_binance_today_are_we%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgqfrc/51k_btc_just_moved_onto_binance_today_are_we/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 08:41:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;51k BTC were just moved onto Binance today. Are we about to get dumped on?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That’s a lot of fucken btc. I was hoping for a little pumpy wumpy after all the dumpy we’ve been handed…but, something tells me whicer moved these btc aren’t using these for a leveraged longs, they’re going to dump on the market. On our faces. Without asking. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This could also be a mind game to psych out dorks who look at this shit. What’s your take? Are we a out to get dumped on? It’ll just be more hodl ti e if we do, but it’d be nice to get out of this goddam range we’ve been in for a year now!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There’s an off-chance its just some exchange maintenance , binance moving their own from cold wallet to exchange type ish, but that seems’s unlikely. Every time i’ve seen this in the past, except for one, we ended up getting dumped on.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Will having mentioned the dump here make it not happen by virtue of the existential law “nobody on &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/r/cryptocurrency&quot;&amp;gt;r/cryptocurrency&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; is ever right , about anything, under any circumstances”?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinglass.com/Balance&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.coinglass.com/Balance&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;
About 30k of the coins ha e already moved back off exchange.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[As a young adult, I view crypto as one of the only ways to potentially own a house/property in the future.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I just turned 21 a week ago today.

I’ve been investing in crypto for just about a year now, but more seriously the
past 7 or so months. No I’m not investing significantly large amounts of money,
but I am allocating a fair percentage of my income into crypto.

Why?

Because buying a house, owning…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgsnu3/as_a_young_adult_i_view_crypto_as_one_of_the_only/?score=376&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgsnu3%2Fas_a_young_adult_i_view_crypto_as_one_of_the_only%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgsnu3%2Fas_a_young_adult_i_view_crypto_as_one_of_the_only%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgsnu3/as_a_young_adult_i_view_crypto_as_one_of_the_only/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 08:41:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I just turned 21 a week ago today. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve been investing in crypto for just about a year now, but more seriously the past 7 or so months. No I’m not investing significantly large amounts of money, but I am allocating a fair percentage of my income into crypto. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Because buying a house, owning some property, or even renting a place has seen prices increase substantially; especially here in Canada, where housing prices jumped over 26% last year. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m not investing on a whim; I take the time to learn the fundamentals and do my research. I buy solid crypto that I personally believe in for the long term. I’m fine waiting, practicing patience, and accumulating over time. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I don’t expect to become rich, and I know damn well I won’t wakeup a millionaire one day. However, I have faith and am optimistic about the future of some projects I hold, like CRO and ALGO for example. (ETH and BTC too, of course). &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Good things come to those who wait. May we all prosper!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Little edit: the feedback I’m receiving is exactly why I love this community so much, thank you all for the kind words! I genuinely hope you all find financial freedom one day.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sad]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sguyk7/sad/?score=355&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsguyk7%2Fsad%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsguyk7%2Fsad%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sguyk7/sad/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 08:41:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Usage Of Crypto In Crime Very Low Compared To Fiat, Admits Europol]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgjiym/usage_of_crypto_in_crime_very_low_compared_to/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgjiym%2Fusage_of_crypto_in_crime_very_low_compared_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgjiym%2Fusage_of_crypto_in_crime_very_low_compared_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgjiym/usage_of_crypto_in_crime_very_low_compared_to/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 08:41:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hodlers at all time high. Hash rate near all time highs, largest whales stacking like crazy. And yet the price does not reflect this. What am I missing here?]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sgmznj/bitcoin_hodlers_at_all_time_high_hash_rate_near/?score=317&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsgmznj%2Fbitcoin_hodlers_at_all_time_high_hash_rate_near%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsgmznj%2Fbitcoin_hodlers_at_all_time_high_hash_rate_near%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sgmznj/bitcoin_hodlers_at_all_time_high_hash_rate_near/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 04:49:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trying to explain crypto to nocoiners is like in the film Idiocracy trying to explain that water is for crops and not just toilets.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Title says it all, it is so hard to explain to anyone about crypto. They all
just treat you with deep suspicion and repeat the same pre-programmed lines back
to you from the banking and media industries.



You guys handle your own currency transactions? You mean that magic…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgdlnc/trying_to_explain_crypto_to_nocoiners_is_like_in/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgdlnc%2Ftrying_to_explain_crypto_to_nocoiners_is_like_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgdlnc%2Ftrying_to_explain_crypto_to_nocoiners_is_like_in%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgdlnc/trying_to_explain_crypto_to_nocoiners_is_like_in/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 04:33:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Title says it all, it is so hard to explain to anyone about crypto. They all just treat you with deep suspicion and repeat the same pre-programmed lines back to you from the banking and media industries.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/crpg9advuue81.png?width=1000&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=75450b3b30bb7e8a565ea9434ba9727ecdd613e1&quot;&amp;gt;You guys handle your own currency transactions? You mean that magic internet money? &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s like, you want decent interest returns for holding your money and lower fees on transactions? Yes! Then stop using the middle man of a bank and start using crypto and stop letting your money get eroded by fees and inflation........But banks are safe for my money, I have a savings account with 0.0000000% interest!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/qq08n4p1wue81.png?width=1280&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=4e772b740c4853c817c94ec895393357a2f7ec4d&quot;&amp;gt;Banks! It&amp;amp;#39;s got what you crave! It&amp;amp;#39;s got interest!*&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You don&amp;amp;#39;t have a savings account with a bank you have lies, they give you a few $$s here and there while they are making huge investments out of your money AND the inflation is actually depleting your savings account even more money. They should be called deflation accounts and not savings accounts!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/b7ns8hupwue81.png?width=1274&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e8ac93cfdb9a993d6171e5c6aa2bf20e33b3063f&quot;&amp;gt;Yeah we decided not to have any children because we cannot afford to now that we let all our money deflate to near zero value instead of investing it in the future of finance&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Of course I have to add not to dump ALL that you have into the nearest shitcoin and wait for &amp;amp;#39;those lambos&amp;amp;#39; to arrive but people that aren&amp;amp;#39;t invested at all in crypto or who paper hand out at the first dip are going to seriously regret it down the road! Those that become their own banks and handle their own finance are going to have significantly more wealth the longer we go while those that let the middle men of banking horde their money will find they have nothing left!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ethereum Fees Drop 53% in 20 Days — Polygon Hermez, Loopring Offer Lowest L2 Fees]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgkw32/ethereum_fees_drop_53_in_20_days_polygon_hermez/?score=368&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgkw32%2Fethereum_fees_drop_53_in_20_days_polygon_hermez%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgkw32%2Fethereum_fees_drop_53_in_20_days_polygon_hermez%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgkw32/ethereum_fees_drop_53_in_20_days_polygon_hermez/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 03:39:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dear brothers and sisters in crypto. future of crypto will not/can't be a single coin. The sooner you understand this the sooner you will stop bashing rival projects.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know everyone here wants some solid profit. I know all of us could use some
juicy $.

But hear me out. Just like the web long before it , each blockchain architecture
serves a different purpose. Sure some will disappear. Sure some might do one or
two thing better than another. But the most likely…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sg04r0/dear_brothers_and_sisters_in_crypto_future_of/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsg04r0%2Fdear_brothers_and_sisters_in_crypto_future_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsg04r0%2Fdear_brothers_and_sisters_in_crypto_future_of%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sg04r0/dear_brothers_and_sisters_in_crypto_future_of/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 02:43:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know everyone here wants some solid profit. 
I know all of us could use some juicy $.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But hear me out. Just like the web long before it , each blockchain architecture serves a different purpose. Sure some will disappear. Sure some might do one or two thing better than another. But the most likely scenario for the future of crypto is a network of integrated blockchains working together.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some will provide security. Some will do transactions and so one. Better projects will replace older ones and the whole concept will live on. It is just short sighted to think one specific chain would solve every problem and provide every service. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto needs to be flexible and evolve according to needs of people/enterprises or else it will fall apart. Don&amp;amp;#39;t defend a single project like it is your religion. The important thing is for crypto revolution to move on and become a part of life for every human being on earth.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is bigger than any single project. Please try to understand this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Ps: I thought it was obvious but seems I have to clarify it. By &amp;amp;quot;not any single project&amp;amp;quot; I don&amp;amp;#39;t mean &amp;amp;quot;every shitty&amp;amp;quot; project will win or survive. Maybe less than a percent of current projects are legit. 
I was talking about several successful project in different application categories. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Best regards&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Vve&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Flash Crash Warning!]]></title><description><![CDATA[TLDR:

F.U.D. Courtesy of The Fed [https://i.redd.it/lnne0752iwe81.gif]

A LOT has changed since NOV ATHs....

We sit on the edge of a Bear Market in many assets, and have a new 8000lb
Gorilla in the room, (a hawkish FED that um, day trades).

Meanwhile, crypto has recently correlated with the VIX…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sglzid/flash_crash_warning/?score=324&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsglzid%2Fflash_crash_warning%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsglzid%2Fflash_crash_warning%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sglzid/flash_crash_warning/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 02:43:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TLDR:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/lnne0752iwe81.gif&quot;&amp;gt;F.U.D. Courtesy of The Fed&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A LOT has changed since NOV ATHs....&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We sit on the edge of a Bear Market in many assets, and have a new 8000lb Gorilla in the room, (a hawkish FED that um, day trades).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Meanwhile, crypto has recently correlated with the VIX (-94% on Friday), so now the SPX and Crypto are joined at the hip:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/dyrvahorewe81.png?width=722&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=74c66bf65f603426cfd18723b4e169d7a6c91006&quot;&amp;gt;ATHs in VIX Correlation&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What&amp;amp;#39;s interesting here is how much the order book has dried up. The book is running very thin (that trend is ongoing), which means that prices can bounce a lot more then would otherwise be the case. It also means that prices will likely come under even more pressure (high volatility does not support price increases in the average asset), in the short term.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Additionally, this set up may create some extra wild price swings that may whack the over leveraged margin &amp;amp;amp; futures traders. How that will affect Exchange Operability remains to be seen-but let&amp;amp;#39;s just say it won&amp;amp;#39;t help them stay more stable. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;;)&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here are some charts that help illustrate the problem, they look like  Rorschach (ink blot) Tests:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/2322juyfewe81.png?width=925&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d6deb7aa59f8cde5abc8249b93b7a51836556e5e&quot;&amp;gt;S&amp;amp;amp;P Book Depth Is Shrinking...see that flash crash point in DEC Week 1?&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/18u5bnxhfwe81.png?width=950&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=c185674b9ffbcb996c7d8b516ff4e4a11e2b351c&quot;&amp;gt;Nasdaq Book Depth Is Shrinking...&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/o6npfgawfwe81.png?width=929&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=aaad2c1a72e6971e9823ad5ea853510216f968f8&quot;&amp;gt;Bid/Ask Spread is HUGE here.....&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;These are indications that volatility is likely to remain significantly elevated in the days ahead-atop a level that is already very high. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;This also suggests that the price declines we have seen in the cryptoverse correction are not over.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; What&amp;amp;#39;s more, January is usually one of the most chill months for volatility-so the fact that we are already running high in a normally chill month-is note worthy here:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/119pzsqogwe81.png?width=946&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=7e4c3e50abe9504ee6c7d6a7d1229d95a079cdae&quot;&amp;gt;January is supposed to be chill bro&amp;amp;#39;......but ain&amp;amp;#39;t!&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here is a chart of Volatility, and Volatility of Volatility, overlaid:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/yzuib1g1qwe81.png?width=1150&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9f83eee07ec3b8e4261700eb6921d814bf17c711&quot;&amp;gt;The VIX is Now Trending Up, Up, Up and away......&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At present, volatility is retreating off its highs, but the trend is clear-and that trend is UP. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Volatility is now bullish trend, where for all of 2021 it was not. That is a huge sea change. As long as the correlation to the VIX remains as titanium strong as it is at present, &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;this suggests that prices will remain under pressure for quite some time.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; (No Virginia, Coin #1 will not be hitting $100k any time soon-as in this year dear.)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Meanwhile the book is thinning to where it was at the December Flash crash.....ruh roh!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;I am not a chicken little, and I am not given to fear. That said, the set up here is ripe for whaler whack-a-mole, Skynet&amp;amp;#39;s favorite game of chance.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;The takeaway?:&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Traders: be on the margin watch!&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;HODLr&amp;amp;#39;s: buckle up for more roller coa$ter action.....&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Good Luck!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin halvings map from start to 1 Satoshi]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sgiu4i/bitcoin_halvings_map_from_start_to_1_satoshi/?score=480&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsgiu4i%2Fbitcoin_halvings_map_from_start_to_1_satoshi%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsgiu4i%2Fbitcoin_halvings_map_from_start_to_1_satoshi%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sgiu4i/bitcoin_halvings_map_from_start_to_1_satoshi/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 01:41:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BREAKNG: Senator from Mississippi introduces bill to recognize Bitcoin in the state code.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sgf6ez/breakng_senator_from_mississippi_introduces_bill/?score=346&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsgf6ez%2Fbreakng_senator_from_mississippi_introduces_bill%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsgf6ez%2Fbreakng_senator_from_mississippi_introduces_bill%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sgf6ez/breakng_senator_from_mississippi_introduces_bill/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:35:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[[PSA] We should do something for todays HALF MILLION lost tragedy to NEVER EVER happen again.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Manual cross post for Original post at r/ethereum
[https://np.reddit.com/r/ethereum/comments/sgat3r/psa_we_should_do_something_for_todays_half/].

r/Ethereum Today's Headline, The Original Post of Said…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgdxtg/psa_we_should_do_something_for_todays_half/?score=329&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgdxtg%2Fpsa_we_should_do_something_for_todays_half%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgdxtg%2Fpsa_we_should_do_something_for_todays_half%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgdxtg/psa_we_should_do_something_for_todays_half/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 00:35:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Manual cross post for &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/ethereum/comments/sgat3r/psa_we_should_do_something_for_todays_half/&quot;&amp;gt;Original post at r/ethereum&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/ethereum/comments/sfz4kw/did_i_just_lose_half_a_million_dollars_by_sending/&quot;&amp;gt;r/Ethereum Today&amp;amp;#39;s Headline, The Original Post of Said Tragedy&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TL,DR: We should start a campaign, here is our appeal:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;All wallet software orienting average user, shall ban the action of, or give the scariest warning it can give if the user initiates a tx that directly calls &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;transfer&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; function to a Contract address.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;We should promote and accelerate the deprecation of raw ERC-20, and the wider adoption of newer, more robust and fault-proof ERC-777 and ERC-1555 standards.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;No matter what role you are playing in the scene - Blockchain developers, DeFi users, NFT hodlers, investors, today&amp;amp;#39;s tragedy is a serious alarm to us all that, Ethereum, along with many other blockchain technologies, are yet to be fully fledged for mass adoption.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is fully understandable because the nature of new technologies is, no matter how many work we do to make the design perfect, it needs to be tested in the field first for problems to be reveal and fixed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;ERC-20 token standard is one of them, it&amp;amp;#39;s such a classic standard with long history and a whole ecosystem built upon it, but we all forgot that the philosophy behind its design is still immature, leading to serious loophole and design failure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sending ERC-20 token to any sort of Smart Contract is pointless and exceedingly dangerous. In usual business logic, if user want a certain smart contract to have certain token, what they should do, and the way the Smart Contract should absolutely implement is: user approve in ERC-20 token contract first, then you make user to call a function exposed by your Contract, in the function, your Contract calls &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;transferFrom&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; function on ERC-20 Token Contract, so that your contract is aware of this transfer.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;An ERC-20 &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;transfer&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; function call, to ANY &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;CONTRACT&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; ADDRESS, initiated by END-USER (EOA address), is POINTLESS and will ALWAYS result in PERMANENT, UNRECOVEABLE TOKEN LOSS.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Today&amp;amp;#39;s tragedy is caused by collective effect of many factor: The nature of Ethereum that all addresses look the same; Lack of user education on smart contract (I see why people blaming &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://weth.io/&quot;&amp;gt;weth.io&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; on this, it&amp;amp;#39;s fully reasonable, today&amp;amp;#39;s victim might came up with the idea him/herself that: hey I send ETH to the contract, got WETH, now I send WETH back, ETH back, that&amp;amp;#39;s what the GIF on &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://weth.io/&quot;&amp;gt;weth.io&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; says! completely not knowing what&amp;amp;#39;s under the hood, the anonymous fallback function and etc.). Lack of on-chain logic checking and preventing this (it would cost everybody&amp;amp;#39;s gas).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But the most unforgivable factor is the NEGLIGENCE of wallet software: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ZERO&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; warning upon sending ERC-20 token to a Contract Address, on the UI I just saw &amp;amp;quot;Contract interaction: Transfer&amp;amp;quot;, and I&amp;amp;#39;m good to go! To PURGE ALL OF MY HODLING with single mouse click!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That&amp;amp;#39;s not how fault tolerance/fault proof should be done - to be honest, that&amp;amp;#39;s zero fault proof.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Green across the board, we are good to go right? POOOOF, SNAFU, a poor guy&amp;amp;#39;s life saving gone.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This issue has been around for years, and of course, everything on chain is accessible, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://etherscan.io/&quot;&amp;gt;etherscan.io&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; can tell if an address is a contract, Infura can tell if it&amp;amp;#39;s a contract. But metamask, ledger live, xxx wallet and etc cannot tell if the address in the text input is a contract.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, once again in the end, We should start a campaign, here is our appeal:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;All wallet software orienting average user, shall ban the action of, or give the scariest warning it can give if the user initiates a tx that directly calls &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;transfer&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; function to a Contract address.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;We should promote and accelerate the deprecation of raw ERC-20, and the wider adoption of newer, more robust and fault-proof ERC-777 and ERC-1555 standards.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Interest in Shiba Inu seems to have dried up completely]]></title><description><![CDATA[A few months ago, the meme-coin Shiba Inu (SHIB) was pretty much in the
spotlight. The cryptocurrency rose astronomically within a short period of time,
and crypto investors' interest in the project was gigantic at times. Shiba Inu
even made it into the top 10 largest cryptocurrencies. However, the…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgi9g0/interest_in_shiba_inu_seems_to_have_dried_up/?score=638&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgi9g0%2Finterest_in_shiba_inu_seems_to_have_dried_up%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgi9g0%2Finterest_in_shiba_inu_seems_to_have_dried_up%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgi9g0/interest_in_shiba_inu_seems_to_have_dried_up/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 23:37:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A few months ago, the meme-coin Shiba Inu (SHIB) was pretty much in the spotlight. The cryptocurrency rose astronomically within a short period of time, and crypto investors&amp;amp;#39; interest in the project was gigantic at times. Shiba Inu even made it into the top 10 largest cryptocurrencies. However, the price of Shiba Inu has since plummeted, and the hype and interest surrounding the project seems to have completely evaporated as well.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Google Trends&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In fact, last year Shiba Inu was so popular that it topped CoinMarketCap in terms of searches. Also on the Google, there was a huge search for, for example, &amp;amp;quot;Shiba Inu&amp;amp;quot; or &amp;amp;quot;Buy Shiba Inu&amp;amp;quot; all over the world.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, this search volume on Google has totally dried up in the last 90 days. Google Trends shows that a peak in terms of interest was reached on October 29 last year. Since then, this search volume has plummeted by a whopping 92%!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/9lts5dtmyve81.png?width=1168&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e667ddbf9ad93d831e1f3d6f02d518bcc574f8c3&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/9lts5dtmyve81.png?width=1168&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e667ddbf9ad93d831e1f3d6f02d518bcc574f8c3&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Shiba Inu Price&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The price of meme-coin did not manage to perform much better in recent months. Since the all-time high set at the end of October 2021, the SHIB price has dropped more than 75%.  In fact, at the beginning of January, Shiba Inu&amp;amp;#39;s market capitalization plummeted by more than $3.5 billion in just one week.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Although the team at Shiba Inu is still working hard behind the scenes to get the project back on track, this seems to have become quite a task. Here and there SHIB still gets listed on a new crypto exchange, but the extreme price appreciation we saw in the past seems to be a thing of the past so far.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Of course, Shiba Inu is not the only cryptocurrency that is performing poorly at the moment. Due to the high uncertainty in both the crypto and equity markets, most cryptocurrencies are deep in the red. Nevertheless, the demise of SHIB can be called an outlier.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: Shib holders and fans, stop attacking me for pointing out your coin has had its day and people have moved to the next Doge/Shib, jeez, chillax and accept the bad investment choices you made&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anybody feel like celebrities are not paying for the Ape NFTs??’]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have seen all over the news of different celebrities paying exorbitant amounts
for the Ape NFTs and it just feels super inorganic and forced.

There are many celebrities that have supposedly bought these NFTs and now have
changed their profile picture to the Ape they own. Some of the prominent…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgbh3x/anybody_feel_like_celebrities_are_not_paying_for/?score=378&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgbh3x%2Fanybody_feel_like_celebrities_are_not_paying_for%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsgbh3x%2Fanybody_feel_like_celebrities_are_not_paying_for%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sgbh3x/anybody_feel_like_celebrities_are_not_paying_for/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I have seen all over the news of different celebrities paying exorbitant amounts for the Ape NFTs and it just feels super inorganic and forced. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are many celebrities that have supposedly bought these NFTs and now have changed their profile picture to the Ape they own. Some of the prominent ones include Future, Lil Baby, and Jimmy Fallon all spending 500K+. And while I don’t doubt they couldn’t afford it as they are all obviously multimillionaires. I do not believe they are actually buying them. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My working theory is that they are simply getting them for or even getting paid to market these NFT’s and it’s just the NFT owners wash trading between their own ETH wallets to create Artificial demand and contribute to the price inflation. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The most recent one I saw was Justin Bieber buying an Ape NFT for around 500 ETH (over 1 million USD). When the base price of the NFT was 250K. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I refuse to believe celebrities at their own willingness are overpaying for these. Once again I understand that a celebrity like Justin Bieber could in theory afford to throw a million at something like this. But just doesn’t seem like something he would rationally do without ulterior motives. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Welcoming any thoughts people have on this? Just want to disclaim I am not against NFT’s and believe the tech and potential of it is amazing, but the current use case is absurd and indicative of a artificially inflated bubble(this is coming from someone that made a few ETH flipping NFTs)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Las Vegas Strip Club Accepting Crypto for Lap Dances]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sg4ssy/las_vegas_strip_club_accepting_crypto_for_lap/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsg4ssy%2Flas_vegas_strip_club_accepting_crypto_for_lap%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsg4ssy%2Flas_vegas_strip_club_accepting_crypto_for_lap%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sg4ssy/las_vegas_strip_club_accepting_crypto_for_lap/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 20:35:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[https://t.co/QEwmhecTmE]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1487854323308584966/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1487854323308584966/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 18:42:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[You are NOT a Crypto "Millionaire/Billionaire" if you simply just converted your already existing wealth or part of it to Crypto.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I keep seeing this "Crypto Billionaire" label thrown around and frankly it
doesn't make sense nor is it an accomplishment.

Most of those who hold such a title were already rich to begin with!

This gives unrealistic expectations in the technology making every joe believe
he can be a millionaire…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sg6cnt/you_are_not_a_crypto_millionairebillionaire_if/?score=336&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsg6cnt%2Fyou_are_not_a_crypto_millionairebillionaire_if%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsg6cnt%2Fyou_are_not_a_crypto_millionairebillionaire_if%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sg6cnt/you_are_not_a_crypto_millionairebillionaire_if/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 18:42:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I keep seeing this &amp;amp;quot;Crypto Billionaire&amp;amp;quot; label thrown around and frankly it doesn&amp;amp;#39;t make sense nor is it an accomplishment.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Most of those who hold such a title were already rich to begin with!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This gives unrealistic expectations in the technology making every joe believe he can be a millionaire with $100. If we actually took the time to research the family backgrounds/immense dollar wealth these successful Crypto influencers already possessed prior to investing, I believe it would help show everyone a glimpse of reality.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Yes there are legends who make it from nothing but they either held since the dark ages or made a barbaric play into a newly released project. Other than that, it is the same old story of &amp;amp;quot;My father gave me a small loan of a million dollars&amp;amp;quot;. The next time you see someone on some &amp;amp;quot;Crypto rich list&amp;amp;quot; or a guy flashing his Crypto gains, consider doing a little research.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[January Market]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sgb8i7/january_market/?score=564&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsgb8i7%2Fjanuary_market%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsgb8i7%2Fjanuary_market%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sgb8i7/january_market/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 17:33:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ethical hacker helps recover millions lost in StableMagnet rug pull]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sg5n7n/ethical_hacker_helps_recover_millions_lost_in/?score=318&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsg5n7n%2Fethical_hacker_helps_recover_millions_lost_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsg5n7n%2Fethical_hacker_helps_recover_millions_lost_in%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sg5n7n/ethical_hacker_helps_recover_millions_lost_in/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 16:32:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I see why crypto skeptics don’t talk to crypto enthusiasts, we are really toxic.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I simply tweeted that BAYC for 100 ETH really doesn’t sit well. It seems dumb no
matter how many exclusive rights you get. Eminem is not going to show up at the
party of crypto degenerates.

The amount of people with little or no knowledge how blockchain and crypto work,
came attacking. At first it…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sg3tkg/i_see_why_crypto_skeptics_dont_talk_to_crypto/?score=309&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsg3tkg%2Fi_see_why_crypto_skeptics_dont_talk_to_crypto%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsg3tkg%2Fi_see_why_crypto_skeptics_dont_talk_to_crypto%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sg3tkg/i_see_why_crypto_skeptics_dont_talk_to_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 16:32:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I simply tweeted that BAYC for 100 ETH really doesn’t sit well. It seems dumb no matter how many exclusive rights you get. Eminem is not going to show up at the party of crypto degenerates. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The amount of people with little or no knowledge how blockchain and crypto work, came attacking. At first it was a good banter and set of well nuanced arguments with mutual respect. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then came these people who started saying “You’re salty”, “Dumb fk” and so on. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I get why people who are negative about crypto block others. It’s really dumb how crypto community just want to add value to so many things that the only way put of it is to sell it to the highest bidder and hence they have to continue to support stupid projects for stupid uses.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[You wake up and you’re a millionaire]]></title><description><![CDATA[Say after waiting patiently and holding a few of your favorite crypto currency
projects for the last 5 years, you wake up and see that they have all gone 300x
and you realize that you are in possession of a life changing amount of money.
What is the very first thing that you buy, what would your…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sga4pf/you_wake_up_and_youre_a_millionaire/?score=524&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsga4pf%2Fyou_wake_up_and_youre_a_millionaire%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsga4pf%2Fyou_wake_up_and_youre_a_millionaire%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sga4pf/you_wake_up_and_youre_a_millionaire/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 16:32:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Say after waiting patiently and holding a few of your favorite crypto currency projects for the last 5 years, you wake up and see that they have all gone 300x and you realize that you are in possession of a life changing amount of money. What is the very first thing that you buy, what would your mind go to first?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As for me I would buy a house. I live in a city that property values are through the roof. It seems like a pipe dream to able to own a home where I am. I would love nothing more than a little backyard for a pupper and a roof for my future children&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: I’m honestly touched by a lot of the answers everyone has given here. There’s a lot of love in these comments. I really hope the best for all of you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PLEASE do not politicize Bitcoin, it only hurts adoption]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sg3sh2/please_do_not_politicize_bitcoin_it_only_hurts/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsg3sh2%2Fplease_do_not_politicize_bitcoin_it_only_hurts%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsg3sh2%2Fplease_do_not_politicize_bitcoin_it_only_hurts%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sg3sh2/please_do_not_politicize_bitcoin_it_only_hurts/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 15:34:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[#Bitcoin RSI=53

Will RSI drop below 50 (indicating downward momentum and start of a bear market), or will RSI stay above 50 and rise again, because at the peak in 2021 RSI did barely go above 90 as well (no high peak = no extreme low). https://t.co/bxyrPsWkQk]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1487765697283432453/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1487765697283432453/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 12:51:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Today, a fellow redditor just sent 195 WETH to WETH's contract adress. That's a half million dollar mistake....]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sg27l5/today_a_fellow_redditor_just_sent_195_weth_to/?score=337&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsg27l5%2Ftoday_a_fellow_redditor_just_sent_195_weth_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsg27l5%2Ftoday_a_fellow_redditor_just_sent_195_weth_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sg27l5/today_a_fellow_redditor_just_sent_195_weth_to/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 12:51:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Which project you think isn't as good people say it is? Projects which are overhyped and yet to deliver the matching results]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm talking about coins which aren't good but people still support them like a
cult.

Pretty much most of bagholders of certain coins are like cults. I'd take my
example that I hold some SHIBA but I'll promote it even knowing that it's a
memecoin. Fundamentally, it's just another memecoins…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfvi0v/which_project_you_think_isnt_as_good_people_say/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfvi0v%2Fwhich_project_you_think_isnt_as_good_people_say%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfvi0v%2Fwhich_project_you_think_isnt_as_good_people_say%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfvi0v/which_project_you_think_isnt_as_good_people_say/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 12:51:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m talking about coins which aren&amp;amp;#39;t good but people still support them like a cult.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Pretty much most of bagholders of certain coins are like cults. I&amp;amp;#39;d take my example that I hold some SHIBA but I&amp;amp;#39;ll promote it even knowing that it&amp;amp;#39;s a memecoin. Fundamentally, it&amp;amp;#39;s just another memecoins following path of dogecoin and is backed by hype so far. Any of these cats, dogs or even some fucking grimacecoin are risky as heck and are a bad investment overall.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Which coins/projects you think are just marketing only and people will regret diving into it?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[While the coastal elites eat up whatever nonsense they are fed by politicians, the men and women who make up the real economy of Canada are making their voices heard.

Beautiful thing to watch 🇨🇦 https://t.co/3N0lxvBu70]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1487730919771459584/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1487730919771459584/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 10:36:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I personally know 6 nurses who are opting for early retirement rather than fight the system any longer. These are all highly skilled &amp; compassionate people who all have natural immunity from serving on the front lines. 

Multiply this to understand the impact on your future care.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1487727141215166470/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1487727141215166470/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 10:36:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[There’s a revolution happening right now in Canada that has sent their tyrannical PM into hiding.

I hope it spreads worldwide.

#CanadaTruckers #ConvoyForFreedom
#TruckersForFreedom2022 

 https://t.co/83DHJwBwGP]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1487731788466249730/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1487731788466249730/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 10:36:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bullish AF! I always use my fortune cookies as financial advice.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sfx1zl/bullish_af_i_always_use_my_fortune_cookies_as/?score=317&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsfx1zl%2Fbullish_af_i_always_use_my_fortune_cookies_as%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsfx1zl%2Fbullish_af_i_always_use_my_fortune_cookies_as%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sfx1zl/bullish_af_i_always_use_my_fortune_cookies_as/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 09:40:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cathie Wood's Ark Invest expects ether to soar over 7,000% and hit a $20 trillion market cap by 2030]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfyipr/cathie_woods_ark_invest_expects_ether_to_soar/?score=310&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfyipr%2Fcathie_woods_ark_invest_expects_ether_to_soar%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfyipr%2Fcathie_woods_ark_invest_expects_ether_to_soar%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfyipr/cathie_woods_ark_invest_expects_ether_to_soar/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 09:40:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I'm a bank teller at a large North American Bank, and every day I'm reminded how much we need Bitcoin.]]></title><description><![CDATA[As someone who works for a bank in a customer-facing retail setting I'm one of
the first people they come to when they have banking issues they need help with,
or complaints with our policies.

These issues/complaints include any and all of the following:

 * Credit/debit card fraud in which their…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sfraxe/im_a_bank_teller_at_a_large_north_american_bank/?score=317&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsfraxe%2Fim_a_bank_teller_at_a_large_north_american_bank%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsfraxe%2Fim_a_bank_teller_at_a_large_north_american_bank%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sfraxe/im_a_bank_teller_at_a_large_north_american_bank/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 09:40:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As someone who works for a bank in a customer-facing retail setting I&amp;amp;#39;m one of the first people they come to when they have banking issues they need help with, or complaints with our policies.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;These issues/complaints include any and all of the following:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Credit/debit card fraud in which their card is being used without their permission.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Card fraud in which their card/personal details where stolen either through phishing or a similar scam.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cards being locked due to &amp;amp;quot;suspicious transactions&amp;amp;quot;(which might not even be suspicious in many cases which just frustrates people)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Checks being put on hold for anywhere between 1-6 business days, or even up to 10 for big checks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Accounts being partially frozen or even closed due to potential 
fraud activity.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Payment apps like Zelle either not letting people link their accounts, or blocking payments due to lack of similar payment activity or whatever they deem &amp;amp;quot;suspicious activity&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Customer cannot easily transfer funds from their old bank to ours because the other bank has no local branches&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Customers wanting large withdrawals, but don&amp;amp;#39;t we don&amp;amp;#39;t have enough cash on hand to give it all to one customer&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;National coin shortage causing frustration for business customers&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Wire transfer fees/processing time&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Maintenance fees&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Overdraft fees&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bank check/money order fees&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Non-customer fees&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Non-customer ATM fees&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Non-transactional account&amp;amp;quot; transfer fees&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Pending transactions taking days to post&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Real companies making charges on people&amp;amp;#39;s cards when they haven&amp;amp;#39;t even been there in months&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;People complaining the ATM doesn&amp;amp;#39;t work after they just stuffed dozens of shitty dirty bills and water stained checks in it&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A couple deposited all their money via bank check from their old bank and it was put on hold for over a week leaving them with no money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Woman wanted to wire $100 to her family but was turned away because Intl wires cost $50 off the top and may or may not have fees on the receiving bank as well.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Guy couldn&amp;amp;#39;t access his money from his old bank across the country which required him to physically be there to initiate a wire.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Guy lost a fairly large bank check in the parking lot a few plazas over and took weeks to get in contact with him to put a stop on it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Checks/cards not showing up in the mail, wasting people&amp;amp;#39;s time to have to come in and reorder and put stops on the lost items.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Old people who literally pay money to buy checks only to drive to the bank, stand in line, and write themselves a check for $100 cash  and ask for a balance - only to repeat this every other day.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;hr/&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The fact that these problems and inconveniences even exist is a problem in itself. Bitcoin fixes all of these because they are completely irrelevant on a Bitcoin system. In economics 101 they teach you that the definition of an efficient market is one where &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;all information is transmitted perfectly, completely, instantly, and for no cost&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Bitcoin dramatically increases efficiency in banking and will inevitably become the standard medium of storing money/value.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Food for thought:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Customers will often ask for their pay checks to deposited as cash. If we can tell the check is legit or if we&amp;amp;#39;re familiar with the person(kyc) we&amp;amp;#39;ll deposit it as cash even though the check is from another institution, meaning in reality the receiving bank isn&amp;amp;#39;t getting anything besides a piece of paper and a promise that the account on the check is good for the funds. Verifying those funds takes a business day or more, but meanwhile the funds get poofed into the persons account at the click of a button. Also as many of you know, since March 2020, deposit institutions are now required to keep 0% of their total deposit accounts in cash reserves. Zero percent! &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So that&amp;amp;#39;s why when I hear someone say that Bitcoin isn&amp;amp;#39;t &amp;amp;quot;backed&amp;amp;quot; by anything, my question is what the hell is a dollar backed by besides dirty green rectangles with some old guy&amp;amp;#39;s signature?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[If there is the biggest lesson to learn from crypto investment, for me it would be "patience". Patience with buying. Patience with hodling. Patience with selling.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have been in crypto since 2018. Many ups and downs along the way, but if
anyone asks me what would be the biggest lesson I learned from those years, I'd
say "patience".

1. Patience with buying

We are all familiar with the term "buy high sell low". Sounds absurd, but it is
actually happening…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfsdn7/if_there_is_the_biggest_lesson_to_learn_from/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfsdn7%2Fif_there_is_the_biggest_lesson_to_learn_from%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfsdn7%2Fif_there_is_the_biggest_lesson_to_learn_from%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfsdn7/if_there_is_the_biggest_lesson_to_learn_from/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 09:40:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I have been in crypto since 2018. Many ups and downs along the way, but if anyone asks me what would be the biggest lesson I learned from those years, I&amp;amp;#39;d say &amp;amp;quot;patience&amp;amp;quot;. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;1. Patience with buying&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We are all familiar with the term &amp;amp;quot;buy high sell low&amp;amp;quot;. Sounds absurd, but it is actually happening every time. Everyone is a genius in a bull run, as the prices shoot up every hour, FOMO comes into play. This chart sums it up nicely:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/wcg4g01byoe81.jpg?width=640&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=cab8009e25203135b00141fbd50a95c15650227b&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/wcg4g01byoe81.jpg?width=640&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=cab8009e25203135b00141fbd50a95c15650227b&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;From my personal experience, I successfully defended the FOMO phase of 2017. In 2018, I bought the first Bitcoin at $7,000 and ETH at $600, thinking they couldn&amp;amp;#39;t possibly go any lower. Hundred of posts back then say the same thing, $6k-7k is &amp;amp;quot;the floor&amp;amp;quot;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Another aspect of patience with buying, is not to fomo into shitcoins. Many people have the mindset of &amp;amp;quot;get rich quick&amp;amp;quot; and jumped into many shitcoins, which turned out to be terrible investment. Again, I was lucky not to fomo into Waltonchain, Dragonchain, Ark, Verge, ICX, Lambda, Komodo, Bitmax, OMG. The ICO boom in 2017 left many broken. The only not-so-good purchases for me were NEO, DASH and Raiblock (now NANO). I sold NEO and NANO last year, making a small profit and not looking back.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Time in the market is more important than timing the market, however it would be better to combine both factors. This is because we as retail investors don&amp;amp;#39;t have a lot of money to play with, so buying now would be surely better than buying in Nov-2021. A wide range of tools can be deployed to strengthen the DCA plan. I prefer an adjusted DCA (buying regularly, but not regardless of any price).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My favorite tools: RSI, MA50, MA200, Mayer Multiplier and Bitcoin rainbow. You can&amp;amp;#39;t time the top or the bottom, but getting 10% close to the range would surely help.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;2. Patience with hodling&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This one is also very important. Crypto is volatile and you normally see people making 1000%, 10000% or even more in a particular project. The OG who bought in early and almost never consider selling, is a different breed. For us, even holding for 4 years would be a commitment. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So again, don&amp;amp;#39;t invest more than what you can afford to lose. You would not want to sell something urgently because the rent payment is due and now you have no cash left.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hodling is hard. Very hard. When you see your portfolio value go down 10% a month or even worse. But the power of holding is huge.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/64k4y7uj1pe81.png?width=1574&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=c3f550fc0df61d1973a549eb7fa1eebed39f84b1&quot;&amp;gt;DCA returns for selected coins https://www.blockchaincenter.net/dollar-cost-averaging/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Right now we are in the red, and one of the worst time to sell in my opinion. However, it should be noted that not everything is worth holding forever. There are a lot of coins from 2016/2017/2018 that could be considered &amp;amp;quot;dead coins&amp;amp;quot; by now. But if you believe in a particular project and support it, you can reduce your cost basis in a hard time like this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Another good thing with holding now is that you can stake and earn passive income. This can lower your cost basis and get you airdrops for some specific coins.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;3. Patience with selling&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Many retail investors lost interest with crypto and can&amp;amp;#39;t bear the fact that their portfolio is now in the red. Hence, many sell low, in the possibly worst time to do so. In a hard time, if you can&amp;amp;#39;t buy more, at least keep hodling the position.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;No one ever goes broke by taking profits, however. It&amp;amp;#39;s always a good idea to DCA out near the top. If the price drops later, you can buy back for cheaper price. I sold some portion of BTC at $60k and bought back at $39k. Not the perfect top or bottom, but at least quite close.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I made some bad selling transactions as well. For example, I bought BNB at $92 just last year, and sold at $270. Now even in a downturn, BNB is still $390. Again, the tools above can help with the short-term as well. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;And for you, what would be the biggest lesson from crypto investing?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Recently Nano fees have reached an ATH]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nano fees just got back to their ATH of $0. No fees at all. it's interesting cuz
one of the most common criticisms of XNO is, "well if there's no fees then
there's no fees paid to nodes/ validators for doing what they do, so why would
anyone run a node?" at first that may seem like it makes sense,…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfmex5/recently_nano_fees_have_reached_an_ath/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfmex5%2Frecently_nano_fees_have_reached_an_ath%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfmex5%2Frecently_nano_fees_have_reached_an_ath%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfmex5/recently_nano_fees_have_reached_an_ath/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 05:37:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Nano fees just got back to their ATH of $0. No fees at all. it&amp;amp;#39;s interesting cuz one of the most common criticisms of XNO is, &amp;amp;quot;well if there&amp;amp;#39;s no fees then there&amp;amp;#39;s no fees paid to nodes/ validators for doing what they do, so why would anyone run a node?&amp;amp;quot; at first that may seem like it makes sense, but actually when push comes to shove an incentive to participiate in decentralization ironically leads to centralization due to economies of scale. Silvio Micali, the Turing award winning professor at the helm of Algorand, believes the same thing and that&amp;amp;#39;s why algorand validators aren&amp;amp;#39;t paid fees. Colin, creator of nano, gives his take on the topic here: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@clemahieu/emergent-centralization-due-to-economies-of-scale-83cc85a7cbef&quot;&amp;gt;https://medium.com/@clemahieu/emergent-centralization-due-to-economies-of-scale-83cc85a7cbef&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Nano has no fees, so it is technically the best decentralized value-transfer technology out there. The best value-transfer technology i have in my country is Venmo, when i send someone $50 on venmo they literally receive it instantly, and for free. But venmo is centralized, they can freeze your funds at any time, they can determine your account is untrustworthy and block you, they can charge a fee when depositing that money to your bank, all kinds of negatives that nano does not have because nano is decentralized. If nano is just like venmo, but decentralized, why isn&amp;amp;#39;t it more popular? There is no other coin in the crypto market that allows you to transact like venmo, free and instant value-transfer, besides nano. I really don&amp;amp;#39;t understand why nano is outside the top 150 if literally no coin serves as a better transfer-of-value tech. After all, value-transfer is not just some ethereal lofty up in the sky use-case, it&amp;amp;#39;s a use case that every single person basically engages in every single day of their life. Nano should get more respect.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[If ETH was going to $180k Cathie would have sold her children into slavery to buy more ETH before telling you.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am more bullish on ETH than any other cryptocurrency. It's my main DCA, I
stopped buying Bitcoin to buy more ETH. I believe The Flippening will happen in
the next 3-5 years.

But I think that 20 trillion dollars market cap is bullshit. Forget ETH, I would
be more than happy if the whole crypto…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfsy5n/if_eth_was_going_to_180k_cathie_would_have_sold/?score=323&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfsy5n%2Fif_eth_was_going_to_180k_cathie_would_have_sold%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfsy5n%2Fif_eth_was_going_to_180k_cathie_would_have_sold%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfsy5n/if_eth_was_going_to_180k_cathie_would_have_sold/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 04:43:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I am more bullish on ETH than any other cryptocurrency. It&amp;amp;#39;s my main DCA, I stopped buying Bitcoin to buy more ETH. I believe The Flippening will happen in the next 3-5 years.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But I think that 20 trillion dollars market cap is bullshit. Forget ETH, I would be more than happy if the whole crypto market cap was that much by 2030.
The only way this could happen is if the US dollar loses massive value and I don&amp;amp;#39;t think it&amp;amp;#39;s possible for that to happen to a degree like in Venezuela, Argentina or even Turkey.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I love my Hopium as much as the next guy but be sure not to overdose on that fucker. To see ETH at $180k we would need for the Money printer to go brrrrr from now till 2030 non stop. Don&amp;amp;#39;t even want to think about the prices of goods and services.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why HODL?! The answer ⤵️]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sfv29u/why_hodl_the_answer/?score=485&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsfv29u%2Fwhy_hodl_the_answer%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsfv29u%2Fwhy_hodl_the_answer%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sfv29u/why_hodl_the_answer/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 03:39:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to avoid telling parents I put 1.4K into crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[Here’s something for some creative answers. So I recently put £1.4K into crypto
coins I believe I think will have a great 2022 and now my parents are wanting
some of that money which I don’t have because yknow it’s in crypto.

So What’s some good ways they’ll understand, because even though I’m…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfsgt7/how_to_avoid_telling_parents_i_put_14k_into_crypto/?score=342&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfsgt7%2Fhow_to_avoid_telling_parents_i_put_14k_into_crypto%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfsgt7%2Fhow_to_avoid_telling_parents_i_put_14k_into_crypto%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfsgt7/how_to_avoid_telling_parents_i_put_14k_into_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 01:45:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here’s something for some creative answers.
So I recently put £1.4K into crypto coins I believe I think will have a great 2022 and now my parents are wanting some of that money which I don’t have because yknow it’s in crypto. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So What’s some good ways they’ll understand, because even though I’m confident in my current investments they for sure will not support it lol as they have no clue how it works and will think I am just throwing my money away. Thinking of just admitting and taking the beatings as they come 😌&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: It’s my own money not theirs&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$1k invested into the Top Ten Cryptos in January 2021 - ONE YEAR REPORT (UP +292%)]]></title><description><![CDATA[EXPERIMENT - Tracking Top 10 Cryptos Of 2021 - ONE YEAR REPORT – UP 292%
[https://preview.redd.it/di7qedz6nme81.png?width=666&format=png&auto=webp&s=7e3cb1ed5174b384991f4271ef5af0ae8df983c7]

Full blog post with all the tables here
[https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2021-top-10…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfiaht/1k_invested_into_the_top_ten_cryptos_in_january/?score=314&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfiaht%2F1k_invested_into_the_top_ten_cryptos_in_january%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfiaht%2F1k_invested_into_the_top_ten_cryptos_in_january%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfiaht/1k_invested_into_the_top_ten_cryptos_in_january/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 00:45:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/di7qedz6nme81.png?width=666&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=7e3cb1ed5174b384991f4271ef5af0ae8df983c7&quot;&amp;gt;EXPERIMENT - Tracking Top 10 Cryptos Of 2021 - ONE YEAR REPORT – UP 292&amp;amp;#37;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Full blog post with all the tables&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2021-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-11&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;January 1st, 2021, I bought $100 of following and turned it into a homemade crypto index fund: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Bitcoin, Ethereum, Tether, XRP, Litecoin, Polkadot, Bitcoin Cash, Cardano, Binance Coin,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Chainlink.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Below is the eleventh monthly update on the progress of the 2021 Experiment.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;tl;dr:&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What&amp;amp;#39;s this all about?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Back in January 2018, I made a homemade crypto Index Fund, purchasing $100 of each of the Top 10. Crypto winter started immediately after, but I haven&amp;amp;#39;t sold or traded and have been reporting monthly ever since. I repeated the Experiment 2019, 2020, 2021, and again in 2022 because I&amp;amp;#39;m a glutton for punishment and to show different entry points. &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Learn more about the history and rules of the Experiments (including why in the world I would include Tether)&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/about/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;2021 Winner&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; - &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BNB (+1239%)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; easily, returning nearly double second place  &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ADA&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; (+639%)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;2021&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Top Ten portfolio (+292%) vs. 2021 Overall Crypto Market (+185%) vs. 2021 S&amp;amp;amp;P&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; (+27%)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;2018+2019+2020+2021 Combined Top Ten Portfolios are returning 406%.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Some exciting new changes for&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/announcing-top-10-2022/&quot;&amp;gt;2022&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;!&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;This is the last month I&amp;amp;#39;ll be releasing four reports, transitioning to two monthly reports.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Incorporated Decentralized Finance (DeFi) for the first time.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Factoring in stablecoin gains&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: In the past, I have not included ROI that is possible with stables in the monthly reports. This year, I will detail ways to build on the $100 of USDC in the 2022 portfolio and gamify it a bit: my goal is to outperform as many as the other cryptos in the 2022 Top Ten Portfolio as possible (simple if it turns out to be a bear year, a bit more challenging if the 2022 market moons).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Giveaways: I’ll be giving away crypto during the year, either through Twitter, Reddit, or my email list. I’m still figuring out the details, but aim to give away around $100 a month in crypto.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Friendly competition (or Battle Royale?): I will compare my homemade 2022 Top Ten Crypto Index Fund Experiment to a Total Crypto Market Cap Index Token ($TCAP &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/TotalCryptoMarketCap/&quot;&amp;gt;r/TotalCryptoMarketCap&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;) to see which one outperforms.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Month Twelve/ONE YEAR REPORT – UP 292%&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ae8s52rkpme81.png?width=940&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=72c4ce39b8a549a21b4279e34ebc52bcd58b87a8&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/ae8s52rkpme81.png?width=940&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=72c4ce39b8a549a21b4279e34ebc52bcd58b87a8&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The 2021 Top Ten Crypto Index Fund consists of: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BTC, ETH, USDT, XRP, Litecoin, DOT, BCH, ADA, BNB,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;LINK&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;December highlights for the 2021 Top Ten Portfolio: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Every crypto in the 2021 in the red&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BNB&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; continues to maintain a strong overall lead&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;After one year, 2021 Top Ten Portfolio is up +292%&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;December Ranking and Dropout Report&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/4ejclttlpme81.png?width=406&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9349277f5e40cf081b2bae6e7af17c29b24ed621&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/4ejclttlpme81.png?width=406&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9349277f5e40cf081b2bae6e7af17c29b24ed621&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Top Ten dropouts since January 2021:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;  one year into the 2021 Top Ten Experiment, three cryptos have dropped out: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Chainlink, Litecoin,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Bitcoin Cash.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;  They have been replaced by &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;SOL&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Luna,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;USDC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;December Winners and Losers&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;December Winners&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; –  None, unless you count &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;USDT&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;December Losers&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; –   &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Litecoin&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; completed a rare clean sweep this month: it was the worst performer in each of the four Experiments, down -30% in December. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;DOT&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; (-27%) was the second worst performer this month.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Tally of Monthly Winners and Losers&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One year into the Experiment, here’s where we stand in terms of the 2021 Top Ten Portfolio’s monthly winners and losers: =&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/vrzcbjynpme81.jpg?width=411&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=19926c085b216b6ea8c4e42b97b7c29f1df65c27&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/vrzcbjynpme81.jpg?width=411&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=19926c085b216b6ea8c4e42b97b7c29f1df65c27&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ADA, BNB,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;USDT&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; are in a three way tie for most monthly victories.  &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ADA&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; has the most monthly losses.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;One Year Update – BNB easily outperforms, all cryptos in green, Litecoin turns in the worst performance&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After a year of back and forth between &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BNB&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ADA, Binance Coin&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; has left &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Cardano&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and the rest of the cryptos in this portfolio well behind.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The $100 investment into first place &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BNB&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; one year ago is now worth &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$1,343.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Besides &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Tether&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Litecoin&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; turned in the worst performance of the 2021 Top Ten Portfolio, up &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+16%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; in 2021. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Total Market Cap for the Entire Cryptocurrency Sector:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/14coh6dppme81.png?width=582&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=34d99d9caa26f60542c12b693ac8c135d7d78a20&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/14coh6dppme81.png?width=582&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=34d99d9caa26f60542c12b693ac8c135d7d78a20&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a sector, crypto is up &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+185%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; in the year lifespan of the 2021 Top Ten Experiment. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You may notice that the 2021 Top Ten Portfolio has produced better returns than the overall crypto market cap (+292% vs. +185%) so far in 2021.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is a bit of an outlier and the gap is closing: the rest of the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/&quot;&amp;gt;Top Ten Experiments&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; are well behind over their respective time frames.  Here are the latest figures:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Buying the Top Ten at equal weight in Jan 2018:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Up +34% vs. +285% for the total crypto market cap. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Starting in Jan 2019?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; +504% for the Top Ten vs. +1,638% for the total market cap. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Starting in Jan 2020?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; +795% for the Top Ten vs. +1,066% for the total Market Cap. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Although the 2021 Top Ten approach has held up quite well compared to the overall market so far, I expect to see it fall behind eventually, like the other experiments.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto Market Cap Low Point in the 2021 Top Ten Crypto Index Experiment: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2021-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-1/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$775B in January 2021&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto Market Cap High Point in the 2021 Top Ten Crypto Index Experiment: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$2.6T&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2021-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-10&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;in October&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Bitcoin Dominance:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/z52d9ayqpme81.png?width=522&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=04408fb7b8f59ab8dc9e643ebe1b1f02ecb0f9da&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/z52d9ayqpme81.png?width=522&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=04408fb7b8f59ab8dc9e643ebe1b1f02ecb0f9da&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BitDom&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; fell in December, ending the month at 40.2%. This is a new low for the 2021 Experiment.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;BitDom Low Point in the 2021 Top Ten Crypto Index Experiment: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2021-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-12&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;40.2% this month.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;BitDom High Point in the 2021 Top Ten Crypto Index Experiment: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2021-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-1/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;70.4% in  January 2021&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Overall return on $1,000 investment since January 1st, 2021:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/o5kg2l4spme81.png?width=337&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=61044a6addc3f518c0a625ce1ecb32b5dd0e6930&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/o5kg2l4spme81.png?width=337&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=61044a6addc3f518c0a625ce1ecb32b5dd0e6930&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The 2021 Portfolio dropped $945 in December.  Overall, the 2021 Top Ten Portfolio is up +292%.  The initial $1000 investment one year ago, on New Year’s Day 2021, is worth &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$3,921&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here’s the month by month ROI of the 2021 Top Ten Experiment, to give you a sense of perspective as we go along:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/pu2vwe0tpme81.png?width=219&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=344da96a8e10f8ac6cfb3721abc9c5d65903b284&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/pu2vwe0tpme81.png?width=219&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=344da96a8e10f8ac6cfb3721abc9c5d65903b284&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The 2021 Top Ten Portfolio has had the best start, by far, of any of the four &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/&quot;&amp;gt;Top Ten Crypto Experiments&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Combining the 2018, 2019, 2020, and 2021 Top Ten Crypto Portfolios&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As most readers are aware, this is the fourth year of an Experiment I started back in January of 2018, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-ten-month-one/&quot;&amp;gt;at the height of the last crypto bull run&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.  Where do we stand if we combine four years of the Top Ten Crypto Index Fund Experiments?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-48&quot;&amp;gt;2018 Top Ten Experiment&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;: up +34% (total value $1,341)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2019-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-36&quot;&amp;gt;2019 Top Ten Experiment&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;: up +504% (total value $6,044)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2020-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-24&quot;&amp;gt;2020 Top Ten Experiment&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;: up +795% (total value $8,951)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2021-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-12&quot;&amp;gt;2021 Top Ten Experiment:&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; up +292% (total value $3,921)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So overall? Taking the four portfolios together, here’s the bottom bottom bottom &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;bottom&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; line: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;After a $4,000 investment in the 2018, 2019, 2020, and 2021 Top Ten Cryptocurrencies,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; the combined portfolios are worth &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$20,257&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; ($1,341 + $6,044 + $8,951 + $3,921).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;That’s up +406%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; on the combined portfolios, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;down from&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2021-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-11&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;last month’s all time high&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for the Top Ten Index Fund Experiments. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here’s a table to help visualize the progress of the combined portfolios:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;📷&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In summary: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;That’s a +406% gain by investing $1k on whichever cryptos happened to be in the Top Ten on January 1st (including stablecoins) for four straight years&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Comparison to S&amp;amp;amp;P 500&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m also tracking the S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 as part of my experiment to have a comparison point to traditional markets&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/qp1mqi4zpme81.png?width=538&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=a299382d6cf43b4586da79c4443c103e898e8318&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/qp1mqi4zpme81.png?width=538&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=a299382d6cf43b4586da79c4443c103e898e8318&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 Index is up &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;27%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; in 2021.  The initial $1k investment I put into crypto one year ago would be worth &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$1,270&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; had it been redirected to the S&amp;amp;amp;P 500.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The 2021 Top Ten Crypto Portfolio is up &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+292%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; over the same time period – the initial $1k investment in crypto one year ago is now worth &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$3,921.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That’s a difference of &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$2,651&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; on a $1k investment in one year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What about in the longer term? What if I invested in the S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 the same way I did during the first four years of the Top Top Crypto Index Fund Experiments? What I like to call the world’s slowest dollar cost averaging method?  Here are the figures:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2018 = $1,780 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2019 = $1,900 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2020 = $1,480 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2021 = $1,270 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Taken together, here’s the bottom bottom bottom &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;bottom&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; line for a similar approach with the S&amp;amp;amp;P: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;After four $1,000 investments into an S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 index fund in January 2018, 2019, 2020, and 2021, my portfolio would be worth $6,430&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; ($1,780 + $1,900 + $1,480 + $1,270).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That is up &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+61%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-ten-month-one/&quot;&amp;gt;since January 2018&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; compared to a &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+406%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; gain of the combined Top Ten Crypto Experiment Portfolios.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To help provide perspective, here’s fancy new chart showing the combined four year ROI for the Crypto Top Ten Experiment vs. the S&amp;amp;amp;P up to this point&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/31ttv391qme81.png?width=575&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d45b693b4b19ec72addaeb526f80e00052caf776&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/31ttv391qme81.png?width=575&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d45b693b4b19ec72addaeb526f80e00052caf776&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Conclusion:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To the long time followers of the Top Ten Experiments, thank you so much for sticking around so long. For those just getting into crypto, I hope these reports will help prepare you for the highs and lows that await on your crypto adventures.  Buckle up, go with the flow, think long term, don’t invest what you can’t afford to lose, and most importantly, try to enjoy the ride!  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Feel free to reach out with any questions and stay tuned for progress reports. Keep an eye out for my parallel projects tracking the Top Ten cryptos as of &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-48&quot;&amp;gt;January 1st, 2018&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; (the OG Experiment), &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2019-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-36&quot;&amp;gt;January 1st, 2019&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2020-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-24&quot;&amp;gt;January 1st, 2020&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, and most recently, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/announcing-top-10-2022/&quot;&amp;gt;January 1st, 2022&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anyone else here not giving a single f-ck about this crash?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Is there anyone else here who is not, even slightly moved by the recent crash? I
sleep like a baby while my portfolio is going down. Why? Because I strongly
believe that we are still at the beginning ot this long journey. If you are
someone who believes in crypto patience is the key. Im not a…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sftafj/anyone_else_here_not_giving_a_single_fck_about/?score=662&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsftafj%2Fanyone_else_here_not_giving_a_single_fck_about%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsftafj%2Fanyone_else_here_not_giving_a_single_fck_about%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sftafj/anyone_else_here_not_giving_a_single_fck_about/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 00:45:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Is there anyone else here who is not, even slightly moved by the recent crash? 
I sleep like a baby while my portfolio is going down. Why?
Because I strongly believe that we are still at the beginning ot this long journey. If you are someone who believes in crypto patience is the key. Im not a gambler. Im an investor. And as an investor, holding the assets that you truly believe in, is much easier during volatile times. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Gamblers who threw in a massive portion of their bank accounts and see them going down in a few days are likely angry or already moved on.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I cant help but feel perfectly fine despite the volatility. Id be lying if I said that Id be happier to get more sats for less fiat but keep that dca on dips and itll pay off in the end&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto.com says 1 billion people will invest in Cryptocurrencies by the end of 2022. "This year is going to be the first year where you cannot say cryptocurrency is not mainstream anymore".]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfqq26/cryptocom_says_1_billion_people_will_invest_in/?score=376&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfqq26%2Fcryptocom_says_1_billion_people_will_invest_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfqq26%2Fcryptocom_says_1_billion_people_will_invest_in%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfqq26/cryptocom_says_1_billion_people_will_invest_in/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 00:45:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Here is what would happen if someone invested every month at the highest price since 2016.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Scenario:

Lets say you have a friend, call him buy-high Chuck, because he has a nag for
buying crypto at the highest price every month. Say he invested 500 dollars
split between bitcoin and ethereum every month since 2016. What would be the end
result?

Method:

I used coinbase api so data was…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfp9bc/here_is_what_would_happen_if_someone_invested/?score=309&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfp9bc%2Fhere_is_what_would_happen_if_someone_invested%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfp9bc%2Fhere_is_what_would_happen_if_someone_invested%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfp9bc/here_is_what_would_happen_if_someone_invested/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 00:45:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Scenario&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Lets say you have a friend, call him buy-high Chuck, because he has a nag for buying crypto at the &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;highest price&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; every month.  Say he invested 500 dollars split between bitcoin and ethereum every month since 2016. What would be the end result?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Method&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I used coinbase api so data was only available since 2016, Jan. For each month I find the highest price and bought 250 USD for BTC and ETH and held it until today&amp;amp;#39;s closing price.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Results&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;the monthly results are really long and I will post a link in the comments.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Here is the summary table though.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;table&amp;gt;&amp;lt;thead&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;ETH-USD&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;BTC-USD&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/thead&amp;gt;&amp;lt;tbody&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;Total_earned&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;$  592,735.26 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;$  263,770.86 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;median_by_month&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;$      1,803.15 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;$          777.90 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;max_per_month&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;$    75,412.06 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;$    21,885.08 &amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;max_per_month_ptc&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;30165&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;8754&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;min_per_month&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;$        (116.35)&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;$        (110.65)&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;min_per_month_ptc&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;-46.54&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;-44.26&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tbody&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/table&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;In summary&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;,&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A 500 dollar split in half between ETH / BTC, bought every month at its highest price,  would total about  ( $856,506.12)  The most that was made with 250 dollar investment is (75,412) for ETH and (21,885) for BTC . This occurred on 2016-12 and 2016-03 respectively, while the lowest ( max loss), is  (-116) dollars for ETH and (-110) dollars for BTC. Importantly the median return for a 250 dollar investment  is 1,800 for ETH and 777 for BTC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Plot&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: total earned per 250 USD investments&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/yacure8uaoe81.png?width=669&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d53fffcc8590b2d248e02f57fb11d1db2acba884&quot;&amp;gt;this should be logarithmic but its would obscure the price&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TLDR :  buy-high Chuck who invested at the highest every month, 500 dollars split between ETH and BTC would had have about  $856,506 USD in his portfolio. Not bad for someone who has a nag for buying at the highest.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;PS: let me know if you have an idea for some number crunching and I will see if I can do it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[‘I made $4m profit on crypto, but the bank won’t let me spend it’]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfjl0h/i_made_4m_profit_on_crypto_but_the_bank_wont_let/?score=319&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfjl0h%2Fi_made_4m_profit_on_crypto_but_the_bank_wont_let%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsfjl0h%2Fi_made_4m_profit_on_crypto_but_the_bank_wont_let%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sfjl0h/i_made_4m_profit_on_crypto_but_the_bank_wont_let/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 00:45:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hey world investors:  

Global debt is a US$400T asset that is programmed to debase (it is a Fiat contract).

#btc is a sub US$1T asset that is programmed as the most secure Store of Value ever created (math + code)

Where do you think the smart money will flow?

#mathishard]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1487553442918899714/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1487553442918899714/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 22:37:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Belgian politician Christophe De Beukelaer becomes the first EU official to be paid a salary in Bitcoin 🚀]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sfheg3/belgian_politician_christophe_de_beukelaer/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsfheg3%2Fbelgian_politician_christophe_de_beukelaer%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsfheg3%2Fbelgian_politician_christophe_de_beukelaer%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sfheg3/belgian_politician_christophe_de_beukelaer/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 22:37:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>