<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing on Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 07:29:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Jack Dorsey: Facebook should have focused on Bitcoin instead of 'Wasting effort and time' on Diem]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/si6vg9/jack_dorsey_facebook_should_have_focused_on/?score=338&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsi6vg9%2Fjack_dorsey_facebook_should_have_focused_on%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsi6vg9%2Fjack_dorsey_facebook_should_have_focused_on%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/si6vg9/jack_dorsey_facebook_should_have_focused_on/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 06:39:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The concept of NFTs is valuable. But a JPEG is not worth millions of dollars.]]></title><description><![CDATA[In fact, I don’t think these JPEGs should be valued for more than 5 digits. And
most of the time its not the market that’s setting these prices. They’re usually
inorganically inflated.

This is exactly why NFT like Bored Apes are so hated. I think the only valuable
thing about Bored Apes is the…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sib6ur/the_concept_of_nfts_is_valuable_but_a_jpeg_is_not/?score=327&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsib6ur%2Fthe_concept_of_nfts_is_valuable_but_a_jpeg_is_not%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsib6ur%2Fthe_concept_of_nfts_is_valuable_but_a_jpeg_is_not%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sib6ur/the_concept_of_nfts_is_valuable_but_a_jpeg_is_not/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 06:39:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In fact, I don’t think these JPEGs should be valued for more than 5 digits. And most of the time its not the market that’s setting these prices. They’re usually inorganically inflated.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is exactly why NFT like Bored Apes are so hated. I think the only valuable thing about Bored Apes is the access to exclusive places and contacts but thats it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Even then, I think this “exclusivity” is REALLY inflated when there are NFTs like Habtoor’s Last Hopium offering almost the same services and exclusivity for much less.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I don’t want to use the word “bubble” cause NFT do in fact have a lot of applications later on. So let’s use the word “inflated”.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[FIAT Money continues to be the Currency of Choice for Criminals, not Crypto: Less than 1% of Crypto Transactions are Connected to Crime, more than $1,600,000,000,000 of FIAT is Connected to Crime each Year]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shx9yt/fiat_money_continues_to_be_the_currency_of_choice/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshx9yt%2Ffiat_money_continues_to_be_the_currency_of_choice%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshx9yt%2Ffiat_money_continues_to_be_the_currency_of_choice%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shx9yt/fiat_money_continues_to_be_the_currency_of_choice/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 05:32:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How many of you actually hold only Bitcoin?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I understand this is a bitcoin sub, but there is no way you ONLY hold Bitcoin
right?]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shy3vj/how_many_of_you_actually_hold_only_bitcoin/?score=309&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshy3vj%2Fhow_many_of_you_actually_hold_only_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshy3vj%2Fhow_many_of_you_actually_hold_only_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shy3vj/how_many_of_you_actually_hold_only_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 02:44:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I understand this is a bitcoin sub, but there is no way you ONLY hold Bitcoin right?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[It will never sit right with me this double tax thing]]></title><description><![CDATA[9-5 people, perhaps not living paycheck to paycheck, but someone who's not more
than half a year of unemployment away from having their life turned on its head
- These people are not going to get much better off by working, nor by saving
money in the bank. They don't have wealthy relatives so…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/si4p19/it_will_never_sit_right_with_me_this_double_tax/?score=327&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsi4p19%2Fit_will_never_sit_right_with_me_this_double_tax%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsi4p19%2Fit_will_never_sit_right_with_me_this_double_tax%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/si4p19/it_will_never_sit_right_with_me_this_double_tax/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 02:44:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;9-5 people, perhaps not living paycheck to paycheck, but someone who&amp;amp;#39;s not more than half a year of unemployment away from having their life turned on its head - These people are not going to get much better off by working, nor by saving money in the bank. They don&amp;amp;#39;t have wealthy relatives so there&amp;amp;#39;s no large inheritance coming their way and they definitely don&amp;amp;#39;t have the money for a downpayment on a permanent residence of their own.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;These individuals know this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So they put a little money into crypto, hoping to make it grow a bit, hoping to take charge a bit. This is money they&amp;amp;#39;ve already been taxed on. It is a risky endeavor but they&amp;amp;#39;re assuming all the risk. It happens that they grow their $2000 worth of crypto into $5000 worth of crypto and they&amp;amp;#39;re ecstatic! - but here comes the government, it needs a cut.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why? Why now? Have they not already paid taxes on this money? The government assumed no risk. The money is still in crypto. Those $5000 can turn to $500 in a hurry. What happens then? Can they deduct it? Maybe, it depends on where you live. At best you can deduct only a small percentage of your loss each year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, they have to pay taxes on the money they&amp;amp;#39;ve made from the money they had already paid taxes on, even if they still risk losing all of it (+ taxes now).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;--&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If the government must tax crypto gains they had no stake in, make it happen ONLY when the gains go back to fiat or when they&amp;amp;#39;re exchanged into some other real-world asset like a car.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Until then, it is play money, an unrealized gain (or loss) that the government has no business putting their noses in. Poker chips that have not yet been exchanged for cash.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sure, as India did, remove their ability to deduct anything. It&amp;amp;#39;s fine. As long as you don&amp;amp;#39;t try to tax their unrealized gains. Or do something stupid like taxing transactions...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit - I know they only pay taxes on their gains, not their initial.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why you should make XMR part of your portfolio]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m sure that a lot of you have heard about Monero (XMR) and that it is
Private/Untraceable [https://imgur.com/a/Skb5L4q] and most commonly used in
“boating accidents” but there’s more to XMR then just that and it’s potential
use cases are solid

A lot of people seem to have this understanding that…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/si3m4a/why_you_should_make_xmr_part_of_your_portfolio/?score=310&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsi3m4a%2Fwhy_you_should_make_xmr_part_of_your_portfolio%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsi3m4a%2Fwhy_you_should_make_xmr_part_of_your_portfolio%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/si3m4a/why_you_should_make_xmr_part_of_your_portfolio/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:42:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m sure that a lot of you have heard about Monero (XMR) and that it is &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/Skb5L4q&quot;&amp;gt;Private/Untraceable&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and most commonly used in “boating accidents” but there’s more to XMR then just that and it’s potential use cases are solid &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A lot of people seem to have this understanding that XMR is used solely for the purpose of buying illicit products on the dark web because it’s untraceable, and yes that does happen, but it’s also happened to Bitcoin before and now countries such as El Salvador have made BTC a national currency.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;XMR can be used for so much more then nefarious acts online for example buying everyday products and subscriptions/services.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why would you want to use XMR for that? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Credit card fraud rose by 44.7% over 2019 to 393,207 reports.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There were 1,108 data breaches in 2020,&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The number of people affected by data breaches was 300Million in 2020 &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;identity theft/fraud cases resulted in losses of $712.4 billion in 2020. That was a 42% increase from 2019.  &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fool.com/the-ascent/research/identity-theft-credit-card-fraud-statistics/&quot;&amp;gt;source&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Paying with a credit/debit card seems simple enough but your putting your information/finances at risk of being compromised and it is a headache to deal with compromised bank cards/credentials &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In comes XMR to solve these issues: Since XMR is so private the risk of having your credit/debit card compromised by a data breech is virtually impossible because you never used the credit or debit card to buy the product/service&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Outside entities cannot decipher addresses trading monero, transaction amounts, address balances, or transaction histories. This is all because of XMRs stealth addresses which obscures the public address to the people involved. This also goes hand in hand with XMRs ring signature technology which makes use of your account keys and a number of public keys pulled from the blockchain using a triangular distribution method. There is no way an outside observer can tell which of the possible signers in a signature group belongs to your account. XMR is so private in fact even the IRS has even offered a bounty of $625K to anyone who can crack the privacy of Monero. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://blockchain.news/news/irs-criminal-investigation-$625-000-bounty-monero-privacy-crack-btc-lightning-network-tracker&quot;&amp;gt;source&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On top of all that delicious technology that XMR has to offer it is also an open source and completely decentralized so anyone can partake in using XMR. No one is excluded.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And the icing on the cake is that XMR is considerably much cheaper to transact with then Bitcoin. Plus all the added benefits with all the extra features that XMR has to offer. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Transaction fees paid (last 100 transactions) &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.monero.how/monero-transaction-fees&quot;&amp;gt;source&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Monero (lowest) 0.000007    $ 0.0010&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin (lowest)    0.000027    $ 1.0647&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Monero (median) 0.000009    $ 0.0014&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin (median)    0.000067    $ 2.5851&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Monero (highest)    0.006938    $ 1.0105&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin (highest)   0.000450    $ 17.4929&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TLDR: you should use XMR wherever possible for your day to day transactions to mitigate your chances of having your credit/debit card and personal information from being compromised.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Privacy is a human right&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[You don’t need to “convince” nor argue with anyone to invest in crypto. It’s not some MLM, Pyramid scheme, Ponzi etc.. When they’ll be interested, they’ll ask.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’ve seen a lot of opinions thrown out here, whether you should or shouldn’t
tell your family, friends, neighbours about crypto.

The general consensus of this subreddit is always: “DCA and HODL!” Yes, the past
already proved that it’s one of the best if not the best strategy out there. But
do we…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/si1abt/you_dont_need_to_convince_nor_argue_with_anyone/?score=322&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsi1abt%2Fyou_dont_need_to_convince_nor_argue_with_anyone%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsi1abt%2Fyou_dont_need_to_convince_nor_argue_with_anyone%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/si1abt/you_dont_need_to_convince_nor_argue_with_anyone/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:42:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve seen a lot of opinions thrown out here, whether you should or shouldn’t tell your family, friends, neighbours about crypto.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The general consensus of this subreddit is always: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;“DCA and HODL!”&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Yes, the past already proved that it’s one of the best if not the best strategy out there. But do we really need to force this motto everywhere we go?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Shouldn’t we focus more on teaching them what crypto actually solves, how it can literally “change” or “transform” the world that were living it to a better place? One of the biggest benefits that crypto is offering to us, is that there will be no more total control of every aspect in our lives. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If these people will be interested in it, they’ll ask, and that’s time when we, crypto investors can try to direct them to the right way, and show them that crypto isn’t some get rich free quick scheme provided by Tai Lopez. Creating financial freedom from crypto or getting wealthy from it is only side effect.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just my poor point of view. Have a nice day.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Did it ever fucking occur to you that if a board certified licensed practicing Cardiologist who has published over 700 peer reviewed research papers and practiced medicine for 30 years says he thinks a treatment is too dangerous that maybe he is not just some conspiracy theorist?]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1488645847772545025/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1488645847772545025/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 23:47:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Criticizing Bitcoin for its high energy use is like criticizing the fire department for using too much water]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bitcoin is energy. Its high energy use is an investment. Bitcoin miners securing
a huge network is a good thing.]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shrxge/criticizing_bitcoin_for_its_high_energy_use_is/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshrxge%2Fcriticizing_bitcoin_for_its_high_energy_use_is%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshrxge%2Fcriticizing_bitcoin_for_its_high_energy_use_is%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shrxge/criticizing_bitcoin_for_its_high_energy_use_is/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 23:32:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin is energy. Its high energy use is an investment. Bitcoin miners securing a huge network is a good thing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thailand scraps 15% crypto capital gains tax following public backlash]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sht91v/thailand_scraps_15_crypto_capital_gains_tax/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsht91v%2Fthailand_scraps_15_crypto_capital_gains_tax%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsht91v%2Fthailand_scraps_15_crypto_capital_gains_tax%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sht91v/thailand_scraps_15_crypto_capital_gains_tax/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 22:32:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin Confirms He’ll Help in Moving Dogecoin to Proof-of-Stake (PoS) Network]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shyser/vitalik_buterin_confirms_hell_help_in_moving/?score=330&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshyser%2Fvitalik_buterin_confirms_hell_help_in_moving%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshyser%2Fvitalik_buterin_confirms_hell_help_in_moving%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shyser/vitalik_buterin_confirms_hell_help_in_moving/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 22:32:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$11 trillion asset manager Fidelity Investments: “Bitcoin is superior form of money and should be considered seperately from other digital assets ”]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shv5aw/11_trillion_asset_manager_fidelity_investments/?score=310&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshv5aw%2F11_trillion_asset_manager_fidelity_investments%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshv5aw%2F11_trillion_asset_manager_fidelity_investments%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shv5aw/11_trillion_asset_manager_fidelity_investments/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 21:32:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Justin Bieber Trolled For Spending $1.3 Million On The Bored Ape NFT Originally Worth $20K; Netizens Say, “That’s More Bullish Than Anything Else Could Be.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shzcq1/justin_bieber_trolled_for_spending_13_million_on/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshzcq1%2Fjustin_bieber_trolled_for_spending_13_million_on%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshzcq1%2Fjustin_bieber_trolled_for_spending_13_million_on%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shzcq1/justin_bieber_trolled_for_spending_13_million_on/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 21:32:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Police looking for drugs discover Mining setup.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/si1gsq/police_looking_for_drugs_discover_mining_setup/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsi1gsq%2Fpolice_looking_for_drugs_discover_mining_setup%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsi1gsq%2Fpolice_looking_for_drugs_discover_mining_setup%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/si1gsq/police_looking_for_drugs_discover_mining_setup/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 21:32:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dont' worry son, we have Bitcoin]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shqndj/dont_worry_son_we_have_bitcoin/?score=342&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshqndj%2Fdont_worry_son_we_have_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshqndj%2Fdont_worry_son_we_have_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shqndj/dont_worry_son_we_have_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 19:38:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MicroStrategy has purchased an additional 660 bitcoins for ~$25.0 million in cash at an average price of ~$37,865 per bitcoin]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shuim3/microstrategy_has_purchased_an_additional_660/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshuim3%2Fmicrostrategy_has_purchased_an_additional_660%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshuim3%2Fmicrostrategy_has_purchased_an_additional_660%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shuim3/microstrategy_has_purchased_an_additional_660/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 18:36:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MicroStrategy has purchased an additional 660 bitcoins for ~$25.0 million in cash at an average price of ~$37,865 per bitcoin.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shujr9/microstrategy_has_purchased_an_additional_660/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshujr9%2Fmicrostrategy_has_purchased_an_additional_660%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshujr9%2Fmicrostrategy_has_purchased_an_additional_660%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shujr9/microstrategy_has_purchased_an_additional_660/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 18:36:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[You guys understand, that El Salvador wants $1.3 billion in funding from the IMF, and that the IMF isn't just randomly asking them to drop BTC as a currency, right?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Two posts are on the front page right now: "El Salvador angrily rejects IMF call
to drop Bitcoin use"
[https://np.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/she2t3/el_salvador_angrily_rejects_imf_call_to_drop/]
and El Salvador Treasury Minister Alejandro Zelaya angrily rejects IMF demand to
drop Bitcoin…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shw6sa/you_guys_understand_that_el_salvador_wants_13/?score=775&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshw6sa%2Fyou_guys_understand_that_el_salvador_wants_13%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshw6sa%2Fyou_guys_understand_that_el_salvador_wants_13%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shw6sa/you_guys_understand_that_el_salvador_wants_13/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 17:42:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Two posts are on the front page right now: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/she2t3/el_salvador_angrily_rejects_imf_call_to_drop/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;El Salvador angrily rejects IMF call to drop Bitcoin use&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shs9au/el_salvador_treasury_minister_alejandro_zelaya/&quot;&amp;gt;El Salvador Treasury Minister Alejandro Zelaya angrily rejects IMF demand to drop Bitcoin as legal tender, “We are a sovereign nation. No international organization is going to make us do anything, anything at all!&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You guys understand that the IMF isn&amp;amp;#39;t just randomly going around demanding stuff, right? Most replies don&amp;amp;#39;t seem to understand that. El Salvador has tried to get &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/article/us-el-salvador-economy-exclusive-idUSKBN2AW1GV&quot;&amp;gt;$1.3 billion in funding from them&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for almost a year now. That&amp;amp;#39;s a ton of money. And sure, edglord Bukele and his corrupt, idiotic government can keep their stance that nobody can &amp;amp;quot;make them&amp;amp;quot; do anything - but nobody is trying to force them to do anything. It&amp;amp;#39;s more of a &amp;amp;quot;yeah we won&amp;amp;#39;t give you money as long as you are gambling with your economy in an irresponsible manner&amp;amp;quot;. Which is a completely reasonable attitude. Why would they just give money to them without conditions?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;El Salvador doesn&amp;amp;#39;t hold any power here. They&amp;amp;#39;re an irrelevant, tiny economy, the IMF couldn&amp;amp;#39;t care less about them. If they want money, they&amp;amp;#39;ll have to comply. Or the dictator once again makes a stupid decision for his country...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Today, Denmark lifted *all* restrictions, while cases are soaring.

The international reaction: Disbelief.

I am leading the largest Danish project on pandemic behavior &amp; I am advising the gov.

Here is why Danes are still supportive. And what may be learned from this.

🧵(1/19) https://t.co/C6E9Fc9D1G]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1488547640480567297/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1488547640480567297/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 17:01:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Economics professor asked “whats the point of bitcoin?”]]></title><description><![CDATA[Today at my university class, the professor asked “whats the point of bitcoin?”
The room was somewhat silent, then some responses about it being purely for
speculation pop corned around the room. I sat in silence while he proceeded to
slander btc and state multiple points of false information, such…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shnu7k/economics_professor_asked_whats_the_point_of/?score=337&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshnu7k%2Feconomics_professor_asked_whats_the_point_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshnu7k%2Feconomics_professor_asked_whats_the_point_of%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shnu7k/economics_professor_asked_whats_the_point_of/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:33:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Today at my university class, the professor asked “whats the point of bitcoin?” The room was somewhat silent, then some responses about it being purely for speculation pop corned around the room. I sat in silence while he proceeded to slander btc and state multiple points of false information, such as “originally the creator pegged bitcoin at 1 us dollar and never meant for it to be priced the way it is, also its backed by nothing, unlike this physical dollar in my pocket. Clearly he doesnt understand bitcoin, but i wonder what would have been the best response to such a question.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[El Salvador Treasury Minister Alejandro Zelaya angrily rejects IMF demand to drop Bitcoin as legal tender, “We are a sovereign nation. No international organization is going to make us do anything, anything at all!"]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shs9au/el_salvador_treasury_minister_alejandro_zelaya/?score=379&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshs9au%2Fel_salvador_treasury_minister_alejandro_zelaya%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshs9au%2Fel_salvador_treasury_minister_alejandro_zelaya%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shs9au/el_salvador_treasury_minister_alejandro_zelaya/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 15:40:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[S2F 62% off, or BTC 62% discount? https://t.co/2Hmo8VBSz4]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1488504929006366721/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1488504929006366721/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 13:44:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Creators of NFT project Doodled Dragons promised to donate all profits to Charities protecting animals. After Collecting money, "Fuck that,Our Charity will now be my Bank Account"]]></title><description><![CDATA[A Solsea-verified NFT project on the Solana Blockchain, Doodled Dragons
announced that they would distribute all profits "straight to charities
protecting animals on the brink of extinction".

They announced on Twitter that they would be donating $30k, "our first donation
to the World Wildlife…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shqevq/creators_of_nft_project_doodled_dragons_promised/?score=315&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshqevq%2Fcreators_of_nft_project_doodled_dragons_promised%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshqevq%2Fcreators_of_nft_project_doodled_dragons_promised%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shqevq/creators_of_nft_project_doodled_dragons_promised/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 13:43:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A Solsea-verified NFT project on the Solana Blockchain, Doodled Dragons announced that they would distribute all profits
 &amp;amp;quot;straight to charities protecting animals on the brink of extinction&amp;amp;quot;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They announced on Twitter that they would be donating $30k, &amp;amp;quot;our first donation to the World Wildlife Fund&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Two hours later, they tweeted &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Actually, Fuck that. Our charity will instead now be.... My Bank Account. Cya Nerds.&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They deleted the Twitter account shortly after that. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Audacity of Scammers. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Stay safe Guys, don&amp;amp;#39;t believe anything especially the new NFT collections and play to earn Crypto games.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[El Salvador President: Bitcoin Will Witness “a Gigantic Price Increase” Soon]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sh32y4/el_salvador_president_bitcoin_will_witness_a/?score=309&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsh32y4%2Fel_salvador_president_bitcoin_will_witness_a%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsh32y4%2Fel_salvador_president_bitcoin_will_witness_a%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sh32y4/el_salvador_president_bitcoin_will_witness_a/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 13:43:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I'll admit it. I didn't trust you guys about Algorand at all. How incredibly foolish of me...]]></title><description><![CDATA[Last few days, I've been playing around on Algorand experimenting with a lot of
stuff. AND I LOVE IT. Silvio Micali really knows his stuff. This network is an
absolute rocket and costs nothing.

Among other things I also tried the "famous" NFT on Algorand. What a crazy
thing. It costs close to…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shq9na/ill_admit_it_i_didnt_trust_you_guys_about/?score=381&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshq9na%2Fill_admit_it_i_didnt_trust_you_guys_about%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshq9na%2Fill_admit_it_i_didnt_trust_you_guys_about%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shq9na/ill_admit_it_i_didnt_trust_you_guys_about/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 13:43:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Last few days, I&amp;amp;#39;ve been playing around on Algorand experimenting with a lot of stuff. AND I LOVE IT. Silvio Micali really knows his stuff. This network is an absolute rocket and costs nothing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Among other things I also tried the &amp;amp;quot;famous&amp;amp;quot; NFT on Algorand. What a crazy thing. It costs close to nothing to mint and put an NFT for sale. This is a complete game changer for artists in animation or music.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The MyAlgo wallet that Ive been using since a few days ago is really innovative too. No programs running on your device, it simply works in your browser via cookies (I assume?). &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I admit, I was really wrong about you guys being super excited for Algo but you cant really blame me after all the disastrous projects that were shilled around here. I&amp;amp;#39;m keeping my eyes on this one.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fidelity compares Gold vs BTC vs Fiat based on first principles of "good" money]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shotki/fidelity_compares_gold_vs_btc_vs_fiat_based_on/?score=328&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshotki%2Ffidelity_compares_gold_vs_btc_vs_fiat_based_on%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshotki%2Ffidelity_compares_gold_vs_btc_vs_fiat_based_on%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shotki/fidelity_compares_gold_vs_btc_vs_fiat_based_on/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 12:48:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kanye West says do not ask him to make f****g NFTs. He would rather make products that are ‘Real’ such as, ‘ Real music, Real Food, Real Clothes and Real Shelter’.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sho53k/kanye_west_says_do_not_ask_him_to_make_fg_nfts_he/?score=382&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsho53k%2Fkanye_west_says_do_not_ask_him_to_make_fg_nfts_he%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsho53k%2Fkanye_west_says_do_not_ask_him_to_make_fg_nfts_he%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sho53k/kanye_west_says_do_not_ask_him_to_make_fg_nfts_he/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 11:32:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[50,000 Bitcoins that were stolen from Bitfinex in 2016 has just moved wallets ($2 Billion)]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shmq7z/50000_bitcoins_that_were_stolen_from_bitfinex_in/?score=405&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshmq7z%2F50000_bitcoins_that_were_stolen_from_bitfinex_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshmq7z%2F50000_bitcoins_that_were_stolen_from_bitfinex_in%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shmq7z/50000_bitcoins_that_were_stolen_from_bitfinex_in/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 10:34:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bored Apes have reached a floor price well above 100 Eth. Maybe it's time to start investing in stupidity.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Honestly, I wonder who could have seen it coming. People are spending thousands
of dollars on Monkey jpegs, and get rewarded for this moronic behavior with
better return rates than almost any other asset can provide. Maybe it's a sign
that instead of investing in utility and smart concepts, people…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shgmmb/bored_apes_have_reached_a_floor_price_well_above/?score=349&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshgmmb%2Fbored_apes_have_reached_a_floor_price_well_above%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshgmmb%2Fbored_apes_have_reached_a_floor_price_well_above%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shgmmb/bored_apes_have_reached_a_floor_price_well_above/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 10:34:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Honestly, I wonder who could have seen it coming. People are spending thousands of dollars on Monkey jpegs, and get rewarded for this moronic behavior with better return rates than almost any other asset can provide. Maybe it&amp;amp;#39;s a sign that instead of investing in utility and smart concepts, people should just invest in stupidity because the majority of buyers are stupid, so the price for stupid assets rises faster. It may sound cynical, but it&amp;amp;#39;s just that I imagined the future to be more...reasonable.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Do something damn it]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sho3ch/do_something_damn_it/?score=349&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsho3ch%2Fdo_something_damn_it%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsho3ch%2Fdo_something_damn_it%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sho3ch/do_something_damn_it/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 10:34:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fidelity's latest report on Bitcoin (emphasis added below)]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shg220/fidelitys_latest_report_on_bitcoin_emphasis_added/?score=316&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshg220%2Ffidelitys_latest_report_on_bitcoin_emphasis_added%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshg220%2Ffidelitys_latest_report_on_bitcoin_emphasis_added%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shg220/fidelitys_latest_report_on_bitcoin_emphasis_added/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 10:34:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Idk if you know the streamer ice poseidon, but he rugpulled his coin for over $500k]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shhtx4/idk_if_you_know_the_streamer_ice_poseidon_but_he/?score=328&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshhtx4%2Fidk_if_you_know_the_streamer_ice_poseidon_but_he%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshhtx4%2Fidk_if_you_know_the_streamer_ice_poseidon_but_he%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shhtx4/idk_if_you_know_the_streamer_ice_poseidon_but_he/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 10:34:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Indian government announces it will bring crypto under legal framework, taxable at 30% of gains. No capital losses or business expenses allowed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Indian government just announced that crypto will be taxed at 30% of gains. This
is the first time the Indian government is discussing crypto taxation. The tax
will apply to all gains on digital virtual assets, and no capital losses will be
allowed. Business expenses will also not be…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shomjg/indian_government_announces_it_will_bring_crypto/?score=661&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshomjg%2Findian_government_announces_it_will_bring_crypto%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshomjg%2Findian_government_announces_it_will_bring_crypto%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shomjg/indian_government_announces_it_will_bring_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 10:34:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Indian government just announced that crypto will be taxed at 30% of gains. This is the first time the Indian government is discussing crypto taxation. 
The tax will apply to all gains on digital virtual assets, and no capital losses will be allowed. Business expenses will also not  be allowed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Gifts in the form of digital currency will be also taxed in the hands of the receiver.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is a landmark announcement as the first time the Indian government is announcing any law or regulation around crypto. So far nothing concrete was announced except rumors in the media. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now crypto being a taxable asset will lead to growth of adoption of crypto in India&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I propose to provide that any income from transfer of any virtual digital asset shall be taxed at the rate of 30%. No deduction in respect of any expenditure or allowance shall be allowed while computing such income, except cost of acquisition: FM Nirmala Sitharaman&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit : Some sources are saying capital gains losses is not allowed only for offsetting it with other income sources. But it is still allowed within crypto. Waiting for more clarity on this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit 2: &amp;lt;del&amp;gt;It seems completely no capital losses.&amp;lt;/del&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.indiabudget.gov.in/doc/memo.pdf&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.indiabudget.gov.in/doc/memo.pdf&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Law mentions &amp;amp;quot;aggregate income from crypto transfers&amp;amp;quot; - some seem to think this means crypto losses can be offset among crypto itself. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, no deduction in respect of any expenditure (other than cost of acquisition) or allowance or set off of any loss shall be allowed to the assessee under any provision of the Act while computing income from transfer of such asset&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Further, no set off of any loss arising from transfer of virtual digital asset shall be allowed against any income computed under any other provision of the Act and such loss shall not be allowed to be carried forward to subsequent assessment years.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit 3: Most reaction seem to suggest 30% is really harsh. Especially when long term capital gains from stocks is like 10%. 30% will apply for developers and builders too, which will mean they will move to friendly tax jurisdictions rather than remain in India. Seems like a dumb and self defeating policy tbh.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The law taxes not profits but even transfers. So even simple actions like staking or moving funds or using a smart contract would become taxable. This is insane. Projects that originated in India like Polygon are already moving out, experts say most crypto companies will follow suit as a crypto native company doesn&amp;amp;#39;t want to deal with 30% tax for every transaction they make&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Taxation is at 30% of gains if you are investing. If you are earning 100% of your income through crypto (lots of Indian freelancers/developers are, the tax will be at 30% of total income, which is definitely harsh)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit 4: CEX like WazirX and CoinDCX will now automatically report trades to the tax authorities as TDS. This is similar to other TDS tax deducted at source policies.  So if you are using them the gov will now automatically find out about your trades. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;While the tax provisions are definitely bad for Indian users, it creates clarity so now some rich guy with a few millions to spare who was interested in crypto, but waiting on the sidelines wondering if it will be totally prohibited or not can start investing as they know its not prohibited but taxed heavily. Could lead to more Indians getting in (i.e. Le india pamp)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[President Biden to Regulate Bitcoin and the DeFi Sector.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sh8rid/president_biden_to_regulate_bitcoin_and_the_defi/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsh8rid%2Fpresident_biden_to_regulate_bitcoin_and_the_defi%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsh8rid%2Fpresident_biden_to_regulate_bitcoin_and_the_defi%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sh8rid/president_biden_to_regulate_bitcoin_and_the_defi/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 10:34:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Ethereum Still Worth the Investment? A deeper look.]]></title><description><![CDATA[ETHEREUM

2021 was a fantastic year for crypto, in particular Ethereum. Ethereum reigns as
the second-largest blockchain despite the slew of competition from Binance SC,
Solana, Avalanche. But it remains far ahead showcased by various metrics, and
there are no signs of slowing down.

TOTAL…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shiy2o/is_ethereum_still_worth_the_investment_a_deeper/?score=407&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshiy2o%2Fis_ethereum_still_worth_the_investment_a_deeper%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshiy2o%2Fis_ethereum_still_worth_the_investment_a_deeper%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shiy2o/is_ethereum_still_worth_the_investment_a_deeper/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 07:43:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Ethereum&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;2021 was a fantastic year for crypto, in particular Ethereum. Ethereum reigns as &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;the second-largest blockchain&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; despite the slew of competition from Binance SC, Solana, Avalanche. But it remains far ahead showcased by various metrics, and there are no signs of slowing down.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h4&amp;gt;Total Value Locked&amp;lt;/h4&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/coinmonks/use-tvl-to-spot-the-next-hot-coin-crypto-market-update-12-28-dbae6020294a&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;How to use TVL metrics&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Ethereum ended 2021 with a Total Value Locked (TVL) of $153 billion and contains nearly 60% of TVL in crypto. Its nearest competitor Terra (LUNA) TVL, sits at $13.3b with 7% of the market. Despite the hype following emerging L1s they remain far from the king.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/blud071uo4f81.png?width=800&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=0e54dd093d848d7b55536a6f9daa638799116601&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/blud071uo4f81.png?width=800&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=0e54dd093d848d7b55536a6f9daa638799116601&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h4&amp;gt;Revenue&amp;lt;/h4&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Ethereum showcased impressive revenue in 2021 totaling $10.9b. The nearest L1 was BSC, which edged on $1.0b of revenue. There are four projects on Ethereum that post larger revenue than BSC. (Filecoin, Axie, Opensea, Uniswap)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Opensea, an NFT marketplace on Ethereum, saw a revenue of $1.5b in 2021 with the emergence of NFTs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/kkgktdovo4f81.png?width=800&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=0fc1a89d4b528841edba4038faf655798a8dc158&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/kkgktdovo4f81.png?width=800&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=0fc1a89d4b528841edba4038faf655798a8dc158&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h4&amp;gt;Layer 2s on Ethereum&amp;lt;/h4&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Layer 2 protocols are taking traction, benefitting from Ethereum’s &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;reliability and security&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. In the future, Ethereum may be a consensus layer for an extensive array of layer 2s that inherit low gas fees and fast TPS speeds.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some top names are Polygon (MATIC), Optimism, Arbitrum, Loopring (LRC), and ZkSync.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h4&amp;gt;Creator Earnings&amp;lt;/h4&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Typically, creators on centralized networks like YouTube, Spotify, Etsy, and OnlyFans, only capture a portion of the revenue they create. As the creator economy on Ethereum begins to evolve, many creators will start to see the benefits of capturing a larger percentage of value utilizing a decentralized network. NFTs for artists is a prime example. Ethereum, as a whole, competes with prominent names in creator economies.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/bj90vk8xo4f81.png?width=800&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=14b7da6a2f6ce455e71cba02cdddbd46535a31c1&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/bj90vk8xo4f81.png?width=800&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=14b7da6a2f6ce455e71cba02cdddbd46535a31c1&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h4&amp;gt;Eth Burning and Deflationary Pressures&amp;lt;/h4&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EIP — 1559 upgrade has been burned 1.7 million ETH&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;at a valuation of $4.6 billion since early Aug 2021. Before EIP-1559, all ETH would remain on the network. Now, supply decreases with every transaction.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/p137lguyo4f81.png?width=800&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=177950e27231b4b6e071da3636bd78f1faa1757a&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/p137lguyo4f81.png?width=800&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=177950e27231b4b6e071da3636bd78f1faa1757a&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Even though Ethereum remains inflationary, the increasing demand sees days of negative issuance. With ETH continuously being locked away, bought for speculation, and utilized for gas fees, Ethereum’s deflationary pressures will exceed new supply. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/b9548ab0p4f81.png?width=800&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=33d952ac0f6b1adc67a4015195e051ad01038bfd&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/b9548ab0p4f81.png?width=800&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=33d952ac0f6b1adc67a4015195e051ad01038bfd&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h4&amp;gt;Conclusion&amp;lt;/h4&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Ethereum remains far ahead of its competition in almost all metrics. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/coinmonks/electric-capital-developer-report-recap-where-are-the-crypto-developers-going-and-why-its-3855aa5dd1d8&quot;&amp;gt;Moreover, it attracted the highest number of developers in 2021&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; that continue to build the ecosystem.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are a few negatives for Ethereum, no doubt. Ethereum is slow, and gas fees are incredibly high. In addition, environmental mandates are beginning to add pressure to the “proof of work” consensus. But, Ethereum contains scheduled upgrades that will improve speed, lower gas fees, and see a switch to an eco-friendly “proof of stake.” Ethereum Consensus Network (formerly Eth 2.0) will be near completion in approximately one year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, what are we left with?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;The largest and fastest-growing ecosystem in crypto&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt; Significant deflationary pressures&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;The emergence of Layer 2 options &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt; Dwindling supply&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt; Hammered down ETH prices&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt; Upcoming improvement upgrades to the network&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt; The emergence of creator economy (NFTS, DAOs, music, writers, games)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nasdaq.com/articles/cathie-wood%3A-ethereum-will-reach-%2420-trillion-market-cap-by-2030&quot;&amp;gt;It’s no wonder Cathie Wood and her team of quants forecast an ETH price of 180k by 2030&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;2022 will be an important year for &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://etherworld.co/2021/12/02/ethereums-latest-roadmap/&quot;&amp;gt;Ethereum upgrades&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. In the past, upgrades are often delayed and I expect no different this time. But, the process seldom detriments the network. So…&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At its current price of $2680, Ethereum could be a complete steal, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;and far as the risk/reward ratio, it remains one of the best crypto investments&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Gabi&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Follow me on&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@TraderGabi&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Medium&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;or subscribe to this FREE daily newsletter on&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://tradergabi.substack.com/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Substack&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;to receive it first!&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I don't know why, but I believe his logic 🤔]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shhxwn/i_dont_know_why_but_i_believe_his_logic/?score=416&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshhxwn%2Fi_dont_know_why_but_i_believe_his_logic%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshhxwn%2Fi_dont_know_why_but_i_believe_his_logic%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shhxwn/i_dont_know_why_but_i_believe_his_logic/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 05:30:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I see it now. Most of us are neither investors nor traders. We are a bunch of gamblers!]]></title><description><![CDATA[I had a post last day advising people to be either a trader or an investor and
god did it get some crazy reactions! Half of you said we are both. Another half
were pissed (don't tell us what to do!). Out of five hundred comments and more ,
only a handful understood what I was actually saying.

Let…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shh81u/i_see_it_now_most_of_us_are_neither_investors_nor/?score=346&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshh81u%2Fi_see_it_now_most_of_us_are_neither_investors_nor%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshh81u%2Fi_see_it_now_most_of_us_are_neither_investors_nor%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shh81u/i_see_it_now_most_of_us_are_neither_investors_nor/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 04:36:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I had a post last day advising people to be either a trader or an investor and god did it get some crazy reactions!
Half of you said we are both. Another half were pissed (don&amp;amp;#39;t tell us what to do!). Out of five hundred comments and more , only a handful understood what I was actually saying.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let me elaborate:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A trader is someone who is trading on daily basis. A trader does not give a damn if it is bear market or bull market. And only like two people said it in comments. When you say  &amp;amp;quot;I am part trader and part investor, I invest in ETH and buy shitcoins for quick bucks&amp;amp;quot; , you mean that you want something that go up a considerable amount to &amp;amp;quot;then&amp;amp;quot; sell it. 
Let me break it up to you. It is called short term investment! A trader can trade BTC or ETH or any other asset with enough price volatility.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A treader will not go around saying: I bought this much Shib but it is now down 30% so I will hold till it go back.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He will sell &amp;amp;quot;the moment&amp;amp;quot; he understands that market movement is downward. Ofc a trader might have a wallet with some BTC for long term investment in it but he/she is still a trader. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I can confidently say that less than 1% of people in this sub are traders. You know why? Because traders are extremely busy trading. And &amp;amp;quot;they know shit&amp;amp;quot;. I am not a trader but some of my friends are , and they don&amp;amp;#39;t have time for their children&amp;amp;#39;s birthday party.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My point wasn&amp;amp;#39;t &amp;amp;quot;it is impossible to do both.&amp;amp;quot;
Rather &amp;amp;quot;it is impossible to be both.&amp;amp;quot;
Why? Because you need to have two separate mindsets. And in the end one mindset is much more dominant. And we are not skilled enough to be both. At least most of us are not. As some of you put it correctly many of us have a &amp;amp;quot;third mentality&amp;amp;quot; which didn&amp;amp;#39;t came to my mind while writing that post. Most of us are neither a trader bor an investor but rather a &amp;amp;quot;gambler&amp;amp;quot;. 
Why? Because as I told you before traders don&amp;amp;#39;t give a fuck about market&amp;amp;#39;s general trend. And investors are usually extremely calculative and patient.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then it hit me. You were right! We are gamblers.
It explains everything!
That is why we try to quit when we lose money but we always come back.
That is why we have like hundred posts here everyday calling the whole cryptomarket a big scam and this is why the same people will go on buying Elonsperm &amp;amp;quot;anyway&amp;amp;quot;.
That is why everyone here is pissed when market is red and in a good mood when it is green.
Isn&amp;amp;#39;t these acts remind you of something?
Like a gambler who had a bad day at casino?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It seems we are far far away from choosing between being a trader or an investor.
For now it is a great step forward if we quit gamblers mindset.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Respect to you all
Vve&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Quick reminder: Visa, Mastercard and many financial institutions tried to block donations to WikiLeaks while they allowed donations to the Ku Klux Klan]]></title><description><![CDATA[Visa, MasterCard, PayPal, Bank of America and other U.S. financial institutions
began to block donations to WikiLeaks in 2010 after the controversial site began
publishing more than 250,000 U.S. State Department cables. Meanwhile they
allowed donations to the KKK.

The Reykjavík District Court…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sh8lct/quick_reminder_visa_mastercard_and_many_financial/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsh8lct%2Fquick_reminder_visa_mastercard_and_many_financial%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsh8lct%2Fquick_reminder_visa_mastercard_and_many_financial%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sh8lct/quick_reminder_visa_mastercard_and_many_financial/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 04:36:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Visa, MasterCard, PayPal, Bank of America and other U.S. financial institutions began to block donations to WikiLeaks in 2010 after the controversial site began publishing more than 250,000 U.S. State Department cables. Meanwhile they allowed donations to the KKK.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Reykjavík District Court ruled that Valitor, which handles Visa and MasterCard payments in Iceland, was in the wrong when it prevented card holders from donating funds to the site. The court ruled that the block should be removed within 14 days or Valitor will be fined the equivalent of about $6,000 a day.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thanks to Crypto Wikileaks could continue to receive donations.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Up to Dec 2021 the donated amount of Crypto was more than $2.2 million (without Monero).&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
It&amp;amp;#39;s untraceable how much XMR (Monero) the organization has received.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.np.wired.com/2012/07/wikileaks-visa-blockade/&quot;&amp;gt;Source : Blocked donations to Wikileaks&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.constantinereport.com/visa-mastercard-ku-klux-klan-yes-wikileaks-no/&quot;&amp;gt;Source: Visa &amp;amp;amp; Mastercard allowing donations to the KKK&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.cryptopotato.com/wikileaks-has-received-2-2-million-worth-of-donations-in-crypto/&quot;&amp;gt;Source: Crypto Donations to Wikileaks&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trying to explain crypto to a friend made me realize something]]></title><description><![CDATA[Today I was talking to a friend of mine, a really skilled graphic designer that
wanted to try minting NTFs but have basically 0 knowledge about blockchain.

I was trying to explain gas fees, minting, different blockchains, proof of stake
vs proof of work, and suddenly I realized something...…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sha2zp/trying_to_explain_crypto_to_a_friend_made_me/?score=322&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsha2zp%2Ftrying_to_explain_crypto_to_a_friend_made_me%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsha2zp%2Ftrying_to_explain_crypto_to_a_friend_made_me%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sha2zp/trying_to_explain_crypto_to_a_friend_made_me/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 03:35:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Today I was talking to a friend of mine, a really skilled graphic designer that wanted to try minting NTFs but have basically 0 knowledge about blockchain.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I was trying to explain gas fees, minting, different blockchains, proof of stake vs proof of work, and suddenly I realized something... Something that I already knew from school days.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You haven&amp;amp;#39;t really completely understood something unless you can explain that easily to somebody else.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I realized that my knowledge about blockchain and stuff is really scarce, so I&amp;amp;#39;m going to read and study, because not being able to explain in simple words why the fuck stuff works the way it works affects my ability to understand where I&amp;amp;#39;m putting my money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is probably something that is not very interesting for you guys, but maybe other people are in my situation... Let&amp;amp;#39;s dive in and educate ourselves!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[#bitcoin Jan 2022 close $38,491
62% below S2F target and outside 1sd band https://t.co/H6XsAhwVuB]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1488312231255232512/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1488312231255232512/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:37:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2018: lets run for office]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shavnz/2018_lets_run_for_office/?score=617&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshavnz%2F2018_lets_run_for_office%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fshavnz%2F2018_lets_run_for_office%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/shavnz/2018_lets_run_for_office/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:37:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bored Ape Yacht Club NFT Sold for $2.85 million in ETH]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sh86pc/bored_ape_yacht_club_nft_sold_for_285_million_in/?score=333&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsh86pc%2Fbored_ape_yacht_club_nft_sold_for_285_million_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsh86pc%2Fbored_ape_yacht_club_nft_sold_for_285_million_in%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sh86pc/bored_ape_yacht_club_nft_sold_for_285_million_in/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:37:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[El Salvador angrily rejects IMF call to drop Bitcoin use]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/she2t3/el_salvador_angrily_rejects_imf_call_to_drop/?score=337&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshe2t3%2Fel_salvador_angrily_rejects_imf_call_to_drop%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshe2t3%2Fel_salvador_angrily_rejects_imf_call_to_drop%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/she2t3/el_salvador_angrily_rejects_imf_call_to_drop/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:37:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[People talk about CRO *so* much I was shocked to find it at .43 cents. With the explosion of Crypto.com, is there any reason CRO wouldn't keep growing for the long run?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Crypto.com reminds me of the Amazon, Facebook, or Google of the Crypto world.
They are spending billions on advertising, they are clearly in it for the long
haul, they have great name recognition. I have no doubt they will throw their
entire bankroll behind big names to lead their different…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shagkp/people_talk_about_cro_so_much_i_was_shocked_to/?score=355&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshagkp%2Fpeople_talk_about_cro_so_much_i_was_shocked_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fshagkp%2Fpeople_talk_about_cro_so_much_i_was_shocked_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/shagkp/people_talk_about_cro_so_much_i_was_shocked_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 01:37:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto.com reminds me of the Amazon, Facebook, or Google of the Crypto world. They are spending billions on advertising, they are clearly in it for the long haul, they have great name recognition. I have no doubt they will throw their entire bankroll behind big names to lead their different departments. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They will buy up smaller start up technology and continue to put huge amounts of money into anything they do. They seem incredibly proactive and on top of things. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Having said that, is there any reason that Crypto.com would thrive but the CRO coin would fail? Doesn&amp;amp;#39;t seem like they would let it wither away if they as a company are doing great, which they seem to be at the moment...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Denmark just ended Covid restrictions
 https://t.co/tg12nar2CJ]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1488284152256516098/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1488284152256516098/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 23:44:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why did the Danish govt lift all Covid restrictions despite rising case numbers?

State modeller Dr Camilla Holten-Møller explains that Omicron was less severe than other variants, which meant fewer hospitalisations and deaths 👇 
https://t.co/fsWKPJTjxL https://t.co/oSIuRAjXrj]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1488237562317660160/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1488237562317660160/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 23:44:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Litecoin’s biggest Upgrade MWEB is Now Released]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sh7qs3/litecoins_biggest_upgrade_mweb_is_now_released/?score=348&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsh7qs3%2Flitecoins_biggest_upgrade_mweb_is_now_released%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsh7qs3%2Flitecoins_biggest_upgrade_mweb_is_now_released%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sh7qs3/litecoins_biggest_upgrade_mweb_is_now_released/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 23:44:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin is Volatile]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sh65x8/bitcoin_is_volatile/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsh65x8%2Fbitcoin_is_volatile%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsh65x8%2Fbitcoin_is_volatile%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sh65x8/bitcoin_is_volatile/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 22:33:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[why didn't they just raise interest rates by 0.25% ???]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sh5xoh/why_didnt_they_just_raise_interest_rates_by_025/?score=321&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsh5xoh%2Fwhy_didnt_they_just_raise_interest_rates_by_025%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsh5xoh%2Fwhy_didnt_they_just_raise_interest_rates_by_025%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sh5xoh/why_didnt_they_just_raise_interest_rates_by_025/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 22:33:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GoFundMe has frozen $4.5 Million in funds collected by protesting Canadian Truckers. Why anti-government protestors use centralised censorable payment systems over decentralised platforms is beyond me]]></title><description><![CDATA[Canadian trucker convoy raised over $4.5m but all of that was frozen by
GoFundMe.

https://vancouver.citynews.ca/2022/01/25/canada-trucker-convoy-gofundme-frozen/

Centralised payment rails can easily be censored by governments. Using them is
literally asking to get de-platformed. Not just this…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sh7cks/gofundme_has_frozen_45_million_in_funds_collected/?score=436&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsh7cks%2Fgofundme_has_frozen_45_million_in_funds_collected%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsh7cks%2Fgofundme_has_frozen_45_million_in_funds_collected%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sh7cks/gofundme_has_frozen_45_million_in_funds_collected/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 21:33:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Canadian trucker convoy raised over $4.5m but all of that was frozen by GoFundMe.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://vancouver.citynews.ca/2022/01/25/canada-trucker-convoy-gofundme-frozen/&quot;&amp;gt;https://vancouver.citynews.ca/2022/01/25/canada-trucker-convoy-gofundme-frozen/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Centralised payment rails can easily be censored by governments. Using them is literally asking to get de-platformed. Not just this time around, GoFundMe has a history of freezing users funds for a number of reasons. Its just similar to PayPal where you have to jump through hoops just to access the funds sent for your cause. They may not overtly admit it, but a company like GoFundMe must be under a lot of pressure by governments to freeze funds that are meant for anti-government protestors. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If crypto is too volatile for them, they can use decentralised stablecoins to raise funds. Something like DAI can be most useful in this scenario - it cannot be frozen, and can be easily exchanged for fiat. Protests are completely legal in most jurisdictions and these protestors have said they will be using the funds for fuel, food and lodgings in taking part in the convoy - all of which is legal. With a crypto credit card, they can spend their DAI or any other coin for all their activities. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why they dont prefer using crypto payment rails over GoFundMe is bewildering. Maybe crypto platforms need more awareness.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>