<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing on Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 21:24:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[9 Years Ago Someone Tipped 48 Bitcoin to a Redditor using a Reddit-BitcoinTip-Bot, Today Worth over 2 Million Dollars]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s1c14b/9_years_ago_someone_tipped_48_bitcoin_to_a/?score=319&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs1c14b%2F9_years_ago_someone_tipped_48_bitcoin_to_a%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs1c14b%2F9_years_ago_someone_tipped_48_bitcoin_to_a%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s1c14b/9_years_ago_someone_tipped_48_bitcoin_to_a/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 20:34:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Insight from conversations I've had lately with local docs in my area: They're angry &amp; fed up. They see the lies &amp; feel betrayed. 

I couldn't agree more.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480975178171662336/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480975178171662336/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 19:37:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[POWELL: WE PROBABLY REMAIN IN AN ERA OF VERY LOW INTEREST RATES]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480959292027158528/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480959292027158528/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 18:42:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Calling everything in crypto a 'coin' is going to be this generations calling every game console a 'Nintendo']]></title><description><![CDATA[Title says it all, the 90s were dominated by a singular games console, the
Nintendo to the point where they had almost the entire market share of the home
video games field. It go the point where Nintendo became THE word for a games
console for those that had only a passing knowledge of the…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s1ek6i/calling_everything_in_crypto_a_coin_is_going_to/?score=316&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs1ek6i%2Fcalling_everything_in_crypto_a_coin_is_going_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs1ek6i%2Fcalling_everything_in_crypto_a_coin_is_going_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s1ek6i/calling_everything_in_crypto_a_coin_is_going_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 17:45:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Title says it all, the 90s were dominated by a singular games console, the Nintendo to the point where they had almost the entire market share of the home video games field. It go the point where Nintendo became THE word for a games console for those that had only a passing knowledge of the subject.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Fast forward to today and bitcoin is the new Nintendo, it has owned and still owns the lions share of the crypto market. Most people have heard of it and probably think all crypto IS just bitcoin. Now people refer to everything as a &amp;amp;#39;coin&amp;amp;#39; no matter what it actually is.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The next generation are going to be making memes about us here in the present not knowing the difference between a v2000 utility chip and a micro contract smart tokeniser is and instead calling them both, coins while trying to tell them that back in my day we didn&amp;amp;#39;t need any of this new age fancy stuff.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: I&amp;amp;#39;m sure it won&amp;amp;#39;t be long before NFTs are called coins as well.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lessons I’ve learned after 7 years of hodling.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Back in late 2014 I bought my first coins, here’s what I’ve learned since…

 1.  Hodling is simple, but it isn’t easy.
 2.  When you get rich very few will be genuinely happy for you. Try to keep
     your success as quiet as possible.
 3.  Consistency is key.
 4.  DCA + smash buying helps soothe…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s1eo2p/lessons_ive_learned_after_7_years_of_hodling/?score=338&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs1eo2p%2Flessons_ive_learned_after_7_years_of_hodling%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs1eo2p%2Flessons_ive_learned_after_7_years_of_hodling%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s1eo2p/lessons_ive_learned_after_7_years_of_hodling/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 17:45:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Back in late 2014 I bought my first coins, here’s what I’ve learned since… &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Hodling is simple, but it isn’t easy.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;When you get rich very few will be genuinely happy for you. Try to keep your success as quiet as possible.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Consistency is key.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;DCA + smash buying helps soothe emotional volatility.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Have a plan and stick to it. &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;The mainstream news is always hilariously wrong about bitcoin.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Shitcoins are a high risk / high reward proposition.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;DONT TRADE. But If you are going to trade you need to measure your performance in bitcoin terms. &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Mining is a profession, not a hobby. &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Frugality is paramount. If people aren’t laughing at your lifestyle, you probably aren’t hodling or stacking hard enough.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Metaverse fans are paying $300,000 for a virtual property instead of buying a real house]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s1cm44/metaverse_fans_are_paying_300000_for_a_virtual/?score=333&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs1cm44%2Fmetaverse_fans_are_paying_300000_for_a_virtual%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs1cm44%2Fmetaverse_fans_are_paying_300000_for_a_virtual%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s1cm44/metaverse_fans_are_paying_300000_for_a_virtual/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 17:45:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Top 10 crypto stereotypes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 1. Bitcoin maximalist.

Dude lives in 2012 and still believes that all coins that aren’t bitcoin are
scams. He can’t see value in any other project outside bitcoin and worship
people like Michael Saylor. Brags about understanding Austrian school of
economics but never really read Mises. Constantly…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s19tiq/top_10_crypto_stereotypes/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs19tiq%2Ftop_10_crypto_stereotypes%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs19tiq%2Ftop_10_crypto_stereotypes%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s19tiq/top_10_crypto_stereotypes/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 17:45:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Bitcoin maximalist.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Dude lives in 2012 and still believes that all coins that aren’t bitcoin are scams. He can’t see value in any other project outside bitcoin and worship people like Michael Saylor. Brags about understanding Austrian school of economics but never really read Mises. Constantly makes comparisons about energy use of bitcoin vs banks and gold.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;The ethereum dude.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He isn’t a maximalist and actually enjoy other projects, but thinks that ethereum is king. Consider the first mover advantage eth has over smart contracts too much to be overcome by other coins. Keep his coins at the exchange for obvious reasons.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;The Cardano geek.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Usually they follow Charles Hoskinson like a cult. Live in a completely isolated world where all that exists is Cardano. They read through each whitepaper but never read about other projects outside of Cardano. They constantly brag about how Cardano is safe due to Haskell and how fast it can become with Hydra. Don’t really do anything with his Cardano, since there’s nothing to do.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;The solana cheated wife.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He knows the network is centralized. He knows it keeps getting offline. He knows how bad the initial token distribution was. But since he gained some money in Solana, he is always looking for explanations about Solana problems and bragging about a zillion tps.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;The obsessed trader.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He can’t hold one coin for over one month. He’s always checking his charts and always getting hyped about new coins. He says he’s into crypto for the long term but his average holding period is one week. Usually loses money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;The CRO boomer.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Uses the debit card and stake. Believes that CRO will be huge. Don’t understand much about crypto in general, but usually has lots of money and stake all his CRO to get shiny metal cards.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;The moonshooter.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He’s always looking for the “next big thing” and very susceptible to YouTubers and influencers. Constantly shill his shitcoins at Reddit and social media. Usually loses money&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;The FUDster.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The crash is always incoming and he’s always afraid of losing all his money. Deep down he believes that crypto is a Ponzi scheme. Usually he’s at mid-age and hide his crypto investments from his wife. Every 10% dip he thinks the world is gonna end. Constantly talks about Tether.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Buy high and sell low.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He knows the theory but can’t help to the opposite. He always FOMO at ATH and paperhand sell at lows. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;The hodler.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He doesn’t really know much about tech details about the projects he invest in. He doesn’t take profits nor take losses. He doesn’t try to time the market. He just hodl. But that doesn’t stop him from getting hyped up when he has unrealized gains and extremely worried when he has unrealized losses.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do you know anyone that are in these stereotypes ?
Do you identify in one of them ?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;*sorry for any potential grammar mistakes. I’m from Brazil and English is my second language.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dogecoin Creator to Mozilla after Mozilla cancelled crypto donations: "thank you for succumbing to an ignorant, reactionary internet mob"]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0mz45/dogecoin_creator_to_mozilla_after_mozilla/?score=309&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0mz45%2Fdogecoin_creator_to_mozilla_after_mozilla%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0mz45%2Fdogecoin_creator_to_mozilla_after_mozilla%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0mz45/dogecoin_creator_to_mozilla_after_mozilla/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 14:38:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A good captain goes down with the ship]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s18qm2/a_good_captain_goes_down_with_the_ship/?score=385&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs18qm2%2Fa_good_captain_goes_down_with_the_ship%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs18qm2%2Fa_good_captain_goes_down_with_the_ship%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s18qm2/a_good_captain_goes_down_with_the_ship/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 13:32:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alright, I admit it, I work in tech, I have been in crypto for 4 years or so, and I genuinely have no idea what crypto is used for other than an investment or money transfer product. You can make apps on it?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Edit to clarify: I like crypto myself, got a punk rock vibe to it. I just don't
know what all it gets used for. Also the job in tech is internal tools dev at a
medium sized game publisher.

Yep. I think about this constantly, I understand the use case for something like
Bitcoin. Transfer money with…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s1azjd/alright_i_admit_it_i_work_in_tech_i_have_been_in/?score=414&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs1azjd%2Falright_i_admit_it_i_work_in_tech_i_have_been_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs1azjd%2Falright_i_admit_it_i_work_in_tech_i_have_been_in%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s1azjd/alright_i_admit_it_i_work_in_tech_i_have_been_in/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 13:32:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit to clarify: I like crypto myself, got a punk rock vibe to it. I just don&amp;amp;#39;t know what all it gets used for. Also the job in tech is internal tools dev at a medium sized game publisher. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Yep. I think about this constantly, I understand the use case for something like Bitcoin. Transfer money with no middle men. I get that. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What the hell are these other chains supposed to be doing? Half my damn portfolio is Ethereum and I genuinely can&amp;amp;#39;t tell you what your supposed to do with it. Why would you develop an app on a Blockchain? Let alone how. Is there some inherent benefit here? God I have no clue. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For the longest time I just thought it was like providing a decentralized version of something like AWS or Azure, like a grass roots server host. Holy shit I was wrong. There&amp;amp;#39;s all sorts of shit you can make apparently. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But yeah idk. Feels good to come clean. I got into it cause it seemed like a smart investment and so far so good. But I&amp;amp;#39;m amazed I&amp;amp;#39;ve not come across any real application of it in my day to day life so far that I&amp;amp;#39;m aware of at least. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I cannot be alone here right? Please. It&amp;amp;#39;s wild to me that I understand more about the idea behind what an NFT is (supposed to be) used for than any application of any other blockchains. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Idk if anyone else is in this camp and feels dumb you&amp;amp;#39;re not alone. I feel ya.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can someone explain to me how people fall for scams like "Send crypto to this adress to double it"?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Seriously I have seen an alarming amout of posts where people have come to this
sub crying about their mistake/greed after falling for these scams. I am much
younger than the average user of this subreddit and I know for a fact that I
would never fall for such scams.

So these scams go something…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s1a7ft/can_someone_explain_to_me_how_people_fall_for/?score=328&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs1a7ft%2Fcan_someone_explain_to_me_how_people_fall_for%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs1a7ft%2Fcan_someone_explain_to_me_how_people_fall_for%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s1a7ft/can_someone_explain_to_me_how_people_fall_for/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 13:32:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Seriously I have seen an alarming amout of posts where people have come to this sub crying about their mistake/greed after falling for these scams. I am much younger than the average user of this subreddit and I know for a fact that I would never fall for such scams.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So these scams go something like this:-
It&amp;amp;#39;s usually a youtube live video of a conference where Elon Musk, Jack Dorsey or Vitalik Buterin with 12k to 20k live viewers which are bots. These conferences are so old that a simple Google image search if these conference would be enough to know for a fact that it is a scam. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Is it just that people are too greedy? I am only 16 and sometimes wonder that if adults are just money hungry dumb dumbs. Please people do not disappoint me.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit:- Thanks for the awards guys, your noti&amp;amp;#39;s have been lost in the sea of other notifications and I am not able to personally thank you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A Bitcoin "Death Cross" is coming up. Just a reminder that there was a "Golden Cross" a few months ago that led to huge dip. These Technical indicators really mean nothing.]]></title><description><![CDATA[So once again, we have a "Death Cross" looming in the Bitcoin chart.
[https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2022/01/10/bitcoin-approaches-death-cross-as-goldman-foresees-4-fed-rate-hikes-this-year/]
This is a "bearish" indicator that occurs when the 50 day MA dips below the 200
day MA.

I just want to…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s13mx2/a_bitcoin_death_cross_is_coming_up_just_a/?score=374&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs13mx2%2Fa_bitcoin_death_cross_is_coming_up_just_a%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs13mx2%2Fa_bitcoin_death_cross_is_coming_up_just_a%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s13mx2/a_bitcoin_death_cross_is_coming_up_just_a/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 11:39:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So once again, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coindesk.com/markets/2022/01/10/bitcoin-approaches-death-cross-as-goldman-foresees-4-fed-rate-hikes-this-year/&quot;&amp;gt;we have a &amp;amp;quot;Death Cross&amp;amp;quot; looming in the Bitcoin chart.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; This is a &amp;amp;quot;bearish&amp;amp;quot; indicator that occurs when the 50 day MA dips below the 200 day MA. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I just want to remind everyone that these indicators don&amp;amp;#39;t really mean anything, and that they shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t be trusted. Just a few months ago we had a &amp;amp;quot;Golden Cross&amp;amp;quot; which was quickly followed by a dip of the entire crypto market by more than 10%.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;These technical indicators are a reductionist tool used to try to explain the movements of the market in simple terms so that morons can justify their investments. The truth is, nobody knows how the market is going to move.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin can do whatever it wants, I’m never selling.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bitcoin could go up to $150,000 or down to $1,000, either way I’m never going to
sell it. Bitcoin can go to $1,000,000 or down to $0.50, either way I’m never
going to sell it. This is not an asset you sell.

I’m going to get a lot of slack from people who will retort ‘It’s okay to take
profits!’…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0u545/bitcoin_can_do_whatever_it_wants_im_never_selling/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0u545%2Fbitcoin_can_do_whatever_it_wants_im_never_selling%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0u545%2Fbitcoin_can_do_whatever_it_wants_im_never_selling%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0u545/bitcoin_can_do_whatever_it_wants_im_never_selling/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 11:39:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin could go up to $150,000 or down to $1,000, either way I’m never going to sell it. Bitcoin can go to $1,000,000 or down to $0.50, either way I’m never going to sell it. This is not an asset you sell.        &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m going to get a lot of slack from people who will retort ‘It’s okay to take profits!’ ‘Stupid mindset’ ‘No point watching your bags die in winter!’ But they are completely missing the point; missing the point that there is no asset greater worth investing in, there is no harder money, no better store of value protected by decentralized global cryptography, no property that is safer to have and easier to move.         &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyone who sells their Bitcoin is still in the fiat mindset, trapped by it, unable to think outside themselves, ignorant to what sound money is and could be.     &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So go ahead, day trade digital gold for your peasant reserve notes. My keys will be in my will.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[It’s official: I’ve mentally reached the point of not caring about price swings]]></title><description><![CDATA[At the beginning of 2021 I got into crypto and like most newbies I was fomoing
at the top and panic selling on the dips. I eventually got into a good DCA
schedule but that’s when the May crash happened and I ended up down a lot. I
kept buying but I definitely felt sad, defeated, like I might not…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0zny8/its_official_ive_mentally_reached_the_point_of/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0zny8%2Fits_official_ive_mentally_reached_the_point_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0zny8%2Fits_official_ive_mentally_reached_the_point_of%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0zny8/its_official_ive_mentally_reached_the_point_of/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 11:39:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At the beginning of 2021 I got into crypto and like most newbies I was fomoing at the top and panic selling on the dips. I eventually got into a good DCA schedule but that’s when the May crash happened and I ended up down a lot. I kept buying but I definitely felt sad, defeated, like I might not see my money again for 3-4 years. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This used to emotionally affect me a lot. I’d stare at charts all day, wake up at 3am and panic sell, or panic buy. Looking back those short term price swings didn’t matter. All those trades did was made my taxes super complicated to calculate. No matter how many posts I read saying this, the experience of going through it yourself is where you learn the most. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now I’ve finally reached the point where I am not emotionally affected at all, and it feels amazing. If the price goes up? I have enough invested that I’d be happy with the profits. If the price goes down? I have another potentially life changing opportunity to load up on more crypto. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TLDR: Good opportunities are ahead, whether the price goes up or down in the short term&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I want my career earnings to last generations. The average NFL career is 3 years and inflation is real.
Saving and preserving money over time is hard, no matter who you are.
In today’s world: How do we save?
This is why I believe in #bitcoin
Almost all professional athletes make]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480847935726407687/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480847935726407687/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 10:47:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[If you picked up ETH between $2900-3100, that is a good price! It's not cheap, its not expensive, just a solid entry point IMO.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Title says it all, but I know I have to write a bunch of shit here for the post
to get some traction.

Like many of you, I bought this delicious dip. I'm out of money now, but I have
an average ETH buy price of $2984...which I think is pretty good. I'm hodling
this for the intermediate term because…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0wlru/if_you_picked_up_eth_between_29003100_that_is_a/?score=319&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0wlru%2Fif_you_picked_up_eth_between_29003100_that_is_a%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0wlru%2Fif_you_picked_up_eth_between_29003100_that_is_a%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0wlru/if_you_picked_up_eth_between_29003100_that_is_a/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 09:37:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Title says it all, but I know I have to write a bunch of shit here for the post to get some traction.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Like many of you, I bought this delicious dip. I&amp;amp;#39;m out of money now, but I have an average ETH buy price of $2984...which I think is pretty good. I&amp;amp;#39;m hodling this for the intermediate term because I expect the price of ETH to rise as the date for ETH 2.0 (a.k.a. The Merge) draws nearer. Any ETH traders that are shorting right now should definitely make sure you close out before the date is confirmed because the hype will come on fast and you&amp;amp;#39;ll get rekt. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Naturally, there could be another delay in the launch which, to be fair, would not be great. But if you check out the number of commits on github for ETH 2 clients, many reference improvements to clients for the merge which tells me the devs are working hard at it. I like it!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Strap in, its going to be a bumpy but very fun year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[While we're all feeling pain, what's everyone's worst crypto investment?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mine was a shitcoin dex aggregator rugpull called octofi. Got cocky from easy
bull run gains, put about 2k in and sold at about a 90% loss after hodling and
hoping too long.

The signs were there that the project was dead. But I was fooled by getting an
entry 50% below ATH, and seeing a quick 50%…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0zv4y/while_were_all_feeling_pain_whats_everyones_worst/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0zv4y%2Fwhile_were_all_feeling_pain_whats_everyones_worst%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0zv4y%2Fwhile_were_all_feeling_pain_whats_everyones_worst%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0zv4y/while_were_all_feeling_pain_whats_everyones_worst/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 09:37:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Mine was a shitcoin dex aggregator rugpull called octofi. Got cocky from easy bull run gains, put about 2k in and sold at about a 90% loss after hodling and hoping too long. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The signs were there that the project was dead. But I was fooled by getting an entry 50% below ATH, and seeing a quick 50% gain followed by a slow rug. So I held way past  being reasonably certain it was dead. Plus it was shilled by a crypto guy who led me to other actual gems, but I guess it&amp;amp;#39;s true that everyone is a genius in a bull run.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Honorable mention to my friend who fomod into eth in May at 4400, sold for a loss then bought around 4k more recently and sold for a loss again. RIP.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hope this helps everyone feel a little better for the state of affairs we&amp;amp;#39;re all in. What&amp;amp;#39;s your worst crypto story?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: I hope we can all take solace and find solidarity in the fact that most of us have made mistakes and poor choices. And maybe even reflect on what led us to those choices. This game rewards risk takers, and we&amp;amp;#39;re all just one yolo away from a lambo, I think. Not car advice.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thanks for sharing everyone.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit 2: besides obvious (in hindsight) rugs and shitcoins, the most common worst choices are VET, fomoing doge and shib, fomoing CRO (also guilty of this) and buying ADA at peak. And ICP. We&amp;amp;#39;ll do better next time homies.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Are you a dummy?]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s0r8r6/are_you_a_dummy/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs0r8r6%2Fare_you_a_dummy%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs0r8r6%2Fare_you_a_dummy%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s0r8r6/are_you_a_dummy/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 08:46:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Hash Rate vs Price (2010-2022)]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s12p72/bitcoin_hash_rate_vs_price_20102022/?score=316&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs12p72%2Fbitcoin_hash_rate_vs_price_20102022%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs12p72%2Fbitcoin_hash_rate_vs_price_20102022%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s12p72/bitcoin_hash_rate_vs_price_20102022/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 08:46:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Billionaire Investor Bill Miller Now Has 50% of His Personal Wealth in Bitcoin]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s0spu5/billionaire_investor_bill_miller_now_has_50_of/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs0spu5%2Fbillionaire_investor_bill_miller_now_has_50_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs0spu5%2Fbillionaire_investor_bill_miller_now_has_50_of%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s0spu5/billionaire_investor_bill_miller_now_has_50_of/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 06:50:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Every Crypto Sub Is The Same Post Over And Over And I'm Going To Die]]></title><description><![CDATA[Please for the love of God stop lecturing imaginary people about not buying
imaginary past dips and then imaginarily chickening out and not buying this one
either. This is all happening in your mind. You are delusional. You are talking
to yourself. And you are making every crypto sub an annoying…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s13kkd/every_crypto_sub_is_the_same_post_over_and_over/?score=570&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs13kkd%2Fevery_crypto_sub_is_the_same_post_over_and_over%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs13kkd%2Fevery_crypto_sub_is_the_same_post_over_and_over%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s13kkd/every_crypto_sub_is_the_same_post_over_and_over/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 06:50:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please for the love of God stop lecturing imaginary people about not buying imaginary past dips and then imaginarily chickening out and not buying this one either. This is all happening in your mind. You are delusional. You are talking to yourself. And you are making every crypto sub an annoying slog through the same goddam post rephrased in different ways over and over and over, ad infinitum, ad nauseum. It&amp;amp;#39;s boring as hell and you look like morons. Your story has become tiresome. Please, I am begging you: find something more interesting to post about, or go cruise Facebook for awhile.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This single machine is earning more than the average Jamaicans salary.

Yes, its just plugged into a dryer outlet. https://t.co/cqr54GqQQd]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480670415605448707/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480670415605448707/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 03:50:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stop f*cking crying already]]></title><description><![CDATA[I went through the same thing in 2018 as what you guys are going through right
now. I bought my coins in the hype of 2017, and watched my portfolio decline in
early 2018. A 80% decline.

Fast-forward now, 4 years later, I have no stress at all and my portfolio is
still greener than green.

In…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s0t64w/stop_fcking_crying_already/?score=345&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs0t64w%2Fstop_fcking_crying_already%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs0t64w%2Fstop_fcking_crying_already%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s0t64w/stop_fcking_crying_already/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 03:31:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I went through the same thing in 2018 as what you guys are going through right now. I bought my coins in the hype of 2017, and watched my portfolio decline in early 2018. A 80% decline.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Fast-forward now, 4 years later, I have no stress at all and my portfolio is still greener than green.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In short, my advice would be:
- enjoy life
- ignore your portfolio for the coming years 
- and I&amp;amp;#39;ll see a happy you in 2025 ;)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Peace out&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian, Floyd Mayweather, Paul Pierce Sued Over Ethereum Max Promotion]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0tl36/kim_kardashian_floyd_mayweather_paul_pierce_sued/?score=434&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0tl36%2Fkim_kardashian_floyd_mayweather_paul_pierce_sued%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0tl36%2Fkim_kardashian_floyd_mayweather_paul_pierce_sued%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0tl36/kim_kardashian_floyd_mayweather_paul_pierce_sued/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 01:20:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bull markets make you money, Bear markets make you rich]]></title><description><![CDATA[While everyone enjoys bull markets, green candles and the weekly increasing net
worth as it pads their ego, bull markets aren't where you get rich. Bear markets
are the rare opportunity for wealth transfers, and are where crypto millionares
are made. If you loaded up on $90 ETH and $4K BTC during…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0nzhn/bull_markets_make_you_money_bear_markets_make_you/?score=323&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0nzhn%2Fbull_markets_make_you_money_bear_markets_make_you%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0nzhn%2Fbull_markets_make_you_money_bear_markets_make_you%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0nzhn/bull_markets_make_you_money_bear_markets_make_you/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 23:31:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;While everyone enjoys bull markets, green candles and the weekly increasing net worth as it pads their ego, bull markets aren&amp;amp;#39;t where you get rich. Bear markets are the rare opportunity for wealth transfers, and are where crypto millionares are made. If you loaded up on $90 ETH and $4K BTC during the March 2020 dip, or either coin from 2019 til then, you&amp;amp;#39;d still be up a TON. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Buying $40K BTC to sell at $60K during a bull market really isn&amp;amp;#39;t going to change your life. Buying during the fear, panic and capitulation is. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know its hard, but I&amp;amp;#39;d urge you to be calm and excited for a bear market. I doubt we will see an 80-90% dip off ATH, but I HOPE we do. I want to dispose of USD shitcoin and load up on limited supply, lower inflation coins like BTC/ETH, and I have been during this year. But sales and discounts allow you to 10x instead of 2x. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The only reason you should have fear, is if you need this money to pay bills in the next few months. But if you hodl for the long term, you should be very happy that we may have another wealth transfer market on the horizon; transferring wealth from those who can&amp;amp;#39;t afford to wait to those who can. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Good luck.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[If you can't keep bitcoin while it's down 80%, you don't deserve it when it's up 10000%]]></title><description><![CDATA[So this is one of my favourite quotes that keep my diamond hand HODLing BTC,
leave yours!

Edit: Yo guys! Thanks for the responses, no matter showing criticism or support.
I don't really know why people are comparing this situation to being in a toxic
relationship, so I will provide another analogy…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s0lrl4/if_you_cant_keep_bitcoin_while_its_down_80_you/?score=340&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs0lrl4%2Fif_you_cant_keep_bitcoin_while_its_down_80_you%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs0lrl4%2Fif_you_cant_keep_bitcoin_while_its_down_80_you%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s0lrl4/if_you_cant_keep_bitcoin_while_its_down_80_you/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 22:40:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So this is one of my favourite quotes that keep my diamond hand HODLing BTC, leave yours!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: Yo guys! Thanks for the responses, no matter showing criticism or support. I don&amp;amp;#39;t really know why people are comparing this situation to being in a toxic relationship, so I will provide another analogy for the quotes: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You have a partner who you have been together for years. Although financially, he/she might not be doing very good, but you know that he/she is TRYING! That&amp;amp;#39;s the main point, there&amp;amp;#39;ll be a great future if u guys stay together. Leaving your partner who is struggling and when they are down is bad...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So one more here, you&amp;amp;#39;re supporting a football club and you know, they can&amp;amp;#39;t win all the games. If you leave your club and go on supporting other clubs when your old club is in a bad form, then don&amp;amp;#39;t come back when they start winning because you simply don&amp;amp;#39;t like the club true heartedly.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I admit it doesn&amp;amp;#39;t feel good when bitcoin dips, but if u paper-handed, then u wont even have the chance to celebrate the highs. So why not have some hopium!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Veteran Bitcoin Hodler answering question about the markets]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s0jbn8/veteran_bitcoin_hodler_answering_question_about/?score=326&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs0jbn8%2Fveteran_bitcoin_hodler_answering_question_about%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs0jbn8%2Fveteran_bitcoin_hodler_answering_question_about%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s0jbn8/veteran_bitcoin_hodler_answering_question_about/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 22:40:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The CDC director just said over 75% of “covid deaths” occurred in people with at least four comorbidities. Since Biden can’t shut down covid, suddenly all this data is getting shared publicly. https://t.co/NKvproy3lx]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480617724631998467/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480617724631998467/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 20:41:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NEW - Director Walensky says CDC will provide data on "how many of the 836,000 deaths in the U.S. linked to Covid are from Covid or how many are with Covid," and adds "Omicron has just been with us for a few weeks."

https://t.co/Htf1hrfX0F]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480633716875710482/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480633716875710482/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 20:41:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[“What the vaccines can't do anymore is prevent transmission."

CDC Director Walensky

https://t.co/s3BjMVBOub]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480617969390653450/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480617969390653450/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 20:41:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin just dipped below where it was a year ago for the first time in 16 months]]></title><description><![CDATA[Edit: some people seem to misunderstand the title, let's pretend I wrote
"Bitcoin just dipped below where it was a year earlier for the first time in 16
months", maybe that's more understandable?

Edit2: many of you still don't understand what I'm doing here, I'll try again:
when I wrote the post,…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0lmal/bitcoin_just_dipped_below_where_it_was_a_year_ago/?score=339&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0lmal%2Fbitcoin_just_dipped_below_where_it_was_a_year_ago%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0lmal%2Fbitcoin_just_dipped_below_where_it_was_a_year_ago%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0lmal/bitcoin_just_dipped_below_where_it_was_a_year_ago/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 20:40:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Edit: some people seem to misunderstand the title, let&amp;amp;#39;s pretend I wrote &amp;amp;quot;Bitcoin just dipped below where it was a year &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;earlier&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; for the first time in 16 months&amp;amp;quot;, maybe that&amp;amp;#39;s more understandable?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Edit2: many of you still don&amp;amp;#39;t understand what I&amp;amp;#39;m doing here, I&amp;amp;#39;ll try again: when I wrote the post, BTC was lower than a year before that, on January 10th, 2021. Yes, for example on July 21st, 2021 BTC went below 30k and was lower than now - but even at that point BTC was much higher than on July 21st, 2020 (a year earlier), when it was at 9k&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I got into crypto in late 2020. During that whole time, whether BTC was up or down in the past days or weeks, you could always &amp;amp;quot;zoom out&amp;amp;quot;, look at the prices a year ago and see that it was still up a ton compared to then.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For the first time since I got into crypto, this is not the case anymore. At the time I write this, BTC is down 1.5% compared to a year ago, compared to Coingecko. So I got curious: when was the last time BTC was down from a year earlier? So I got the data and looked into how BTC opening prices changed to a year earlier every day since 2013.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To answer the question: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;September 14th, 2020,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; when it was very closely below where it was a year earlier. The last time it was lower than a year earlier for more than a few scattered days was June to July 2020, the last time it was consistently down a lot compared to a year earlier for a long time was in early 2019. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/BfBfXWu&quot;&amp;gt;Here is the data for the past 3 years in an ugly graph&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, you can see it was up for the vast majority of the time and was more than 1,000% up in March 2021 compared to March 2020.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Widening the time frame, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/9BxCR52&quot;&amp;gt;here you can see the whole time frame I analyzed&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, and, not very surprisingly, BTC has also been up compared to a year earlier for the vast majority of the time as well.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some more fun facts:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;BTC was up 8,671% from a year earlier on November 30th, 2013&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;BTC was down 90% from a year earlier on January 16th, 2019&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;during the whole time frame, BTC was up compared to a year earlier for 2634 days and down for 627 days&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;the longest timeframe BTC was continuously up compared to a year earlier was from December 6th, 2015 to October 31st, 2018 (1,060 days)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;the longest timeframe BTC was continuously down compared to a year earlier was from November 16th, 2014 to November 2nd, 2015 (351 days)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you have any questions, please ask!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies will not "kill" fiat and people who think so are ignorant. But, Crypto and Fiat can coexist, and competitiveness in that financial world suits us all]]></title><description><![CDATA[Many "advocates" of cryptocurrencies often say that the revolution is coming to
us and that cryptocurrencies will take down Fiat.

Sometimes individuals remind us that the whole purpose of cryptocurrencies is
that a decentralized financial system allows us freedom and independence from a
third…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0j4bp/cryptocurrencies_will_not_kill_fiat_and_people/?score=309&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0j4bp%2Fcryptocurrencies_will_not_kill_fiat_and_people%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0j4bp%2Fcryptocurrencies_will_not_kill_fiat_and_people%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0j4bp/cryptocurrencies_will_not_kill_fiat_and_people/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 20:40:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Many &amp;amp;quot;advocates&amp;amp;quot; of cryptocurrencies often say that the revolution is coming to us and that cryptocurrencies will take down Fiat.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sometimes individuals remind us that the whole purpose of cryptocurrencies is that a decentralized financial system allows us freedom and independence from a third party as we conduct our transactions.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But still crypto will never replace fiat fully.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto and Fiat will coexist.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Fiat money has been used for longer and is accepted more globally then crypto, but crypto offers many advantages that fiat currencies do not have, especially when we talk about inflation and creating a fair financial system.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Unlike gold that has gold in it and silver that has silver in it ,fiat as paper has worthless paper in it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But the central government gives value to this paper and it exists only because the central government says that it has purchasing power.  Also, with the help of the central power, states preserve power, and thus peace with all manipulation that comes with it.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is precisely those states that will simply never hand over that power, but will jealously guard it, and whatever crypto does, fiat will historically still be there.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto will not replace Fiat, but with cryptocurrencies we get one strong alternative that we can use whenever we want, and banks will therefore have to change their business.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Forget Crypto, the entire stock market could crash in the upcoming months and you should prepare.]]></title><description><![CDATA[As much as I'd love all these signals to be FUD, the truth is, it's not. Even
the Crypto market dipping for the two months is largely due to the stock market
trending down along with energy prices all over the world. People can say what
they want, but the FED has printed way too much money over the…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0oa0j/forget_crypto_the_entire_stock_market_could_crash/?score=493&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0oa0j%2Fforget_crypto_the_entire_stock_market_could_crash%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0oa0j%2Fforget_crypto_the_entire_stock_market_could_crash%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0oa0j/forget_crypto_the_entire_stock_market_could_crash/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 20:40:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As much as I&amp;amp;#39;d love all these signals to be FUD, the truth is, it&amp;amp;#39;s not. Even the Crypto market dipping for the two months is largely due to the stock market trending down along with energy prices all over the world. People can say what they want, but the FED has printed way too much money over the past 18 months. You cannot raise the supply of the USD by 50% and expect no consequences.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Buffet&amp;amp;#39;s Indicator&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/07bsaiv2sva81.png?width=960&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=584a05154be7cee599786270d69ea42e813bdc25&quot;&amp;gt;Buffet Indicator: Anything Above 140&amp;amp;#37; is \&amp;amp;quot;Extreme Danger\&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The way the stock market is booming right now is nothing more than abnormal. The S&amp;amp;amp;P500 alone is &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;100%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; higher than what it was in March 2020 while actual productivity has shrunk with people leaving jobs faster than ever. Moreover, the housing market booming makes zero sense. Houses continue to skyrocket in value faster than the already high inflation rate can keep up.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Companies are also being overvalued by hundreds of times if you compare their profits to the stock market. If you look at Tesla, it is often the most used example of an overvalued company, and even then it pales to some of the most overvalued companies in the market right now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Prof. Dr. Robert Shiller&amp;amp;#39;s Bubble Checklist Made in 2010.&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;1. Sharp increases in the price of an asset like real estate or shares&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;☑&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;2. Great public excitement about said increases&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;   &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;☑&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;3. An accompanying media frenzy&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;☑&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;4. Stories of people earning much money, causing envy among people who are not&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;   &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;☑&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;5. Growing interest in asset class among the general public&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;☑&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;6. ”New era” theories to justify unprecedented price increases&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;   &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;☑&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;7. A decline in lending standards&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;   &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;☑&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;The Illusion of Prosperity&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Every hyperinflationary event is always followed by a fake illusion of prosperity. We&amp;amp;#39;ve seen this happen with the Weimar Republic, Venezuela, Zimbabwe and Lebanon. For example, in the months following hyperinflation in the Weimar Republic, people were becoming wealthier in the millions despite coming out of a war just months earlier. The market was doing so good that it was called the &amp;amp;quot;Golden Twenties&amp;amp;quot; in Germany.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, as the hyperinflation got closer, &amp;amp;quot;The citizenry saw prices going up due to shortages — and as more currency was produced to pay ever-rising union wages — buying activity became a frenzy.&amp;amp;quot; This is very similar to the worker, logistics and countless other shortages we are facing today, this is not normal.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The interest rates of 0.25% by the Fed are also another indication of money supply being overstretched. The interest rates have been kept artificially low for way too long. Any country that has kept interest rates this low has always faced some kind of crash or economic crisis. The US can only do so for so long.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Be Prepared&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Recessions &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;are the inevitable result of the business cycle in a capitalist economy,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; never believe people that say &amp;amp;quot;this time is different,&amp;amp;quot; and be prepared if things go south. Moreover, something even worse than all these indications is the debt level growing right before our eyes which is nearly $30 Trillion and growing exponentially. Moreover, the Nasdaq is already 8% down from it&amp;amp;#39;s ATH, while the S&amp;amp;amp;P500 is 4% down. Maybe the crash comes in a few months or even years.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The best thing you can do right now to protect yourself is to keep an emergency fund that can act as a hedge in the case of hyperinflation or a sudden crash such as Gold or staked Crypto. Always be prepared for the worst because the current state of the economy is eerily similar to what has happened in the past right before a major economic crash.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WISE token and WISB token are scamming investors and stealing their BNB - You should avoid this coin at all cost! (proof inside)]]></title><description><![CDATA[WISE token and WISB are scamming investors of their money and lining their
pockets under the pretense of "development" of over 2 million dollars so far.
When in fact they've been turning it into BUSD, USDC, and various other
cryptocurrencies.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VJVkgGHt33c&t=343s here…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0p455/wise_token_and_wisb_token_are_scamming_investors/?score=344&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0p455%2Fwise_token_and_wisb_token_are_scamming_investors%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0p455%2Fwise_token_and_wisb_token_are_scamming_investors%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0p455/wise_token_and_wisb_token_are_scamming_investors/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 20:40:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;WISE token and WISB are scamming investors of their money and lining their pockets under the pretense of &amp;amp;quot;development&amp;amp;quot; of over 2 million dollars so far. When in fact they&amp;amp;#39;ve been turning it into BUSD, USDC, and various other cryptocurrencies. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VJVkgGHt33c&amp;amp;amp;t=343s&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VJVkgGHt33c&amp;amp;amp;t=343s&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; here is where the scam starts, he states where the coins will go and how the investor earns their yield. Promising to stake the bnb sent to them in return for WISB tokens. So let&amp;amp;#39;s track it and see where these coins went.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Let&amp;amp;#39;s track down where the initial half of the liquidity went to:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;1) Adding liquidity transaction&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://bscscan.com/tx/0xcf9bba00c849ff47f21b908935b02c95e174028af8bc68acb7f4f8401e212993&quot;&amp;gt;https://bscscan.com/tx/0xcf9bba00c849ff47f21b908935b02c95e174028af8bc68acb7f4f8401e212993&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;10,659.53 BNB (half of liquidity was sent)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To 0x88ecfe0a6428a104a8bde2f31ae771ae4d37f6b4 wallet&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Everything is fine here as it was advertised initially.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;2) After this this the wallet sent tokens to 0x1d60202d34444950e7cbad48a37245928e6184f6&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A couple of transaction proofs:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://bscscan.com/tx/0x43465ac119f88408022a97a436de2b32240f4a6d9fca2d37bb9ec6afa40f7de8&quot;&amp;gt;https://bscscan.com/tx/0x43465ac119f88408022a97a436de2b32240f4a6d9fca2d37bb9ec6afa40f7de8&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://bscscan.com/tx/0xae93f3ed2916d74459277711b22b17491339f4d07c005f2a01d02966019e62c8&quot;&amp;gt;https://bscscan.com/tx/0xae93f3ed2916d74459277711b22b17491339f4d07c005f2a01d02966019e62c8&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Check here:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://bscscan.com/txs?a=0x1d60202d34444950e7cbad48a37245928e6184f6&quot;&amp;gt;https://bscscan.com/txs?a=0x1d60202d34444950e7cbad48a37245928e6184f6&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As you can see here BNB were sent to BSC Hub (BNB staking)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;404.002+ 100.002+ 373.032+ 300.002+ 537.002+ 3,800.002+ 1,191.992 = 6,706.034 BNB&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After that, I lost track of where the remaining tokens went to because it was converted to BUSD, binance-peg USD, and mixed between wallets. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;The question is where is the other 3,953.496 BNB? (37% of 10k BNB)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It was initially advertised in videos that all of the 10k will go to BNB staking and rewards will be airdropped to WISB stakers.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some amount from rewards may go to developers&amp;amp;#39; salaries (but has to be reported how much, where, for what, etc).  Does a developer get paid 2 million per year? Lol.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;From what I can see 37% or 3.9k BNB ($2M at current price valuation) was converted to BUSD and USDC. After that was sent to multiple wallets, check it here:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://bscscan.com/token/0xe9e7cea3dedca5984780bafc599bd69add087d56?a=0x1d60202d34444950e7cbad48a37245928e6184f6&quot;&amp;gt;https://bscscan.com/token/0xe9e7cea3dedca5984780bafc599bd69add087d56?a=0x1d60202d34444950e7cbad48a37245928e6184f6&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://bscscan.com/token/0x55d398326f99059ff775485246999027b3197955?a=0x1d60202d34444950e7cbad48a37245928e6184f6&quot;&amp;gt;https://bscscan.com/token/0x55d398326f99059ff775485246999027b3197955?a=0x1d60202d34444950e7cbad48a37245928e6184f6&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;- plus some of BNB was converted to random tokens, added liquidity, and moved around inside (liquidity beneficiary) wallet:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://bscscan.com/address/0x88ecfe0a6428a104a8bde2f31ae771ae4d37f6b4&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;https://bscscan.com/address/0x88ecfe0a6428a104a8bde2f31ae771ae4d37f6b4&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hmm? Do they not realize we can see these transactions on a public ledger? This is literally the point of blockchain technology, are we that stupid? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As you can see in the videos Peter says that all BNB will go to staking.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Really 37% are gone to his &amp;amp;quot;development&amp;amp;quot; 2 million on development? Lol what are they developing for 2 million? Their wallets thats what.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And it is not clear if all rewards from staking are airdropped because he says $30k are airdropped weekly, however staking rewards can&amp;amp;#39;t be exactly $30k in value, excess of that must be cut to his wallets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TL;DR the team is lining their pockets whilst leading on investors and essentially money-grabbing under the pretense of development.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Who else stopped giving a fuck about their losses?]]></title><description><![CDATA[This will be seen as Hopium. But it's not. This volatility will be just a blip
in the long run.

I still believe in crypto no matter how many FUDs and bearish post got upvoted
to frontpage. This is a rare chance to get a life changing wealth and I will
never forgive myself if I didn't take my…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0mpq3/who_else_stopped_giving_a_fuck_about_their_losses/?score=488&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0mpq3%2Fwho_else_stopped_giving_a_fuck_about_their_losses%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0mpq3%2Fwho_else_stopped_giving_a_fuck_about_their_losses%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0mpq3/who_else_stopped_giving_a_fuck_about_their_losses/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 16:53:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This will be seen as &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Hopium&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. But it&amp;amp;#39;s not. This volatility will be just a blip in the long run.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I still believe in crypto no matter how many FUDs and bearish post got upvoted to frontpage. This is a rare chance to get a life changing wealth and I will never forgive myself if I didn&amp;amp;#39;t take my shot.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know we&amp;amp;#39;re all in crypto for the money. But it&amp;amp;#39;s &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;much easier to HODL&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and keep DCAing if you understand what Bitcoin and other good cryptos are trying to achieve.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So take time off the chart to learn more about blockchain tech, DeFi, how banks fucked the economy in 2008, etc.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I will just keep my DCA on 1st and 13th every month.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[If you get 3-4 shots of the same thing in 1 year, and you still get infected and transmit the pathogen, then please don’t call it a vaccine. Call it whatever you like, but don’t call it a vaccine.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480552858969858048/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480552858969858048/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 15:45:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I'm scared, and I'm tired of pretending I'm not]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know, I know, this will be seen as FUD. But it's not. I firmly believe we will
get better in the mid to long term.

But this is just reminding me of 2018 too much. Day after day, week after week,
my portfolio is losing a few %. With no end in sight. And the reasons are pulled
out of thin air.…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0jqoy/im_scared_and_im_tired_of_pretending_im_not/?score=328&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0jqoy%2Fim_scared_and_im_tired_of_pretending_im_not%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0jqoy%2Fim_scared_and_im_tired_of_pretending_im_not%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0jqoy/im_scared_and_im_tired_of_pretending_im_not/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 15:45:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know, I know, this will be seen as FUD. But it&amp;amp;#39;s not. I firmly believe we will get better in the mid to long term.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But this is just reminding me of 2018 too much. Day after day, week after week, my portfolio is losing a few %. With no end in sight. And the reasons are pulled out of thin air. September slump, November shenanigans, Christmas shopping, you name it. Now in 2022, I&amp;amp;#39;m just waiting for the same ol&amp;amp;#39; sayings from 2018. Chinese new year, wall street bonuses, January to end, March madness, and whatever idiotic saying there was to explain something that cannot be explained.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now with the FED rates raised (and more rates raised foreseen), I just can&amp;amp;#39;t help but feel... defeated.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I didn&amp;amp;#39;t invest more than I&amp;amp;#39;m willing to lose. I will not suffer financially if I lose EVERYTHING I have in crypto. That said, does anyone here LIKE losing any money?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know it&amp;amp;#39;s volatile. That&amp;amp;#39;s why I love crypto. But this seems like it has no end in sight. And it just smells like 2018 all over again. And I just fall into this slump of how I felt back then. 10-20% dump daily. Going on for days and weeks. BTC was down 80% from ATH. All other alts over 90% (yes, even ETH). It&amp;amp;#39;s terribly exhausting.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Maybe I&amp;amp;#39;ll feel better smack down in the middle of bear run. That way I know there&amp;amp;#39;s no other option but to buy/DCA and stake. But now... I&amp;amp;#39;m scared.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: Thank you for the awards (really not necessary), kind words, words of re-assurance, people calling me female genitalia and whoever said to &amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;be scared more quietly&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;. That one made my day. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[If Bitcoin was at $100K right now, people would be asking for another chance to buy under 50K. Now that we are under 50K they don’t want it.]]></title><description><![CDATA[As the title says now that we are under 50k people are waiting to buy under 40k.
People always panic to buy when market is at extreme fear while the extreme fear
is what we wished for when market was pumping like crazy.

Every 40-50% correction people panic to buy thinking what if it’s a bear…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0jy5e/if_bitcoin_was_at_100k_right_now_people_would_be/?score=943&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0jy5e%2Fif_bitcoin_was_at_100k_right_now_people_would_be%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0jy5e%2Fif_bitcoin_was_at_100k_right_now_people_would_be%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0jy5e/if_bitcoin_was_at_100k_right_now_people_would_be/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 15:45:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As the title says now that we are under 50k people are waiting to buy under 40k. People always panic to buy when market is at extreme fear while the &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;extreme fear&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; is what we wished for when market was pumping like crazy. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Every 40-50% correction people panic to buy thinking what if it’s a bear market then I can buy way lower than that. These are the people who always ask for the &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Dip Dip&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; but never bought the dip. When it&amp;amp;#39;s actually arrived. If you are here for long term every correction is a huge opportunity we were asking for when market was extreme greed. I don’t know if it’s a bear market or not but I know it’s a good opportunity to buy low.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is 0.28 BTC still an noble/achievable goal for the average person?]]></title><description><![CDATA[In terms of long term wealth building, eventual payoff, and safety net?

The 0.28 number seems to always be thrown around, but is there a consensus on
whether it's still relevant?

When people ask me questions about BTC, I always respond with "one if you can
afford it, or as much as you can until…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s09lc6/is_028_btc_still_an_nobleachievable_goal_for_the/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs09lc6%2Fis_028_btc_still_an_nobleachievable_goal_for_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs09lc6%2Fis_028_btc_still_an_nobleachievable_goal_for_the%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s09lc6/is_028_btc_still_an_nobleachievable_goal_for_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 15:45:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In terms of long term wealth building, eventual payoff, and safety net?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The 0.28 number seems to always be thrown around, but is there a consensus on whether it&amp;amp;#39;s still relevant?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When people ask me questions about BTC, I always respond with &amp;amp;quot;one if you can afford it, or as much as you can until then,&amp;amp;quot; but this doesn&amp;amp;#39;t seem to stick with people as much as exact numbers.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I try to never give investment/financial advice unless people directly ask for it, but of course when it comes to Bitcoin people are either fascinated or laugh it off. Is 0.28 still a number worth bringing up as an achievable goal for newbies?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Throwback to when this Sub was celebrating BTC hitting $2,000 ATH in 2017 - We should be extremely grateful for $40,000]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s057m2/throwback_to_when_this_sub_was_celebrating_btc/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs057m2%2Fthrowback_to_when_this_sub_was_celebrating_btc%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs057m2%2Fthrowback_to_when_this_sub_was_celebrating_btc%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s057m2/throwback_to_when_this_sub_was_celebrating_btc/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 15:45:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Salvadoran Bitcoin miners powered by volcano geothermal.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s0jc7i/salvadoran_bitcoin_miners_powered_by_volcano/?score=392&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs0jc7i%2Fsalvadoran_bitcoin_miners_powered_by_volcano%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs0jc7i%2Fsalvadoran_bitcoin_miners_powered_by_volcano%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s0jc7i/salvadoran_bitcoin_miners_powered_by_volcano/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 14:40:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Warning: Dont use DESO, allegedly a "decentralised social network". It asks to enter your seed to login, and whats worse - they store your seed in plaintext locally.]]></title><description><![CDATA[DeSo is supposedly a decentralised social media platform that has recently
launched its token without even a platform yet.

When creating an account, it asks to enter your seed to login.

Sign up with…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0fqa7/warning_dont_use_deso_allegedly_a_decentralised/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0fqa7%2Fwarning_dont_use_deso_allegedly_a_decentralised%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0fqa7%2Fwarning_dont_use_deso_allegedly_a_decentralised%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0fqa7/warning_dont_use_deso_allegedly_a_decentralised/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 14:40:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;DeSo is supposedly a decentralised social media platform that has recently launched its token without even a platform yet. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When creating an account, it asks to enter your seed to login. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/fu0dsrxoqta81.jpg?width=1540&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=95280a2b5b642d8cc9720f054e565de1d6c03125&quot;&amp;gt;Sign up with seed&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Yeah.. sure jan. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is such a horrible security practice that just doesnt need any explanation. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Definitely, nothing untoward can happen by entering your seed to login everytime.. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Oh wait.. they themselves prove how it could go horribly wrong.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Not only do you have to enter the seed, they are storing the seed in plaintext locally&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/6daob58frta81.jpg?width=1364&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9d14ad1888df882dbd70864c84197a5b63a7dd14&quot;&amp;gt;Seed stored in plaintext&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This horrendous security practice was noticed by user Nptacek. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The whole platform stinks tbh, if you go to their home page, its full of buy their shitcoin links instead of an actual social network. Decentralised social media networks like Mirror and GM already exist that do not have any token and can be used already. Mirror especially is growing in popularity as an alternative to Medium among crypto users. It doesnt have any token, and only uses Metamask to verify the authenticity of your account. For example Vitalik could verify himself with his ENS address. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Whereas DESO seems to be only interesting in pushing their token first and has a market cap of over $650m without even a functional product. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why should I buy a token to use a decentralised social media network first?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Expert warns against buying the dip.” Ok, it’s time to buy more.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0eo5y/expert_warns_against_buying_the_dip_ok_its_time/?score=339&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0eo5y%2Fexpert_warns_against_buying_the_dip_ok_its_time%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0eo5y%2Fexpert_warns_against_buying_the_dip_ok_its_time%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0eo5y/expert_warns_against_buying_the_dip_ok_its_time/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 14:40:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cardano Reaches Goal of Planting 1M Trees]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0hxtd/cardano_reaches_goal_of_planting_1m_trees/?score=639&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0hxtd%2Fcardano_reaches_goal_of_planting_1m_trees%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs0hxtd%2Fcardano_reaches_goal_of_planting_1m_trees%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s0hxtd/cardano_reaches_goal_of_planting_1m_trees/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 13:39:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[It is a lot better to walk alone than with a crowd going in the wrong direction.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480498127627067397/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480498127627067397/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 12:51:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[So we have an upcoming eventual mega market crash - stocks/sp500/nasdaq composite index which will simply obliterate BTC and on the other hand we have Jeff Booth, Greg Foss, Michael Saylor and the rest of the mega bulls saying it's pure math and a matter of time before BTC 200-300k+! Let's discuss!]]></title><description><![CDATA[So US Government decides to increase yield on bonds , reduce reckless money
printing and a bunch of other decisions that will eventually make stock
investors move a lot of their money from stocks to bonds. Basically stocks
become kind of a risky and uncertain assets while bonds become the…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rzzq32/so_we_have_an_upcoming_eventual_mega_market_crash/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frzzq32%2Fso_we_have_an_upcoming_eventual_mega_market_crash%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frzzq32%2Fso_we_have_an_upcoming_eventual_mega_market_crash%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rzzq32/so_we_have_an_upcoming_eventual_mega_market_crash/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 11:31:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So US Government decides to increase yield on bonds , reduce reckless money printing and a bunch of other decisions that will eventually make stock investors move a lot of their money from stocks to bonds. Basically stocks become kind of a risky and uncertain assets while bonds become the opposite, safe haven, almost zero risk and guaranteed yield. That will eventually crash stocks/sp500 and so on. Understandably this means all huge institutional investors will take their money out of BTC. At best we are expecting another 2-3 to 4 year bear market before markets start to recover. BTC may as well go 10k under easily and stay there for a long time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On the other hand Jeff Booth and  Greg Floss may say that government can reduce money printing and improve bonds yields but that&amp;amp;#39;s just  temporary and eventually they will have to start printing lots of money again to avoid stock markets to crash because nobody wants that. Also they may say inflation is going to get worse and worse due to the money printing and the best bet against inflation is Bitcoin.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But my opinion is that Bitcoin is not dependant on reddit users/bitcoin forums/youtube gurus etc. It&amp;amp;#39;s dependant on the big money! And big money is controlled mostly by people who consider BTC a very risky asset! (of course with the exceptions of Saylor, Cathie Wood and the early BTC Whales who have diamond hands for lifetime)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So I&amp;amp;#39;m thinking who exactly is going to put a lot of money in Bitcoin in a market crisis where stock are going down by 50% and more in a couple of weeks/months. Who is going to risk it? Also is US Government really able to prevent another mega stock market crash? Nasdaq Composite Index is currently at all time highs up around 600% from 2010!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let&amp;amp;#39;s discuss this topic until we figure out every possible scenario!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Who else is in this cycle ?]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s00nfx/who_else_is_in_this_cycle/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs00nfx%2Fwho_else_is_in_this_cycle%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs00nfx%2Fwho_else_is_in_this_cycle%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s00nfx/who_else_is_in_this_cycle/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 11:31:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why I'm going to start taking profit (and you should too)]]></title><description><![CDATA[+205%

That's how much my portfolio had gained at one point last year.

Life was really looking up. I had hit my goal for crypto gains for the year and
I considered taking some profits.

"Maybe just my initial investment," I thought to myself.

But no, I'm a HODLer. I believe in the tech long term.…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s049st/why_im_going_to_start_taking_profit_and_you/?score=318&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs049st%2Fwhy_im_going_to_start_taking_profit_and_you%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs049st%2Fwhy_im_going_to_start_taking_profit_and_you%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s049st/why_im_going_to_start_taking_profit_and_you/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 11:31:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;+205%&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;That&amp;amp;#39;s how much my portfolio had gained at one point last year.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Life was really looking up. I had hit my goal for crypto gains for the year and I considered taking some profits.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Maybe just my initial investment,&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; I thought to myself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But no, I&amp;amp;#39;m a HODLer. I believe in the tech long term. I believe that the coins I&amp;amp;#39;m invested in, will in 5-10 years time form the foundations of decentralised AI, finance and web3.0 infrastructure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m likely to see a bear market or dip soon&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; but who cares?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The short-term dips won&amp;amp;#39;t matter in 5 years time!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;These kinds of gains take years in the stock market, and I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen them in less than a year&amp;amp;quot;.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; I was naive, waking up to my portfolio at higher highs every morning.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;-8%&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;That&amp;amp;#39;s my portfolio today.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;All those unrealised gains, lost. Everything that was once beautiful flourishing green, is red like the blood of a slaughtered goat.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I considered selling some of my gains at the top, but I was too greedy. I wanted more. Had I taken some profits, I would&amp;amp;#39;ve had the opportunity to buy in at much lower prices.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;What am I going to do?&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m still HODLing.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; But I&amp;amp;#39;ve decided during the next bull run, I will take profit &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;(nothing massive, the initial investment or less)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and hold those funds in wait for a significant dip. The dips do come and will come and I think it really benefits your mental health to be able to take some amount of profit.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[OOPS! US 10y yields jump &gt;1.80% for 1st time since Jan2020. US #inflation data out on Wed will be keenly watched as concerns grow the Fed is behind the curve in tackling elevated price pressures. US CPI may have accelerated to 7% in Dec. https://t.co/3uWeCz2QwM]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480469788463935489/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480469788463935489/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 10:37:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This dip is a blessing for those who believe in ₿Itcoin’s long term value]]></title><description><![CDATA[If you actually believe in ₿Itcoin’s inherit value in a world of infinitely
printed fiat with a user-base growing at twice the speed of the internet’s
user-base growth, a majority of all are dollar cost averaging their income of
infinitely printed fiat into ₿Itcoin’s finite Satoshi supply, then you…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s051aw/this_dip_is_a_blessing_for_those_who_believe_in/?score=322&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs051aw%2Fthis_dip_is_a_blessing_for_those_who_believe_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs051aw%2Fthis_dip_is_a_blessing_for_those_who_believe_in%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s051aw/this_dip_is_a_blessing_for_those_who_believe_in/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 10:34:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you actually believe in ₿Itcoin’s inherit value in a world of infinitely printed fiat with a user-base growing at twice the speed of the internet’s user-base growth, a majority of all are dollar cost averaging their income of infinitely printed fiat into ₿Itcoin’s finite Satoshi supply, then you love these dips. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“The ignorance of the majority is your opportunity.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are corporations and nations adopting it. This is bigger than any sights I saw of Bitcoin’s potential of success ten years ago, so I’m even more excited about its future now than I was then buying the dips and subscribing to this model of though. So take advantage and buy while the world is ignorance. All this now means today is that you’re still plenty early.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When Bitcoin’s drops are only ten percent from its all time highs, that’s when you know you’ll be late ish and it’s returns long term will be no where near where it’s long term returns are today&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Satoshi speed new guys and OGs. Let’s use the world’s ignorance today to our advantage and stack the sats that they’re too ignorant to today to value&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>