<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing on Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 19:25:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[In less than 4 words describe, your game plan in the market?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Title is super self explanatory, i just thought this would be interesting. Here
are 5 top crypto strategies worth noting. Good Luck!

Day Trading - As a digital asset investor, you should be familiar with various
resources and strategies. Basically, there are two types of trading strategies
you can…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rzlpre/in_less_than_4_words_describe_your_game_plan_in/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frzlpre%2Fin_less_than_4_words_describe_your_game_plan_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frzlpre%2Fin_less_than_4_words_describe_your_game_plan_in%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rzlpre/in_less_than_4_words_describe_your_game_plan_in/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 18:40:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Title is super self explanatory, i just thought this would be interesting. Here are 5 top crypto strategies worth noting. Good Luck!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Day Trading&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;  - As a digital asset investor, you should be familiar with various resources and strategies. Basically, there are two types of trading strategies you can choose from. Active, which requires more time and attention and involves constant monitoring, and passive, which allows for a more hands-off approach.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Trend Tading&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - One of the active strategies, trend trading, also sometimes known as position trading, is a tactic in which an investor will hold their position for a longer span of time, usually a few months. If you choose to be a trend trader, you need to keep up with directional trends and know how to take advantage of them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Scalping&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - The last active strategy on our list is scalping, which focuses on small moves repeated over and over again and taking advantage of inefficiencies in the market such as gaps in liquidity. Scalpers open and close their positions in a short period of time, sometimes even in a matter of seconds.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;HODL&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - If none of the active strategies seem like something you would be interested in, you might explore passive ones such as the buy and hold strategy. In this strategy, investors purchase a large sum of assets and hold it for a long time without paying attention to market fluctuations.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Index Investing&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - Finishing off with another passive investment strategy, index investing focuses on buying ETFs, which you can purchase on centralized cryptocurrency exchanges. You can create a crypto index by creating a basket of all of your assets and then making a special token that will track their combined performance.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fiat is mass formation psychosis.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rzpp7p/fiat_is_mass_formation_psychosis/?score=360&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frzpp7p%2Ffiat_is_mass_formation_psychosis%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frzpp7p%2Ffiat_is_mass_formation_psychosis%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rzpp7p/fiat_is_mass_formation_psychosis/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 17:33:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Forgot my old wallet, turns out it had 1BTC inside, HODL = WIN]]></title><description><![CDATA[Found the seed of my old wallet (before coldstorage)

I'm ecstatic, I thought I emptied everything our to my cold wallets

Value in 2020 was just under 10k, value now it's over 40k!

30k profit just by hodling (forgetting ;)) your coins. Why are people being
scared they'll lose some fiat? Just wait…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rzn269/forgot_my_old_wallet_turns_out_it_had_1btc_inside/?score=342&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frzn269%2Fforgot_my_old_wallet_turns_out_it_had_1btc_inside%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frzn269%2Fforgot_my_old_wallet_turns_out_it_had_1btc_inside%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rzn269/forgot_my_old_wallet_turns_out_it_had_1btc_inside/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 17:33:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Found the seed of my old wallet (before coldstorage)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m ecstatic, I thought I emptied everything our to my cold wallets&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Value in 2020 was just under 10k, value now it&amp;amp;#39;s over 40k!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;30k profit just by hodling (forgetting ;)) your coins. Why are people being scared they&amp;amp;#39;ll lose some fiat? Just wait 2 years and check your assets again.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you don&amp;amp;#39;t convert you don&amp;amp;#39;t lose, it&amp;amp;#39;s that simple!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/bjxx9z02jma81.jpg?width=981&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9b7b93d08b5dda80461ddca081a1306ac8d4defa&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/bjxx9z02jma81.jpg?width=981&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9b7b93d08b5dda80461ddca081a1306ac8d4defa&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[So we are firmly in Stage 4 of the markets dropping.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Stage 1: People refer to a large, sudden, and unexplainable drop in price as a
'correction', anyone referring to it as a crash gets shunned.

Stage 2: People start responding to any question with 'just don't look at the
charts all the time' and get offended when people want to talk about crypto on…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rzu4kl/so_we_are_firmly_in_stage_4_of_the_markets/?score=397&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frzu4kl%2Fso_we_are_firmly_in_stage_4_of_the_markets%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frzu4kl%2Fso_we_are_firmly_in_stage_4_of_the_markets%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rzu4kl/so_we_are_firmly_in_stage_4_of_the_markets/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 17:33:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Stage 1: People refer to a large, sudden, and unexplainable drop in price as a &amp;amp;#39;correction&amp;amp;#39;, anyone referring to it as a crash gets shunned.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Stage 2: People start responding to any question with &amp;amp;#39;just don&amp;amp;#39;t look at the charts all the time&amp;amp;#39; and get offended when people want to talk about crypto on a crypto subreddit.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Stage 3: Some people start using the word crash without being downvoted while others are confident that it will be going back up soon.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Stage 4: People are now confident that it will definitely be going lower and will always go lower, the crypto dream is dead and so is the stock market. Everything is ruined. Other times the market has gone down get referenced constantly. The phrase &amp;amp;#39;crypto winter&amp;amp;#39; starts being repeated frequently.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Stage 5: EVERY question gets answered with &amp;amp;#39;we don&amp;amp;#39;t know shit about fuck&amp;amp;#39;. Some people start commenting &amp;amp;#39;go outside and touch grass&amp;amp;#39; to every post no matter the context.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Final Boss Stage: The suicide hotline number gets posted.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This down market shows why hamsters are better investors than most humans.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Mr Goxx the crypto trading hamster had performed better than most human
investors at the same time period.

How did a fukin hamster was able to bit your average crypto investors ? What'
the secret ?

Just look at the reactions of most cryptonuts of this sub during the ongoing
market carsh and you…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rzpxwr/this_down_market_shows_why_hamsters_are_better/?score=313&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frzpxwr%2Fthis_down_market_shows_why_hamsters_are_better%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frzpxwr%2Fthis_down_market_shows_why_hamsters_are_better%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rzpxwr/this_down_market_shows_why_hamsters_are_better/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 17:33:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Mr Goxx the crypto trading hamster had performed better than most human investors at the same time period.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How did a fukin hamster was able to bit your average crypto investors ? What&amp;amp;#39; the secret ?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just look at the reactions of most cryptonuts of this sub during the ongoing market carsh and you will find your answer.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A hamster can&amp;amp;#39;t read and so doesn&amp;amp;#39;t know anything about bull markets, bear markets or crab markets. Unlike humans their investment process is not emotionally hampered by the fear and greed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hamsters are not suceptible to FUD fear, uncertainty and doubt. They are not going to YOLO their lifesavings to buy a pupcum coin at ATH because of FOMO.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Unlike most of us hamsters don&amp;amp;#39;t buy high and sell low because of FOMO and fear.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Be like a hamster and free yourself from the emotions caused by regular checking charts and watching too much YouTube influencers.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You know that having a good strategy and following it religiously is the only way that can do better than a fookin hamster.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto has a major problem, and that's poor user experience design]]></title><description><![CDATA[I see great potential in crypto to be the next paradigm shift that transforms
the global economy. Though, as a UI Designer and UX Researcher, most crypto
products make no sense to the average user—they're complex, cumbersome, and
require a ton of focused knowledge to not lose money.

Many of my…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rzmssf/crypto_has_a_major_problem_and_thats_poor_user/?score=327&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frzmssf%2Fcrypto_has_a_major_problem_and_thats_poor_user%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frzmssf%2Fcrypto_has_a_major_problem_and_thats_poor_user%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rzmssf/crypto_has_a_major_problem_and_thats_poor_user/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 16:33:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I see great potential in crypto to be the next paradigm shift that transforms the global economy. Though, as a UI Designer and UX Researcher, most crypto products make no sense to the average user—they&amp;amp;#39;re complex, cumbersome, and require a ton of focused knowledge to not lose money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Many of my colleagues, friends and others alike have told me they&amp;amp;#39;ve tried a ton of different apps to get into crypto and it&amp;amp;#39;s been difficult. The apps ask for a lot of info, there&amp;amp;#39;s a ton of charts, random numbers, obscure percentages, plenty of colorful logos... Even though I know exactly what they&amp;amp;#39;re referring to, it&amp;amp;#39;s overwhelming for them to hear me explain the fundamentals of private keys, public keys, liquidity pools, volatility, yield, hodling, DeFi, staking, gas fees, minting, tokens—among many others. We simply cannot expect wide-scale adoption for even one billion people if they need to know what all these mean.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Product designers in crypto have done a good job at translating the needs of the software engineers and the needs of their respective organizations, but only a few companies have focused on effortless user-friendly experiences. Some have come close ((which I do applaud them!)), but compare the design of popular crypto apps to that of popular apps in other categories; eg. Instagram, Twitter, YouTube, Messenger. These companies have honed their experience design to accommodate all types of people globally (regardless of their differences). Those who have no knowledge of how a story works, or how a message is sent, or how to find an album, can easily hop on to these apps and figure it out in seconds. This experience design has developed so strongly over the years that they&amp;amp;#39;ve found ways to keep user&amp;amp;#39;s eyes glued to their screens for hours on end. Some design aspects even become part of popular culture, like Tinder&amp;amp;#39;s swipe left or swipe right.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We&amp;amp;#39;re currently at peak &amp;amp;#39;hype&amp;amp;#39; levels with Web3 and DeFi. Even though I love the idea of it taking over, I don&amp;amp;#39;t believe it&amp;amp;#39;s ready for the scale we want it to be. We&amp;amp;#39;re going to need top-tier design strategies. Do consider that there are still people in the present day that struggle to do basic tasks on their computer or phone—and I&amp;amp;#39;m pretty sure we&amp;amp;#39;ve all met plenty before—we need to design for people like this in mind. I&amp;amp;#39;m an Android guy personally, but Apple has done exceptionally well in product design that flows throughout its ecosystem of apps and devices. It&amp;amp;#39;s straightforward and gets the job done. Yes there are questionable hiccups here and there, but for the most part, it&amp;amp;#39;s pretty seamless and it works for the masses. These are models we should follow.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Good design is beautiful but &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;great&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; design is invisible.
The moment a person has to pause &amp;amp;amp; search up how to do something in an app, that immediately decreases their interest &amp;amp;amp; their long-term retention. Invisible design shows that a user can get their tasks done without having to focus in on individual elements.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Essentially, I want to get to the point where I can suggest a friend, colleague or a family member a crypto app and I don&amp;amp;#39;t have to explain anything to them, they&amp;amp;#39;ll be able to figure everything out within minutes after downloading. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And for the note I like the simplified approach of Strike. It&amp;amp;#39;s visually bland but it succeeds its goal. It&amp;amp;#39;s had extreme success in El Salvador, where less fortunate communities use Bitcoin for daily transactions. Truly an app where no special prior knowledge is needed. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Open to your thoughts, please let me know if there&amp;amp;#39;s anything I missed or touched on in an odd way.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Airbnb may implement bitcoin and cryptocurrencies payments in 2022]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rzftnf/airbnb_may_implement_bitcoin_and_cryptocurrencies/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frzftnf%2Fairbnb_may_implement_bitcoin_and_cryptocurrencies%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frzftnf%2Fairbnb_may_implement_bitcoin_and_cryptocurrencies%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rzftnf/airbnb_may_implement_bitcoin_and_cryptocurrencies/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 15:39:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This sub is the best place for entertainment and crypto news, but the worst place for advice. Don’t come here if you need advice.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Today, one half of the experts of this sub seem sure that we have entered a bear
market while the other half is sure this dip is nothing but a tiny hiccup and
are advising everyone to BTFD. In the coming days, when one of the two things
will play out, one half of our r/cc [/r/cc] experts will jump…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rzoq1i/this_sub_is_the_best_place_for_entertainment_and/?score=388&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frzoq1i%2Fthis_sub_is_the_best_place_for_entertainment_and%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frzoq1i%2Fthis_sub_is_the_best_place_for_entertainment_and%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rzoq1i/this_sub_is_the_best_place_for_entertainment_and/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 15:39:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Today, one half of the experts of this sub seem sure that we have entered a bear market while the other half is sure this dip is nothing but a tiny hiccup and are advising everyone to BTFD. In the coming days, when one of the two things will play out, one half of our &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/r/cc&quot;&amp;gt;r/cc&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; experts will jump out and start shitposting how they perfectly predicated the market and had you listened to them, you would be having your own lambo today. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The fact is nobody knows what will happen. The market could continue to go sideways for months, or it could shoot back up or completely crash in an hour. Looking at former cycles doesn&amp;amp;#39;t help us all that much; nothing is guaranteed to repeat itself. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The sub is a great source of entertainment but it is the worst place for advice. People like to pretend they know what will happen - and I think some really think they know it and are telling that to themselves - because they read it in the stars (and call it technical analysis) or just look at some metrics that support their claims and ignore others. Don&amp;amp;#39;t believe them, nobody knows anything.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;tl;dr: nobody knows shit about fuck, don&amp;amp;#39;t believe anyone who pretends they do.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thanks @InfiniteAleWork for sending over some Hop-to-Flow beer to @21milofficial in The Netherlands! Super tasty hazy IPA and an excellent combi with Dutch "bitterballen"🍻🍻 https://t.co/MWWgH9IKEE]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480163949794541575/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480163949794541575/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 13:36:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[There will not be a 80-90% correction, this isn’t 2017.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Like the title says, and in response to many posts I see here telling people to
prepare for such a dip, or the others that gain appropriate Notoriety saying
they held through the last dip, it’s not applicable nowadays. Apple and…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rzm6s3/there_will_not_be_a_8090_correction_this_isnt_2017/?score=357&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frzm6s3%2Fthere_will_not_be_a_8090_correction_this_isnt_2017%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frzm6s3%2Fthere_will_not_be_a_8090_correction_this_isnt_2017%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rzm6s3/there_will_not_be_a_8090_correction_this_isnt_2017/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 13:35:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Like the title says, and in response to many posts I see here telling people to prepare for such a dip, or the others that gain appropriate Notoriety saying they held through the last dip, it’s not applicable nowadays. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.pinimg.com/originals/1d/07/80/1d0780af11c64e18c8c6d2fa52f4e995.jpg&quot;&amp;gt;Apple and oranges&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.        &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Retail and Industry are now heavily involved in cryptocurrency‘s, it went mainstream last year, The richest man in the world openly share the fact they HODL. I helped my mother set her account up last month! This is not the same space anymore.          &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m not trying to spread hopium, just want us all to know the times they are a changing!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I know some people have lost faith in this #bitcoin bull market. However we are only halfway into the cycle (2020-2024). And although BTC experiences some turbulence at $1T, the yellow gold cluster at S2F60/$10T (small black dots are 2009-2021 gold data)  is still the target IMO. https://t.co/xWFQKKnndP]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480159024112934913/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480159024112934913/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 12:50:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ok, ID-10t, I’m going to school you again, not because it’s going to be of use for you, since you’re just getting paid to attack #Bitcoin and defend fiat, but because the people deserve to know you are a fraud. https://t.co/BbDGGnyjuu]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480118398826827779/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1480118398826827779/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 10:42:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Are r/CC users overly enthusiastic in posting comments, but overly stingy when giving upvotes? I scraped data for Top 100 posts and compared them to similar subreddits to check]]></title><description><![CDATA[An unexpected trend I noticed recently is that posts with low upvote counts
routinely make it to the frontpage.

This is common in smaller communities, but there are 4 million+ subscribers
here. You’d expect posts on the frontpage would have a couple thousand upvotes
instead of a few hundred…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rzicfg/are_rcc_users_overly_enthusiastic_in_posting/?score=344&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frzicfg%2Fare_rcc_users_overly_enthusiastic_in_posting%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frzicfg%2Fare_rcc_users_overly_enthusiastic_in_posting%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rzicfg/are_rcc_users_overly_enthusiastic_in_posting/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 10:41:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;An unexpected trend I noticed recently is that posts with low upvote counts routinely make it to the frontpage.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is common in smaller communities, but there are 4 million+ subscribers here. You’d expect posts on the frontpage would have a couple thousand upvotes instead of a few hundred each.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I dug into the numbers to check if it’s true.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;I exported our top 100 posts and compared the upvotes-to-comments ratio to subreddits that share our hobby of yolo-ing life savings because a stranger told us to&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That&amp;amp;#39;s Wallstreetbets and SuperStonk.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I scraped &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/bt09arh&quot;&amp;gt;data from 300 posts in the last 30 days&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; into a javascript object notation (JSON) file. Then I converted it into CSV format to find the headers that contained the info I needed: post title, upvote count, comment count, post type, flair, and a few others.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After that, it was just a matter of &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/ooakgfR&quot;&amp;gt;cleaning it up in Excel&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and making some pivot tables to combine data from all 3 subreddits.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Result 1: Users of Cryptocurrency give massively less upvotes than Wallstreetbets and SuperStonk&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And it’s not even close. Here’s a summary of all 300 posts I scraped:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;table&amp;gt;&amp;lt;thead&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;Subscribers&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;Total Upvotes&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;Total Comments&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;Upvote-to-Comment Ratio&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/thead&amp;gt;&amp;lt;tbody&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;Cryptocurrency&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;4,286,758&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;455,146&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;135,170&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;3.37&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;Wallstreetbets&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;11,449,899&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;2,170,981&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;90,523&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;23.98&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;SuperStonk&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;720,403&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;1,734,892&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;69,300&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;25.03&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tbody&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/table&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;Table&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;formatting&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;brought&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;to&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;you&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;by&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://xl2reddit.github.io/&quot;&amp;gt;ExcelToReddit&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You are &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;612% more likely to get an upvote in Wallstreetbets&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; or Superstonk than on Cryptocurrency.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Other revealing stats are:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;We have 62% less subscribers than Wallstreetbets, but Cryptocurrency has 49% more comments&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Superstonk has 83% less subscribers, but they give 281% more upvotes than Cryptocurrency&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A high upvote-to-comment ratio means that there are more upvotes than comments. A &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;low ratio means users comment more&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; than upvote.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Result 2: If you look at SELFPOSTS ONLY, Cryptocurrency also gives way less upvotes than anywhere else&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Memes are allowed in both Wallstreetbets and SuperStonk which tend to be more upvote-heavy than comments.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you exclude those, this is what you get:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;table&amp;gt;&amp;lt;thead&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;Total Upvotes&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;Total Comments&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;Upvote-to-Comment Ratio&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/thead&amp;gt;&amp;lt;tbody&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;Cryptocurrency&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;325,455&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;115,203&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;2.83&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;Wallstreetbets&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;102,821&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;12,588&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;8.17&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;SuperStonk&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;392,629&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;19,136&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;20.52&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tbody&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/table&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Your selfpost is still 189% more likely to get an upvote in Wallstreetbets, and 625% more likely in SuperStonk.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Result 3: We also give out less post appreciation awards than other subreddits&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Superstonk is way ahead at an insane 221 awards per post, then WSB is next with 65.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cryptocurrency is last with an average of 51 awards.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;table&amp;gt;&amp;lt;thead&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;# of Posts&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;Total Awards Given&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;Avg Awards per Post&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/thead&amp;gt;&amp;lt;tbody&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;Cryptocurrency&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;100&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;5,083&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;51&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;Wallstreetbets&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;100&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;6,459&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;65&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;SuperStonk&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;100&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;22,066&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;221&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tbody&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/table&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This counts all awards: reddit gold, silver, helpful, facepalm, wholesome etc.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Conclusion/TLDR&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cryptocurrency is the Scrooge McDuck of upvotes. We like leaving comments a lot, but we don’t upvote the post we’re commenting on as often.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why though?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Never selling]]></title><description><![CDATA[I wonder how many Bitcoiners, like me, are truly never selling (in any
materially relevant way)? Genuinely? How many people here are in it for their
grandkids for example? I feel a little intense and crazy when I think that way
but that’s just the truth]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rzbhpp/never_selling/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frzbhpp%2Fnever_selling%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frzbhpp%2Fnever_selling%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rzbhpp/never_selling/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 09:31:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I wonder how many Bitcoiners, like me, are truly never selling (in any materially relevant way)? Genuinely? How many people here are in it for their grandkids for example? I feel a little intense and crazy when I think that way but that’s just the truth&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Now I can watch the bear market and crash in style 😂]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rzgfau/now_i_can_watch_the_bear_market_and_crash_in_style/?score=347&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frzgfau%2Fnow_i_can_watch_the_bear_market_and_crash_in_style%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frzgfau%2Fnow_i_can_watch_the_bear_market_and_crash_in_style%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rzgfau/now_i_can_watch_the_bear_market_and_crash_in_style/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 08:30:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This sub 2 months ago: You will never see Bitcoin below $50k ever again]]></title><description><![CDATA[Two months ago when Bitcoin hit its all time high of $69k, pretty much all you
would hear from people around here was that the days of Bitcoin below $50k was a
thing of the past--with members posting all these astrological TA charts
proclaiming how the 'maximum pain' from here on forward was around…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rzg6i1/this_sub_2_months_ago_you_will_never_see_bitcoin/?score=480&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frzg6i1%2Fthis_sub_2_months_ago_you_will_never_see_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frzg6i1%2Fthis_sub_2_months_ago_you_will_never_see_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rzg6i1/this_sub_2_months_ago_you_will_never_see_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 04:53:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Two months ago when Bitcoin hit its all time high of $69k, pretty much all you would hear from people around here was that the days of Bitcoin below $50k was a thing of the past--with members posting all these &amp;lt;del&amp;gt;astrological&amp;lt;/del&amp;gt; TA charts proclaiming how the &amp;amp;#39;maximum pain&amp;amp;#39; from here on forward was around the $55k mark. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But what caught my attention more than anything was all the people whining and complaining how they &amp;amp;#39;wished&amp;amp;#39; they had bought in when BTC was in the low 40s and how they had missed that glorious opportunity. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Well fellas... its time to put up or STFU cause that time is today. But judging by things around here I am guessing the modus operandi is going to be more and more whining, this time about how they &amp;amp;#39;wished&amp;amp;#39; they had sold. And then a couple of weeks or months from now when the market recovers (as it always does) we&amp;amp;#39;ll have the same people whining about how they missed that golden opportunity of buying low yet again.. no wonder we have that prophetic joke about buying high and selling low. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I think its about time to disrupt that problematic pattern of behavior.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Being a little kind towards newbies won’t take anything away from us. As a sub, we should be guiding the new people entering this sub rather than scaring them away by being rude.]]></title><description><![CDATA[A lot of newbies entered the market when it was pumping, and seeing the value of
your investment plummet like this really scares the hell out of everyone. It
doesn’t help anyone to scold and taunt newbies asking about the bear market and
belittling them by saying shit like “if you needed your money…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rz67m3/being_a_little_kind_towards_newbies_wont_take/?score=316&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frz67m3%2Fbeing_a_little_kind_towards_newbies_wont_take%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frz67m3%2Fbeing_a_little_kind_towards_newbies_wont_take%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rz67m3/being_a_little_kind_towards_newbies_wont_take/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 02:41:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A lot  of newbies entered the market when it was pumping, and seeing the value of your investment plummet like this really scares the hell out of everyone. It doesn’t help anyone to scold and taunt newbies asking about the bear market and belittling them by saying shit like “if you needed your money back so soon, you shouldn’t have invested in crypto” or “if you did your own research, you wouldn’t be scared like this now”. Even if that&amp;amp;#39;s true, there are plenty of nicer ways to say it and we don&amp;amp;#39;t need to be driving away newbies who will ultimately help grow the market. We are all in this together, that is the whole point of decentralized finance.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin as a retirement account?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am 31, and wondering if anyone else around this age has chosen to not put
money into a retirement account at work and instead put it into Bitcoin instead?
Obviously this isn’t a very traditional or risk-off approach but I believe in
this thing and I think it could work. It’s been amazing watching…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ryvni4/bitcoin_as_a_retirement_account/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fryvni4%2Fbitcoin_as_a_retirement_account%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fryvni4%2Fbitcoin_as_a_retirement_account%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ryvni4/bitcoin_as_a_retirement_account/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 02:00:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I am 31, and wondering if anyone else around this age has chosen to not put money into a retirement account at work and instead put it into Bitcoin instead? Obviously this isn’t a very traditional or risk-off approach but I believe in this thing and I think it could work. It’s been amazing watching Bitcoin transcend into society over the past year. Or if not retirement, do you do anything against the grain or that is not very common with Bitcoin that you don’t know anyone else does?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why I think we’re in a supercycle.]]></title><description><![CDATA[BTC supply is growing at less than 2%.

Previous cycles it was ~ 4 or 8 %.

90% is mined.

BTC is now more scarce than gold, before it wasn’t due to the supply growth.

That’s it, that’s the reason. No TA or anything dumb speculation over whether
another country will adopt.

Moon eventually 🌗]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rz3ubb/why_i_think_were_in_a_supercycle/?score=344&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frz3ubb%2Fwhy_i_think_were_in_a_supercycle%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frz3ubb%2Fwhy_i_think_were_in_a_supercycle%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rz3ubb/why_i_think_were_in_a_supercycle/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:53:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;BTC supply is growing at less than 2%.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Previous cycles it was ~ 4 or 8 %. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;90% is mined. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;BTC is now more scarce than gold, before it wasn’t due to the supply growth.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That’s it, that’s the reason.  No TA or anything dumb speculation over whether another country will adopt. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Moon eventually 🌗&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How will strippers be tipped, in a hyperbitcoinized world?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Serious question! One of the enjoyable features of physical cash, is that you
can gently place it in the stripper's thong, to tip her. The stripper enjoys it
(or at least acts like she does), and you get to feel benevolent and loving.
It's just, a great feature. But, it's a whole lot less sexy, to…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rz5xom/how_will_strippers_be_tipped_in_a/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frz5xom%2Fhow_will_strippers_be_tipped_in_a%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frz5xom%2Fhow_will_strippers_be_tipped_in_a%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rz5xom/how_will_strippers_be_tipped_in_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 22:35:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Serious question!  One of the enjoyable features of physical cash, is that you can gently place it in the stripper&amp;amp;#39;s thong, to tip her.  The stripper enjoys it (or at least acts like she does), and you get to feel benevolent and loving.  It&amp;amp;#39;s just, a great feature.  But, it&amp;amp;#39;s a whole lot less sexy, to ask her for a wallet address while she&amp;amp;#39;s pole dancing, you know?  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How will that industry be affected by the adoption of Bitcoin?  How will we tip strippers???&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[If you bought and HODL every top 10 coin for exactly 5 years since 01/08/2017 until today this is what would've happened.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Let's put things in perspective, imagine you invested in and still holding every
coin from top 10 exactly 5 years ago until today. The ranking is based on the
Historical Snapshot - 08 January 2017 by CMC



Coin Price in USD 08 Jan 2017 Price in USD 08 Jan 2022 Percentage change 1.
Bitcoin 911.20…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rz00vl/if_you_bought_and_hodl_every_top_10_coin_for/?score=324&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frz00vl%2Fif_you_bought_and_hodl_every_top_10_coin_for%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frz00vl%2Fif_you_bought_and_hodl_every_top_10_coin_for%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rz00vl/if_you_bought_and_hodl_every_top_10_coin_for/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 22:35:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let&amp;amp;#39;s put things in perspective, imagine you invested in and still holding every coin from top 10 exactly 5 years ago until today. The ranking is based on the  Historical Snapshot - 08 January 2017 by CMC&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;table&amp;gt;&amp;lt;thead&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Coin&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Price in USD 08 Jan 2017&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Price in USD 08 Jan 2022&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Percentage change&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/th&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/thead&amp;gt;&amp;lt;tbody&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;1. Bitcoin&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;911.20&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;41,894.82&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+ 4 498 %&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;2. Ethereum&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;10.29&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;3,208.72&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+ 31 082 %&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;3. XRP&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;0.006233&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;0.7649&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+ 12 171 %&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;4. Litecoin&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;3.99&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;134.30&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+ 3 266 %&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;5. Monero&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;13.47&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;193.48&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+ 1 336 %&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;6. Ethereum Classic&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;1.45&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;30.47&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+ 2 001 %&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;7. Dash&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;12.54&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;140.63&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+ 1 021 %&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;8. Augur&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;4.56&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;16.39&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+ 259 %&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;9. MaidSafeCoin&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;0.09385&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;0.338&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+ 260 %&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;10. Steem&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;0.1525&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;0.3931&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+ 157 %&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/td&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tr&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/tbody&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/table&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Everyone can make his own conclusions about long term holding. For me a small surprise is that despite some of these coins are currently far from top 10  they are still profitable even after 5 years.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin looks on track to close a 7th consecutive day in red. The last time happened was in 2018.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bitcoin looks on track to close a 7th consecutive day in red and we need to go
back all the way to 2018 to see a similar occurrence. That time, the 7-day
downtrend started on 29th July at a price of around $8500 (not the peak of the
run just like right now). After 7 days of falling back then, it…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rz65o0/bitcoin_looks_on_track_to_close_a_7th_consecutive/?score=363&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frz65o0%2Fbitcoin_looks_on_track_to_close_a_7th_consecutive%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frz65o0%2Fbitcoin_looks_on_track_to_close_a_7th_consecutive%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rz65o0/bitcoin_looks_on_track_to_close_a_7th_consecutive/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 21:40:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin looks on track to close a 7th consecutive day in red and we need to go back all the way to 2018 to see a similar occurrence. That time, the 7-day downtrend started on 29th July at a price of around $8500 (not the peak of the run just like right now). After 7 days of falling back then, it saw a bounce for one day and then fell another 20% before finding any sense of stability. If history is any indicator, then the carnage has only just begun. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Winter is coming and we know what&amp;amp;#39;s coming with it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just sell it all]]></title><description><![CDATA[Absolute panic every second or third post. Everything from "It's just a dip" -
"bear market/crypto winter" - "Everything but Bitcoin and Ethereum is going to
zero". Lol calm down.

If you're sweating, just sell everything. Cryptocurrencies in general are
extremely volatile and if this makes you…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rz7vqj/just_sell_it_all/?score=504&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frz7vqj%2Fjust_sell_it_all%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frz7vqj%2Fjust_sell_it_all%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rz7vqj/just_sell_it_all/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 21:40:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Absolute panic every second or third post. Everything from &amp;amp;quot;It&amp;amp;#39;s just a dip&amp;amp;quot; - &amp;amp;quot;bear market/crypto winter&amp;amp;quot; - &amp;amp;quot;Everything but Bitcoin and Ethereum is going to zero&amp;amp;quot;. Lol calm down. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you&amp;amp;#39;re sweating, just sell everything. Cryptocurrencies in general are extremely volatile and if this makes you nervous than maybe this stuff isn&amp;amp;#39;t for you. Stocks are more stable and might be your thing. We could see another 50%+ drop and nobody wants to see you drop of a heart attack because of it. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you&amp;amp;#39;re day trading you know this is how it goes, if you&amp;amp;#39;re doing anything else, delete your chart app or whatever.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitboy has been involved in 7 Crypto scams in the past all of the projects he worked on either got Exit Scammed or Rug pulled. He has deleted all the videos of scam projects he shilled to his community.]]></title><description><![CDATA[You might have already seen the flyer of his rates, I'm going to mention again
if someone have not seen it yet.

This is what he charges for his videos:

Dedicated Review: $35,000

Livestream Mention: $20,000

YouTube Interview: $40,000

Telegram AMA: $10,000

Website Article: $2,500.

I have no…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryzs07/bitboy_has_been_involved_in_7_crypto_scams_in_the/?score=574&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryzs07%2Fbitboy_has_been_involved_in_7_crypto_scams_in_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryzs07%2Fbitboy_has_been_involved_in_7_crypto_scams_in_the%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryzs07/bitboy_has_been_involved_in_7_crypto_scams_in_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 20:45:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You might have already seen the flyer of his rates, I&amp;amp;#39;m going to mention again if someone have not seen it yet.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is what he charges for his videos:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Dedicated Review: $35,000&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Livestream Mention: $20,000&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;YouTube Interview: $40,000  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Telegram AMA: $10,000&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Website Article: $2,500.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I have no idea how this person has over 1 Million subscribers while he has been scamming the community for years. Please If you are new in Crypto market please stay away from YouTubers they are not your friends.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;1: MYX&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He made a video on $MYX and the token is currently down 90% from its ATH. He has deleted the video which he made on MYX.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/myx-network/&quot;&amp;gt;https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/myx-network/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;2: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;DistX&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He also made a video on DistX with the title &amp;amp;quot;My most low cap Gem in Crypto&amp;amp;quot;  He later on change the title to &amp;amp;quot;New crypto coin with 1000x Potential&amp;amp;quot; This Token is currently down 99% from its ATH. The charts shows it&amp;amp;#39;s just a pump and dump Token.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/distx/&quot;&amp;gt;https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/distx/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/v4xx6bbrqga81.jpg?width=975&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=b75c50d878c977d949c6ca86a890e758cf58de04&quot;&amp;gt;He changed the title.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;3: Zao Finance&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He made a tweet on this token in 2020. This token got exit scammed.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;4: ETHY&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This token got rug pulled.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/hxvvpdxirga81.jpg?width=1277&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=ed04cbcdc5f95a235c4421b53094dda1a41d0988&quot;&amp;gt;This video is also deleted.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;5: LOCK Meridian Network&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Currently down 98% from its ATH. The video on it also deleted by Bitboy.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;6,7: CPH and PAMP&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;CPH coin got delayed for years and video is also deleted.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;PAMP video is currently unlisted. Down -100% from ATH.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
ATH: $2.3&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Current Price: $0.0012  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;For detail thread:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://nitter.net/zachxbt/status/1478082010807742468#m&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;https://nitter.net/zachxbt/status/1478082010807742468#m&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;All Credit goes to Zachxbt (Twitter)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Solana Formally Admits having Network Clogging]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryx3uj/solana_formally_admits_having_network_clogging/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryx3uj%2Fsolana_formally_admits_having_network_clogging%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryx3uj%2Fsolana_formally_admits_having_network_clogging%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryx3uj/solana_formally_admits_having_network_clogging/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 20:45:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tonight we're gonna ride the all-time highs!]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ryxj0w/tonight_were_gonna_ride_the_alltime_highs/?score=316&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fryxj0w%2Ftonight_were_gonna_ride_the_alltime_highs%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fryxj0w%2Ftonight_were_gonna_ride_the_alltime_highs%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ryxj0w/tonight_were_gonna_ride_the_alltime_highs/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 20:45:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Fear &amp; Greed Index is at 10 as of March 2020. The difference? The price of Bitcoin is at $42K this time, and it had touched $3.2K in March 2020. Don't panic, just zoom out.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Bitcoin Fear & Greed Index is at 10 today. The lowest level since March
2020. At that time, the COVID-19 pandemic had just started to spread around the
world, and we had a liquidity crisis in all liquid markets.

This caused the price of Bitcoin to drop by more than 50% in a few hours to a
low…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryweqj/bitcoin_fear_greed_index_is_at_10_as_of_march/?score=326&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryweqj%2Fbitcoin_fear_greed_index_is_at_10_as_of_march%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryweqj%2Fbitcoin_fear_greed_index_is_at_10_as_of_march%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryweqj/bitcoin_fear_greed_index_is_at_10_as_of_march/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 18:42:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Bitcoin Fear &amp;amp;amp; Greed Index is at 10 today. The lowest level since March 2020. At that time, the COVID-19 pandemic had just started to spread around the world, and we had a liquidity crisis in all liquid markets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This caused the price of Bitcoin to drop by more than 50% in a few hours to a low of $3.2K on some trading platforms.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The fear was extreme. However, a strong rebound was quickly observed thanks to the HODLers of last resort who had seen a unique opportunity to seize. What happened next proved them right.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Today, the price of Bitcoin is at $42K. This is almost 40% lower than the ATH of November 10, 2021, at $69K. But is it time to give in to extreme fear? I don&amp;amp;#39;t think so. Above all, we must keep control of our emotions and take a step back. Don&amp;amp;#39;t panic and take a step back. It&amp;amp;#39;s as simple as that.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you doubt it, ask yourself this question: would you have been in extreme fear if someone had told you two years ago that the price of Bitcoin would have been $42K in January 2022? I don&amp;amp;#39;t think so!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Don&amp;amp;#39;t let short-term volatility override Bitcoin&amp;amp;#39;s long-term goals. In a few years, the current period will not even appear on the Bitcoin price chart.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Stay strong, Stay Bitcoin HODLers.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just stake your assets and calm the f**k down.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I understand that the greed & fear meter is all the way down to 10.

I also understand this dip is not what people expected after so many ExPeRtS
claimed BTC would reach 100k and ETH 10k lmfao

I also also do understand that any newcomer will be scared af if they just put
their Xmas money into…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryyj5w/just_stake_your_assets_and_calm_the_fk_down/?score=330&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryyj5w%2Fjust_stake_your_assets_and_calm_the_fk_down%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryyj5w%2Fjust_stake_your_assets_and_calm_the_fk_down%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryyj5w/just_stake_your_assets_and_calm_the_fk_down/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 18:42:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I understand that the greed &amp;amp;amp; fear meter is all the way down to 10.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I also understand this dip is not what people expected after so many ExPeRtS claimed BTC would reach 100k and ETH 10k lmfao&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I also also do understand that any newcomer will be scared af if they just put their Xmas money into crypto.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What I have learnt though is, if you got any kind of crypto rewards based on staking, then please just lock it up for some solid good months or years and forget about this. It helps you mentally and also it is in my opinion the best call for a long term hodler.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In my case, I have been sipping coffee watching Reddit go nuts and keeping calm as hell because I have Ethereum staked, CRO staked for the card and in their DeFi Earn (all locked) and the rest of coins I have them staked and all these secured with a hardware wallet which I genuinely find it too much of a hassle to get to start using again for the sake of panic selling.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is just better to watch the world burn while you know it will eventually heal up again.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Stake your coins, earn interest and lock it up for a while. It will help you A LOT mentally.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;NOTE: any PoW hodlers (unstakable coins obviously), try to get them into a DeFi earning system like Compound or Aave. Any centralised ones can be Nexo&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Remember, a public ledger is public forever. Don't think you're going to cheat on your taxes and get away with it just because they don't catch you this year. They have forever to catch you.]]></title><description><![CDATA[In most countries (including the US, contrary to popular opinion) there is no
statute of limitations on intentional tax fraud. Governments will eventually
catch up and easily scrape blockchains for any transactions you make that
originated from KYC exchanges (and all of the companies you…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryspiw/remember_a_public_ledger_is_public_forever_dont/?score=307&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryspiw%2Fremember_a_public_ledger_is_public_forever_dont%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryspiw%2Fremember_a_public_ledger_is_public_forever_dont%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryspiw/remember_a_public_ledger_is_public_forever_dont/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 18:42:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In most countries (including the US, contrary to popular opinion) there is no statute of limitations on intentional tax fraud. Governments will eventually catch up and easily scrape blockchains for any transactions you make that originated from KYC exchanges (and all of the companies you KYC/transact with will eventually compile your complete blockchain financial history). &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It doesn&amp;amp;#39;t matter how many DEXs and convoluted txs you made, unless you&amp;amp;#39;re using Secret Network or Monero, they will be able to follow all of it if they can tie your name to any piece. If they deem your under reporting to be significant, you will get a bill, with outrageous interest charges, and they will garnish your wages. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Unless you route all your KYC deposits and withdrawals through XMR and withdraw/deposit everything to your XMR wallet before trading on non-kyc exchanges, your tx history will be public information forever. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Governments and random companies will track every move you make in greater detail than has ever been possible. It might take them 10 years, but if you&amp;amp;#39;re leaving all of your txs on public blockchains, they have all the time in the world to setup automated systems to identify and track you (and FYI, if you&amp;amp;#39;re not using Brave or Firefox carefully, Google knows all of your wallet extension addresses). &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Non-kyc exchanges examples include: Mandala, Kucoin, Coinex... &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This message sponsored by: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Monero &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Because the yearly global black market is larger than the GDP of any country in Europe &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;TM&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: FYI, if you are audited by the IRS, you are presumed guilty until proven innocent. If they see deposits, you have to prove that you don&amp;amp;#39;t owe them money. So unless you want to live like a drug dealer, you are going to pay taxes for every dollar you cash out of crypto. Make no mistake about that. XMR might simplify your paperwork, but the end result will be the same. The title really is the point of this post.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit 2: No, there is no statute of limitations for intentional errors in the US (search for &amp;amp;quot;fraud&amp;amp;quot;): &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.irs.gov/irm/part25/irm_25-006-001r&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.irs.gov/irm/part25/irm_25-006-001r&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hodlers of Last Resort!]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rypp1r/hodlers_of_last_resort/?score=323&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frypp1r%2Fhodlers_of_last_resort%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frypp1r%2Fhodlers_of_last_resort%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rypp1r/hodlers_of_last_resort/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 17:33:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The European Bank Unicredit threatens to close all accounts of clients who buy crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[Everything started on Twitter when a user showed a screenshot of a conversation
with Unicredit customer support. He complained that he couldn't send money to
FTX or Crypto.com

The support told him to not do it because it's against the bank's policy. He
asked where this policy was written and the…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryw1sr/the_european_bank_unicredit_threatens_to_close/?score=604&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryw1sr%2Fthe_european_bank_unicredit_threatens_to_close%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryw1sr%2Fthe_european_bank_unicredit_threatens_to_close%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryw1sr/the_european_bank_unicredit_threatens_to_close/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 12:39:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Everything started on Twitter when a user showed a screenshot of a conversation with Unicredit customer support. He complained that he couldn&amp;amp;#39;t send money to FTX or Crypto.com&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The support told him to not do it because it&amp;amp;#39;s against the bank&amp;amp;#39;s policy. He asked where this policy was written and  the answer was &amp;amp;quot;it&amp;amp;#39;s not written in the contract, it&amp;amp;#39;s just a policy we have&amp;amp;quot;. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The customer service told him also that anyone who tries to send money to any crypto exchange will be reported (to whom? Lol) and their account will be terminated. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;After this post became trending on Twitter, the official Unicredit account tweeted a statement confirming that their policies forbid customers to send money to any crypto exchange.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can see the thread here, however it&amp;amp;#39;s written in Italian but you can use Google translate: 
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/UniCredit_IT/status/1479527599890173952?t=9PYE2-UqUCvtIdRMHjZEsw&amp;amp;amp;s=19&quot;&amp;gt;https://twitter.com/UniCredit_IT/status/1479527599890173952?t=9PYE2-UqUCvtIdRMHjZEsw&amp;amp;amp;s=19&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I don&amp;amp;#39;t have an account at Unicredit because it&amp;amp;#39;s a terrible bank previously related with the worse politicians in the country, however it&amp;amp;#39;s a big European bank (mostly Italian and French) so I advise every customer to close their account and move to another bank.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NEW - Dutch government withholds excess mortality data: Scientists are now criticizing the government's continued failure to release the data for an independent investigation.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1479776410923417605/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1479776410923417605/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 11:44:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why is ETH &amp; BTC Dropping Like it’s Hot]]></title><description><![CDATA[According to Time, the big drops this week to Ethereum and Bitcoin have followed
a disappointing December jobs report, and the release of minutes from the
Federal Reserve Board's December meeting, which signaled the central bank would
begin slowing down measures to prop up the economy as it…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rytkcq/why_is_eth_btc_dropping_like_its_hot/?score=316&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frytkcq%2Fwhy_is_eth_btc_dropping_like_its_hot%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frytkcq%2Fwhy_is_eth_btc_dropping_like_its_hot%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rytkcq/why_is_eth_btc_dropping_like_its_hot/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 11:44:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;According to Time, the big drops this week to Ethereum and Bitcoin have followed a disappointing December jobs report, and the release of minutes from the Federal Reserve Board&amp;amp;#39;s December meeting, which signaled the central bank would begin slowing down measures to prop up the economy as it continues to improve. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, 18% of Bitcoins hash rate comes out of Kazakstan where the power went out January 5th for several hours due to the political turmoil  which then caused an approx 12% drop in BTC price then it was downhill from there. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Basically, fear over interest rates and turmoil in Kazakstan is storing up a lot of crap in the crypto world. Let’s get ready to get this party started!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[With the Fear and Greed indicator at 10 today and many worried about the future of crypto, its time for an updated repost of the post that I did 8 months ago analysing the fear measurement and what it has usually meant for price. Now updated with more data.]]></title><description><![CDATA[For those you aren't aware, the Crypto Fear and Greed index uses 5-6
measurements to assess the current sentiment of the market and then rates that
level of emotion on a scale of 1 to 100. 1 is extreme fear and 100 is extreme
greed.

Those measurements are objective of course - they look at…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rytehw/with_the_fear_and_greed_indicator_at_10_today_and/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frytehw%2Fwith_the_fear_and_greed_indicator_at_10_today_and%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frytehw%2Fwith_the_fear_and_greed_indicator_at_10_today_and%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rytehw/with_the_fear_and_greed_indicator_at_10_today_and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 10:37:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For those you aren&amp;amp;#39;t aware, the Crypto Fear and Greed index uses 5-6 measurements to assess the current sentiment of the market and then rates that level of emotion on a scale of 1 to 100. 1 is extreme fear and 100 is extreme greed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Those measurements are objective of course - they look at volatility, social media, momentum, dominance, google trends and (now paused) surveys.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here is the link to the site, you can look at the chart, click &amp;amp;quot;max&amp;amp;quot; and you will see a movement of the index since the start of 2018.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://alternative.me/crypto/fear-and-greed-index/&quot;&amp;gt;https://alternative.me/crypto/fear-and-greed-index/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In theory, the idea should be that in cases of extreme fear, the market is terrified and panic selling, and it is a good buying opportunity. When the market is in a state of extreme greed, people are getting extreme fomo and buying regardless of the elevated prices. Hopefully you get the picture.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There is a lot of movement in the chart but it is the extreme fear and greed regions that interest me - specifically around the region of 80 plus or 20 below.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Today the fear and greed index is at 10 - almost a record low.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Looking at the index to date, there are only six other times in the past where the index has plunged below 20. I thought it would be helpful to look at that regions, what was happening and the price at that point, and to think of those as historical buying points (note that during the &amp;amp;quot;China Ban&amp;amp;quot; crash in September, we got to 20, but never went below that).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;6 February 2018 - Index Score: 8. BTC Price $6,852.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is probably the point at which there was a realization we truly were in a bear market, with bitcoin already down around 65% since its top. While buying at this point (the start of a 1 year bear market) is not exactly enticing, that price was more or less the average price for most of the year. Certainly not a bad entry point if you had resisted the temptation to buy in the entire bull market of 2017.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;1 April 2018 - Index Score 16. BTC Price $6,975&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Around March of 2018 was a bit of a &amp;amp;quot;dead cat bounce&amp;amp;quot; with the price recovering to nearly $12,000. Many people breathed a sigh of relief, portfolios turned green and it seemed like the bear market was over. Nope. Bitcoin immediately crashed right back down again to prices similar to February. Hence a moment of extreme fear.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Again, this wasn&amp;amp;#39;t a particularly bad buying point historically, having just avoiding fomo of the surge in bitcoin up to that much higher price level.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;25 November 2018 - Index Score 9. BTC Price $3,895&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now we&amp;amp;#39;re talking. This was the time of the infamous &amp;amp;quot;hash wars&amp;amp;quot; when BCH forked and the markets plunged into absolute chaos. Bitcoin crashed through its $6,000 support level and halved in price.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This was an absolute buying opportunity - perhaps the opportunity of a lifetime, with an average price around this level for six months. Happy to say I bought right through but not enough. Each buy at the time seemed painful, and it was embarassing at times for people to even know you were in crypto.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also recall that at $3,100 very few people were calling this the bottom (shout out to Smart Contractor from twitter here who picked it). Many had buy ladders down to $1.3k, and it seemed a fall to at least the mid $2,000s was obvious. A little bit like those all calling for $25k right now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;22 August 2019 - Index Score 5. BTC $10,124&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This one might feel like a bit of an anomaly, but in some ways it feels quite similar to today. Bitcoin had just ripped from $4k to around $14k and the bull run was on. After a short period, bitcoin fell sharply and the price started to collapse downwards. I think &amp;amp;quot;5&amp;amp;quot; is a bit extreme for fear but this was the realization that the bull market might be over. For the next six months, the bitcoin price let out steam down to $6.5k (aside from one day when President Xi managed to pump us back to $10,300 - oh for the days when China would actually pump our prices).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So not a great buying spot, but better than FOMOing at $14k and historically still not bad.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;13 March 2020 - Index Score 10. BTC $5,142&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I don&amp;amp;#39;t think this one needs much explanation. The corona effect was sharp and deadly, with the bitcoin price absolutely collapsing quickly. Again, I don&amp;amp;#39;t think we have any debate that this was one hell of a buying opportunity. Even more if you had cash to deploy in the weekend. One person I know bought ETH at $85 or so at that point. And there are some people suggesting the charts today are quite similar to this. Hmmmm.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;20 May / 22 June / 21 July = Index Score 11, 10 and 10.  BTC around the $30,000 mark.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Each of these points marked a point in time where Bitcoin was teetering on the edge of the $30k mark (or slightly below) and many were calling for a massive break and plunge to $20k.  We all know what happened, and we now can say that indeed these were great buying points.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I believe I posted my original post when the Fear index was around 15 and the BTC price was $37k.  Not a perfect time to buy, but hardly that bad.   Now at that last fear point (21 July) - the absolute worst time to sell, I saw on youtube a person who was so convinced BTC was about to plunge he converted his 3 year BTC savings $20k into a leveraged short, then when that was nearly margin called on the super pump, he used his credit card to borrow $21k more to short, and lost it all. That is what fear does to you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Today - Index Score 10.  BTC = $41,900&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And here we are.  What I think is interesting is that this is by FAR the highest the price has ever been with fear at this range.  Which is kind of amusing in some ways, as I feel the realistic worst case crash might take us back down to $30k or so, the same price at which we were just as scared last time.  And I think the fear is fairly real here, with at least one person I know in real life &amp;amp;quot;cashing out&amp;amp;quot; at 41k.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Put another way, if BTC had jumped $12k from $30k to $42k in that mid-year bear period, I imagine people would be calling for extreme greed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[You’ve invested more than you can afford to lose, it’s time to deal with it.]]></title><description><![CDATA[It seems like every post in this sub lately is trying to convince people what to
do with their money.

Whether it’s “buying the dip”, “it’s just a dip”, or something like “who else is
still hodling”, it seems like we have some people here panicking.

You made the decision to buy what coin and how…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rympyj/youve_invested_more_than_you_can_afford_to_lose/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frympyj%2Fyouve_invested_more_than_you_can_afford_to_lose%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frympyj%2Fyouve_invested_more_than_you_can_afford_to_lose%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rympyj/youve_invested_more_than_you_can_afford_to_lose/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 09:44:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It seems like every post in this sub lately is trying to convince people what to do with their money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Whether it’s “buying the dip”, “it’s just a dip”, or something like “who else is still hodling”, it seems like we have some people here panicking. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You made the decision to buy what coin and how much of that coin, so please stop trying to turn this into an echo chamber and convince people to buy/hodl. We are all our own people with our own financial responsibilities, and we don’t owe each other anything. We are not a collective group and no one here owes us anything. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You might get rich off crypto, but you more than likely won’t. Why? Because most of us don’t have the patience or mental fortitude to hold through bear markets and crashes that it takes to see your investment go to the moon. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do your own research, invest what you can afford to lose, and deal with the consequences of your actions. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Have a good weekend, my dudes!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cops can’t access $60M in seized bitcoin—fraudster won’t give password]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryh4rn/cops_cant_access_60m_in_seized_bitcoinfraudster/?score=331&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryh4rn%2Fcops_cant_access_60m_in_seized_bitcoinfraudster%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryh4rn%2Fcops_cant_access_60m_in_seized_bitcoinfraudster%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryh4rn/cops_cant_access_60m_in_seized_bitcoinfraudster/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 08:42:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Apps to report payments over $600 per year to the IRS]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10372327/Venmo-PayPal-Cash-App-report-transactions-totaling-600-IRS.html

Is the way forward to buy using cash on local stores?]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ryca5o/apps_to_report_payments_over_600_per_year_to_the/?score=324&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fryca5o%2Fapps_to_report_payments_over_600_per_year_to_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fryca5o%2Fapps_to_report_payments_over_600_per_year_to_the%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ryca5o/apps_to_report_payments_over_600_per_year_to_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 06:32:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10372327/Venmo-PayPal-Cash-App-report-transactions-totaling-600-IRS.html&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10372327/Venmo-PayPal-Cash-App-report-transactions-totaling-600-IRS.html&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Is the way forward to buy using cash on local stores?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin below $50,000 Presents a Perfect Buying Opportunity, According to New York's Mayor]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ry68qz/bitcoin_below_50000_presents_a_perfect_buying/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fry68qz%2Fbitcoin_below_50000_presents_a_perfect_buying%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fry68qz%2Fbitcoin_below_50000_presents_a_perfect_buying%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ry68qz/bitcoin_below_50000_presents_a_perfect_buying/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 06:32:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NYC Mayor Undeterred by Falling Bitcoin Price, Says Buying the Dip Could Yield 'Good Profit']]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryd152/nyc_mayor_undeterred_by_falling_bitcoin_price/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryd152%2Fnyc_mayor_undeterred_by_falling_bitcoin_price%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryd152%2Fnyc_mayor_undeterred_by_falling_bitcoin_price%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryd152/nyc_mayor_undeterred_by_falling_bitcoin_price/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 04:49:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A new tech startup wants to gamify the U.S. court system by allowing everyday Americans to bet on lawsuits using tradable crypto tokens. It calls the process an "initial litigation offering."]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryi61d/a_new_tech_startup_wants_to_gamify_the_us_court/?score=375&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryi61d%2Fa_new_tech_startup_wants_to_gamify_the_us_court%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryi61d%2Fa_new_tech_startup_wants_to_gamify_the_us_court%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryi61d/a_new_tech_startup_wants_to_gamify_the_us_court/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 03:40:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can we take a moment to appreciate Harmony ONE and their amazing roadmap?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I sincerely dont want to sound like another shill, but their roadmap is speaking
volume!


BITCOIN BRIDGE

Still planning to have the launch this month. It should be an external launch so
onboarding externals for running vaults. Some minor details to take care of
still, but the launch is still…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ry42r2/can_we_take_a_moment_to_appreciate_harmony_one/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fry42r2%2Fcan_we_take_a_moment_to_appreciate_harmony_one%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fry42r2%2Fcan_we_take_a_moment_to_appreciate_harmony_one%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ry42r2/can_we_take_a_moment_to_appreciate_harmony_one/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 03:40:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I sincerely dont want to sound like another shill, but their roadmap is speaking volume!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Bitcoin Bridge&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Still planning to have the launch this month. It should be an external launch so onboarding externals for running vaults. Some minor details to take care of still, but the launch is still planned for this month.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Trustless Ethereum bridge&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Expecting a month of work, but hoping to finish everything by the end of this month.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Streaming sync and fast sync&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Fixing last problem before launch on Testnet. No update currently.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Cross Shard Transactions&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Needs a few more rounds of iteration and feedback on designs. A few more weeks until start of implementation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Polygon Bridge&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The team is working on this currently. More updates will come on this including date of launch in a few weeks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Staking Derivatives&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Currently working on the consistency of the bots and this is taking longer than expected. Once this is stable, they will work on a technical plan for updates and final dates.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;!!!Smart contract staking allows metamask users to stake!!! THATS HUGE&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Cross Chain API&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is as far as it can go before the bots and bridge are out. Once these are up and running, it should be a generic solution and finished shortly after.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Cosmos Bridge&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;An external team is currently working on this. There should be a progress update sometime next week. The end goal is to launch in February.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Secure Resharding&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Working with the Research DAO. Waiting on the write up adn finalizing design.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;1 second finality&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The feature is a major change so it is still under review. Increasing the gas fees slightly will help grow the block time and help with spam attacks as well, while still keeping the fees small for users.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Decentralized RPC&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bringing in more partners to help with this. Should be done by the end of January. Currently working on new ways to continue becoming more decentralized.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Decentralized Ops&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is used for onboarding teams to help with ops. Used to introduce a new Devnet.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;Ambassador DAO&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;goal for 2022 is 100 meetups per month around the world. The first meeting meeting will take place this month. Establishing a way to pay governors currently.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Apart from that, the recent crash did barely any damage to the coins price. Harmony is going strong and it is accumulating to the new ATH. When everyone is talking about ZK rollups on ETH, maybe more people should look in ONE and their immensely cheap gas fees.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I’ve been living in El Salvador for the past 5 weeks using only BTC. No cash, no credit cards. It can be done!]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m an Italian podcaster and I’ve been traveling in the whole country to report
the state of Bitcoin adoption. You can read my chronicles on my website. We post
in English as well as in Italian. Hope u guys enjoy. 👊🏻]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rygur8/ive_been_living_in_el_salvador_for_the_past_5/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frygur8%2Five_been_living_in_el_salvador_for_the_past_5%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frygur8%2Five_been_living_in_el_salvador_for_the_past_5%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rygur8/ive_been_living_in_el_salvador_for_the_past_5/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 01:51:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m an Italian podcaster and I’ve been traveling in the whole country to report the state of Bitcoin adoption. You can read my chronicles on my website. We post in English as well as in Italian. Hope u guys enjoy. 👊🏻&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cops can’t access $60M in seized bitcoin — fraudster won’t give password]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rycxwi/cops_cant_access_60m_in_seized_bitcoin_fraudster/?score=334&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frycxwi%2Fcops_cant_access_60m_in_seized_bitcoin_fraudster%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frycxwi%2Fcops_cant_access_60m_in_seized_bitcoin_fraudster%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rycxwi/cops_cant_access_60m_in_seized_bitcoin_fraudster/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 23:42:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[To Everyone Still Holding Let me See Those Beautiful Hands...]]></title><description><![CDATA[This post is intended to be a bit of a wellness check and morale boost during
these red days.

I know many are really disappointed that we didn’t quite see 100K EOY as many so
called “experts” have been predicting. And now we’re seeing a lot of red to
start the new year. Which is a good reminder…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryh5oj/to_everyone_still_holding_let_me_see_those/?score=349&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryh5oj%2Fto_everyone_still_holding_let_me_see_those%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryh5oj%2Fto_everyone_still_holding_let_me_see_those%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryh5oj/to_everyone_still_holding_let_me_see_those/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 23:42:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This post is intended to be a bit of a wellness check and morale boost during these red days. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know many are really disappointed that we didn’t quite see 100K EOY as many so called “experts” have been predicting. And now we’re seeing a lot of red to start the new year. Which is a good reminder that stonks along with Crypto don’t always go up in a straight line. But no need to be worried if we zoom out and look at how far we have come in a 1, 2, 5 years we see a lot of reason to still be super bullish. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now is the time to start up the old fiat miner and be getting ready as much disposable cash as you can to start DCAing into the market if you haven’t already been. If this is truly a bear (which I am still not convinced) this is where fortunes are made. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So don’t lose interest like many retailer investors are doing just cause we aren’t seeing crazy gains. Remember smart money is accumulating right now. So for once let’s not be dumb money and “buy high sell low” but instead be smart money and “buy low, buy lower, buy lowest, then sell high”. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So to those still holding on and stacking sats I am proud of you and I bet your mom is too. So to all those that haven’t lost faith and still accumulating during these uncertain times let me see those beautiful hands!!!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why your $20 buy order does matter]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’ve been noticing recently that people are saying “the ones saying buy the dips
are only throwing $20 at it”

So what? There buying crypto not every single person can throw a couple hundred
dollars at every dip, some people don’t have the luxury of having expendable
fiat to throw into crypto if…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rybq06/why_your_20_buy_order_does_matter/?score=319&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frybq06%2Fwhy_your_20_buy_order_does_matter%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frybq06%2Fwhy_your_20_buy_order_does_matter%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rybq06/why_your_20_buy_order_does_matter/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 22:36:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve been noticing recently that people are saying “the ones saying buy the dips are only throwing $20 at it” &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So what? There buying crypto not every single person can throw a couple hundred dollars at every dip, some people don’t have the luxury of having expendable fiat to throw into crypto if they did they would put more in crypto &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What you need to understand is not everyone has a high paying job or the cost of living in there area is higher then some, or they have a family to support and $20/week is all they can afford to spend on crypto. so how much you throw at a dip should be irrelevant&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What does matter though is that there at least buying the crypto dip and the amount shouldn’t be criticized. Instead we should be applauding the fact there at least thinking of there future &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;$20/week times 52 weeks= $1,040 a $20 buy order does add up quickly over time &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TLDR: We shouldn’t be criticizing peoples buy order amounts we don’t know what there finances or weekly expenses are. There at least buying crypto when they can&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Facts: Retail is not interested in BTC. Retail is chasing alt plays, NFTs and other trades where they can make money, and not Bitcoin. Bitcoin's network effect is stagnating massively and growth is falling off a cliff.]]></title><description><![CDATA[First of all, its wrong to say retail is not in crypto anymore - Anecdotal, I
was just in an NFT free mint that got sold out in literally 10 mins. Its a
little obscure project which might very well go to zero in about 2 weeks, but
even this one's discord server has over 10k users in just about 3…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ry8rsx/facts_retail_is_not_interested_in_btc_retail_is/?score=324&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fry8rsx%2Ffacts_retail_is_not_interested_in_btc_retail_is%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fry8rsx%2Ffacts_retail_is_not_interested_in_btc_retail_is%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ry8rsx/facts_retail_is_not_interested_in_btc_retail_is/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 21:37:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;First of all, its wrong to say retail is not in crypto anymore - Anecdotal, I was just in an NFT free mint that got sold out in literally 10 mins. Its a little obscure project which might very well go to zero in about 2 weeks, but even this one&amp;amp;#39;s discord server has over 10k users in just about 3 days. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And there are hundreds if not more such NFTs projects all over cryptoverse. This is all retail for you. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now, lets not turn this into NFT hate thread, I like to gamble on NFTs, some gamble on sports, some gamble on coins..so let that be.. its not the main topic of this post. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My point is that the retail are still in crypto as a whole. Some of them surely left with the crash, but many are around. To mint these NFTs you definitely need some crypto. Activity across many networks are still growing. OpenSea still is guzzling gas and is the top most used dapp. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The retail are just not interested in BTC at all. Many users are playing play to earn games or gambling NFTs. They are just not interested in buying Bitcoin&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Key stats:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;BTC activity is still at 2018 bear market levels. It hasnt grown at all. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.blockchain.com/charts/n-transactions&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.blockchain.com/charts/n-transactions&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This one is even more worrying for BTC - people have literally stopped using BTC since July: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://jochen-hoenicke.de/queue/#BTC,1y,weight&quot;&amp;gt;https://jochen-hoenicke.de/queue/#BTC,1y,weight&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There is no network effect growth whatsoever. Without network effect, the price doesnt grow much. In the absence of clear valuation models like discounted cash flow, network growth and volume transacted has been used to arrive at valuations for networks/blockchains, and here you have BTC&amp;amp;#39;s network growth falling off a cliff. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With other networks, people are not just investing and forgetting about it, but actively doing things - whether its lending or swapping tokens or minting some dumb jpeg. This brings people to explore the network, as seen by the rise in number of participants in almost every chain that has managed to get limelight. All of these chains have growing txn/day stats. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With Bitcoin, all one can do is invest and forget. In contrast to the above networks, the txn/day is still at 2018 levels. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A BTC argument is that LN adoption is increasing, but there is no real evidence for that. You cannot know how many LN transactions happen a day, and just volume increase to a few hundred million cannot substantiate tremendous growth. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sound money, censorship resistance etc are all good narratives but if the network usage is stagnating like above, it is really a cause to worry.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2 bananas, 591 sats ($0.25 / R4) and a Lightning Network fee of just 1 satoshi. Using @MuunWallet in South Africa's township.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rycq79/2_bananas_591_sats_025_r4_and_a_lightning_network/?score=496&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frycq79%2F2_bananas_591_sats_025_r4_and_a_lightning_network%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frycq79%2F2_bananas_591_sats_025_r4_and_a_lightning_network%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rycq79/2_bananas_591_sats_025_r4_and_a_lightning_network/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 20:42:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[LRC lets people mint an NFT for JUST $2.50, over 100X CHEAPER than on Opensea.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Loopring Layer 2 can now mint NFT's for just 100 gwei, or $2.50. This is
extremely cheap compared to what creators would have to pay on ETH L1 (~$300).

This removes a massive barrier to entry and is a huge step in the right
direction for crypto to get more mainstream adaption. Most artists don't…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryfl8u/lrc_lets_people_mint_an_nft_for_just_250_over/?score=815&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryfl8u%2Flrc_lets_people_mint_an_nft_for_just_250_over%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fryfl8u%2Flrc_lets_people_mint_an_nft_for_just_250_over%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ryfl8u/lrc_lets_people_mint_an_nft_for_just_250_over/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 20:42:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Loopring Layer 2 can now mint NFT&amp;amp;#39;s for just &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;100 gwei&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, or &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$2.50&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. This is &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;extremely&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; cheap compared to what creators would have to pay on ETH L1 (~$300).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This removes a &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;massive&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; barrier to entry and is a &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;huge&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; step in the right direction for crypto to get more mainstream adaption. Most artists don&amp;amp;#39;t have alot of capital so it&amp;amp;#39;s important to keep minting as &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;cheap&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; as &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;possible&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; so we can get more people into the cryptoverse.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You could previouisly get similar costs by using sidechains, but LRC manages to keep these low prices while SIMULTANEOUSLY maintaining &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Layer 1 security&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This isn’t a “20% correction.” This is a 40%+ bear market.]]></title><description><![CDATA[BTC is at $41-42k. ATH was at $69k. That’s a 40% drop from ATH, and that drop
has just been growing and growing for more than two months now.

That’s a bear market. Yeah, it’s not a crypto winter, but multiple months of
falling prices qualifies as a bear market, even if it’s short. Just like…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rydqsa/this_isnt_a_20_correction_this_is_a_40_bear_market/?score=660&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frydqsa%2Fthis_isnt_a_20_correction_this_is_a_40_bear_market%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frydqsa%2Fthis_isnt_a_20_correction_this_is_a_40_bear_market%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rydqsa/this_isnt_a_20_correction_this_is_a_40_bear_market/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 20:42:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;BTC is at $41-42k. ATH was at $69k. That’s a 40% drop from ATH, and that drop has just been growing and growing for more than two months now. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That’s a bear market. Yeah, it’s not a crypto winter, but multiple months of falling prices qualifies as a bear market, even if it’s short. Just like last summer was a bear market. It might get worse, or it might not. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Call it what it is. It’s not something to be afraid of; bear markets are where foundations are built. The people who are saying “Oh, this is just a dip” or “This is just a typical correction” are in denial and don’t know what the fuck they’re talking about.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[On this day, a year ago: Bitcoin hits $40,000 for first time]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ry19jv/on_this_day_a_year_ago_bitcoin_hits_40000_for/?score=319&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fry19jv%2Fon_this_day_a_year_ago_bitcoin_hits_40000_for%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fry19jv%2Fon_this_day_a_year_ago_bitcoin_hits_40000_for%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ry19jv/on_this_day_a_year_ago_bitcoin_hits_40000_for/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 17:43:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>