<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing on Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 05:22:33 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA["I still can't believe that this is the protest that would prove every Bitcoin crank a prophet. And for me to have to slice a piece of humble pie, and admit that I was wrong on crypto's fundamental necessity in Western democracies." David Heinemeier Hansson - Creator of Ruby on Rails]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sy12lp/i_still_cant_believe_that_this_is_the_protest/?score=320&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsy12lp%2Fi_still_cant_believe_that_this_is_the_protest%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsy12lp%2Fi_still_cant_believe_that_this_is_the_protest%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sy12lp/i_still_cant_believe_that_this_is_the_protest/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 04:33:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Canada's Ontario Securities Commission has apparently reported tweets from Kraken and Coinbase CEOs to law enforcement after they criticized Canada's Emergencies Act]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sy7kbm/canadas_ontario_securities_commission_has/?score=434&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsy7kbm%2Fcanadas_ontario_securities_commission_has%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsy7kbm%2Fcanadas_ontario_securities_commission_has%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sy7kbm/canadas_ontario_securities_commission_has/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 03:33:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BEGINNERS GUIDE to CRYPTOCURRENCY - All You Need to Know if You're Just Starting Out!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi all! This is going to be a VERY long post, I did my best to explain the
things I struggled with at the beginning of my Crypto journey. I am not an
expert by any means, but I feel I can provide valuable information to those
newer than me who are trying to get started but are overwhelmed by the…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sy4y4g/beginners_guide_to_cryptocurrency_all_you_need_to/?score=319&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsy4y4g%2Fbeginners_guide_to_cryptocurrency_all_you_need_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsy4y4g%2Fbeginners_guide_to_cryptocurrency_all_you_need_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sy4y4g/beginners_guide_to_cryptocurrency_all_you_need_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 02:37:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hi all! This is going to be a &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;VERY&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; long post, I did my best to explain the things I struggled with at the beginning of my Crypto journey. I am not an expert by any means, but I feel I can provide valuable information to those newer than me who are trying to get started but are overwhelmed by the amount of information on the internet.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I also have a Crypto/Finance &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCZPtriLb37Vth1KQ2u7PmGw&quot;&amp;gt;Youtube Channel&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and the text below is the transcript of my video. If you will gain some useful knowledge and have some time, I would &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;really&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; appreciate if you&amp;amp;#39;d take a look. :) &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TOPICS I COVER IN THIS POST&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Cryptocurrency&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Centralized vs Decentralized&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Distributed Ledger&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Blockchain&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Satoshi&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Bitcoin&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;White Paper&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Proof of Work&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Mining&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Proof of Stake&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ethereum&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Smart Contracts&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Coin vs Token&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Tokenomic&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Exchanges&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Wallets&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Mnemonic Phrases&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Types of Crypto&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;DEFI&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;DEXs&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Lending and Borrowing DAPPs&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;1. Cryptocurrency&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let’s start from ground zero: cryptocurrencies. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Everyone has heard of this term, but few know what it means. It derives from two words: cryptography and currency. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Cryptography&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; is at the basis of all cryptocurrencies as all of them depend on it to secure transaction records, to control the creation of additional coins, to verify the transfer of coins, and most importantly, to make them decentralized.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Secondly, they’re called &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;currency&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; because well, cryptos are a currency.. &amp;lt;del&amp;gt;for the most part&amp;lt;/del&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now, a cryptocurrency is a form of digital asset, so online, based on a network that is distributed across a vast number of computers, and they are based on something referred to as a distributed ledger, or, more specifically, blockchain technology.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;2. Centralized and Decentralized&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The difference between centralized and decentralized is that in a centralized system, as the name suggests, the power and control are in the hands of a central authority, usually it’s a very small and limited group of individuals, such as the owner of a business, or the director of bank, whereas a decentralized system is controlled by everyone who partakes in that system. In the case of crypto, it can be you, me, and everyone else.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The main point of cryptocurrencies is that they are decentralized, which contrasts with the traditional monetary payment systems such as banks and financial institutions, which are heavily centralized.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;3. Distributed Ledger&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A distributed ledger is a &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;PUBLIC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; decentralized database that is shared and synchronized by multiple people who have equal access to all the information shared across that network and can own an identical copy of it. Nobody is cut out, and everyone who wishes to partake in it, can do so.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One of the types of these distributed ledger databases is none other than blockchain, which is what cryptocurrencies are fundamentally based on.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;4. Blockchain&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A blockchain is a database that is shared among the participants, also called computers or nodes, of a network, and it stores information digitally. They are best known for their crucial role in cryptocurrency systems for maintaining a secured and decentralized record of transactions.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The mind-blowing innovation is that this technology guarantees the security of the data stored in it, without the need for a trusted third party, in other words not only there will be no need to have a central authority, but this technology was designed to be entirely public to anyone. You don’t see a bank’s internal transaction, you don’t see a company’s financial statements, but you see each Bitcoin user’s balance and transactions.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Another key difference between a typical database and a blockchain is how the data is structured. A blockchain, collects information together in groups, known as blocks, that hold sets of information together. These digital blocks, which are blocks just metaphorically speaking but not in the literal sense, have certain storage capacities, for example, each Bitcoin’s block is &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;1MB&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and can contain on average &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;2500 transactions&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When a block is filled and completed, it is linked to the previous completed block in a way we’ll see shortly, effectively forming a chain of blocks containing data, known as a blockchain.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;5. Satoshi&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This brings us to the first and most famous cryptocurrency that everyone knows, Bitcoin. It was created in &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;January 2009&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; by the pseudonymous &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Satoshi Nakamoto&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. No one to this day knows who he is, and people have been speculating about his identity for over a decade with speculations ranging from, for example, that he may have been a group of people rather than a single individual, or perhaps even one of the three letter agencies. There are a few valid candidates, but no one knows for sure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One thing however that is for sure is Satoshi’s hatred for banks and for the people at the top who hold the power to control financial systems to the point where they can willingly cause citizens to lose their livelihoods, homes, and sometimes, even lives through financial crashes, without any repercussion, such as the 2008 housing market crash.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Satoshi is said to own close to &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;1 million Bitcoins&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; divided in multiple addresses, which would place him at a net worth of 40 billion dollars today if it’s true, and IF he is still alive, and those are two big ifs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;6. White Paper&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Satoshi published the white paper of BTC in &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;October 2008.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; A white paper, in cryptocurrency, is a document released by a project’s funders, not only in the case of Bitcoin, but in the case of any &amp;lt;del&amp;gt;serious&amp;lt;/del&amp;gt; crypto project.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A white paper gives technical information about a project and its future roadmap. Satoshi’s vision for Bitcoin was quote “A purely peer-to-peer version of electronic cash would allow online payments to be sent directly from one party to another without going through a financial institution&amp;amp;quot;. He wanted people to have the means to make payments with a currency, Bitcoin, without being under the control of the big guys at the top while doing so.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But then begs the question.. how is consensus achieved? How do all the participants agree which transactions are valid and which are not, in a situation where everything is public and everyone, including bad people, can see everything?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;7. Consensus Mechanism&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here comes into play the part of consensus mechanisms. It is the process through which the nodes in charge of a blockchain database achieve consensus on the validity of each transaction and decide if to proceed with it, or not.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Being that everyone can take part in a blockchain we needed something to prevent any malicious user trying to hijack the network, for example, by creating fake transactions where he gives himself all the Bitcoins in existence and becomes the richest person in the world. This is also known as the double spending problem, and Bitcoin was the first system to solve it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To solve this, cryptocurrencies need some type of consensus method, through which, everyone taking part in the system, comes to a mutual agreement. There are multiple types of consensus mechanisms, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;the two main ones are Proof of Work and Proof of Stake&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;8. Proof of Work&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Proof of Work (PoW) is a decentralized consensus mechanism that requires all the participants of a network to spend computational power, solving a complex mathematical equation, commonly referred to as mining, to prevent anybody from manipulating the system.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now, let’s start with an example to make things easier.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are two friends, Bob and Alice. Each have $20 worth of Bitcoin and Bob sends Alice $10 of those $20, in a Bitcoin transaction. The transaction is placed in a block together with about 2500 other transactions, the block then gets confirmed and recorded into the blockchain. Now, Bob effectively has $10 worth of BTC, and Alice has $30 worth of BTC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To avoid Bob claiming he never sent that $10 worth of Bitcoin in the original block, there was let’s call it a code, more specifically &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;hash&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, placed in that block and it looked like this:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;000000000019d6689c085ae165831e934ff763ae46a2a6c172b3f1b60a8ce26f&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(First Bitcoin&amp;amp;#39;s Block Hash)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That hash uniquely identified the block which got filled with Bob and Alice’s transaction. It was created through an algorithm, and it was a sort of summary of all those unique 2500 transactions that took place in that block.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The following block will not only have its own unique hash as well, but that hash will merge with Bob and Alice’s block’s hash, forming a final hash and connecting the two blocks together, effectively creating a chain of linked blocks where each new block is connected to the previous one.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The third block will again have its own hash merged with the hash of the second block, which was merged with the hash of Bob and Alice’s block.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The catch point is, if just 1 of those 2500 transactions in each block is altered, the entire hash for that block will change, even if the other 2499 transactions are intact. This will inevitably cause the second block to be invalid as its hash wouldn’t match with the first block’s hash, which will cause the third block to not match with the hash of the second one and so on, and so on, effectively creating a chain  of events. &amp;lt;del&amp;gt;I know, this joke was not funny at all, but I wanted to say it.&amp;lt;/del&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do you see where I am getting with this?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The transactions are in the blocks, and all the blocks are linked together.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If Bob would alter his original transaction, the hash of the block in which the transaction was placed would change and would make all the following blocks with all the transactions in them, invalid. To successfully fake or alter a transaction, he would need to control a majority, at least 51%, of the entire computing power of the Bitcoin blockchain, to manipulate the following blocks quicker than the honest participants of the network.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;All of this, finally brings us to mining.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;9. Mining&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Mining, which is applied to any cryptocurrency based on Proof of Work such as Bitcoin, Ethereum (for now), Dogecoin, Litecoin and many more, is the process by which new coins enter in circulation. It is also the way a network confirms new transactions, and it is a critical component of a blockchain ledger&amp;amp;#39;s maintenance and development.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Participants need to use their computational power through specific mining hardware, called application-specific integrated circuit, or &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ASIC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;s, to solve a complex and random mathematical equation in order to create a new block.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Put in simple terms, those very powerful machines have to guess a certain number. The more computer power you have, the higher the chances to guess that number before anyone else does are.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Whoever guesses it first, will effectively create a new block and new Bitcoins (or any other crypto that is mined) into existence, and those Bitcoins will be rewarded to them as a reward for the time and effort they had to put in to sustain the network.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This process allows for the removal of bad players from the ecosystem, as taking part in it requires huge amounts of resources such as space, electricity, and especially the costs of mining hardware.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You need to know however that not all Proof of Work cryptos require ASIC card to be mined. It depends on the algorithm on which a crypto is built on. Any mineable crypto can be mined in one of two ways, either through ASIC cards or normal GPUs such as Nvidia or AMD cards.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For example, to mine Ethereum, the second largest crypto, you can do it from your computer’s graphics card and does not require you to buy any additional components, and that’s why all Nvidia’s new 3000 series GPUs are always sold out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Mining has extensively been up to debate as it consumes a lot of electricity due to the huge power consumption of graphics cards. Back in the day, you could mine Bitcoin from your laptop, but those days are long gone now. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now. Here is where the genius of Satoshi comes into place, which is applied to any proof of work cryptocurrency, not just Bitcoin.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The more powerful GPUs get, the more difficult it will become to solve this mathematical equation and create new blocks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Wait.. what? Shouldn’t it become faster rather than slower, if more powerful components become available? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin was programmed so that one block would be mined every 10 minutes on average, and every 2016 blocks, or about two weeks, or the algorithm calculates how long it took to mine those blocks. If it took more than 14 days it means that it was too difficult and the difficulty will decrease, if it took less than 14 days it means that it was too easy, and the difficulty will increase. The more people enter the network and start mining, the more difficult mining becomes to obtain the same results and the more powerful GPU’s will be required to produce those same results.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Each Bitcoin block rewards 6.25 Bitcoins to the winner. This reward is cut in half approximately every 4 years and it is called halving.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At the beginning, the reward was 50 BTC per block. The first halving happened in 2012 and it reduced the block reward to 25 BTC. The second halving was in 2016 and it reduced the reward to 12.5 BTC, and finally, the last halving happened in May 2020 which brought the reward to 6.25BTC per block. The next one will be in 2024 and it will drop the reward to 3.125 BTC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On a final note, mining crypto on your own, especially in the case of Bitcoin, is close to impossible unless you are considerably wealthy, because it would require an absurd amount of capital just to have a small chance to mine a block, that’s why there are networks called mining pools, made of thousands if not tens of thousands of people combining their computing power to mine one specific crypto together and proportionally split the block rewards. The vast majority of mining pools are either in Bitcoin or Ethereum.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;10. Proof of Stake&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As the second most used consensus mechanism, we have Proof of Stake. The holders of a Proof of Stake crypto will deposit and lock up, called staking, the coins of that crypto that they own, and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;become a validator&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. By doing this, they will get the chance to be chosen to validate the next block, and whoever does it, will be rewarded the block reward.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Whether a validator will get chosen to validate the next block will depend on different factors, two of the main ones are randomness and how many coins they staked. This cuts out the gigantic energy and resources consumption that happens with Proof of Work as with Proof of Stake you do not require any sort of specific computer hardware.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At the same time however, people argue that this consensus mechanism tends to reward those already wealthy, as the more coins you have, the more likely the chances to be randomly selected and earn the block rewards are.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some argue that this makes the ecosystem more centralized as wealthier individuals become even wealthier, however, the same argument can also be applied to Proof of Work, as if you have more capital you can afford to buy more mining equipment which in contrast will generate more revenue. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;11. Ethereum&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This connects us to Ethereum. The second largest cryptocurrency by market cap since its creation in 2016, second only to Bitcoin.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Ethereum has always been on POW just like Bitcoin, but it is currently migrating to POS to solve several issues such as transaction fees, called gas fees, and transactions per second.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The main difference from Bitcoin, is that Ethereum features a key technology called “smart contracts”.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;12. Smart Contracts&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Smart contracts are automated programs, built on the Ethereum blockchain, or any other blockchain with smart contract capabilities. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;They are fully controlled by code&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and once deployed on the blockchain, they cannot be changed or altered. They allow you to build multiple programmable functions on top of them, to be executed once a criteria is met.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With Bitcoin, for example, all you can do is transfer the coin as a means of payment and you cannot build anything on top of its blockchain. With Ethereum however, besides transferring its main coin, Ether, you can build and create all sorts of applications on it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And no, Ether and Ethereum are not quite exactly the same thing. Ethereum is the blockchain, the network, the foundation, whereas Ether is the native coin of the blockchain.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The most famous examples of smart contracts by far, are well, NFTs, and it shouldn’t really come at a surprise.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On the other hand, however, there are also useful smart contracts that provide real financial services, such as crypto lending and borrowing, decentralized exchanges, liquidity pools, insurance services, and much more, but we will get into that a bit later.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;13. Coin vs Token&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now. All of them are cryptocurrencies, but not all of them are coins or tokens. Many people call them coins when in reality, they are tokens or call them tokens when in reality, they are coins.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The difference is that &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;a coin is native to its own blockchain&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, Ether is a coin native to its own blockchain called Ethereum. Bitcoin is a coin native to its own blockchain called Bitcoin. Shiba inu, however, is a token because it is built on Ethereum’s blockchain. Creating a fully operable blockchain is way more difficult than creating a token on an already established blockchain.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;14. Tokenomics&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now, let’s get into how the value of a cryptocurrency is derived and its tokenomics, which is simply a term that indicates the economics of a crypto.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Supply&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; - The first and most important thing of any given cryptocurrency is the supply. This can be further divided into three categories:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Maximum Supply&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Total Supply&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Circulating Supply&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Maximum Supply&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - It is the amount of tokens or coins of a crypto that will ever exist, including the ones that will be created through mining, staking, or made available in the future. Bitcoin&amp;amp;#39;s maximum supply is 21,000,000 coins which will only be reached in over 100 years from now. Ethereum, on the other hand, has an unlimited max supply.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Total Supply&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; – It is the amount of coins or tokens of a crypto currently in existence, including the ones that may not be publicly available, such as those locked in an escrow or held by the team, but without counting the coins or tokens yet to be created and put into existence through mining, staking etc.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Circulating Supply&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - Circulating supply is the amount of a crypto in circulation in the present moment and in the hands of the general public, EXCLUDING the coins or tokens of that crypto, that are locked or held by entities such as the team behind the project.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Market Cap&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; – Market capitalization, or market cap for short, is the dollar value of all the coins or tokens of a crypto combined and it is calculated by multiplying the total supply by the last price a single coin or token was sold for. In the case of Bitcoin, there are approximately 18,950,000 Bitcoins, and with about $40,000 per coin, it would place the market cap at around 750 billion dollars.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;15. Exchanges&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now, However, begs the question, where are these cryptocurrencies bought from and how do you store them safely?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cryptocurrencies are generally bought from what are called &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;centralized exchanges&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. They are regulated companies which provide you the service of acting as a trusted middlemen between the people who want to sell a specific crypto, and the people who want to buy it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They decide which cryptos to list and there is no exchange that has all the cryptos in existence listed. It is a decision up to them. There are exchanges which list as many cryptos as possible to earn as much as they can, and exchanges known for listing as few as possible, but when they do, it’s all over the news &amp;lt;del&amp;gt;*cough* Coinbase *cough*&amp;lt;/del&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The way they stay in business is by charging a small commission on each trade. The typical commission fee averages between 0.05% and 0.1%, and the larger your order will be, the lesser you will pay in fees.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;16. Wallets&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After you purchase a cryptocurrency on an exchange, the next step is always choosing how to store it safely. There are two main types of crypto storages. Custodial and non-custodial wallets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Custodial Wallets -&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Someone else retains custody of your assets. You do not own your cryptos but they do, on your behalf. These are mostly the previously mentioned exchanges, and this is where the famous phrase in the crypto community “not your keys, not your coins” comes from.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;By giving up custody of your funds, you have a better peace of mind because you do not bear the responsibility of securing your assets and all the risks involved with it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Crypto community however has mixed feelings on whether holding your cryptos on an exchange is worth it due to previous exchange hacks which resulted in stolen and lost funds on multiple occasions. On top of that, it totally ruins the goal of crypto: to escape from the control of centralized entities and aiming to be our own banks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Non-Custodial Wallets&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; - These are the wallets that you personally own and hold your crypto in. They can be mainly divided into two categories: hot wallets and cold wallets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Hot Wallets&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; - They are software, usually apps you can download on your phone, such as the Trust wallet, Exodus or Coinbase wallet. They do offer a fantastic grade of protection and are free to use. You are the only owner of your assets and under most circumstances they are more than enough to protect what you hold, but if your device becomes compromised, you can lose everything. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The most famous hot wallet by far is Metamask. It’s an Ethereum based wallet that comes as a web browser extension and every Ethereum compatible blockchain, such as Binance Smart Chain, Polygon and Avalanche, plus all the decentralized applications built on those blockchains, are compatible with Metamask. They also have a mobile app, but it’s not used as often.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Cold Wallets&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; - They are offline physical devices such as the Ledger Nano and the Trezor. You usually connect them to the computer through a cable and use a specific program to access them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The difference is that you will have to write your mnemonic phrase, we’ll get into what it is shortly, and approve transactions from the device itself which cannot get accessed unless someone has physical access to it, and as it is offline it can’t be hacked. They offer a way higher grade of protection because they do not rely on the security of your mobile phone or computer and that’s why they cost from around $60 to $200 to buy, depending on the type and features. For this reason, it isn’t the best option if you do not have much money to begin investing with. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Broadly speaking, most crypto holders, including myself, tend to agree that if you have a small capital to invest, it might be better to keep it on an established exchange, especially if it is in Ethereum, and transferring those coins out would cost a fortune in transaction fees.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The most important thing to know if you decide to buy a hardware wallet, is to &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ALWAYS&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; buy it from the official company’s website and not from a third-party seller, even if you might find it discounted. This is because you would increase the risk of receiving a tampered device, which is by no means worth it just to save a few dollars.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;17. Mnemonic Phrases&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now, mnemonic phrases. All you need to know to keep your crypto safe is that when you create a so called “account” on a wallet, you are given a random set of 12-18-24 words which is called a mnemonic phrase. This combination of words will act as a password to access all your crypto. These words are randomly chosen from a specific list of 2048 words, and each word can all be identified by the first four letters. This technology was designed so that we could have a human readable “password” instead of a random set of numbers and letters.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;THE MOST IMPORTANT THING&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; you need to understand is that your crypto will &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;NOT&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; be stored in that mobile app or ledger device, but on the blockchain. The wallets are just a gateway, like an intermediary, that provide an easy-to-use interface for everyone.  The one and only thing you must carefully store, is the mnemonic phrase.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you lose your phone with a hot wallet installed, or a hardware device like the ledger nano, nothing will happen to your crypto as long as you still have access to the mnemonic phrase, which you can use to restore your crypto on a new wallet.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You absolutely &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;MUST&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; write down on at least two pieces of paper those words, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;NEVER&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; take pictures or screenshots of them, store them safely and never tell anyone where they are.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do not try to bury your ledger nano 10 feet under the ground, the only thing that matters is the mnemonic phrase which can be restored on any wallet, both hot and cold. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As you can imagine, the difficulty with self-custody is evident. If you lose access to both your seed phrase and to the device where it was connected, your crypto will be lost forever. Hacking a mnemonic phrase is impossible, and 99% of those “hacking” claims you see online are simply because people’s phones or computers were either compromised or they accidentally screenshotted or emailed themselves the mnemonic phrase, or sometimes even both, for the sake of comfort, and it got leaked.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;18. Types of Cryptocurrencies&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Going back to Cryptos. There are many types of cryptocurrencies, but only about eight are the most common:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Store of Values&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Smart Contracts&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Stablecoins&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Payments&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Privacy&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Exchange Tokens or Coins&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Governance tokens&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Sh*tcoins&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Store of Value&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - They are designed to hold their value and purchasing power over time. The only crypto which is arguably considered to be one is Bitcoin because it has always tremendously increased in value over time since its inception rather than losing value like our beloved fiat currencies. People believe it is an effective hedge against inflation and that’s why Bitcoin is sometimes referred to as digital gold.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Smart Contract&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - They are designed to be programmable and allow building applications on their blockchain, for different purposes. The most famous and used one, is Ethereum. This brought to the creation of Decentralized finance, or DEFI, in which we’ll get into in a minute. Other examples of smart contract cryptos are Binance Smart Chain, Avalanche and Solana.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Stablecoins&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - They are usually pegged to fiat currencies, mostly, to the US dollar. They hold all the properties of any other crypto, but their value is… stable. For example, when a stablecoin is indeed pegged to the dollar, the goal will always be to maintain and hold the value of one dollar per coin. They aim to eliminate price volatility and to provide a stable medium of exchange without the need to cash out, or, in other words, without the need to withdraw those dollars to your bank account. Examples are: USDT (to avoid), USDC, BUSD and DAI&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Payment&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - They are very fast and cost very little to transact with. They are exceptionally good for transferring money quickly and cheaply. However, they tend to be more centralized as they require powerful machines to run them which normal people have no access to.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Privacy&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - They have.. well, privacy. You see, the thing with Bitcoin that not many understand is that it is pseudonymous. All the transactions, addresses and balances are nameless, but public. Everything can be easily tracked, but nobody knows which address you own. If, however, someone finds it out, they will immediately see how much you own, who you sent crypto to, and all your transactions. There are cryptos, however, that offer full privacy and anonymity of balances and transactions. Examples are Monero and Zcash.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Exchange Tokens or Coins&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - They are created by the exchanges from which you can purchase crypto. They offer you perks such as fee discounts if you hold their coin or token and use it to pay for the fees. The most famous one is by far Binance, and its coin, Binance coin. If you paid attention I said coin, and that is because Binance also created its own blockchain called Binance Smart Chain, with BNB as the native coin, just like ETH is the native coin of Ethereum.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Governance Tokens&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - They grant voting and management powers to their users. They are very important in DeFi ecosystems such as Uniswap.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Memecoins, also called Sh\&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;tcoins* - They are always created on other blockchains, just like Shiba Inu is on Ethereum. The only major exception is Dogecoin, which has its own blockchain. They serve no purpose or utility and people just buy them in the hopes of making money, which sometimes works, don’t get me wrong, otherwise we wouldn’t be hearing about them, but the best way to describe them, is gambling.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;19. DeFi&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now that we covered the basics of the basics, and I know it’s lot, especially if you’re a beginner, let’s get into the final part with a bit more complex stuff.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;DeFi&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; - As we mentioned, smart contracts are automated programs that are built to follow a specific function, such as if I give you X amount of ETH, I receive X amount of a token built on Ethereum. Once deployed on a blockchain, these smart contracts cannot be changed, hence they are decentralized.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you combine multiple smart contracts into something more complex, you get decentralized finance, or DeFi, with decentralized applications, or &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;DAPPs&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;DeFi is a collective term for financial products and services that are built on a blockchain and are accessible to anyone. These services are always open and there are no centralized authorities who can block payments or deny you access to something, as everything is fully based on code.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In other words, DeFi cuts out the middleman and offers financial services to everyone, and unlike banks, it does so without discrimination. Let’s get now into a couple of examples of real world use cases.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Decentralized Exchanges&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; - They are simply exchanges where you can trade cryptocurrencies, with the difference that they are decentralized. They are built on one or multiple blockchains and you can trade any token built on that blockchain (or blockchains). These can range from stablecoins, to governance tokens, to meme coins.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The main pros of using a decentralized exchange is the fact that you do not need to create an account or share your personal information, everything is done in a completely anonymous way. You usually just need to create a Metamask wallet, and you are good to go.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On the downside however, if you want to trade Ethereum based tokens, you will pay astronomical transaction fees, and on top of that, you will be the only person responsible for any loss of funds.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The most famous example is Uniswap, and you can use it to trade any token built on Ethereum.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Lending and Borrowing&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; - I’ll start this one with an example. Let’s say you own 2000$ worth of ETH and you believe that it is going to go to the moon soon. Let’s also hypothetically say that you find yourself in a real-life emergency situation and you need 1000$.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You will now have two options. You can either sell half of your ETH and call it a day, but miss out on an eventual price appreciation, or you can lock up your ETH as collateral in a lending and borrowing decentralized application and borrow 1000$ worth of a stable coin against the collateral that you just deposited. This way, you will end up with keeping your position in ETH and be able to ride it and you will also get the $1000 you need.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To get back your ETH you would obviously need to pay back your debt of $1000 plus the occurring borrowing fees.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Respectively, if you wish to earn passive income, you can lock up your Crypto with the ability to withdraw it anytime (zoom face) and lend it to those interested in borrowing it just like in our previous example. In exchange, you will earn an interest, which is way higher than the 0.5% that a bank’s savings account gives you, while the inflation rate for 2021 rose up 7%.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;20. Conclusion&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you had the patience to read through these ~5500 words, thank you so much and I hope you gained some value!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I am intrigued by Biden’s executive order on crypto.]]></title><description><![CDATA[As many of you know Biden is expected to sign an executive order on crypto
regulation this week. I believe this is nothing but great news. Some of you
right about now are probably thinking I am crazy because “regulation” is never a
good thing. But in this case it is, or should I say, could be.…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxuulh/i_am_intrigued_by_bidens_executive_order_on_crypto/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxuulh%2Fi_am_intrigued_by_bidens_executive_order_on_crypto%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxuulh%2Fi_am_intrigued_by_bidens_executive_order_on_crypto%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxuulh/i_am_intrigued_by_bidens_executive_order_on_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 01:03:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As many of you know Biden is expected to sign an executive order on crypto regulation this week. I believe this is nothing but great news. Some of you right about now are probably thinking I am crazy because “regulation” is never a good thing. But in this case it is, or should I say, could be. Shining the light on crypto and providing a base set of regulations could open the door to a whole new world of investors such as major institutions and every day investors such as you and me. Crypto will never be widely accepted by the majority until there are some forms of regulation. Now saying that, I am not for overstepping the boundaries and the government going all out to try to kill crypto in general. But I am for a small set of regulations to ease the mind of those on the fence for investing or making it any option for their investors. How does everyone else feel? This is just a general discussion to go over the possible pros and cons of the executive order.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Avalanche-based protocol reportedly rug-pulled within hours of launch]]></title><description><![CDATA[I really don't understand how this is legal. Atom Protocol, was rug pulled
within a day of launching. The developers posted a message on Twitter before
deleting all its social…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxsdqp/avalanchebased_protocol_reportedly_rugpulled/?score=347&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxsdqp%2Favalanchebased_protocol_reportedly_rugpulled%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxsdqp%2Favalanchebased_protocol_reportedly_rugpulled%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxsdqp/avalanchebased_protocol_reportedly_rugpulled/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 22:40:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I really don&amp;amp;#39;t understand how this is legal. Atom Protocol, was rug pulled within a day of launching. The developers posted a message on Twitter before deleting all its social channels:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/jlc71errj6j81.png?width=1214&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=68e0da357c6442d31c69d6c6e3c3f4783e6d76b7&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/jlc71errj6j81.png?width=1214&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=68e0da357c6442d31c69d6c6e3c3f4783e6d76b7&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Discord channel was turned off too. The sale of its token ATM has also been halted. It had a Know-Your-Customer (KYC) protocol in place. Users are now questioning Assure DeFi after it conducted the KYC for Atom Protocol.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/l3sifh5tj6j81.png?width=1268&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=21e95b976afda34e77096878b084c567bd999874&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/l3sifh5tj6j81.png?width=1268&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=21e95b976afda34e77096878b084c567bd999874&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m really shocked about this one. There has to be a deterrent in place to prevent this from happening.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto Is Not Decentralized]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is really aimed specifically at the BTC maxis, but holds true for pretty
much every project out there. Decentralization was the point, right? Well, it
didn't work.

Using BTC as the example: the proof of work concept points it towards a
decentralized concept - but in actual practice, it's…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxy32g/crypto_is_not_decentralized/?score=347&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxy32g%2Fcrypto_is_not_decentralized%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxy32g%2Fcrypto_is_not_decentralized%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxy32g/crypto_is_not_decentralized/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 22:40:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is really aimed specifically at the BTC maxis, but holds true for pretty much every project out there. Decentralization was the point, right? Well, it didn&amp;amp;#39;t work.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Using BTC as the example: the proof of work concept points it towards a decentralized concept - but in actual practice, it&amp;amp;#39;s not. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/baqvw45sq7j81.png?width=1172&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=c367e68a3056e16d53b28ddd3ff8add662fddf58&quot;&amp;gt; Pool Distribution &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;FOUR MINERS CONTROL 53% OF BITCOIN&amp;amp;#39;S HASHING POWER.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What this shows is that there is a preferred nature to progression - and it&amp;amp;#39;s actively at odds with the concept of decentralization. BTC set an incredibly high bar for hashing while holding appeal for people to try it. The issue is that the for the common person, BTC mining is cost prohibitive. So, what do people naturally do when something is cost prohibitive? &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;They pool their resources&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Which, normally, works out great! Except that&amp;amp;#39;s the exact &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;opposite&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; of what the mission was: decentralization. Pooling resources is literally &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;centralization&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;. By removing the individual autonomy of participants - the original targeted democratic governance is reduced to an oligopoly.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Almost every single thing people love about crypto - the exploding value, the decentralization, etc., is all fundamentally undercut by the processes you use to exploit it. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How do you buy BTC? We used to buy it P2P. Now, the most common outlet is a CEX. From decentralized - to centralized. CEXs are nothing but &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;pooled resources&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, when people claim BTC is &amp;amp;#39;decentralized&amp;amp;#39; all I can do is laugh. It&amp;amp;#39;s a network dominated by four entities and entirely reliant on centralized exchanges. That&amp;amp;#39;s why it is what it is today. BTC doesn&amp;amp;#39;t hit $30k, 40k+ without massive money coming in - and that money is, surprise... pooled. &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;That&amp;amp;#39;s what institutional investments are&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;: &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;pooled resources&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;BTC had an incredible vision - but the reality is, it has been entirely usurped - and largely by the same people that still sing it&amp;amp;#39;s original vision as if that&amp;amp;#39;s somehow what made it what it is today. Which is simple not true.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[#bitcoin 200 week moving average still increasing. Ignore volatility, focus on the trend. https://t.co/6nruFNj9ne]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1495836741680435202/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1495836741680435202/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 20:41:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dude posts on r/bitcoin that BTC "saved his life" because he couldn't access his bank account when he was getting gas and sold some BTC to buy some. I have some advice how you can save your life in an emergency like that.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Okay, the story
[https://np.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/sxe145/bitcoin_saved_my_life/] is
really tragic, so only read if you are emotionally prepared. OP was on a little
road trip with his family and when he wanted to get gas his card didn't work. He
called the bank and

> they had froze my…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxtqbf/dude_posts_on_rbitcoin_that_btc_saved_his_life/?score=335&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxtqbf%2Fdude_posts_on_rbitcoin_that_btc_saved_his_life%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxtqbf%2Fdude_posts_on_rbitcoin_that_btc_saved_his_life%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxtqbf/dude_posts_on_rbitcoin_that_btc_saved_his_life/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 19:31:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Okay, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/sxe145/bitcoin_saved_my_life/&quot;&amp;gt;the story&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; is really tragic, so only read if you are emotionally prepared. OP was on a little road trip with his family and when he wanted to get gas his card didn&amp;amp;#39;t work. He called the bank and &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;they had froze my accounts due to &amp;amp;quot;suspected fraudulent activity&amp;amp;quot; and said there was nothing they could do for 24 hours&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sure, that&amp;amp;#39;s how it works, this is a real story. You know, it&amp;amp;#39;s just like that totally not just Hollywood trope but real thing that police have to wait 24 hours to look for a missing person. Okay, so in this real situation OPs life was threatened - stranded, probably in the US - how could one survive for 24 hours?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Well, fortunately OP found a solution:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I remembered I had some money in bitcoin. I was able to find a crypto atm (didn&amp;amp;#39;t even know those existed) within a quarter mile that I walked to. At this atm, I was able to sell some of my bitcoin and withdraw cash from the atm, which I was then able to use to buy gas to get home. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Phew, he escaped death this time. Someone posted this story on this sub as well before, titling it &amp;amp;quot;That’s why we need Crypto&amp;amp;quot;. And that&amp;amp;#39;s absolutely true! But just in case you ever get into such a life-threatening situation and don&amp;amp;#39;t have crypto, I have some advice for you:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;don&amp;amp;#39;t die, ideally. There is nothing dangerous about the situation, worst case is you&amp;amp;#39;ll have to spend the night somewhere close-by and pay once your accounts get unfrozen (even though it&amp;amp;#39;s reeeeally unlikely that your accounts, plural, all get frozen and that your wife, who is accompanying you, seemingly doesn&amp;amp;#39;t have any)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;carry a bit of cash with you? I know, cash is not as obvious as crypto and many people don&amp;amp;#39;t know you can exchange it for goods, but it actually works quite well, with instant, free transactions&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;To sum up: don&amp;amp;#39;t make up incredibly stupid stories that try to show how useful crypto is, and then make up a situation that could much more easily be solved using cash. Yes, we all like crypto and hope it will have a lot of utility in the future, but we don&amp;amp;#39;t have to pretend it&amp;amp;#39;s more essential than it is in today&amp;amp;#39;s world.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is this huge for adoption news for us or is the government tying to make appreciating tax dollars? Either way, is this good or bad for crypto ?]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sxwwd8/is_this_huge_for_adoption_news_for_us_or_is_the/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsxwwd8%2Fis_this_huge_for_adoption_news_for_us_or_is_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsxwwd8%2Fis_this_huge_for_adoption_news_for_us_or_is_the%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sxwwd8/is_this_huge_for_adoption_news_for_us_or_is_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 19:31:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trudeau Government Moves to Make Expanded Surveillance Powers over Financial Transactions ‘Permanent’]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sxpkb8/trudeau_government_moves_to_make_expanded/?score=318&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsxpkb8%2Ftrudeau_government_moves_to_make_expanded%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsxpkb8%2Ftrudeau_government_moves_to_make_expanded%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sxpkb8/trudeau_government_moves_to_make_expanded/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 19:31:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[We will all be bank free soon.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sxxbzb/we_will_all_be_bank_free_soon/?score=539&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsxxbzb%2Fwe_will_all_be_bank_free_soon%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsxxbzb%2Fwe_will_all_be_bank_free_soon%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sxxbzb/we_will_all_be_bank_free_soon/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 19:31:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Keep stacking those sats in the eye of the storm🙂]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sxrn5v/keep_stacking_those_sats_in_the_eye_of_the_storm/?score=368&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsxrn5v%2Fkeep_stacking_those_sats_in_the_eye_of_the_storm%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsxrn5v%2Fkeep_stacking_those_sats_in_the_eye_of_the_storm%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sxrn5v/keep_stacking_those_sats_in_the_eye_of_the_storm/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 18:39:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[After losing more than 100k in Leverage and Spot trading, I finally understood what Warren Buffet means]]></title><description><![CDATA[Not going to be a long post fellas, but I've had my fair share of buying Doge at
0.69 on Spot, various leverage trades on random coins, followed TG channels for
"signals", needless to say, I never knew when to sell or when to buy.

There is an indicator called "Bitcoin fear and greed…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxrt6h/after_losing_more_than_100k_in_leverage_and_spot/?score=333&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxrt6h%2Fafter_losing_more_than_100k_in_leverage_and_spot%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxrt6h%2Fafter_losing_more_than_100k_in_leverage_and_spot%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxrt6h/after_losing_more_than_100k_in_leverage_and_spot/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 17:37:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Not going to be a long post fellas, but I&amp;amp;#39;ve had my fair share of buying Doge at 0.69 on Spot, various leverage trades on random coins, followed TG channels for &amp;amp;quot;signals&amp;amp;quot;, needless to say, I never knew when to sell or when to buy.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There is an indicator called &amp;amp;quot;Bitcoin fear and greed chart&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://alternative.me/crypto/fear-and-greed-index/&quot;&amp;gt;https://alternative.me/crypto/fear-and-greed-index/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The formula is simple, if you see it over 70-80 and &amp;amp;quot;Extreme Greed&amp;amp;quot; is present, this is when you should consider transferring cryptos into USDTs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now let&amp;amp;#39;s say you&amp;amp;#39;ve been sitting on USDT coins, and you feel like you want to buy a dip that just happened. Before you do that, you head over to the same damn chart, and check what it says.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anytime below 25-20 is an excellent time to buy.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And that&amp;amp;#39;s it folks, the formula is extremely easy. Now we are seeing Extreme fear on the chart at 25. Is it a good time to buy?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CRO is the #1 growing ticker on reddit over the past three months]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sx5udr/cro_is_the_1_growing_ticker_on_reddit_over_the/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsx5udr%2Fcro_is_the_1_growing_ticker_on_reddit_over_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsx5udr%2Fcro_is_the_1_growing_ticker_on_reddit_over_the%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sx5udr/cro_is_the_1_growing_ticker_on_reddit_over_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 17:37:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin wallet rejects Canada’s Court demand to freeze funds citing technically impossible]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxv8fd/bitcoin_wallet_rejects_canadas_court_demand_to/?score=457&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxv8fd%2Fbitcoin_wallet_rejects_canadas_court_demand_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxv8fd%2Fbitcoin_wallet_rejects_canadas_court_demand_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxv8fd/bitcoin_wallet_rejects_canadas_court_demand_to/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 16:34:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vitalik Buterin confirms Bear market by showing up to conference dressed as a grizzly.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Vitalik had earlier hinted that the crypto community would welcome a long
winter. He said that crypto could benefit from a crash as short term speculative
attention is not good in the long run, while builders could benefit from less
attention from speculators.

Now he has made his strongest…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxp4n2/vitalik_buterin_confirms_bear_market_by_showing/?score=457&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxp4n2%2Fvitalik_buterin_confirms_bear_market_by_showing%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxp4n2%2Fvitalik_buterin_confirms_bear_market_by_showing%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxp4n2/vitalik_buterin_confirms_bear_market_by_showing/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 11:33:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Vitalik had earlier hinted that the crypto community would welcome a long winter. He said that crypto could benefit from a crash as short term speculative attention is not good in the long run, while builders could benefit from less attention from speculators. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now he has made his strongest statement yet confirming the bear market, as he showed up to the EthDenver conference dressed as a bear. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/hmnqu19nc5j81.jpg?width=623&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=0ed400f123b11ec14e6c91039a6c9e26fe8bdc36&quot;&amp;gt;Lord Saviour bear. &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Few other shots of the bear spotted in the wild:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/isukgm8rc5j81.jpg?width=555&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=728ca572bf3ca15f32bcc7bbf4904edf482aaf2f&quot;&amp;gt;The menacing bear&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/farksdfvc5j81.jpg?width=1200&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d94260c21c8e5fd42bf36141e8da81fe3b4f61b9&quot;&amp;gt;Fashion speaks louder than words. &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto markets have corrected steeply from their highs made in 2021 and the weak price action looks set to continue as geopolitical risks and fed tightening cycle are set to play out throughout 2022. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, there is a debate among crypto market participants as to what actually constitutes a bear market. In stocks, a bear market is typically said to occur when stock prices crash by 20%. However given the volatile nature of crypto markets, 20% is a rather low threshold, and it is debatable whether 50% would also constitute a bear market or if it is just a down trend in an historically up only market. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In this context, Vitalik Buterin - one of the prominent leaders of the space laying it down is a rather strong statement that we are indeed in a bear market.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Saved My Life]]></title><description><![CDATA[This happened about a week ago.

Was heading home from a little road trip and had to stop around about 2 hours
away from home for gas. Had the wife and kids with me. Went to fill up and my
cards keep getting declined. Try to call the bank and they had froze my accounts
due to "suspected fraudulent…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sxe145/bitcoin_saved_my_life/?score=329&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsxe145%2Fbitcoin_saved_my_life%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsxe145%2Fbitcoin_saved_my_life%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sxe145/bitcoin_saved_my_life/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 09:31:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This happened about a week ago. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Was heading home from a little road trip and had to stop around about 2 hours away from home for gas. Had the wife and kids with me. Went to fill up and my cards keep getting declined. Try to call the bank and they had froze my accounts due to &amp;amp;quot;suspected fraudulent activity&amp;amp;quot; and said there was nothing they could do for 24 hours. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;No way to access any of my money and didn&amp;amp;#39;t have enough gas to make it home. Was starting to get a little nervous. Then I remembered I had some money in bitcoin. I was able to find a crypto atm (didn&amp;amp;#39;t even know those existed) within a quarter mile that I walked to. At this atm, I was able to sell some of my bitcoin and withdraw cash from the atm, which I was then able to use to buy gas to get home. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Insanely lucky I had funds that were practical/useful when my bank was not accessible. And thus I realized the true benefit of Bitcoin. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just wanted to share, as I&amp;amp;#39;ve never seen, firsthand, the practical use of crypto currency before. Here was a situation where I was unable to access a resource through a &amp;amp;quot;respected&amp;amp;quot; financial institution, but i was able to access and utilize crypto currency. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TLDR: Stuck out of town and needed gas. Bank accounts frozen but was able to use BTC to pay and get home.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trudeau Government Moves to Make Expanded Surveillance Powers over Financial Transactions ‘Permanent’]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxha8f/trudeau_government_moves_to_make_expanded/?score=400&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxha8f%2Ftrudeau_government_moves_to_make_expanded%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxha8f%2Ftrudeau_government_moves_to_make_expanded%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxha8f/trudeau_government_moves_to_make_expanded/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 06:44:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What do you say to people who dismiss crypto as a 'Ponzi Scheme'?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'll be honest, I'm always a bit flustered when this one gets levelled, because
I never know where to begin in trying to debunk it. This is mainly because there
are absolutely aspects of crypto investing that give off Ponzi vibes to the
uninitiated - just look at all those rugged tokens, even the…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sx5fij/what_do_you_say_to_people_who_dismiss_crypto_as_a/?score=307&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsx5fij%2Fwhat_do_you_say_to_people_who_dismiss_crypto_as_a%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsx5fij%2Fwhat_do_you_say_to_people_who_dismiss_crypto_as_a%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sx5fij/what_do_you_say_to_people_who_dismiss_crypto_as_a/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 04:39:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ll be honest, I&amp;amp;#39;m always a bit flustered when this one gets levelled, because I never know where to begin in trying to debunk it. This is mainly because there are absolutely aspects of crypto investing that give off Ponzi vibes to the uninitiated - just look at all those rugged tokens, even the DAO&amp;amp;#39;s that make headlines because of sudden price plummets etc. And no doubt the 2017ish Bitcoin craze where thousands of people bought the top before a very cold winter is still fresh in people&amp;amp;#39;s minds, alongside BTC&amp;amp;#39;s current price situation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So my question is: how do you guys address the common accusation that we&amp;amp;#39;re all just crabs trying to claw our way to the tippy-top of a grand digital ponzi? Many thanks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Edit:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; To those saying &amp;amp;quot;nothing&amp;amp;quot;, I appreciate the pragmaticism - but I&amp;amp;#39;m after retorts that address the core scepticisms that a lot of people display towards crypto. Either way, I always ask myself &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;am I still early??&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; I wonder if the internet&amp;amp;#39;s early days were met with a similar response.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lil Yachty, Soulja Boy Sued For Crypto Pump And Dump Scheme]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxedqc/lil_yachty_soulja_boy_sued_for_crypto_pump_and/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxedqc%2Flil_yachty_soulja_boy_sued_for_crypto_pump_and%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxedqc%2Flil_yachty_soulja_boy_sued_for_crypto_pump_and%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxedqc/lil_yachty_soulja_boy_sued_for_crypto_pump_and/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 03:46:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nice try]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sxflum/nice_try/?score=541&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsxflum%2Fnice_try%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsxflum%2Fnice_try%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sxflum/nice_try/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 02:44:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fix The Money]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sx8p3h/fix_the_money/?score=331&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsx8p3h%2Ffix_the_money%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsx8p3h%2Ffix_the_money%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sx8p3h/fix_the_money/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 01:45:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A Coin Named Polyroll Lost 100% of its value in less than 24 hours]]></title><description><![CDATA[So in less than 24 hours, a polygon-chain coin named Polyroll just rug pulled
90,000 of its holders. Im repeating, 90 freaking thousand holders. What worrying
is that the project (scam) was backed by ChainLink itself. They even tweeted it
on their official twitter about this coin and how this coin…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sx561g/a_coin_named_polyroll_lost_100_of_its_value_in/?score=340&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsx561g%2Fa_coin_named_polyroll_lost_100_of_its_value_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsx561g%2Fa_coin_named_polyroll_lost_100_of_its_value_in%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sx561g/a_coin_named_polyroll_lost_100_of_its_value_in/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 00:35:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So in less than 24 hours, a polygon-chain coin named Polyroll just rug pulled 90,000 of its holders. Im repeating, 90 freaking thousand holders. What worrying is that the project (scam) was backed by ChainLink itself. They even tweeted it on their official twitter about this coin and how this coin is the number 1 polygon casino game coin.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edited: PolygonDaily with 56k followers also recommended this project to its followers.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This shows why countries can ban cryptos easily when projects that were trusted for years like ChainLink recommend you scam coins like this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The project was verifies by RugDoc, the doxxed team, and a well built website with 90k holders. Anyone can blindfoldedly buy this. What lesson do we learn from this?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Banano team quietly passes 1 TRILLION points with Folding@Home.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I feel like this isn't getting enough credit than it deserves.

Banano is a memecoin branch off Nano, but users are given free Banano when
utilizing Folding @ Home.

For those that don't know, people can use their computing power to run
simulations of protein folding and movement of proteins. This…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sx2zxk/banano_team_quietly_passes_1_trillion_points_with/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsx2zxk%2Fbanano_team_quietly_passes_1_trillion_points_with%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsx2zxk%2Fbanano_team_quietly_passes_1_trillion_points_with%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sx2zxk/banano_team_quietly_passes_1_trillion_points_with/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 00:35:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I feel like this isn&amp;amp;#39;t getting enough credit than it deserves.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Banano is a memecoin branch off Nano, but users are given free Banano when utilizing Folding @ Home.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For those that don&amp;amp;#39;t know, people can use their computing power to run simulations of protein folding and movement of proteins. This can help with developing new cures.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Banano team is literally the #1 team with over the last couple of days, &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;surpassing 1 TRILLION points.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is just insane.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Covid Moonshot literally just found a new anti-viral and credits &amp;lt;a href=&quot;mailto:Folding@Home&quot;&amp;gt;Folding@Home&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. And honestly, with Banano being the #1 team, that&amp;amp;#39;s a huge accomplishment.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;We employed Folding@Home a worldwide distributed computing network where hundreds of thousands of volunteers around the world contributed computing power to create the world’s first exascale computing resource to compute the free energy of binding of all 20,000+ crowdsourced submissions&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;We also thank the numerous volunteers that contributed compound designs to the COVID moonshot and to the citizen scientist volunteers of Folding@home for donating their computing resources, and Amazon Web Services for key support of Folding@home infrastructure&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.1101/2020.10.29.339317v3.full.pdf&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.1101/2020.10.29.339317v3.full.pdf&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Credit Suisse whistleblower leak: Bank facilitated $80 BN money laundering for Human traffickers, drug dealers and murderers. Actual criminals continue to launder via the largest banks, but you be damned if you earn a little bit of spare income in crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[A whistleblower has leaked account data from Credit Suisse, which shows that
some of the most notorious criminals across the world maintain accounts with the
bank, including alleged human traffickers, Venezuela officials who looted the
country at the same time the people there faced massive…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxc5di/credit_suisse_whistleblower_leak_bank_facilitated/?score=379&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxc5di%2Fcredit_suisse_whistleblower_leak_bank_facilitated%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxc5di%2Fcredit_suisse_whistleblower_leak_bank_facilitated%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxc5di/credit_suisse_whistleblower_leak_bank_facilitated/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 00:35:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A whistleblower has leaked account data from Credit Suisse, which shows that some of the most notorious criminals across the world maintain accounts with the bank, including alleged human traffickers, Venezuela officials who looted the country at the same time the people there faced massive inflation, and a billionaire who ordered girlfriend’s murder. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The investigation: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.occrp.org/en/suisse-secrets/historic-leak-of-swiss-banking-records-reveals-unsavory-clients&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.occrp.org/en/suisse-secrets/historic-leak-of-swiss-banking-records-reveals-unsavory-clients&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;These are some of the clients of the bank described in the whistleblower article: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A Yemeni spy chief implicated in torture. The sons of an Azerbaijani strongman who rules a mountainous territory as his own private fiefdom. Bureaucrats accused of looting Venezuela’s oil wealth and hastening its descent into humanitarian crisis.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Credit Suisse’s clients included the family of an Egyptian intelligence chief who oversaw torture of terrorism suspects for the CIA; an Italian accused of laundering criminal funds for the infamous ‘Ndrangheta criminal group; a German executive who bribed Nigerian officials for telecoms contracts; and Jordan’s King Abdullah II, who held a single account worth 230 million Swiss francs ($223 million) at its peak, even as his country raked in billions in foreign aid.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Venezuelan elites accused of plundering the state oil firm funneled hundreds of millions of dollars into Credit Suisse accounts. The money flowed during a period when widespread looting from government coffers precipitated an economic collapse that has prompted six million people to flee the country and driven others into near starvation. The bank kept its Venezuelan clients’ accounts open even as global media exposed corruption cases against many of them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;These kind of people have zero problems laundering their ill gotten wealth via the banking system, but damn if you earned more than $600 in staking rewards, you have to start reporting via Form 1099, if you spend $10k in crypto, it will have to be reported directly to the IRS. All these regulations and laws are put in place to track crypto because regulator and central bankers constantly attack crypto as a conduit for money laundering. However the biggest criminal enterprises solely rely on the banking system for laundering their funds.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Drug cartels or Venezuelan elites who looted their own government have no issues with KYC, but if you make a p2p or anonymous crypto transaction, you can risk your funds being locked!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The loops you have to go to have your crypto income accounted as a legitimate source of earning, only for those in the government to accuse crypto of facilitating money laundering, crimes and whatnot...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But when the actual allegations come out its invariably the central banking system that facilitates money transmission operations for some of the largest criminal enterprises in the world, including drug cartels and human rights abusers and corrupt rulers. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;These are quotes from employees of Credit Suisse:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“When someone wants to engage in money laundering after he loots assets of the country, for example, he needs to transfer the money. So holders of big accounts go directly to the very senior managers,” he said.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The system was based on plausible deniability, said former employees. Bankers are given strict rules, but the incentives are to ignore them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“The bank’s compliance department are masters of plausible deniability,” the former senior manager said. “Never ask a question you do not want to know the answer to.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Other articles covering this leak: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2022/02/20/business/credit-suisse-leak-swiss-bank.html&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.nytimes.com/2022/02/20/business/credit-suisse-leak-swiss-bank.html&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Last week it was all “bull run is back on” and now it’s crypto winter is officially here. Stop living week to week y’all, it’s a good way to burn out.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Basically what the title says, last week many Americans were super bullish on
the Super Bowl and all the crypto ads where the “bull run was back on”. People
started to get the BTC to 100 or 200k posts ready to go and any potential war
between russia and Ukraine were dismissed as FUD.

Fast forward…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxcrbv/last_week_it_was_all_bull_run_is_back_on_and_now/?score=320&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxcrbv%2Flast_week_it_was_all_bull_run_is_back_on_and_now%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsxcrbv%2Flast_week_it_was_all_bull_run_is_back_on_and_now%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sxcrbv/last_week_it_was_all_bull_run_is_back_on_and_now/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 00:35:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Basically what the title says, last week many Americans were super bullish on the Super Bowl and all the crypto ads where the “bull run was back on”. People started to get the BTC to 100 or 200k posts ready to go and any potential war between russia and Ukraine were dismissed as FUD. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Fast forward to a whole 7 days later and there are multiple posts about being in a crypto winter for the foreseeable future. This is the volatility that comes with the territory of being in the space so instead of riding the roller coaster it might benefit some to just unplug from the daily/weekly news and chart watching. If you set your limit orders and price alerts then go live your life, it’s much harder to be affected by the constant volatility. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Who knows what’s in store for next week? Personally I think it’s bearish news for the foreseeable future with, coming interest rate hikes, tax season, and the constant threat of global conflict despite institutional involvement being at an all time high.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nobody blames FIAT when criminals launder money, but when they use Crypto, it’s a Crypto problem.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The same thing was happening during the beginnings of the internet era. If
someone was kidnapped or murdered by someone they met on the internet, media
blamed the internet.

Decades later, people are over it because internet is a necessary part of their
lives.

The world’s ‘regulated’ banks are…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sx9agt/nobody_blames_fiat_when_criminals_launder_money/?score=363&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsx9agt%2Fnobody_blames_fiat_when_criminals_launder_money%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsx9agt%2Fnobody_blames_fiat_when_criminals_launder_money%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sx9agt/nobody_blames_fiat_when_criminals_launder_money/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 00:35:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The same thing was happening during the beginnings of the internet era. If someone was kidnapped or murdered by someone they met on the internet, media blamed the internet.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Decades later, people are over it because internet is a necessary part of their lives.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The world’s ‘regulated’ banks are laundering more than $2 trillion every year. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If that was a case of Cryptocurrency, there would be numerous “BREAKING NEWS” topics, posts, titles about how Crypto is ruining the whole world financial system, helping the criminals and all kinds of panic stories.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Will we ever get importial news? Did you know that terrorists sometimes drive in cars and are drinking bottled water? Did you know that when you don’t breathe you die? And also that every 60 seconds in Africa, a minute passes?? Wow.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Opensea NFT hack explain Thread]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 1. 28 days ago the hacker uploads a new smart contract, he already knows well
    that his goal is to get as many signatures as possible

 2. He starts sending emails with phising websites. They tell you to sign a
    message to login/migrate to the new Opensea smart contract

Instead you are…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swshf5/opensea_nft_hack_explain_thread/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswshf5%2Fopensea_nft_hack_explain_thread%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswshf5%2Fopensea_nft_hack_explain_thread%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swshf5/opensea_nft_hack_explain_thread/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 00:35:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;28 days ago the hacker uploads a new smart contract, he already knows well that his goal is to get as many signatures as possible&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He starts sending emails with phising websites. They tell you to sign a message to login/migrate to the new Opensea smart contract&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Instead you are signing a private sale (0 eth) of your NFTs to the hacker&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Today he executes the smart contract function to steal the NFTs before their listings expire&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He can do that because he has your signatures stored on his server&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;As a final note, always check what you are signing, because one click makes a difference.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can revoke access to your NFTs from official Etherscan website:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://etherscan.io/tokenapprovalchecker&quot;&amp;gt;https://etherscan.io/tokenapprovalchecker&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;📢 All this is what we believe to have happened, but the investigation is still ongoing&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Details check this Twitter thread 🧵 &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/isotile/status/1495234649970421760?s=21&quot;&amp;gt;https://twitter.com/isotile/status/1495234649970421760?s=21&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: JUST IN: Over $200M worth of NFTs reportedly stolen from OpenSea phishing hack&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I tried Cardano DeFi for the first time and it was incredibly bad]]></title><description><![CDATA[Look I'm not someone who's just dipping their toes into DeFi for the first time,
I've used other networks and various protocols and I want to know what went so
wrong with my first Cardano experience. So please keep an open mind.

Here's my story:

Installed Nami wallet.

Started a withdrawal of…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sx3yhs/i_tried_cardano_defi_for_the_first_time_and_it/?score=373&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsx3yhs%2Fi_tried_cardano_defi_for_the_first_time_and_it%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsx3yhs%2Fi_tried_cardano_defi_for_the_first_time_and_it%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sx3yhs/i_tried_cardano_defi_for_the_first_time_and_it/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 22:35:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Look I&amp;amp;#39;m not someone who&amp;amp;#39;s just dipping their toes into DeFi for the first time, I&amp;amp;#39;ve used other networks and various protocols and I want to know what went so wrong with my first Cardano experience. So please keep an open mind.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here&amp;amp;#39;s my story:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Installed Nami wallet. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Started a withdrawal of just 5 Ada from Kraken to this wallet, it took 30 minutes (??) for funds to arrive.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Went to SundaeSwap, tried to swap 1 Ada for 1.4 Sundae but kept saying that I have insufficient funds, apparently Sundae has additional fees that I was not aware of (2.5 Ada + some refundable deposit of 2 Ada).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Waited another 30 minutes to withdraw more Ada.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Big red warning on the Sundae page that the network is heavily congested. Checked the explorer and blocks were indeed (85%+) full while running at 2 tps. How is that possible?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;First 4 swap attempts failed with 0 warnings, nothing to be found on-chain in the explorer, just pending attempts that disappeared after reconnecting my wallet.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The 5th one I think was recorded on-chain and remained in pending.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;40 minutes later another on-chain swap attempt magically appeared, probably from the first 4 &amp;amp;quot;failed&amp;amp;quot; txs. Wtf?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Tried to cancel this second order...cancellation pending with 0 feedback on what is happening, tried to cancel 3 more times... nothing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Exactly one hour and 7 minutes later the first swap completed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m used to getting near instant confirmations and swaps on other networks, 1 hour+ is definitelly the longest I&amp;amp;#39;ve ever had to wait on any Dex by a factor of 1000x and combined with all the fails and weird behaviour that I got I can&amp;amp;#39;t call this a good UX. What exactly went so wrong and what&amp;amp;#39;s the solution? Please don&amp;amp;#39;t call me a fudder because none of this is made up and anyone can try it for themselves.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The more I learn, the more I think I should convert all of my alts into BTC. Is this logical?]]></title><description><![CDATA[My crypto investments are primarily BTC and ETH, but a solid chunk in alts as I
thought a few of them had good potential for short-term gains. However, the more
I learn about Bitcoin the more I want to go all in on BTC especially with the
recent political climate. My plan is to hold long-term (10+…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/swr7x3/the_more_i_learn_the_more_i_think_i_should/?score=328&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fswr7x3%2Fthe_more_i_learn_the_more_i_think_i_should%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fswr7x3%2Fthe_more_i_learn_the_more_i_think_i_should%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/swr7x3/the_more_i_learn_the_more_i_think_i_should/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 22:35:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My crypto investments are primarily BTC and ETH, but a solid chunk in alts as I thought a few of them had good potential for short-term gains. However, the more I learn about Bitcoin the more I want to go all in on BTC especially with the recent political climate. My plan is to hold long-term (10+ years). &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m curious if this community finds this logical or not. I am a software engineer and I think a generally smart person but there are so many factors that could affect this in the next 5-10 years I can’t help but second guess myself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[There is a massive PsyOp going on to poison the public perception of Bitcoin.]]></title><description><![CDATA[They’re here. They’re trying to divide the community, splinter it, make it
easier to control. Be vigilant.

This will be downvoted but much like the saying “The Revolution will not be
televised”, “The truth will not be upvoted”

Be vigilant friends. Bitcoin is not political. Bitcoin is for…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sx4a9b/there_is_a_massive_psyop_going_on_to_poison_the/?score=417&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsx4a9b%2Fthere_is_a_massive_psyop_going_on_to_poison_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsx4a9b%2Fthere_is_a_massive_psyop_going_on_to_poison_the%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sx4a9b/there_is_a_massive_psyop_going_on_to_poison_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 22:35:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They’re here. They’re trying to divide the community, splinter it, make it easier to control. Be vigilant. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This will be downvoted but much like the saying “The Revolution will not be televised”, “The truth will not be upvoted”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Be vigilant friends. Bitcoin is not political. Bitcoin is for everyone.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[You should definitely not listen to this sub during any major movements in crypto.]]></title><description><![CDATA[As we are currently having some major downtrends in the crypto market its way
more important to stick to your plan than ever. But also major movements are the
time where this sub is overly bipolar.

This sub is something way more volatile than crypto. Any minor movement causes a
complete shift from…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sx71xo/you_should_definitely_not_listen_to_this_sub/?score=313&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsx71xo%2Fyou_should_definitely_not_listen_to_this_sub%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsx71xo%2Fyou_should_definitely_not_listen_to_this_sub%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sx71xo/you_should_definitely_not_listen_to_this_sub/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 22:35:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As we are currently having some major downtrends in the crypto market its way more important to stick to your plan than ever. But also major movements are the time where this sub is overly bipolar. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This sub is something way more volatile than crypto. Any minor movement causes a complete shift from bull to bearish in this subs sentiment. And during major movements like this, the sub goes completely crazy. Making predictions of either 100k in a week or as now 18k tomorrow. If you would listen to this sub you would absolutely master buy high sell low. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You should not listen to anyone actually during rough times and during very amazing times. Those are the moments you should keep your plan to yourself. Just strictly follow it and sell/buy when YOU think it&amp;amp;#39;s right. That way you won&amp;amp;#39;t regret it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Don’t get too pressed on ETH2.0. Vitalik himself admitted on the Bankless podcast that it may take 6 years for it to full be completed.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Chill out and take your time cause its most probable that ETH2.0 in its final
form will take years to be completed.

This doesn’t mean that we’ll have to wait 6 years to have a highly performing
Ethereum network.

The main focus, as Vitalik stated, should be 2 things:

• The move to PoS

•…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sx3qhn/dont_get_too_pressed_on_eth20_vitalik_himself/?score=472&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsx3qhn%2Fdont_get_too_pressed_on_eth20_vitalik_himself%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsx3qhn%2Fdont_get_too_pressed_on_eth20_vitalik_himself%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sx3qhn/dont_get_too_pressed_on_eth20_vitalik_himself/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 20:31:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Chill out and take your time cause its most probable that ETH2.0 in its final form will take years to be completed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This doesn’t mean that we’ll have to wait 6 years to have a highly performing Ethereum network.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The main focus, as Vitalik stated, should be 2 things:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;• The move to PoS&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;• Sharding&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Any additional features are just polishing the network to make it as perfect as possible.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the meantime, Vitalik is solely focused on Zk rollups as the future of scalability for Ethereum.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This decision to build around rollups came back in 2020 when Vitalik wrote an article titled “A roll-up-centric ethereum roadmap” where he explained how Ethereum would be all in on rollup tech (Give it a read its very interesting).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I guess this is why he’s so fond of MATIC recently considering they’ve invested into every single ZK rollup tech available on the market and have proven to be top dogs when it comes to scalability.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So while the final stage or ETH2.0 might take a while, we should soon start seeing a lot more improvement from both Ethereum and side chains like Polygon.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I finally understand Bitcoin.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I finally understand the purpose of Bitcoin. About two weeks ago I recently won
a little bit of money gambling and couldn’t transfer it to my bank, I could
however withdraw it in BTC and was just going to set up an account on Coinbase
and withdraw it when it hit. I didn’t know anything about BTC or…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sx3zs1/i_finally_understand_bitcoin/?score=313&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsx3zs1%2Fi_finally_understand_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsx3zs1%2Fi_finally_understand_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sx3zs1/i_finally_understand_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 18:32:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I finally understand the purpose of Bitcoin. About two weeks ago I recently won a little bit of money gambling and couldn’t transfer it to my bank, I could however withdraw it in BTC and was just going to set up an account on Coinbase and withdraw it when it hit. I didn’t know anything about BTC or crypto (and I still know very little) and after this price drop I started panicking a teeny bit and was confused. I found the subreddit  and started browsing it and I realized, Bitcoin isn’t about making a profit or a quick buck, it’s a slap in the face to the government and banks who think they can control every aspect of our life. It’s a slap in the face to people like Trudeau who thinks they can freeze our accounts because we don’t comply to their every demand. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thank you all for showing me the real meaning behind crypto and BTC. Going to invest a little more and get a cold wallet soon. F the Gov n F the greedy ass banks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[California-based Lengthwise Brewing Company is going on the Bitcoin Standard and is now accepting Bitcoin payments]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/swys6j/californiabased_lengthwise_brewing_company_is/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fswys6j%2Fcaliforniabased_lengthwise_brewing_company_is%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fswys6j%2Fcaliforniabased_lengthwise_brewing_company_is%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/swys6j/californiabased_lengthwise_brewing_company_is/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 17:32:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Best video I've ever seen explaining how blockchains work. I actually feel like I'm starting to understand it now.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swmqzq/best_video_ive_ever_seen_explaining_how/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswmqzq%2Fbest_video_ive_ever_seen_explaining_how%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswmqzq%2Fbest_video_ive_ever_seen_explaining_how%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swmqzq/best_video_ive_ever_seen_explaining_how/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 15:42:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/swyh5m/bitcoin/?score=329&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fswyh5m%2Fbitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fswyh5m%2Fbitcoin%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/swyh5m/bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coinbase Rewards White Hat Hacker Who Found Infinite Money Glitch With $25 Gift Card]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swu8o2/coinbase_rewards_white_hat_hacker_who_found/?score=346&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswu8o2%2Fcoinbase_rewards_white_hat_hacker_who_found%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswu8o2%2Fcoinbase_rewards_white_hat_hacker_who_found%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swu8o2/coinbase_rewards_white_hat_hacker_who_found/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto taxes are a shit show]]></title><description><![CDATA[(US Taxes) I’ve tried multiple tax tools trying to get my taxes straight this
year and none of them are coming through, either the API fails to load or CSV
won’t import.

I have used around 10 exchanges and some of them have hundreds of transactions I
need to correct plus these dust drops in my…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swnsow/crypto_taxes_are_a_shit_show/?score=316&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswnsow%2Fcrypto_taxes_are_a_shit_show%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswnsow%2Fcrypto_taxes_are_a_shit_show%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swnsow/crypto_taxes_are_a_shit_show/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(US Taxes) I’ve tried multiple tax tools trying to get my taxes straight this year and none of them are coming through, either the API fails
to load or CSV won’t import. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I have used around 10 exchanges and some of them have hundreds of transactions I need to correct plus these dust drops in my trust wallet causing it to say I have 4 mill in unrealized gains wtf. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I can’t be the only one pulling my hair out trying not to get audited. What are you guys doing for yours? Any tips? This experience has made a hodler out of me!!!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: thanks guys you make me feel better knowing we are all struggling together 💪🏻💪🏻&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just got rugged. Half my 'folio gone.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Just woke up in the morning, found out my coin exit-scammed. I believed in the
project, it wasn't a shitty dog-coin, it was a decentralized casino, which I
thought was a novel idea. Today, the team announced they're ceasing operations,
price's dropped 95%, can't even withdraw coins from the staking…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swz40j/just_got_rugged_half_my_folio_gone/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswz40j%2Fjust_got_rugged_half_my_folio_gone%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswz40j%2Fjust_got_rugged_half_my_folio_gone%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swz40j/just_got_rugged_half_my_folio_gone/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just woke up in the morning, found out my coin exit-scammed. I believed in the project, it wasn&amp;amp;#39;t a shitty dog-coin, it was a decentralized casino, which I thought was a novel idea. Today, the team announced they&amp;amp;#39;re ceasing operations, price&amp;amp;#39;s dropped 95%, can&amp;amp;#39;t even withdraw coins from the staking contract from the site, and I don&amp;amp;#39;t wanna even bother with it, cause it&amp;amp;#39;d be a tiny amount. Apparently the devs didn&amp;amp;#39;t sell any coins, which I don&amp;amp;#39;t really believe. What&amp;amp;#39;s worse, I could&amp;amp;#39;ve sold for a nice 2x profit, but I believed in the project and bought the dip.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The warning signs were kind of there, the audit had some things that in hindsight, were kind of dodgy. Don&amp;amp;#39;t even know why I&amp;amp;#39;m writing this, I can survive without the money, but it is a real freacking kick in the gut...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Lesson 1. Don&amp;amp;#39;t go all in on microcaps (really shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t have done that).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Lesson 2. Don&amp;amp;#39;t be an idiot.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;RIP my folio, won&amp;amp;#39;t have money to invest in crypto for a while.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Justin Trudeau Announced as New VP of Marketing at Bitcoin Foundation]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swyq7s/justin_trudeau_announced_as_new_vp_of_marketing/?score=316&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswyq7s%2Fjustin_trudeau_announced_as_new_vp_of_marketing%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswyq7s%2Fjustin_trudeau_announced_as_new_vp_of_marketing%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swyq7s/justin_trudeau_announced_as_new_vp_of_marketing/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ukraine Legalizes Bitcoin]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swtbrn/ukraine_legalizes_bitcoin/?score=332&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswtbrn%2Fukraine_legalizes_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswtbrn%2Fukraine_legalizes_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swtbrn/ukraine_legalizes_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[An NFT project named Squiggles bought their own NFTs and then put it for a discount , making Millions]]></title><description><![CDATA[An NFT project named Squiggles came under a bad reputation after it was linked
to a network of NFT scams. This resulted in their project's hype almost dying
just before the release of their NFT project (It later got removed from Open
Sea). Yet after a few hours of release they still made about 7…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swign1/an_nft_project_named_squiggles_bought_their_own/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswign1%2Fan_nft_project_named_squiggles_bought_their_own%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswign1%2Fan_nft_project_named_squiggles_bought_their_own%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swign1/an_nft_project_named_squiggles_bought_their_own/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 12:42:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;An NFT project named Squiggles came under a bad reputation after it was linked to a network of NFT scams. This resulted in their project&amp;amp;#39;s hype almost dying just before the release of their NFT project (It later got removed from Open Sea). Yet after a few hours of release they still made about 7 million dollars. How does a project associated with NFT scam make 7 million dollars?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Looking close at those 7 million dollars. A lot of the buyers were brand new . I mean, there were so many that had never done anything on ether scan before. A series of shadow wallets all created by one person that was all buying tons of Squiggles. Millions of dollars worth of fake volume and then immediately flipping them on open sea for less money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/aj4gj6wqhui81.png?width=1920&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9d8bd44803349f78092840e79a7068f15225c8fe&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/aj4gj6wqhui81.png?width=1920&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9d8bd44803349f78092840e79a7068f15225c8fe&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/t29cy81shui81.png?width=1920&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9360c5cbf28912b9d0d826a9f2407648e0b429a4&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/t29cy81shui81.png?width=1920&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9360c5cbf28912b9d0d826a9f2407648e0b429a4&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A single account, that spent 800 Ethereum, which is over 2 million dollars spread across two transactions, that created hundreds of new wallets .Each of these shadow wallets, then bought three squiggles a piece and immediately listed them on open sea for less money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You might be wondering why do this? Why buy two million dollars worth of squiggles only to sell them for less? Well, the only reason that makes sense to me is they were trying to give the illusion of huge interest to get people to buy in to make people think this had a lot of trading volume , a lot of hype. The only people who could possibly want to do that is of course the team behind squiggles.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Avalanche network is sweating like a pig now with 14$ gas fees]]></title><description><![CDATA[Remember when MATIC was sweating like a pig just from one sunflower game on its
network? ..well same shit is repeating now with Avalanche. According to the
users fees are even higher than ETH right now

User reports over 14$ gas fee for…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swvr4p/avalanche_network_is_sweating_like_a_pig_now_with/?score=386&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswvr4p%2Favalanche_network_is_sweating_like_a_pig_now_with%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswvr4p%2Favalanche_network_is_sweating_like_a_pig_now_with%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swvr4p/avalanche_network_is_sweating_like_a_pig_now_with/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 12:42:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Remember when MATIC was sweating like a pig just from one sunflower game on its network? ..well same shit is repeating now with Avalanche. According to the users fees are even higher than ETH right now &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/Avax/comments/swil2r/fees_what_the_fuck_14_usd_for_a_withdraw/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=mweb3x&quot;&amp;gt;User reports over 14$ gas fee for transaction&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The reason for congestion?  A game with crabs called Crabada. Yes, I&amp;amp;#39;m serious. It&amp;amp;#39;s sunflower fiasco all over again just this time it&amp;amp;#39;s crabs instead of flowers. And this time too, it&amp;amp;#39;s the network that is supposed to bring us extremely low fees and speedy transactions. I&amp;amp;#39;m investment in AVAX but stuff like this really maks me wonder sometimes.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crazy what one little game with crabs can do to a network&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Do you believe that BTC can reach 1 million in 10 years time?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know no one knows shit about fuck. But do you believe that bitcoin will reach
1 million in 10 years time given all the slow adoption of BTC in every company.
Fidelity, Cathy woods and prominent billionaires like Michael saylors thinks and
believe that BTC will reach around that price target.…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swjdap/do_you_believe_that_btc_can_reach_1_million_in_10/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswjdap%2Fdo_you_believe_that_btc_can_reach_1_million_in_10%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswjdap%2Fdo_you_believe_that_btc_can_reach_1_million_in_10%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swjdap/do_you_believe_that_btc_can_reach_1_million_in_10/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 07:36:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know no one knows shit about fuck. But do you believe that bitcoin will reach 1 million in 10 years time given all the slow adoption of BTC in every company. Fidelity, Cathy woods and prominent billionaires like Michael saylors thinks and believe that BTC will reach around that price target. Fidelity, BlackRock, and greayscale our some of the big institutions accumulating BTC on the sideline and giving way to major adoptions to conservative investors and curious investors who wants to dip in digital assets.  Given that big institutions are entering the market are you seeing the bright future of BTC along the way.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So do you buy whatever the price it? Do you accumulate continuously no matter what the price action it? Do you HODL and do you believe that we will reach this kind of market outlooks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I want to hear your opinions about this one.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Exit FIAT and Enter BTC]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/swnhkf/exit_fiat_and_enter_btc/?score=336&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fswnhkf%2Fexit_fiat_and_enter_btc%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fswnhkf%2Fexit_fiat_and_enter_btc%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/swnhkf/exit_fiat_and_enter_btc/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 07:36:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[OpenSea Hacker Currently Stealing Mass Amounts of Ethereum]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swqcbz/opensea_hacker_currently_stealing_mass_amounts_of/?score=325&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswqcbz%2Fopensea_hacker_currently_stealing_mass_amounts_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswqcbz%2Fopensea_hacker_currently_stealing_mass_amounts_of%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swqcbz/opensea_hacker_currently_stealing_mass_amounts_of/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 07:36:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[El Salvador’s GDP grew 10.3% in 2021. And now its exports (a main driver of economic growth) grew 13% this January, compared to January 2021.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/swkhcj/el_salvadors_gdp_grew_103_in_2021_and_now_its/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fswkhcj%2Fel_salvadors_gdp_grew_103_in_2021_and_now_its%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fswkhcj%2Fel_salvadors_gdp_grew_103_in_2021_and_now_its%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/swkhcj/el_salvadors_gdp_grew_103_in_2021_and_now_its/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 06:32:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[REVOKE OPENSEA ACCESS NOW! Opensea is getting DRAINED by a hacker!]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is urgent. Open sea is being hacked RIGHT NOW and peoples accounts are
getting drained! Over 300 ETH has been taken already!

The attacker hacker is selling the stolen NFTs to others to pull ETH out -
Currently they have over 300 ETH in their wallet! AND GROWING!

Make sure to REVOKE ALL OS…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swqo7a/revoke_opensea_access_now_opensea_is_getting/?score=316&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswqo7a%2Frevoke_opensea_access_now_opensea_is_getting%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswqo7a%2Frevoke_opensea_access_now_opensea_is_getting%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swqo7a/revoke_opensea_access_now_opensea_is_getting/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 04:41:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is urgent. Open sea is being hacked RIGHT NOW and peoples accounts are getting drained! Over 300 ETH has been taken already!  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The attacker hacker is selling the stolen NFTs to others to pull ETH out - Currently they have over 300 ETH in their wallet! AND GROWING!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Make sure to REVOKE ALL OS APPROVALS ACESS NOW! To keep your funds safe!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/oe5u72r25wi81.jpg&quot;&amp;gt;https://i.redd.it/oe5u72r25wi81.jpg&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/0xfoobar/status/1495208279210876930?s=21&quot;&amp;gt;https://twitter.com/0xfoobar/status/1495208279210876930?s=21&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Jon_HQ/status/1495194181744021508&quot;&amp;gt;https://twitter.com/Jon_HQ/status/1495194181744021508&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;REVOKE ACESS ON OPEANSEA RIGHT NOW! Lots of details are still not known!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Opensea is getting exploited, right now]]></title><description><![CDATA[Opensea is getting exploited, right now

Reports/rumors that people who migrated their listings to their new contract are
getting their nfts drained right now. Doodle, Azukis, NFT Worlds, BAYC... all
worth over 10ETH+

Opensea have been advertising at the top of their website to users so they…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swoel1/opensea_is_getting_exploited_right_now/?score=436&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswoel1%2Fopensea_is_getting_exploited_right_now%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fswoel1%2Fopensea_is_getting_exploited_right_now%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/swoel1/opensea_is_getting_exploited_right_now/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 03:44:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Opensea is getting exploited, right now&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Reports/rumors that people who migrated their listings to their new contract are getting their nfts drained right now. Doodle,  Azukis, NFT Worlds, BAYC... all worth over 10ETH+&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Opensea have been advertising at the top of their website to users so they would migrate their listings before feb 25th...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is a wallet who has been exploiting the contract : &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://opensea.io/0x3e0defb880cd8e163bad68abe66437f99a7a8a74?tab=activity&quot;&amp;gt;https://opensea.io/0x3e0defb880cd8e163bad68abe66437f99a7a8a74?tab=activity&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/ajfromdiscord/status/1495185887625367556?s=21&quot;&amp;gt;twitter 1&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/jon_hq/status/1495194178355011586?s=21&quot;&amp;gt;twitter 2&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you are affected, revoke all OS APPROVALS using revoke.cash ASAP&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit : someone suggests that it might be a phishing attack that was weeks in the making &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/0xfoobar/status/1495208279210876930?s=21&quot;&amp;gt;twitter 3&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit 2: seems like the attacker has stolen over 700 eth worth as of yet&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler Filler&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>