<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing on Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 10:35:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Between 8th and 15th of June 2021 BTC pumped from 31k to 41k, just to crash down to 29k seven days later]]></title><description><![CDATA[Please keep in mind that just seven months ago we had almost the same pump,
which took BTC up to EXACTLY where it is right now. This is not the only
similarity - back then BTC pumped from 35k to 39k within 14 hours, while
yesterday we saw a pump from 37k to 41k in 9 hours.

This uptrend was short…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl7c30/between_8th_and_15th_of_june_2021_btc_pumped_from/?score=309&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl7c30%2Fbetween_8th_and_15th_of_june_2021_btc_pumped_from%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl7c30%2Fbetween_8th_and_15th_of_june_2021_btc_pumped_from%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl7c30/between_8th_and_15th_of_june_2021_btc_pumped_from/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 09:42:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please keep in mind that just seven months ago we had almost the same pump, which took BTC up to EXACTLY where it is right now. This is not the only similarity - back then BTC pumped from 35k to 39k within 14 hours, while yesterday we saw a pump from 37k to 41k in 9 hours.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This uptrend was short lived and BTC was above 40k for just 2 days, to crash even lower than previously in the next week.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is also worth noting that we are far from &amp;amp;quot;invalidating weeks of FUD&amp;amp;quot; (as one of the top post claims, the one about a potential short squeeze), because we are basically at the support level from just 2 weeks ago - after going below 45k in January, BTC was testing the 40k-41k support for a while, just to crash below it on 20th of January. This was just sixteen days ago!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The only positive aspect about current situation is that you can kind-of see a slight uptrend since hitting 33k on 24th of January when you zoom out, but this means as much as the current alignment of stars on the night sky.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Whether we go &amp;amp;quot;up only&amp;amp;quot; or continue the downtrend remains to be seen. Personally my bets are 50% on going up and 50% on going down, so as you see I have a pretty strong opinion about the current state of the market (;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;tl;dr: 100k BTC end of month! (;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Buying Bitcoin every month for 53 months now (since Oct 2017) - update]]></title><description><![CDATA[Been buying Bitcoin every month since late 2017. Nearly always with the same
amount, few exceptions when I got a bonus from work etc. Basically, I wanted to
go all-in but didn't have any savings, so decided to buy with max amount that I
can, every month from the salary. I kinda had the idea of…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sl4tg0/buying_bitcoin_every_month_for_53_months_now/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsl4tg0%2Fbuying_bitcoin_every_month_for_53_months_now%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsl4tg0%2Fbuying_bitcoin_every_month_for_53_months_now%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sl4tg0/buying_bitcoin_every_month_for_53_months_now/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 08:37:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Been buying Bitcoin every month since late 2017. Nearly always with the same amount, few exceptions when I got a bonus from work etc. Basically, I wanted to go all-in but didn&amp;amp;#39;t have any savings, so decided to buy with max amount that I can, every month from the salary. I kinda had the idea of stacking my way to a million dollars (or euros), however long it would take. Because the way I see Bitcoin, I have no doubt it&amp;amp;#39;s gonna happen. Sooner if I stack more, and later if stack less.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I saw stacking sats become a meme and people posting screenshots on Twitter. But I felt like the bigger picture was missing. How much can you achieve by simply stacking sats all the time? This is my idea of a blueprint. I stack with certain amount and have been doing it for a certain while. You can take a look at the progress and get and idea how it would work for you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In short, its gonna take time. And its gonna require patience and nerves. Bitcoin is gonna test you, and there&amp;amp;#39;s no shortcuts to success. My advice: start stacking, keep stacking! Promise yourself to stack at least 4 years before you even think about giving up. I document my journey here in the blog. Enjoy reading and I hope you have great success stacking sats!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://er-bybitcoin.com/stacking-em-volume-19-ferbuary-2022/&quot;&amp;gt;https://er-bybitcoin.com/stacking-em-volume-19-ferbuary-2022/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Am I the only one that still has no idea what the Metaverse is actually meant to be?]]></title><description><![CDATA[So what on earth is it?

Is it just the idea that we'll all be playing MMORPGs all day with VR? Rather
then chatting with someone on zoom I'll spend half an hour wiring up my VR kit
so I can chat to their avatar in a pretend conference room? And then we'll go to
a pretend coffee bar where we'll…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skzhyx/am_i_the_only_one_that_still_has_no_idea_what_the/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskzhyx%2Fam_i_the_only_one_that_still_has_no_idea_what_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskzhyx%2Fam_i_the_only_one_that_still_has_no_idea_what_the%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skzhyx/am_i_the_only_one_that_still_has_no_idea_what_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 02:49:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So what on earth is it?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Is it just the idea that we&amp;amp;#39;ll all be playing MMORPGs all day with VR? Rather then chatting with someone on zoom I&amp;amp;#39;ll spend half an hour wiring up my VR kit so I can chat to their avatar in a pretend conference room? And then we&amp;amp;#39;ll go to a pretend coffee bar where we&amp;amp;#39;ll pretend to drink coffee that we&amp;amp;#39;ll buy with crypto?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Is it just the idea of a persistent online virtual world? But which world? Presumably anyone can make their own metaverse? Does Eve Online count as the metaverse? Habbo Hotel? Or does it have to have VR?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Isn&amp;amp;#39;t the internet just the metaverse? Or does it always require some sort of game like VR interface to count?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And what role does Blockchain play in the metaverse? Is it intended to support the persistence and the idea of one true metaverse? But whose Blockchain? Surely anyone can create their own Blockchain for their own metaverse? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why are people buying virtual land in the metaverse? What utility does it have? And given it&amp;amp;#39;s just a simulation, the land itself is presumably infinite? So why pay for it?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Am I just an old grumpy man?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Let's see whether sentiment really changed that quickly. What's your guess, educated or not: $30k or $50k, which comes first?]]></title><description><![CDATA[You're very welcome to explain your outlook and explain why you feel bullish or
bearish, but please don't annoy us with nobody knowing feces about fornication.
I'm asking in order to determine the current outlook.

I'm asking about how you feel about the market at this moment in time, not to
get…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl7jfh/lets_see_whether_sentiment_really_changed_that/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl7jfh%2Flets_see_whether_sentiment_really_changed_that%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl7jfh%2Flets_see_whether_sentiment_really_changed_that%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl7jfh/lets_see_whether_sentiment_really_changed_that/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 02:49:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You&amp;amp;#39;re very welcome to explain your outlook and explain why you feel bullish or bearish, but please don&amp;amp;#39;t annoy us with nobody knowing feces about fornication. I&amp;amp;#39;m asking in order to determine the current outlook. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m asking about how you feel about the market at this moment in time, not to get out your crystal ball and prophesize what&amp;amp;#39;s actually and definitely going to happen.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Are you afraid it&amp;amp;#39;s all just a dead cat bounce and we&amp;amp;#39;ll be down sooner rather than later?
Are we yet to hit the bottom?
Are you optimistic we&amp;amp;#39;re on our way to a new ATH?
Are you simply confused? 
Did I crack the 500 characters minimum this time?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bullish or bearish, how do you feel?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Proof-of-Reserves audit shows Kraken holds $19B in BTC and ETH and proved every coin was on spot]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/slitx8/proofofreserves_audit_shows_kraken_holds_19b_in/?score=749&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fslitx8%2Fproofofreserves_audit_shows_kraken_holds_19b_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fslitx8%2Fproofofreserves_audit_shows_kraken_holds_19b_in%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/slitx8/proofofreserves_audit_shows_kraken_holds_19b_in/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 02:16:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This is how insanely secure the Bitcoin network really is]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bitcoin is the most secure network in existence. The way the network is built is
pure genius and the bigger it gets, the more secure it becomes.

In 2011, Dan Kaminsky, a leading Internet-security researcher, investigated the
currency and was sure he would find major weaknesses.

Kaminsky is famous…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/slhkes/this_is_how_insanely_secure_the_bitcoin_network/?score=376&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fslhkes%2Fthis_is_how_insanely_secure_the_bitcoin_network%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fslhkes%2Fthis_is_how_insanely_secure_the_bitcoin_network%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/slhkes/this_is_how_insanely_secure_the_bitcoin_network/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 02:16:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin is the most secure network in existence. The way the network is built is pure genius and the bigger it gets, the more secure it becomes.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In 2011, Dan Kaminsky, a leading Internet-security researcher, investigated the currency and was sure he would find major weaknesses. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Kaminsky is famous among hackers for discovering, in 2008, a fundamental flaw in the Internet which would have allowed a skilled coder to take over any Web site or even to shut down the Internet. Kaminsky alerted the Department of Homeland Security and executives at Microsoft and Cisco to the problem and worked with them to patch it. He is one of the most adept practitioners of “penetration testing,” the art of compromising the security of computer systems at the behest of owners who want to know their vulnerabilities.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Guess what he said when he tried to break Bitcoin?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;“When I first looked at the code, I was sure I was going to be able to break it. The way the whole thing was formatted was insane. Only the most paranoid, painstaking coder in the world could avoid making mistakes.”&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He thought he had identified nine ways to compromise the system and scoured Nakamoto’s code for an insertion point for his first attack. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But when he found the right spot, there was a message waiting for him. “Attack Removed,” it said. The same thing happened over and over, infuriating Kaminsky. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;“I came up with beautiful bugs. But every time I went after the code there was a line that addressed the problem.”&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He was like a burglar who was certain that he could break into a bank by digging a tunnel, drilling through a wall, or climbing down a vent, and on each attempt he discovered a freshly poured cement barrier with a sign telling him to go home. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;“I’ve never seen anything like it,”&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; Kaminsky said, still in awe.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;“Either there’s a team of people who worked on this or this guy is a genius.”&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TLDR: Buy Bitcoin&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2011/10/10/the-crypto-currency/&quot;&amp;gt;Source&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Imagine how weird it felt for an 1960s vendor to accept payments from a plastic card. Same goes with crypto now.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Imagine what it felt like accepting the first credit card payments in the world.
The concept of intangible money, money that can’t be physically seen, has always
been a hard concept for humans to grasp.

Some countries and cities now like Dubai and New York use more credit cards than
cash. Yet the…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl0gz1/imagine_how_weird_it_felt_for_an_1960s_vendor_to/?score=313&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl0gz1%2Fimagine_how_weird_it_felt_for_an_1960s_vendor_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl0gz1%2Fimagine_how_weird_it_felt_for_an_1960s_vendor_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl0gz1/imagine_how_weird_it_felt_for_an_1960s_vendor_to/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 01:02:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Imagine what it felt like accepting the first credit card payments in the world. The concept of intangible money, money that can’t be physically seen, has always been a hard concept for humans to grasp.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some countries and cities now like Dubai and New York use more credit cards than cash. Yet the transition from cash to credit cards took a very long time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Meaning crypto will eventually become legal tender if we keep up this pace (and will most probably be adopted faster than credit cards got adopted).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are even crypto credit cards that are paving the way for crypto payment adoption. They’re so easy to acquire. Platforms like Binance and Coinbase offer them. I have mine from CoinOvy.
These crypto credit cards will be a great way to transition from digital payments to full crypto payments.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Senator Ted Cruz bought the dip. How about you, anon?]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skvqez/senator_ted_cruz_bought_the_dip_how_about_you_anon/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskvqez%2Fsenator_ted_cruz_bought_the_dip_how_about_you_anon%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskvqez%2Fsenator_ted_cruz_bought_the_dip_how_about_you_anon%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skvqez/senator_ted_cruz_bought_the_dip_how_about_you_anon/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 20:30:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CNBC: "Bitcoin miners are helping the Texas grid brace for winter storm impact". Great article! ...why I don't see it in r/Technology?]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/03/winter-storm-descends-on-texas-bitcoin-miners-shut-off-to-protect-ercot.html

They only post FUD about Bitcoin/Crypto, articles full of lies and
misinformation. But this great factual article is nowhere to be seen there:

> As a major winter storm descends on Texas,…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skzb2s/cnbc_bitcoin_miners_are_helping_the_texas_grid/?score=315&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskzb2s%2Fcnbc_bitcoin_miners_are_helping_the_texas_grid%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskzb2s%2Fcnbc_bitcoin_miners_are_helping_the_texas_grid%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skzb2s/cnbc_bitcoin_miners_are_helping_the_texas_grid/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 19:30:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/03/winter-storm-descends-on-texas-bitcoin-miners-shut-off-to-protect-ercot.html&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.cnbc.com/2022/02/03/winter-storm-descends-on-texas-bitcoin-miners-shut-off-to-protect-ercot.html&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They only post FUD about Bitcoin/Crypto, articles full of lies and misinformation. But this great factual article is nowhere to be seen there:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a major winter storm descends on Texas, crypto miners are powering down operations to help ease the burden on the state’s already beleaguered power grid. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The chief concern is that we might see a repeat of February 2021, when a deep freeze devastated large swaths of the state, leaving 10 million Texans without electricity and resulted in a multisystem meltdown that “was within minutes of a much more serious and potentially complete blackout.” Hundreds of people died amid the multiday outage. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Riot Blockchain, one of the biggest publicly traded crypto mining companies in America, began shutting down power to its Rockdale mine on Tuesday, a process that occurs in phases.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“As the storm has progressed, we have continued to decrease our power consumption by 98%-99%. So currently, we are only using 1%-2% of power,” said Trystine Payfer, Riot’s director of communications. Payfer told CNBC Riot will continue to manage its power usage as needed until there is “no extreme stress on the ERCOT grid.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Riot’s stock closed nearly 7% lower on Wednesday, and it is down over 31% year-to-date. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Several other crypto miners across Texas have followed suit in voluntarily curtailing energy consumption in the run-up to the arctic blast.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The CEO of Rhodium Enterprises, a fully integrated bitcoin miner using liquid-cooled infrastructure, tweeted that Texas-based bitcoin miners were curtailing their load starting Wednesday, in order to “help provide excess power reserves” for the storm. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“We are proud to help stabilize the grid and help our fellow Texans stay warm,” wrote Rhodium CEO Nathan Nichols.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Other crypto miners said they will respond in real-time to the needs of the grid.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The grid is called ERCOT, which is short for the Electric Reliability Council of Texas, the organization tasked with operating it. To run smoothly, ERCOT requires a perfect balance between supply and demand. Having too much power and not enough buyers is just as bad as everyone wanting to fire up their air conditioning units on the same day in July.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Whinstone CEO Chad Harris takes CNBC on a tour of the largest bitcoin mine in North America.
Whinstone CEO Chad Harris takes CNBC on a tour of the largest bitcoin mine in North America.
For years, ERCOT has struggled with fluctuating energy prices and sporadic service, which is why it strikes deals with flexible energy buyers, like crypto miners. Through established “demand response” programs, ERCOT will actually pay major industrial users to cut power.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“They’re expecting the same kind of grid load as you would have at peak summertime, so they’ll likely curtail miners at some point on Friday or Saturday,” explained Fred Thiel, CEO of Marathon Digital, another major player in the U.S. mining industry.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin miners specifically, and demand response more generally, are a powerful tool in the toolbox for grid management, according to Lee Bratcher, president of the Texas Blockchain Council.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Marathon’s Thiel tells CNBC that miners have been coordinating with ERCOT since last week to get ahead of any potential problems with the grid.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“Everybody wants to collaborate, everybody wants to voluntarily do whatever it takes to support ERCOT,” he said.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The question now is when the baseload that miners use (the baked-in energy demand from miners as a collective) is shut down and transferred back to the grid, does that provide the grid with what it needs to keep functioning as normal?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“This is a key test moment for the industry,” continued Thiel.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Whether crypto miners going offline en masse in one of the biggest crypto mining jurisdictions in the world will move the price of bitcoin, the answer is probably no.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The supply delta from changing the pace of mining is typically minimal, and any price moves in bitcoin or other major proof-of-work cryptocurrencies would likely have more to do with macro factors and overall risk-off behavior.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;WATCH NOW
VIDEO02:51
A war is brewing among states in the US to attract bitcoin miners
Big test for bitcoin miners
Many in the mining industry tell CNBC that the next few days are a high-stakes way of testing out whether the narrative of crypto miners being good for the grid bears out under pressure. The state’s growing crypto mining contingent ballooned after China banished all crypto miners last May.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“Bitcoin miners want to be good stewards of grid stability,” said Alex Brammer of Luxor Mining, a cryptocurrency pool built for advanced miners. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“We are incentivized financially but also from a political narrative, and therefore, regulatory perspective. We want to show the world we contribute to the health and resilience of the grid, and we know that all eyes will be on us throughout this first big test of the year,” continued Brammer.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That financial incentive is key. Miners are not altruistically opting to do the grid a solid by sometimes powering down some or all of its bitcoin miners to free up electricity for those in need. Instead, there are a lot of financial perks baked into its arrangement with the nonprofit organization that operates Texas’ grid. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“Imagine how much you would have to pay Amazon to say, ‘Hey, there’s too much demand for power. Please power down your data center,’” said bitcoin mining engineer Brandon Arvanaghi, who now runs Meow, a company that enables corporate treasury participation in crypto markets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“But it can do that with bitcoin very easily, because all you have to do is pay the miners slightly more than what they would have made mining for bitcoin that hour,” continued Arvanaghi, who calls the setup a “a win-win.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If the grid operators pay the miners a penny more than they would have made from mining in any given hour, then they’ll gladly power down. And from Thiel’s experience, they get curtailment requests less than 3% of the time in the course of a year, which he estimates comes to about five to ten hours a month.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Even bitcoin miners that haven’t cut a deal with ERCOT sometimes voluntarily power down at times of peak consumption when prices shoot higher.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The price of power per hour is all over the place, routinely going negative.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Shaun Connell, the EVP of power at Lancium, tells CNBC that in 2020, the price of energy in West Texas was negative between 10% and 20% of the time. The price dips below zero when supply outpaces demand.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In 2021, the price of power per hour was negatively priced 9% of the time, while 5% of all hours peaked above $100. Extreme tails like the ones shown in the chart below aren’t a good thing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Scales
In 2021, had miners voluntarily cut back their uptime expectation from 100% to 95%, they would have slashed their per megawatt hour price from $178 to $25, according to data from Lancium, a Houston-based energy tech company that specializes in bitcoin mining. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Strategically timed energy curtailment proves especially vital for the Texas grid, which exists as its own little island. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Unlike the rest of the continental U.S. that belongs to either the Eastern or Western interconnection (the names of the two interconnected power grids linking states), 90% of Texas runs on ERCOT, a deregulated and independent network of energy providers that is not tethered to any other grid in the U.S. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;While this competitive market often drives down the price of power as providers compete on cost to capture customers, it also means that there is less of a safety net baked into the grid. This presents problems in the face of calamitous events, such as a power shortage or a natural disaster, like the fatal winter storm in early 2021. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Adding a “controllable load resource” like bitcoin miners to the grid acts as a sort of life insurance policy. It’s almost like a hedge against disaster.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And it’s no skin off the back of bitcoin miners. Bitcoin has no uptime requirement, nor is the gear worn down by regularly powering off and on. It’s pretty much a win, win.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“That’s the beauty of bitcoin — it’s something no other industry can really do,” Arvanaghi told CNBC. “It’s very synergistic.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Not everyone agrees
Not all are convinced that bitcoin miners are the solution.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“Miners are a strain on the grid, not a help,” said Ben Hertz-Shargel of Wood Mackenzie, a provider of commercial intelligence for the world’s natural resources sector. Hertz-Shargel is concerned that bitcoin mining would only raise peak demand, ultimately adding stress to the system.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hertz-Shargel predicts that bitcoin could more than double demand growth in ERCOT’s territory, but unlike pro-crypto Republican Sen. Ted Cruz, Hertz-Shargel doesn’t think that additional demand is a good thing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;″The analogy I like to use is that if you start smoking two packs a day and then cut back to one pack on holidays, that doesn’t make smoking good for your health,” he says.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hertz-Shargel argues that ERCOT should be focused on grid improvements to make it easier to get power from solar and wind farms to big consumption centers, and that bitcoin miners aren’t the right way to deal with demand fluctuations. Instead, he argues, “the intermittency of renewables should be met with demand response from societally-beneficial loads, like industrial facilities, commercial buildings, and residential air conditioners — or energy storage.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But ERCOT interim CEO Brad Jones thinks bitcoin miners can be helpful.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Jones has been touring the state and hosting public events to answer questions from Texans about the electric grid. Besides winter weather, the impact of cryptocurrency mining on the grid is a common question.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“I’m pro bitcoin...but I’m too risk averse to be an investor in bitcoin,” Jones told a crowd of residents in Frisco, Texas in December. The ERCOT chief went on to explain the mutually beneficial relationship between the grid and bitcoin miners.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“A lot of these solar and wind can produce power down to a negative power range, negative $23 per megawatt hour,” Jones said. “These bitcoins see that as a great opportunity. They can get paid to use power. And that’s why they’re coming to the state. But that’s not necessarily bad.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Jones makes the point that negative power isn’t healthy for the market. Bitcoin miners “soak up” some of that negative power, and when the cost of electricity gets slightly higher than what they’re willing to pay for it (around $100, according to Jones), they shut off.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“So I think it’s really a valuable potential resource for us.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto prices may fall at a rate the world has never seen before]]></title><description><![CDATA[Here are some valid reasons why this may happen

Because literally anything can happen, dummy.

This is just a simple reminder that just because a post makes you feel good,
doesn't make it true. And just because you don't agree with a post, doesn't make
it wrong.

Prices fell for a couple months…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl9uyn/crypto_prices_may_fall_at_a_rate_the_world_has/?score=548&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl9uyn%2Fcrypto_prices_may_fall_at_a_rate_the_world_has%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl9uyn%2Fcrypto_prices_may_fall_at_a_rate_the_world_has%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl9uyn/crypto_prices_may_fall_at_a_rate_the_world_has/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 18:33:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here are some valid reasons why this may happen&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Because literally anything can happen, dummy.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is just a simple reminder that just because a post makes you feel good, doesn&amp;amp;#39;t make it true. And just because you don&amp;amp;#39;t agree with a post, doesn&amp;amp;#39;t make it wrong.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Prices fell for a couple months and this place was a ghost town. We&amp;amp;#39;ve seen a couple good days and everybody is an expert again.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A vast majority of the 4.4M members of this sub are not experts, have very little experience, have never read a whitepaper, could not explain blockchain to their parents, and have very little skin in the game. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Not everybody, but most.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Great analyses can go unnoticed, and garbage can be upvoted to the moon.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I hate how the concept of NFTs is now reduced to JPEGs. There are much more amazing applications for NFTs.]]></title><description><![CDATA[NFT technology is one of the best and most interesting technologies that came
out of blockchain.

Its kinda frustrating seeing how people instantly think of JPEGs once you
mention NFTs.

NFTs can be used in MANY ways. Tickets, product listing, identity verification
and much more.

And yes I…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl84r7/i_hate_how_the_concept_of_nfts_is_now_reduced_to/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl84r7%2Fi_hate_how_the_concept_of_nfts_is_now_reduced_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl84r7%2Fi_hate_how_the_concept_of_nfts_is_now_reduced_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl84r7/i_hate_how_the_concept_of_nfts_is_now_reduced_to/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 18:33:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;NFT technology is one of the best and most interesting technologies that came out of blockchain.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Its kinda frustrating seeing how people instantly think of JPEGs once you mention NFTs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;NFTs can be used in MANY ways. Tickets, product listing, identity verification and much more.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And yes I understand that some of these expensive jpegs like Bored Ape come with services and exclusivity but I think they’re super inflated in price. Some projects like Last Hopium offer literally the same exclusivity in contacts and experiences for much more comprehendible prices.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;People should really start focusing more on the applications that NFT technology can be used in instead of paying attention to overinflated jpegs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BTC has just undone a month's worth of decline in 24 hours; this is why the crypto market is so entertaining]]></title><description><![CDATA[It never closes and that's probably where the obsession lies for so many:
there's no weekend or nighttime reprieve from the upticks and downticks. You
know that when you go to bed and when you wake up in the morning something will
have changed in your portfolio; things jump up or fall off of a…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl4rdn/btc_has_just_undone_a_months_worth_of_decline_in/?score=325&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl4rdn%2Fbtc_has_just_undone_a_months_worth_of_decline_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl4rdn%2Fbtc_has_just_undone_a_months_worth_of_decline_in%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl4rdn/btc_has_just_undone_a_months_worth_of_decline_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 17:34:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It never closes and that&amp;amp;#39;s probably where the obsession lies for so many: there&amp;amp;#39;s no weekend or nighttime reprieve from the upticks and downticks. You know that when you go to bed and when you wake up in the morning something will have changed in your portfolio; things jump up or fall off of a cliff our of nowhere and you&amp;amp;#39;re just lying there thinking about what you&amp;amp;#39;re going to buy when it all works out (because it feels like an inevitability); you wake up and shrug off the -5% because you&amp;amp;#39;re sure that eventually it&amp;amp;#39;ll be made up, and it might not even take that long because of how quickly things seem to gain or lose momentum. At first it&amp;amp;#39;s stressful but if you stick around you develop a kind of gallows humour where you just laugh and wait for the next day to come around to throw more coins into the money pit. Because one day you know you&amp;amp;#39;ll have enough for that little impractical squashed-looking yellow car.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Congrats to beginners who survived the dive under 40K ! Bravo Bravo Bravo !]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey, to all who didn't sell under 40K, congrats!

We are still far away from ATH BUT you are not one of those who sold at a loss
in order to swing trade. The climb is not yet achieved and we may dive further
but you have shown your balls of steel and deserve recognition.

Bonus points if you bought…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl4zki/congrats_to_beginners_who_survived_the_dive_under/?score=334&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl4zki%2Fcongrats_to_beginners_who_survived_the_dive_under%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl4zki%2Fcongrats_to_beginners_who_survived_the_dive_under%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl4zki/congrats_to_beginners_who_survived_the_dive_under/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 17:34:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hey, to all who didn&amp;amp;#39;t sell under 40K, congrats!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We are still far away from ATH BUT you are not one of those who sold at a loss in order to swing trade. The climb is not yet achieved and we may dive further but you have shown your balls of steel and deserve recognition.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bonus points if you bought the dip under 40K ! You may even already be back in profit depending on how much your poured into the dip.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Honestly be proud of you, crypto is wild and can grind your nerves but in the long run you may make good money !&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TLDR: Congrats to those who didn&amp;amp;#39;t sell at a loss in the hope to swing trade.TLDR2: Obvious WOW congrats to those who were able to swing trade and successfully did it !&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let&amp;amp;#39;s keep calm and continue to DCA/ buy dips/ but stay steady !&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dit is het moment om na te denken over de toekomst. Spreek je samen met ons uit voor een onverdeelde samenleving waar deelname niet afhankelijk is van een gezondheidspas. Doe je mee? Sluit je aan bij onze coalitie. https://t.co/PLRpKJfMwS

#onverdeeldopen https://t.co/08IzSoCR8U]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1489995619825500161/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1489995619825500161/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 16:38:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Everytime]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sl64xs/everytime/?score=473&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsl64xs%2Feverytime%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsl64xs%2Feverytime%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sl64xs/everytime/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 16:38:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Have you ever heard an intelligent, well-spoken person who clearly understands blockchain technology say it's all a scam or it's going nowhere or it's not the future?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Exactly. 90% of the criticism you read about blockchain, web3, etc is written by
people who literally do not know what it is or how it works. Obviously, if you
do not know how something works, you can't see potential in it in terms of what
it can do. If you think the limits of NFTs are jpegs of…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl6cmh/have_you_ever_heard_an_intelligent_wellspoken/?score=443&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl6cmh%2Fhave_you_ever_heard_an_intelligent_wellspoken%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl6cmh%2Fhave_you_ever_heard_an_intelligent_wellspoken%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl6cmh/have_you_ever_heard_an_intelligent_wellspoken/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 16:38:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Exactly. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;90% of the criticism you read about blockchain, web3, etc is written by people who&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;literally do not know what it is or how it works&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Obviously, if you do not know how something works, you can&amp;amp;#39;t see potential in it in terms of what it can do. If you think the limits of NFTs are jpegs of monkeys or in-game upgrades and Bitcoin is just internet money which takes a lot of energy to move around, you do not understand why there is all the hype around them. It would of course look like a ponzi scheme to you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Low intelligence, and the lack of understanding of the world around you and the way it works lends itself to conspiratorial thinking. This is found in &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psypost.org/2021/07/new-study-indicates-conspiracy-theory-believers-have-less-developed-critical-thinking-ability-61347&quot;&amp;gt;study after study&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. If things around you are confusing and you don&amp;amp;#39;t understand them, but it seems like at least &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;some&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; people understand them, of course you would think they are in cahoots. It&amp;amp;#39;s easier to say they must be in cahoots than to acknowledge your own intellectual failings. You are the dementia patient who won&amp;amp;#39;t admit or lacks the awareness to know that they are just forgetting where they put things, so you instead accuse everybody around you of stealing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the same way, lack of understanding about blockchain leads you to believe it&amp;amp;#39;s all a conspiracy, ponzi scheme, FOMO/hype nonsense, etc. Are there some conspiracies in the world? Of course. But is your average watcher of &amp;amp;quot;Ancient aliens&amp;amp;quot; or subscriber to the conspiracy subreddit the smartest duck in the room? No. The world is too complicated, and they seek a simple solution which makes them seem like they understand everything, they don&amp;amp;#39;t want to be somebody who is confused all the time, they just want the world to make sense, and conspiracy gives them a simple explanation that does, even if it seems fantastical to others. It&amp;amp;#39;s a very understandable human response to having too much information, and we all do it from time to time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;All the intelligent, well-spoken people I know who -- understand blockchain tech --have no problem thinking creatively about many, many use cases for it&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. People who are much smarter than me, who can explain what a zk-rollup is and why it matters. They may say that a lot of the NFT stuff is hype, or guardedly say that crypto can&amp;amp;#39;t solve everything, or that web3 has some kinks to work out, because of course it does, it is a new technology. Intelligent people &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;are not afraid of nuance and complexity&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; because they can keep track of it all. They don&amp;amp;#39;t jump to the conclusion that it&amp;amp;#39;s all or nothing, or that because they don&amp;amp;#39;t understand it, it must not have value. They aren&amp;amp;#39;t afraid to admit when they are wrong, or that their understanding may change in the future, they understand the world is not binary and that some things are complex enough that they lack the knowledge to fully understand them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto is the future. Tech geniuses see it. Major financial institutions see it. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Your friend who thinks crypto is a scam doesn&amp;amp;#39;t. And that&amp;amp;#39;s ok, they don&amp;amp;#39;t have to.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; They would have said the same thing about the internet, and they&amp;amp;#39;ll be using it in 20 years whether they&amp;amp;#39;re excited about it or not.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But if you really want to challenge them, ask questions. Ask them &amp;amp;quot;why?&amp;amp;quot; and you will quickly find they have no fucking idea what they are even talking about. So don&amp;amp;#39;t waste your time debating them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;PS If you are interested in learning more about how cryptocurrency works and can help the development of science please check out &amp;lt;a href=&quot;http://np.reddit.com/r/cryptoforscience&quot;&amp;gt;http://np.reddit.com/r/cryptoforscience&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[40% of all US currency was printed in the last 12 months]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skt8dq/40_of_all_us_currency_was_printed_in_the_last_12/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskt8dq%2F40_of_all_us_currency_was_printed_in_the_last_12%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskt8dq%2F40_of_all_us_currency_was_printed_in_the_last_12%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skt8dq/40_of_all_us_currency_was_printed_in_the_last_12/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 15:32:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My first cash out in 9 years]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skuu2n/my_first_cash_out_in_9_years/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskuu2n%2Fmy_first_cash_out_in_9_years%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskuu2n%2Fmy_first_cash_out_in_9_years%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skuu2n/my_first_cash_out_in_9_years/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 15:32:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why I believe we are all still a decade early to crypto.]]></title><description><![CDATA[This post is a serious one I made after reading this article. [
https://moxie.org/2022/01/07/web3-first-impressions.html ]

> Shout out to Moxie for actually talking about how shit has just become super
> overcomplicated for coders to even begin to get into. This article is probably
> the best…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl3h00/why_i_believe_we_are_all_still_a_decade_early_to/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl3h00%2Fwhy_i_believe_we_are_all_still_a_decade_early_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl3h00%2Fwhy_i_believe_we_are_all_still_a_decade_early_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl3h00/why_i_believe_we_are_all_still_a_decade_early_to/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 15:32:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This post is a serious one I made after reading this article. [ &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://moxie.org/2022/01/07/web3-first-impressions.html&quot;&amp;gt;https://moxie.org/2022/01/07/web3-first-impressions.html&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; ] &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Shout out to Moxie for actually talking about how shit has just become super overcomplicated for coders to even begin to get into. This article is probably the best critique of the current crypto space I&amp;amp;#39;ve ever read ^&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We have these ideas of immutable, trustless, decentralized platforms but most of them have become mutable and centralized with all trust put in the hands of a few servers.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cardano, for example, the fact that &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptosrus.com/cardstarter-and-sundaeswap-a-falling-out-story/&quot;&amp;gt;sundaeswap took 6 months to release and it&amp;amp;#39;s not even fully ready yet&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; …&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coin.fyi/news/cardano/cardstarter-and-every-single-project-it-has-launched-smells-of-a-scam-nmrfpt&quot;&amp;gt;plus looking like they rugged cardstarter&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, it’s not a good look!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Trustless&amp;amp;quot; doesn&amp;amp;#39;t make sense when there&amp;amp;#39;s still just a team of greedy humans on the other end of single phone line. I recall when my friends where first getting into crypto a few months ago, best believe it wasn&amp;amp;#39;t &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;‘for the tech’&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;, it was pure greed, they were aping hundreds into doggy coins hoping to make millions out of thin air. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Arweave, which was made to solve the issue of NFTs being backed by on centralized servers, is still putting trust in the hands of others, so it&amp;amp;#39;s not exactly &amp;amp;quot;trustless&amp;amp;quot; and things can still be flagged for deletion and stuff like that. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.arweave.org/technology&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.arweave.org/technology&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;  = &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Finally, those that maintain gateways (the servers you will likely use to view the permaweb) can also apply content moderation policies to further safeguard their users.&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s tricky though, like if you have permanent jpeg storage on a truly immutable permanent server what about criminal abuse material and other f’ed up stuff like that from being put on there ‘for good’? That&amp;amp;#39;s why Arweave has a democratic processes for removal of content if it&amp;amp;#39;s deemed necessary, but the problem is it&amp;amp;#39;s SLOW! &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just like Cardano, just like ETH, and Bitcoin, Dogecoin, and so on. All these truly decentralized things are slow as shit.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Compare the time it takes to load this:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://audius.co/neonanesthetics&quot;&amp;gt;https://audius.co/neonanesthetics&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;With this:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/4h3dx3iH28dTFooTspQqxd&quot;&amp;gt;https://open.spotify.com/artist/4h3dx3iH28dTFooTspQqxd&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This just really highlights the sheer magnitude of the blockchain trilemma: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Low Cost, Speed, Decentralization. Pick 2.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I still believe in crypto, but if this doesn&amp;amp;#39;t make you think...I&amp;amp;#39;ve always said there will probably be a dominant cryptocurrency in the future that solves all of these issues, but less and less am I thinking it will be any networks available today. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It will likely be built upon 6G network protocols, or some similar competing concept; 6G will basically mishmash the current 5G super-speed, satellite based internet, to that of the internet of things, peer2peer data transfer, and blockchain(s). &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here&amp;amp;#39;s a journal article from last summer: &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Blockchain and 6G: The Future of Secure and Ubiquitous Communication&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/pdf/2106.05673.pdf&quot;&amp;gt;https://arxiv.org/pdf/2106.05673.pdf&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;  = &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;the trustless nature of blockchain would make it easier to manage and audit 3D network resources and AI model parameters in 6G networks.&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Another example, in Windows update there&amp;amp;#39;s this:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/jfd16glvkzf81.png?width=732&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=8119e238830ba28eba85c150763a516e13c85373&quot;&amp;gt;Microsoft Windows Update Delivery Optimization&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now extrapolate that concept out to creating the blockchain and the internet itself, not just simple data transfer - it&amp;amp;#39;ll be a mix of current cell-tower tech sped up a thousand-fold by decentralizing server loads through peer2peer means, encrypted, and under consensus - all while having latency speeds measured in single digit milliseconds!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here is a latency test of my internet to google: Top is with VPN routed through Portugal : Bottom is without VPN.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/szcppeg2lzf81.png?width=722&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=4ae7a88e08ba577ff67785c362d5beba976f4b17&quot;&amp;gt;Ping Command to Test Your Network&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We need speeds 1 order of magnitude faster than the current best case scenario technologies, and 2 orders of magnitude faster than what&amp;amp;#39;s the more &amp;amp;quot;practical&amp;amp;quot; speeds we&amp;amp;#39;re used to. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To conclude this spiel, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;I think we&amp;amp;#39;re about a decade away from this all.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Till then, I am still having fun learning about money, economics, fiancé, decentralization issues, network effects, but less and less am I feeling married to any single current network/blockchain because they all seem to be unable to carry the load that will weigh on future technological shoulders.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[It's incredible how quickly a few green candles changes the general sentiment in this subreddit.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I don't want to come off as a killjoy; I'm as hyped as anyone here. But it was
only a few days ago when everyone thought we were in the middle of a bear
market, a few green candles later and it's posts calling for altseason and short
squeezes. It's insane what one day of green does to people. Pumps…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl2kun/its_incredible_how_quickly_a_few_green_candles/?score=424&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl2kun%2Fits_incredible_how_quickly_a_few_green_candles%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsl2kun%2Fits_incredible_how_quickly_a_few_green_candles%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sl2kun/its_incredible_how_quickly_a_few_green_candles/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 13:30:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I don&amp;amp;#39;t want to come off as a killjoy; I&amp;amp;#39;m as hyped as anyone here. But it was only a few days ago when everyone thought we were in the middle of a bear market, a few green candles later and it&amp;amp;#39;s posts calling for altseason and short squeezes. It&amp;amp;#39;s insane what one day of green does to people. Pumps are exciting, but we need to calm down a bit.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Don&amp;amp;#39;t forget we are still in a downtrend, and history shows that pumps can disappear as fast as they appeared. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So don&amp;amp;#39;t make any reckless decisions, stick to the plans you made before this pump, and calm down a bit. You&amp;amp;#39;ll do better if you stay humble and keep a level head on yourself. Cheers.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blockfi Horrible Loan Experience (FORTUNE Lost)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Took out a loan for $300K and put up 600K worth of BTC as collateral. Market
kept going down so I kept posting collateral as needed to keep the loan healthy.



I got an email saying that the loan was being called back because of "indirect
exposure to a mixing service"



I appealed the decision…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skxpr7/blockfi_horrible_loan_experience_fortune_lost/?score=478&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskxpr7%2Fblockfi_horrible_loan_experience_fortune_lost%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskxpr7%2Fblockfi_horrible_loan_experience_fortune_lost%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skxpr7/blockfi_horrible_loan_experience_fortune_lost/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 11:30:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Took out a loan for $300K and put up 600K worth of BTC as collateral. Market kept going down so I kept posting collateral as needed to keep the loan healthy.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I got an email saying that the loan was being called back because of &amp;amp;quot;indirect exposure to a mixing service&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I appealed the decision because I bought the BTC back in May of 2020 and kept it on my Trezor the entire time. However, since I didn&amp;amp;#39;t buy it on an exchange and the person before me mixed it (BISQ) I get absolutely screwed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In summary I took out a loan when BTC was 65,000, Cost me over $6000 in origination fees, paid two months of loan payments ($2500+), got liquidated at $37,000 a few MINUTES before a pump to $42,000 today because of &amp;amp;quot;indirect mixing exposure&amp;amp;quot; and now I lost more than half of my BTC holdings, have a huge tax bill, and was screwed out of a fortune.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;DO NOT USE BLOCKFI LOANS. Worst experience I have ever had in Bitcoin&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: Since everybody keeps saying &amp;amp;quot;Dont take loans to buy crypto&amp;amp;quot; I am adding this comment to the main post&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;My bank did not consider BTC as an asset. I took out the loan with the intention of showing the balance in my bank account so I can get the mortgage and was planning on paying off the loans to get my BTC back.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Didnt work out......&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT 2: Most importantly the main problem for me was the P2P nature of the transaction. They literally do not allow you to buy your BTC from any private source that does not perform KYC. This is the biggest piece of fuckery of the entire situation that people need to pay very close attention to. I didnt, and it cost me 100s of thousands&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://blockfi.com/prohibited-uses/&quot;&amp;gt;https://blockfi.com/prohibited-uses/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can the new Coinbase user agreement legally force you to agree to whatever terms they want by blocking access to assets you already own?]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skv4t2/can_the_new_coinbase_user_agreement_legally_force/?score=315&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskv4t2%2Fcan_the_new_coinbase_user_agreement_legally_force%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskv4t2%2Fcan_the_new_coinbase_user_agreement_legally_force%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skv4t2/can_the_new_coinbase_user_agreement_legally_force/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 10:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Mr. Saylor!]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skftz6/happy_birthday_mr_saylor/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskftz6%2Fhappy_birthday_mr_saylor%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskftz6%2Fhappy_birthday_mr_saylor%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skftz6/happy_birthday_mr_saylor/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 10:39:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[$250M of Shorts rekt after Bitcoin surged to $40k: One Shorter Lost $3M with just one Order]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sklg6p/250m_of_shorts_rekt_after_bitcoin_surged_to_40k/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsklg6p%2F250m_of_shorts_rekt_after_bitcoin_surged_to_40k%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsklg6p%2F250m_of_shorts_rekt_after_bitcoin_surged_to_40k%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sklg6p/250m_of_shorts_rekt_after_bitcoin_surged_to_40k/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 08:31:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Fundraiser For Canadian Truckers Launches Following GoFundMe Suspension]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skwhpz/bitcoin_fundraiser_for_canadian_truckers_launches/?score=338&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskwhpz%2Fbitcoin_fundraiser_for_canadian_truckers_launches%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskwhpz%2Fbitcoin_fundraiser_for_canadian_truckers_launches%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skwhpz/bitcoin_fundraiser_for_canadian_truckers_launches/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 08:31:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[More than $100M worth of Bitcoin shorts liquidated in last 24 hours! 🥳 🎉🎉🎉]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skvvj8/more_than_100m_worth_of_bitcoin_shorts_liquidated/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskvvj8%2Fmore_than_100m_worth_of_bitcoin_shorts_liquidated%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskvvj8%2Fmore_than_100m_worth_of_bitcoin_shorts_liquidated%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skvvj8/more_than_100m_worth_of_bitcoin_shorts_liquidated/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 06:39:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Peter Schiff on Bitcoin]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skqtlh/peter_schiff_on_bitcoin/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskqtlh%2Fpeter_schiff_on_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskqtlh%2Fpeter_schiff_on_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skqtlh/peter_schiff_on_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 05:41:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[U.S. Senator Ted Cruz bought up to $50,000 worth of Bitcoin during the dip]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skv0hf/us_senator_ted_cruz_bought_up_to_50000_worth_of/?score=343&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskv0hf%2Fus_senator_ted_cruz_bought_up_to_50000_worth_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskv0hf%2Fus_senator_ted_cruz_bought_up_to_50000_worth_of%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skv0hf/us_senator_ted_cruz_bought_up_to_50000_worth_of/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 04:42:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Did I miss something on this pump?]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skrwp1/did_i_miss_something_on_this_pump/?score=335&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskrwp1%2Fdid_i_miss_something_on_this_pump%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskrwp1%2Fdid_i_miss_something_on_this_pump%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skrwp1/did_i_miss_something_on_this_pump/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 03:36:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GOOD NEWS: America COMPETES Act passes House without 'disastrous' provision on crypto]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skrlye/good_news_america_competes_act_passes_house/?score=330&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskrlye%2Fgood_news_america_competes_act_passes_house%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskrlye%2Fgood_news_america_competes_act_passes_house%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skrlye/good_news_america_competes_act_passes_house/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 03:36:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas is bracing for bitter cold temperatures as a major storm descends on the state. Crypto miners are stepping in and powering down to help alleviate some of the pressure on the power grid. [CNBC]]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skpt0x/texas_is_bracing_for_bitter_cold_temperatures_as/?score=360&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskpt0x%2Ftexas_is_bracing_for_bitter_cold_temperatures_as%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskpt0x%2Ftexas_is_bracing_for_bitter_cold_temperatures_as%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skpt0x/texas_is_bracing_for_bitter_cold_temperatures_as/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 03:36:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin surges toward $40K as stocks volatility keeps Wall Street on edge]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skfuqq/bitcoin_surges_toward_40k_as_stocks_volatility/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskfuqq%2Fbitcoin_surges_toward_40k_as_stocks_volatility%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskfuqq%2Fbitcoin_surges_toward_40k_as_stocks_volatility%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skfuqq/bitcoin_surges_toward_40k_as_stocks_volatility/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 02:40:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A Crypto short squeeze might be happening right now, and it can completely reverse the current trajectory of the market.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bitcoin seems to have shot past its $40k barrier in a matter of hours, and it is
likely to continue considering how many people are shorting the market right
now. Crypto hasn't yet lost its steam and it was dragged down by the stock
market for the past few days. This has accumulated A LOT of…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skm0fa/a_crypto_short_squeeze_might_be_happening_right/?score=482&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskm0fa%2Fa_crypto_short_squeeze_might_be_happening_right%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskm0fa%2Fa_crypto_short_squeeze_might_be_happening_right%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skm0fa/a_crypto_short_squeeze_might_be_happening_right/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 01:18:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin seems to have shot past its $40k barrier in a matter of hours, and it is likely to continue considering how many people are shorting the market right now. Crypto hasn&amp;amp;#39;t yet lost its steam and it was dragged down by the stock market for the past few days. This has accumulated A LOT of shorters.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/lx6hz6ct4vf81.jpg?width=1525&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=3a4eec27f4f445c3f55ba4977521da9c6237463b&quot;&amp;gt;Short positions are extremely high&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just looking at this alone should give you a picture of what has been happening. There are a lot of people that are shorting the market right now, and a Bitcoin short squeeze is likely considering that whales have been eating up the weeks long selling pressure with huge purchases. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Short  Squeeze Indications&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt; &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Substantial amount of buying pressure.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;  ✅ &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;RSI below 30 for an unnatural amount of time.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; ✅ &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Short interest way above 20%.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;  ✅ &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Huge sudden uptick in price.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; ✅ &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The market indications are suggesting a textbook short squeeze scenario for Bitcoin, and that might potentially reverse the Crypto market&amp;amp;#39;s trajectory. Remember, Bitcoin is already 10% up in a matter of a few hours. This means people shorting are at a loss and they will either have to sell at a loss or borrow more shares, driving up the price. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TLDR:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Bitcoin closed one of the biggest green candles in over a year, and it is most likely the beginning of a short squeeze due to an unusually large amount of people shorting the market. Moreover, surpassing 40k in a matter of  hours just invalidated weeks of FUD. If this continues, investors will be looking at a bullish Crypto market and a bearish stock market which is possibly the best environment for another huge bull run.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does anyone know the cause of today's 7% pump?]]></title><description><![CDATA[It went from 37 to 39 in a few minutes. Any known reason? Big news or some short
squeeze?]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skhyo5/does_anyone_know_the_cause_of_todays_7_pump/?score=313&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskhyo5%2Fdoes_anyone_know_the_cause_of_todays_7_pump%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskhyo5%2Fdoes_anyone_know_the_cause_of_todays_7_pump%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skhyo5/does_anyone_know_the_cause_of_todays_7_pump/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 01:18:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It went from 37 to 39 in a few minutes. Any known reason? Big news or some short squeeze?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Super Bowl jumps on the NFT bandwagon with 2022 tickets sold as NFTs]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skca74/super_bowl_jumps_on_the_nft_bandwagon_with_2022/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskca74%2Fsuper_bowl_jumps_on_the_nft_bandwagon_with_2022%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskca74%2Fsuper_bowl_jumps_on_the_nft_bandwagon_with_2022%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skca74/super_bowl_jumps_on_the_nft_bandwagon_with_2022/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 01:18:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This pump feels weird to me]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bitcoin had a pretty big pump today and the chart looks pretty good lately.
Maybe I have PTSD from all the failed rallies lately, but it's giving me a weird
feeling.

Getting back above 40K, with an RSI above 50 is a good sign, whales have been
buying according to Will Clemente's on chain…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skikem/this_pump_feels_weird_to_me/?score=334&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskikem%2Fthis_pump_feels_weird_to_me%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskikem%2Fthis_pump_feels_weird_to_me%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skikem/this_pump_feels_weird_to_me/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 01:18:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin had a pretty big pump today and the chart looks pretty good lately. Maybe I have PTSD from all the failed rallies lately, but it&amp;amp;#39;s giving me a weird feeling.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Getting back above 40K, with an RSI above 50 is a good sign, whales have been buying according to Will Clemente&amp;amp;#39;s on chain analysis.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But I&amp;amp;#39;m still feeling very cautious, as if we&amp;amp;#39;ll get another big dump soon.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m starting to feel more bullish tho, but with all the weird stuf going on in crypto and stocks lately, I can&amp;amp;#39;t really trust any pumps anymore lol.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This feeling will probably change if the pump continues, but does anyone else feel the same?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[You know the market's pumping when the exchanges all suddenly 'go down']]></title><description><![CDATA[Title says it all, tried to look at my portfolio on Coinbase just now and what a
surprise:


INVESTIGATING LATENCY


WE'RE INVESTIGATING LATENCY ON COINBASE.COM AND THE MOBILE APP AND DIFFICULTY
WITH TRADES / PAYMENTS. OUR TEAMS ARE WORKING TO RESTORE FULL SERVICE ASAP.

Interesting that the…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skm2km/you_know_the_markets_pumping_when_the_exchanges/?score=348&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskm2km%2Fyou_know_the_markets_pumping_when_the_exchanges%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskm2km%2Fyou_know_the_markets_pumping_when_the_exchanges%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skm2km/you_know_the_markets_pumping_when_the_exchanges/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 01:18:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Title says it all, tried to look at my portfolio on Coinbase just now and what a surprise:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Investigating Latency&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;We&amp;amp;#39;re investigating latency on Coinbase.com and the mobile app and difficulty with trades / payments. Our teams are working to restore full service ASAP.&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Interesting that the exchanges never go down when the market crashes. When that happens and everyone scrambles online to try and paperhand sell their crypto in a race to the bottom they seem to always work impeccably.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, the markets suddenly surge over 10% and they suddenly just cannot handle the bandwidth. Almost as if they had significantly too little crypto in their reserves and a sudden price hike would mean they didn&amp;amp;#39;t have the time to increase their reserves. Almost as if they were expecting the market to drop further and that gamble didn&amp;amp;#39;t pay off so better bring out the ol &amp;amp;#39;we&amp;amp;#39;re experiencing technical difficulty please stand by.&amp;amp;#39;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Of course perhaps it&amp;amp;#39;s all a giant coincidence it happens every time....&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[40k has been breached REPEAT 40k has been breached! The bear market is gone and 100k Btc is on the way.]]></title><description><![CDATA[We all know that there's such a thing as a bear market, but where is it? I don't
see it, that's because it's a myth from the days of old and we're men of science
and reason now. You see, we're in a new age in the crypto world, it's called the
bull summer, basically get your umbrella drinks out…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sknd3a/40k_has_been_breached_repeat_40k_has_been/?score=855&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsknd3a%2F40k_has_been_breached_repeat_40k_has_been%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsknd3a%2F40k_has_been_breached_repeat_40k_has_been%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sknd3a/40k_has_been_breached_repeat_40k_has_been/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 23:30:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We all know that there&amp;amp;#39;s such a thing as a bear market, but where is it? I don&amp;amp;#39;t see it, that&amp;amp;#39;s because it&amp;amp;#39;s a myth from the days of old and we&amp;amp;#39;re men of science and reason now. You see, we&amp;amp;#39;re in a new age in the crypto world, it&amp;amp;#39;s called the bull summer, basically get your umbrella drinks out because we&amp;amp;#39;re only going up from here.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is your captain speaking, we are flying at over 100k Btc soon, fasten your seatbelts and keep your pants on please (seriously no indecent exposure). Soon, all your wildest dreams will come true, see you on the other side of riches and b... beaches, sandy beaches.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A bipartisan group of U.S. House representatives has reintroduced a bill that would exempt consumers from paying taxes on crypto payments of less than $200]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skc3gl/a_bipartisan_group_of_us_house_representatives/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskc3gl%2Fa_bipartisan_group_of_us_house_representatives%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskc3gl%2Fa_bipartisan_group_of_us_house_representatives%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skc3gl/a_bipartisan_group_of_us_house_representatives/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 23:30:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Over $100 million shorts liquidated over the last 4 hours. Bears are getting rekt!]]></title><description><![CDATA[According to data from Coinglass [https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData] 88%
of the total liquidated positions during the last four hours were shorts. This
figure may change quite a bit as it was 85% when I started writing this post and
now it's at 88%. The 122 million figure may change as well…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skjq3a/over_100_million_shorts_liquidated_over_the_last/?score=323&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskjq3a%2Fover_100_million_shorts_liquidated_over_the_last%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskjq3a%2Fover_100_million_shorts_liquidated_over_the_last%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skjq3a/over_100_million_shorts_liquidated_over_the_last/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 23:30:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;According to data from &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinglass.com/LiquidationData&quot;&amp;gt;Coinglass&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; 88% of the total liquidated positions during the last four hours were shorts. This figure may change quite a bit as it was 85% when I started writing this post and now it&amp;amp;#39;s at 88%. The 122 million figure may change as well as time passes.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some simple math of 88% multiplied by 122 million means that approximately 107 million dollars in shorts were liquidated. Take that bears!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At the time of writing, over 50 million dollars were Bitcoin shorts and over 40 million dollars were Ethereum shorts. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The largest single liquidation order happened on Okex - BTC-USDT-SWAP valued at $3.18 million.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the past 24 hours, 54542 traders were liquidated.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is the risk of trading with leverage and the saying &amp;amp;quot;invest only what you can afford to lose&amp;amp;quot; applies the most if you decide to dabble with this strategy.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I love it when shorts are liquidated. I hope this trend continues and we go onwards and upwards.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[50% of dollars were created in the last 2 years. Why haven’t we seen hyperinflation in the US?]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skf6fp/50_of_dollars_were_created_in_the_last_2_years/?score=351&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskf6fp%2F50_of_dollars_were_created_in_the_last_2_years%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskf6fp%2F50_of_dollars_were_created_in_the_last_2_years%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skf6fp/50_of_dollars_were_created_in_the_last_2_years/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 20:35:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[60,000 Indians have signed a petition for the government to lower crypto tax and to not tax crypto income at 30%.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skhopf/60000_indians_have_signed_a_petition_for_the/?score=323&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskhopf%2F60000_indians_have_signed_a_petition_for_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskhopf%2F60000_indians_have_signed_a_petition_for_the%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skhopf/60000_indians_have_signed_a_petition_for_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 20:35:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin returns to $40K, liquidating over $50M of shorts in hours]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skj71b/bitcoin_returns_to_40k_liquidating_over_50m_of/?score=509&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskj71b%2Fbitcoin_returns_to_40k_liquidating_over_50m_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskj71b%2Fbitcoin_returns_to_40k_liquidating_over_50m_of%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skj71b/bitcoin_returns_to_40k_liquidating_over_50m_of/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 20:35:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hats off to Kraken, who now let users verify that the balances they hold are backed by real assets]]></title><description><![CDATA[While I'm not the biggest fan of centralized exchanges, I think it's still the
best way for noobs to learn about crypto. In this sense, the trust relationship
between holders and CEXs is crucial: when you buy BTC or ETH, you want the
exchange to actually own these tokens.

That's why I was very…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skhyo2/hats_off_to_kraken_who_now_let_users_verify_that/?score=412&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskhyo2%2Fhats_off_to_kraken_who_now_let_users_verify_that%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskhyo2%2Fhats_off_to_kraken_who_now_let_users_verify_that%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skhyo2/hats_off_to_kraken_who_now_let_users_verify_that/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 20:35:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;While I&amp;amp;#39;m not the biggest fan of centralized exchanges, I think it&amp;amp;#39;s still the best way for noobs to learn about crypto. In this sense, the trust relationship between holders and CEXs is crucial: when you buy BTC or ETH, you want the exchange to actually own these tokens.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That&amp;amp;#39;s why I was very pleased to learn today that Kraken has &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kraken.com/proof-of-reserves/?utm_source=content+announcement&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;amp;utm_campaign=por+announcement&amp;amp;amp;utm_content=content+link&amp;amp;amp;j=239745&amp;amp;amp;sfmc_sub=49972818&amp;amp;amp;l=227_HTML&amp;amp;amp;u=3691634&amp;amp;amp;mid=514004678&amp;amp;amp;jb=121&quot;&amp;gt;just launched a new way&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for their customers to verify, with cryptographic proof, that their tokens are actually in their accounts.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s called &amp;amp;quot;proof of reserves&amp;amp;quot;, and here&amp;amp;#39;s how it works. Twice a year, an auditor takes an anonymized snapshot of all balances held and aggregates them into what is called a Merkle tree, a private database that encapsulates all client balances. Some cryptographic magic happens (the actual operation is quite complicated to go over in this post), and voilà! Users can now verify their balances with a few clicks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;You don&amp;amp;#39;t have to take Kraken words for granted : they can prove to you they&amp;amp;#39;re actually holding the tokens you bought.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In full disclosure, I have to say that I&amp;amp;#39;ve been a Kraken customer since I started in crypto, so I&amp;amp;#39;m not entirely neutral. However, in my opinion, this kind of practice allows our ecosystem to gain credibility. The days of Mt. Gox and Quadriga are well and truly over!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[It doesn’t matter if you agree with your government or not. PAY YOUR TAXES]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tax Fraud is serious

First of all no government is perfect there will always be some degree of
corruption and wasteful spending. As for actually agreeing with how your
government spends money, most people don’t, that’s why there are differing
political parties.

Live in a third world dictatorship…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skh83b/it_doesnt_matter_if_you_agree_with_your/?score=375&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskh83b%2Fit_doesnt_matter_if_you_agree_with_your%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fskh83b%2Fit_doesnt_matter_if_you_agree_with_your%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/skh83b/it_doesnt_matter_if_you_agree_with_your/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 18:39:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Tax Fraud is serious &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;First of all no government is perfect there will always be some degree of corruption and wasteful spending. As for actually agreeing with how your government spends money, most people don’t, that’s why there are differing political parties. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Live in a third world dictatorship full of corruption, well fuck pay your taxes anyway so you don’t get arrested. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Most of the sub lives in the United States, a democracy with 538 people fighting on where money is spent every day. If you don’t like it vote differently. I know crypto has a big libertarian base, but your views do not justify cheating the system. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“I’d rather donate the money”, Do it then! Guess what, tax deductions for charities exist if you want to donate your profits. Put your money where your mouth is and stop making excuses&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you hide your crypto profits you are no better than millionaires with offshore accounts&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;wow some of you are incapable of civil discussion and feel the need to insult anyone with a different opinion than you&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My king is NOT dead!!!]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skg0jo/my_king_is_not_dead/?score=404&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskg0jo%2Fmy_king_is_not_dead%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskg0jo%2Fmy_king_is_not_dead%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skg0jo/my_king_is_not_dead/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 17:34:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Imagine if your parents had a whole Bitcoin for you before you were even able to say the word Bitcoin]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skbzrh/imagine_if_your_parents_had_a_whole_bitcoin_for/?score=427&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskbzrh%2Fimagine_if_your_parents_had_a_whole_bitcoin_for%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fskbzrh%2Fimagine_if_your_parents_had_a_whole_bitcoin_for%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/skbzrh/imagine_if_your_parents_had_a_whole_bitcoin_for/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 16:32:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Super Bowl is now being called ‘Crypto Bowl’ as upstart finance firms spend millions on T.V. ads]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sk5a09/the_super_bowl_is_now_being_called_crypto_bowl_as/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsk5a09%2Fthe_super_bowl_is_now_being_called_crypto_bowl_as%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsk5a09%2Fthe_super_bowl_is_now_being_called_crypto_bowl_as%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sk5a09/the_super_bowl_is_now_being_called_crypto_bowl_as/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 16:32:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[💥Intel will present its new #Bitcoin mining ASIC chip on February 23!]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1489616758117965827/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1489616758117965827/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 15:40:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Myanmar military recently announced 1 year jail for owning crypto and now is planning their own cryptocurrency.Fuck these governments.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sk8s8c/myanmar_military_recently_announced_1_year_jail/?score=847&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsk8s8c%2Fmyanmar_military_recently_announced_1_year_jail%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsk8s8c%2Fmyanmar_military_recently_announced_1_year_jail%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sk8s8c/myanmar_military_recently_announced_1_year_jail/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 15:40:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>