<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing on Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 10:36:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[There was a time when I believed that competent people with good intentions were running things.

Times have changed.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492788648701480964/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492788648701480964/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 09:41:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does anyone still believe CBDCs are a good idea at this point? 😂 https://t.co/aUAZdKM7oS]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492788874782949377/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492788874782949377/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 09:41:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cash app activating lightning is the biggest game changer. It is the tipping point. Exponentially accelerating adoption begins now.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cash app now enables its 70 million active users to send money internationally
using lightning to any other lightning compatible wallet. Not only can users
send funds instantly and for free to any other cash app user but also to any
strike user or lightning wallet on earth.

This is how network…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sr2i2l/cash_app_activating_lightning_is_the_biggest_game/?score=313&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsr2i2l%2Fcash_app_activating_lightning_is_the_biggest_game%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsr2i2l%2Fcash_app_activating_lightning_is_the_biggest_game%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sr2i2l/cash_app_activating_lightning_is_the_biggest_game/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 08:32:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cash app now enables its 70 million active users to send money internationally using lightning to any other lightning compatible wallet. Not only can users send funds instantly and for free to any other cash app user but also to any strike user or lightning wallet on earth. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is how network effects start. Now all cash app users are compatible with all strike users and LN wallet users. Once venmo plugs into lightning all venmo users will be compatible with all cash app, strike and LN wallet users. At this point if you use any other app like paypal or transferwise or wechat or your banks online banking app you are not part of the network. You are not part of the group of people all connected to each other on lightning, and you are stuck within your one single app unable to interact with all of the people on the open lightning network. All you can do is send money to other people who happen to use the exact app you are using. Thats like only being able to send email to people who use the same email provider you use.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One by one apps plug into lightning and network effects take hold. If you don&amp;amp;#39;t offer lightning compatibility you are essentially cut off from the world.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;All of a sudden 10 of the largest financial and social apps and their 2 billion users are all on the lightning network and all freely transferring money between each other instantly and at no cost. If you are a merchant do you keep only accepting visa essentially alienating anyone using any financial app? Or do you download a lightning compatible POS app so any of those 2 billion people can pay you from their app of choice. You are a business person so you figure out how those 2 billion people can pay you from whatever app they use by making sure your business POS system is lightning compatible. All of a sudden people are paying you using messenger twitter whatsapp IG venmo cashapp and strike and you no longer need to pay visas extortionate 2% transaction fees so your profit margin doubles.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Its at this point anyone accepting visa looks like a dinosaur trying to only accept checks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This all plays out within the next 24 to 36 months.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The world is about to change for the better.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Canada Set To Become Crypto Power House With The Introduction Of A New Cryptocurrency Bill]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sr1t4s/canada_set_to_become_crypto_power_house_with_the/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsr1t4s%2Fcanada_set_to_become_crypto_power_house_with_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsr1t4s%2Fcanada_set_to_become_crypto_power_house_with_the%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sr1t4s/canada_set_to_become_crypto_power_house_with_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 06:31:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[No one wants to talk to you. Sorry but you're being scammed]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know, there are warnings everywhere about scams, but I just don't understand
how some people fall for these types of scams.

A lot of scams begin with a simple conversation. If a random stranger just send
you a private message saying "hi", theres already a 99.9999% chance its a
scammer. I'm sorry…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqzyuq/no_one_wants_to_talk_to_you_sorry_but_youre_being/?score=316&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqzyuq%2Fno_one_wants_to_talk_to_you_sorry_but_youre_being%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqzyuq%2Fno_one_wants_to_talk_to_you_sorry_but_youre_being%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqzyuq/no_one_wants_to_talk_to_you_sorry_but_youre_being/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 06:31:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know, there are warnings everywhere about scams, but I just don&amp;amp;#39;t understand how some people fall for these types of scams. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A lot of scams begin with a simple conversation. If a random stranger just send you a private message saying &amp;amp;quot;hi&amp;amp;quot;, theres already a 99.9999% chance its a scammer. I&amp;amp;#39;m sorry but no one wants to talk to you, you&amp;amp;#39;re not special, you&amp;amp;#39;re not the lucky winner who is going to test a new project. You&amp;amp;#39;re being scammed. You would think everyone knows that but if they are doing it, its because it works.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, no exchange or bank is ever going to ask you for your password. So please, be smart and never trust anyone, if you have the slightest doubt about the legitimacy of something, call your exchange, call your bank, make a post, but dont take any risk!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Super Bowl is not gonna affect the price tomorrow, next week, or next super bowl.]]></title><description><![CDATA[A top post is just pure 'trust me bro' hopium hypenomics at work with a a title
to entice. Here's a fact for you all, viewership of the superbowl has been
consistently going down for more than a decade since 2010. So less people are
watching the game in general. About half of those people are just…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sr6tz4/the_super_bowl_is_not_gonna_affect_the_price/?score=319&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsr6tz4%2Fthe_super_bowl_is_not_gonna_affect_the_price%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsr6tz4%2Fthe_super_bowl_is_not_gonna_affect_the_price%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sr6tz4/the_super_bowl_is_not_gonna_affect_the_price/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 05:40:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A top post is just pure &amp;amp;#39;trust me bro&amp;amp;#39; hopium hypenomics at work with a a title to entice. Here&amp;amp;#39;s a fact for you all, viewership of the superbowl has been consistently going down for more than a decade since 2010. So less people are watching the game in general. About half of those people are just there for the ads and a majority of them are gonna be sharing the ads on Facebook, a social media platform that didn&amp;amp;#39;t grow last period and has an aging userbase to boot. So less people and mostly older that aren&amp;amp;#39;t gonna take financial risk are watching. I doubt Auntie BJ is gonna invest in crypto because Tom Brady told them about FTX. I can see my brother who uses facebook and has no teeth left seeing the ad and wanting to FOMO in. So that&amp;amp;#39;s the audience they&amp;amp;#39;re mainly getting.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s also just Americans. No one in Europe is gonna be watching the game and or gives a shit about Tom Brady. No one in Brazil is gonna be watching. Americans are not the only people invested in crypto, most South Koreans have no idea how American football works or again, gives a shit about ads that they wouldn&amp;amp;#39;t understand without subtitles and who is gonna be writing subtitles for ads for an American sporting event outside of Spanish and English?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Lastly, why would the news care about a crypto ad? Do you expect an interview with Tom Brady breaking it down his involvement and a full history on the past year of crypto? I&amp;amp;#39;ll bet they will talk about how much is spent on the ads this year and how much FTX grew and paid Tom Brady and then move on with their day.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This idea that a single ad during an American sporting event is gonna put us into a bull run is just silly. This is Saturday Night Live or Doge day again. There&amp;amp;#39;s no reason to think prices will go up except for hope. But they wanna cover their tracks and say it&amp;amp;#39;ll affect the prices in future. Okay, I drank coffee this morning and so the prices will go back up &amp;amp;#39;someday&amp;amp;#39;, that&amp;amp;#39;s my prediction based on nothing substantial.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Uber will accept cryptocurrencies... Would you pay via Bitcoin? :)]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sqjk4v/uber_will_accept_cryptocurrencies_would_you_pay/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsqjk4v%2Fuber_will_accept_cryptocurrencies_would_you_pay%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsqjk4v%2Fuber_will_accept_cryptocurrencies_would_you_pay%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sqjk4v/uber_will_accept_cryptocurrencies_would_you_pay/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 05:40:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[We need to do something about banks robbing us]]></title><description><![CDATA[Banks collected $12.4 billion dollars in overdraft fees in 2020. That means
banks took over $12 billion dollars from people with no money during a global
pandemic.

My bank takes between $50/70 dollars in overdraft fees every quarter. Yearly APY
on my saving account is so bad that it’s actually…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqyfdw/we_need_to_do_something_about_banks_robbing_us/?score=307&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqyfdw%2Fwe_need_to_do_something_about_banks_robbing_us%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqyfdw%2Fwe_need_to_do_something_about_banks_robbing_us%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqyfdw/we_need_to_do_something_about_banks_robbing_us/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 05:40:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Banks collected $12.4 billion dollars in overdraft fees in 2020. That means banks took over $12 billion dollars from people with no money during a global pandemic.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My bank takes between $50/70 dollars in overdraft fees every quarter. 
Yearly APY on my saving account is so bad that it’s actually never worth it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I staked most of my crypto which gives me back so much more than my robber of a bank that when crypto goes mainstream we are saved from these robbers.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I do need my bank account because I have not a lot of other choices to pay for stuff or receive. I did learn to stake my savings after buying stable coins with it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cant wait for massive crypto adoptions.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: I am debt free as of next month. I got lucky with a coin people on /CC dislike a lot. I sold it on it’s all time high and bought back at the recent crash and set aside the amount I needed for my debt. Next month is the last payment :)
I wont make the same mistakes again.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit 2:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I actually said I dont want to be able to overdraft day one 1 signed there. I guess they did it wrong but at that moment I didnt bother changing it. Which was dumb&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I just found this folder on a old hard drive from 2013. Can I do anything with this?]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sr57yn/i_just_found_this_folder_on_a_old_hard_drive_from/?score=423&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsr57yn%2Fi_just_found_this_folder_on_a_old_hard_drive_from%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsr57yn%2Fi_just_found_this_folder_on_a_old_hard_drive_from%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sr57yn/i_just_found_this_folder_on_a_old_hard_drive_from/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 02:47:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto Investors Concerned Global Nuclear War May Negatively Affect Market]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sr30cj/crypto_investors_concerned_global_nuclear_war_may/?score=409&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsr30cj%2Fcrypto_investors_concerned_global_nuclear_war_may%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsr30cj%2Fcrypto_investors_concerned_global_nuclear_war_may%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sr30cj/crypto_investors_concerned_global_nuclear_war_may/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 01:51:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I strongly believe that tomorrow's Super Bowl crypto adverts are going to cause the start of the next bull run!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Title sums it up but for those that don't know tomorrow during the Super Bowl
there is going to be advertisements from crypto dot com and other cryptos. This
is going to be the single biggest advertising advent reaching the largest number
and demographics of people that crypto has ever had.

Do I…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sr04jy/i_strongly_believe_that_tomorrows_super_bowl/?score=600&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsr04jy%2Fi_strongly_believe_that_tomorrows_super_bowl%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsr04jy%2Fi_strongly_believe_that_tomorrows_super_bowl%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sr04jy/i_strongly_believe_that_tomorrows_super_bowl/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 23:37:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Title sums it up but for those that don&amp;amp;#39;t know tomorrow during the Super Bowl there is going to be advertisements from crypto dot com and other cryptos. This is going to be the single biggest advertising advent reaching the largest number and demographics of people that crypto has ever had.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do I believe that just seeing these adverts is going to double our portfolio&amp;amp;#39;s tomorrow? No.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do I believe that there is going to be any significant price action tomorrow? Certainly not!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do I believe that tomorrow is going to be a focal point for the average public to talk about crypto? Yes.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And what happens every time the public take an interest in crypto? The media always follow through with more reports, articles, predictions etc and the larger investor, realising that the public are likely to start FOMOing in buy up the lower price quickly. And the more attention crypto gets the harder retail predictably starts FOMOing in which causes a feedback loop pushing prices sky high until large investor money swoops out of the market and crashes the price again.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So from the charts tomorrow will look like any other day but looking back from the future I bet my sats that it is the beginning of a significant upswing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: I apparently have to add that I&amp;amp;#39;m not American, I just appreciate the power advertising to retail especially one of the most lucrative retail markets of Americans that have on average the most disposable income and are the most likely to invest (as they have to as they have no social programmes!)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[These 23 year-old Texans made $4 million last year mining bitcoin off flare gas from oil drilling]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/squ87u/these_23_yearold_texans_made_4_million_last_year/?score=328&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsqu87u%2Fthese_23_yearold_texans_made_4_million_last_year%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsqu87u%2Fthese_23_yearold_texans_made_4_million_last_year%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/squ87u/these_23_yearold_texans_made_4_million_last_year/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 23:37:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WARNING: Guy, from famous YouTube channel, is shilling Solana. Channel is not neutral anymore.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Since the video comparing Solana vs Algo [https://youtu.be/RzucrCRGYkM] this guy
never stopped shilling Solana despite all the bugs and problems.

Even in the last video about Phantom Wallet [https://youtu.be/zI-Xd9vVnwY] he is
speaking more about Solana, then the Phantom itself.

It is clear to me…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqx6id/warning_guy_from_famous_youtube_channel_is/?score=322&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqx6id%2Fwarning_guy_from_famous_youtube_channel_is%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqx6id%2Fwarning_guy_from_famous_youtube_channel_is%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqx6id/warning_guy_from_famous_youtube_channel_is/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 23:37:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Since the video comparing &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/RzucrCRGYkM&quot;&amp;gt;Solana vs Algo&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; this guy never stopped shilling Solana despite all the bugs and problems. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Even in the last video about &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/zI-Xd9vVnwY&quot;&amp;gt;Phantom Wallet&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; he is speaking more about Solana, then the Phantom itself. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is clear to me that the team behind this channel received huge pile of money to keep on speaking about “VC blockchain” despite all the problems this centralized piece of tech has. Just watch his latest videos and count how many times he mentioned Solana. That’s just stupid. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Even when speaking about &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cryptopotato.com/solana-woes-worsen-in-320-million-120k-weth-wormhole-bridge-hack&quot;&amp;gt;Wormhole Hack&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; the guy literally said - “Yeah, whatever. Solans is still fastest blockchain out there. Anyway..” Watch it for yourself &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/LluzXOKRlXQ&quot;&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Channel is not neutral. It’s bought by Solana foundation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BlackRock wants to steal all your crypto, don’t let them.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sources say BlackRock, the world’s LARGEST asset manager, is preparing to offer
cryptocurrency trading services to investor clients. They manage over $10
trillion in assets via public pension schemes, family funds, endowments, and
sovereign wealth funds. BlackRock also owns 16.3% of…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqtbjl/blackrock_wants_to_steal_all_your_crypto_dont_let/?score=378&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqtbjl%2Fblackrock_wants_to_steal_all_your_crypto_dont_let%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqtbjl%2Fblackrock_wants_to_steal_all_your_crypto_dont_let%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqtbjl/blackrock_wants_to_steal_all_your_crypto_dont_let/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 19:32:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sources say BlackRock, the world’s LARGEST asset manager, is preparing to offer cryptocurrency trading services to investor clients. They &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;manage over $10 trillion in assets&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; via public pension schemes, family funds, endowments, and sovereign wealth funds. BlackRock also owns 16.3% of MicroStrategy.         &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;While this type of adoption allows giant whales to borrow from BlackRock pledging crypto assets as collateral, similar to how Wall Street banks and large financial institutions like Goldman Sachs, Morgan Stanley, and Citi are creeping into cryptocurrencies, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;best believe these legacy financial institutions do not have our best DeFi interests at heart.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;         &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They are forcing other sea creature from us small shrimp to large fish and sharks to compete with their crypto allocations. They know what will make them money and it’s make us believe we need their services. &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Tldr; You don’t want these giant centralized powers controlling your cryptocurrency.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What would make you sell all your bitcoin?]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sqcsnh/what_would_make_you_sell_all_your_bitcoin/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsqcsnh%2Fwhat_would_make_you_sell_all_your_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsqcsnh%2Fwhat_would_make_you_sell_all_your_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sqcsnh/what_would_make_you_sell_all_your_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 19:32:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[‘Let’s Go Brandon’ Crypto Coin Turns Into Total Dumpster Fire]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqmowy/lets_go_brandon_crypto_coin_turns_into_total/?score=307&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqmowy%2Flets_go_brandon_crypto_coin_turns_into_total%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqmowy%2Flets_go_brandon_crypto_coin_turns_into_total%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqmowy/lets_go_brandon_crypto_coin_turns_into_total/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 19:32:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hundreds of thousands of Australians demonstrate today in their capital city to demand an end to the COVID police state.
https://t.co/b6OZszC47h]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492535696065810433/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492535696065810433/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 16:55:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Agents had to 'wrest' a phone out of the hands of one of the accused bitcoin launderers as she repeatedly tried to lock the device]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqok00/agents_had_to_wrest_a_phone_out_of_the_hands_of/?score=325&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqok00%2Fagents_had_to_wrest_a_phone_out_of_the_hands_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqok00%2Fagents_had_to_wrest_a_phone_out_of_the_hands_of%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqok00/agents_had_to_wrest_a_phone_out_of_the_hands_of/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 16:32:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ethereum Founder Vitalik Buterin Writes In Russian, Plea Russia Not To Go For War]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqsa45/ethereum_founder_vitalik_buterin_writes_in/?score=459&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqsa45%2Fethereum_founder_vitalik_buterin_writes_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqsa45%2Fethereum_founder_vitalik_buterin_writes_in%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqsa45/ethereum_founder_vitalik_buterin_writes_in/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 16:32:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Whale Suddenly Moves Over $489,000,000 in BTC]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqofaf/bitcoin_whale_suddenly_moves_over_489000000_in_btc/?score=330&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqofaf%2Fbitcoin_whale_suddenly_moves_over_489000000_in_btc%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqofaf%2Fbitcoin_whale_suddenly_moves_over_489000000_in_btc%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqofaf/bitcoin_whale_suddenly_moves_over_489000000_in_btc/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 15:31:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I now understand why Proof of Work is so cool. Took me more than 10 minutes though]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sqognn/i_now_understand_why_proof_of_work_is_so_cool/?score=434&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsqognn%2Fi_now_understand_why_proof_of_work_is_so_cool%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsqognn%2Fi_now_understand_why_proof_of_work_is_so_cool%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sqognn/i_now_understand_why_proof_of_work_is_so_cool/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 14:34:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[[OC] I've made an analysis tool for cryptocurrency source code. Here are the results for Bitcoin, Ethereum, Solana, EOS.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey r /cc,

I’m working on a project that can bring more transparency to blockchain projects
and their development. Blockchain development is usually done in an open-sourced
way, where anyone can see what developers are working on. But this information
is usually only accessible to people who are…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqpuhy/oc_ive_made_an_analysis_tool_for_cryptocurrency/?score=355&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqpuhy%2Foc_ive_made_an_analysis_tool_for_cryptocurrency%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqpuhy%2Foc_ive_made_an_analysis_tool_for_cryptocurrency%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqpuhy/oc_ive_made_an_analysis_tool_for_cryptocurrency/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 14:34:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hey r /cc,&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m working on a project that can bring more transparency to blockchain projects and their development. Blockchain development is usually done in an open-sourced way, where anyone can see what developers are working on. But this information is usually only accessible to people who are developers themselves. Browsing a git repository, trying to understand what a commit, branch, or tag does is not really understandable for most non-developers. With the tool I&amp;amp;#39;m developing I&amp;amp;#39;m planning to shed a bit of light on what teams are doing and how the projects are progressing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In this post, I&amp;amp;#39;d like to go over some of the metrics I&amp;amp;#39;ve found interesting on different blockchains and how they can be used to understand the development of a project. All of the results I describe here are based on the tool I&amp;amp;#39;ve written and my personal experience in software development. Someone else with a different background might interpret the results differently.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m filtering out changes with more than 1000 lines and less than 100 lines. In my opinion, outside of this range, there is too much noise to be useful. I&amp;amp;#39;m also just inspecting the block producer code. In the next iterations, I&amp;amp;#39;ll take a look into entire organizations with all repositories. Let&amp;amp;#39;s start with bitcoin itself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/6pya36ib4eh81.png?width=2062&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=c6141e3f03eeae7bcdd4c47d91d6fafb0932a3ee&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/6pya36ib4eh81.png?width=2062&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=c6141e3f03eeae7bcdd4c47d91d6fafb0932a3ee&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;From the executive summary, I can see that ~9 % of the contributors who contribute to bitcoin are still onboard. But on the knowledge retention, we can see that some of the &amp;amp;quot;heavy hitters&amp;amp;quot; have left the project. Usually, this number starts at 100% for new projects and slowly decreases. Knowledge retention is a measure of how many lines of code which was edited by a certain contributor and if that contributor is still on-board. Remember that bitcoin had this block size war at some point, so it&amp;amp;#39;s normal to see some of the developers who contributed to bitcoin leave the project. Having a refactoring rate of ~60 % means that more than half of its codebase is re-written. And it&amp;amp;#39;s more or less in normal bounds.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/38njz74c4eh81.png?width=2062&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=ad3d07018d264085068778f2022b4b97341c146f&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/38njz74c4eh81.png?width=2062&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=ad3d07018d264085068778f2022b4b97341c146f&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Looking at the versions chart, it shows a steady and continuous development. If we look at some of the latest large updates, we can see that they are mostly rewrites. Of course, it&amp;amp;#39;s necessary to check more messages to get a better understanding but I want to leave it to users.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let&amp;amp;#39;s move on to the Ethereum project.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/jsn1lk4f4eh81.png?width=2048&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=7c882e71a3536ff20e0c00b13047aa06f2a08706&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/jsn1lk4f4eh81.png?width=2048&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=7c882e71a3536ff20e0c00b13047aa06f2a08706&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Ethereum shows worse results in the executive summary than bitcoin. This is quite surprising to me because Ethereum is a younger project than bitcoin. Yet the constant delays in their releases and always changing targets and deadlines, it seems like the metrics make sense. Only 7% of the contributors are still onboard, and the onboarded contributors only contributed 0.39% of the total changes. I would expect the new teams to re-do the same mistakes that previous teams did or re-write the same code again to understand it easier. I think a 60% refactoring rate is what we can assume to be generally good. But lower numbers would probably mean that projects are adding features faster than Ethereum and Bitcoin.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/bpco6j3g4eh81.png?width=2042&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=b781d229af8621c5471440878ba73351fc7255c5&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/bpco6j3g4eh81.png?width=2042&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=b781d229af8621c5471440878ba73351fc7255c5&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On the versions chart, last month seems like getting a bit more silent in Ethereum miner development. But keep in mind, this data is only from go-ethereum project, maybe the team might have their focus on some other repository nowadays.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now Solana.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/3vi6799h4eh81.png?width=2074&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=7e20865a1b620ca2b690a7c30e056f24b5d56f11&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/3vi6799h4eh81.png?width=2074&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=7e20865a1b620ca2b690a7c30e056f24b5d56f11&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Solana shows better results in the executive summary than Ethereum. But because Solana is a much younger project, higher team and knowledge retention is expected. This will result in faster deliveries and more features. But it&amp;amp;#39;s important to check this measure from time to time to see if they start bleeding talent.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/mjrzaj6i4eh81.png?width=2040&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=70046d0077a79310d5af93032f20d65be504dcaf&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/mjrzaj6i4eh81.png?width=2040&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=70046d0077a79310d5af93032f20d65be504dcaf&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Looking at the versions chart, we can see that there is constant development with more systematic changes which would be expected from an &amp;amp;quot;industry like development&amp;amp;quot; project with focused teams and serious project management. In a commit message from 2019, we can see that they were already trying to offload some work to GPU&amp;amp;#39;s from start. Yet I&amp;amp;#39;m curious what other changes are done in the subject, so I&amp;amp;#39;m going to search for updates with GPU messages in them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/tm9b8uij4eh81.png?width=2048&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d6a35ae9ed4410f0612f2405b4ef2c9c65e356b4&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/tm9b8uij4eh81.png?width=2048&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d6a35ae9ed4410f0612f2405b4ef2c9c65e356b4&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hmm, interestingly it seems like there is not much development being done with GPU term in the message.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Ok now let&amp;amp;#39;s move on to EOS.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/06x71zdk4eh81.png?width=2040&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d1516662b8182f6eaddde966e2b628c344479e1e&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/06x71zdk4eh81.png?width=2040&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d1516662b8182f6eaddde966e2b628c344479e1e&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m putting it here as it verifies the data I have. EOS is an old project which is riddled with issues. The executive summary shows that ~0% of the contributors are still onboard. This means no one is contributing to the project systematically anymore for 90 days. This is a very interesting metric to look at because it&amp;amp;#39;s really hard to onboard people back onto a codebase as complicated as EOS.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/qhan02al4eh81.png?width=2042&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=ef1af6b99d17370e3c76906b9fcd78f2774735a5&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/qhan02al4eh81.png?width=2042&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=ef1af6b99d17370e3c76906b9fcd78f2774735a5&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the versions chart, we can see that there is a sudden drop in the development NOV 2020. Afterward, it seems like it&amp;amp;#39;s completely stopped in MAY 2021(the chart of EOS ends here, not today). Of course, there might be some changes happening, but our filters are filtering them out, with these settings.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I think that&amp;amp;#39;s enough for now, I&amp;amp;#39;ll be updating the tool with the new data I find and I&amp;amp;#39;ll be adding more metrics. In the next weeks, I&amp;amp;#39;ll set up a notification system where users can get e-mails or push notifications when certain filter results bring new data. ex, you can subscribe to GPU updates on Solana and you&amp;amp;#39;ll get an e-mail when there is a new update.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you&amp;amp;#39;d like to access the tool while I&amp;amp;#39;m developing it, you can subscribe to my Patreon(&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.patreon.com/gkaykck&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.patreon.com/gkaykck&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;) and get an access link to the tool. After you get the access link, you are free to share it with friends if you&amp;amp;#39;d like, but I will update the key from time to time and post a new key on my Patreon page only to subscribers. So you can make your friends beg you for the new link :). But keep in mind that the application is really resource intensive and expensive to host as it&amp;amp;#39;s scanning through many gigabytes of data on every filter change. So I would ask you to not publish the access link on any online forums, the application can become unusable until the next key change.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Currently, you can inspect the following blockchain miners with the application;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Bitcoin&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Ethereum&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Stellar&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Avax&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Matic&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Cosmos&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Cardano&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Polkadot&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Algorand&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Solana&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Hedera&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Elrond&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Filecoin&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Theta&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Helium&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Monero&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- IOTA&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Flow&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- EOS&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- The Graph&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Loopring&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Arweave&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- Kadena&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you&amp;amp;#39;d like to suggest a new blockchain repository or use the tool for inspecting a repository you have, please get in contact with me through Patreon!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cheers!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[More than 500 Million people worldwide tomorrow are tuning in to watch the Super Bowl... Ads]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tomorrow millions of viewers worldwide are sitting in front of their devices.
"It will be late night here in germany where i live, but i cant wait to see the
exciting super bowl ads", a man from Berlin says "Who will win? CRO or FTX?".

But viewers are complaining, there is just too much sports…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqpdpr/more_than_500_million_people_worldwide_tomorrow/?score=503&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqpdpr%2Fmore_than_500_million_people_worldwide_tomorrow%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqpdpr%2Fmore_than_500_million_people_worldwide_tomorrow%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqpdpr/more_than_500_million_people_worldwide_tomorrow/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 13:41:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Tomorrow millions of viewers worldwide are sitting in front of their devices. &amp;amp;quot;It will be late night here in germany where i live, but i cant wait to see the exciting super bowl ads&amp;amp;quot;, a man from Berlin says &amp;amp;quot;Who will win? CRO or FTX?&amp;amp;quot;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But viewers are complaining, there is just too much sports between the commericals. &amp;amp;quot;I wanna see my ad, not some guys throwing around a ball, i mean, the spirit of football is to represent a neoliberal capitalist view, why do we need this childish men on the field between our proud american ads?&amp;amp;quot;, one fan from New York adds.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The crypto space took over the super bowl this year. &amp;amp;quot;Which means, we have to adapt our play to make sure our sponsors are happy&amp;amp;quot;, says an anonymous Quarterback. &amp;amp;quot;Before we pass the ball to another player, we need to pay gas fees, i hope my salary is enough for that eth...?&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Intel, the semiconductor giant, announced its #Bitcoin mining chips will ship later this year. Argo Blockchain, BLOCK (formerly known as Square) and GRIID Infrastructure are among our first customers. 

https://t.co/RjeLwii0RF]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492426988782563328/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492426988782563328/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 10:38:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What happened to the "winter of death" for the unvaccinated - Biden was screaming about a few months ago?]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492417248337739777/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492417248337739777/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 08:36:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Keep Calm and Carry On: Bitcoin Balance on Exchanges just Hit a 3-year Low.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sqglwp/keep_calm_and_carry_on_bitcoin_balance_on/?score=451&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsqglwp%2Fkeep_calm_and_carry_on_bitcoin_balance_on%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsqglwp%2Fkeep_calm_and_carry_on_bitcoin_balance_on%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sqglwp/keep_calm_and_carry_on_bitcoin_balance_on/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 08:34:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[This is how the ex-Safemoon COO lives after a rambunctious 5 months of a copy-pasted BSC token.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Estimates are in that this is a $12,000 jacket, a $30,000 rolex and he's flying
in a private jet.
[https://preview.redd.it/i321smcr0xg81.jpg?width=614&auto=webp&s=ba5ba47930228a5180f8d4a6bdc04e6f002f39ce]

Further proof that money doesn't buy style...

Want some backstory? You ain't alone - Jack…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sq5vlh/this_is_how_the_exsafemoon_coo_lives_after_a/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsq5vlh%2Fthis_is_how_the_exsafemoon_coo_lives_after_a%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsq5vlh%2Fthis_is_how_the_exsafemoon_coo_lives_after_a%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sq5vlh/this_is_how_the_exsafemoon_coo_lives_after_a/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 08:34:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/i321smcr0xg81.jpg?width=614&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=ba5ba47930228a5180f8d4a6bdc04e6f002f39ce&quot;&amp;gt;Estimates are in that this is a $12,000 jacket, a $30,000 rolex and he&amp;amp;#39;s flying in a private jet.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Further proof that money doesn&amp;amp;#39;t buy style... &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Want some backstory? You ain&amp;amp;#39;t alone&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; - Jack joined Safemoon in April as their Chief Operations Officer and was often seen alongside the CEO, spinning a vast web of bullshit while the devoted&amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;TM&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; threw in tens of thousands of dollars while Safemoon&amp;amp;#39;s market valuation performed a triple-salchow off the 10m diving board straight down to the gutter of the all-time-lows where it&amp;amp;#39;s currently been wallowing like a sickly pig.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As to what Jack &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;actually did&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;, well that&amp;amp;#39;s more difficult. I&amp;amp;#39;d like to think he was there to produce an air of legitimacy to the project but even that&amp;amp;#39;s a bit of a stretch, considering his previous employment had him working as a... &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;checks notes&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;... oh yes, a part-time DJ, no-name Twitch Streamer and he ran the twitter account of Ben Philips, some influencer dude.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/link/q0p7qz/video/c3k47r4jcar71/player?utm_source=reddit&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=usertext&amp;amp;amp;utm_name=SafeMoonInvesting&amp;amp;amp;utm_content=t3_q0p7qz&quot;&amp;gt;Anyway, here&amp;amp;#39;s Jack and Ben Phillips romping around London, eating gold-plated Tomahawk steak at a cost of £1,500 per meal..&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/link/q0p7qz/video/7z7jr9ijdar71/player?utm_source=reddit&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=usertext&amp;amp;amp;utm_name=SafeMoonInvesting&amp;amp;amp;utm_content=t3_q0p7qz&quot;&amp;gt;[Video 2]&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/0kuoaeyydar71.png?width=902&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=5be389c715198793978c5a14ed14dbadf87eba8d&quot;&amp;gt;Looking fresh, Jack&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;hr/&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;hr/&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;But what&amp;amp;#39;s the &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;real&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; story here?&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;hr/&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;hr/&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I think if people make money off Crypto, that&amp;amp;#39;s fair play. Less so when it&amp;amp;#39;s by stringing along Investors by promising them wealth while delivering products you know are broken (Safemoon wallet released under his watch!)  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But that all goes out the window when these people repeatedly claimed they didn&amp;amp;#39;t own any Safemoon. So when someone who worked as a part-time DJ suddenly comes into dramatic wealth, it does raise &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;some&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; red-flags, especially when they have gone on record over multiple AMA&amp;amp;#39;s saying none of the devs are the whale wallets cashing out millions of dollars at a time...  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And this behaviour came directly after &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/86u7kvgknom71.jpg&quot;&amp;gt;handing in his notice&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for &amp;amp;quot;toxicity&amp;amp;quot; reasons (perhaps the investors he strung along for 5 months were getting a bit rowdy?)  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Toxicity is a weird way to say &amp;amp;quot;Dumping the bags we claimed we never owned&amp;amp;quot;, but, whatever.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Just another shitcoin story.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Russia legalized bitcoin as currency to hedge against a weak Russian ruble and Biden sanctions. What do you guys think?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Putin supports legalizing bitcoin as currency because he’s threatening war and
Biden’s economic sanctions would hurt the ruble. He could still transact in the
world economy through bitcoin. I’m wondering everyone’s opinion on this.]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sq9b8z/russia_legalized_bitcoin_as_currency_to_hedge/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsq9b8z%2Frussia_legalized_bitcoin_as_currency_to_hedge%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsq9b8z%2Frussia_legalized_bitcoin_as_currency_to_hedge%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sq9b8z/russia_legalized_bitcoin_as_currency_to_hedge/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 05:31:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Putin supports legalizing bitcoin as currency because he’s threatening war and Biden’s economic sanctions would hurt the ruble. He could still transact in the world economy through bitcoin. I’m wondering everyone’s opinion on this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Uber CEO: We are absolutely going to accept cryptocurrency payments]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqdsn8/uber_ceo_we_are_absolutely_going_to_accept/?score=358&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqdsn8%2Fuber_ceo_we_are_absolutely_going_to_accept%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqdsn8%2Fuber_ceo_we_are_absolutely_going_to_accept%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqdsn8/uber_ceo_we_are_absolutely_going_to_accept/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 03:41:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What Is the Purpose of the Loopring Project?]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/spyu91/what_is_the_purpose_of_the_loopring_project/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fspyu91%2Fwhat_is_the_purpose_of_the_loopring_project%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fspyu91%2Fwhat_is_the_purpose_of_the_loopring_project%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/spyu91/what_is_the_purpose_of_the_loopring_project/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 03:41:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Happy Bitcoin Friday 🎷🦭]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/spzkdu/happy_bitcoin_friday/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fspzkdu%2Fhappy_bitcoin_friday%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fspzkdu%2Fhappy_bitcoin_friday%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/spzkdu/happy_bitcoin_friday/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 02:32:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin as hard money vs utility coins.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/spns3m/bitcoin_as_hard_money_vs_utility_coins/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fspns3m%2Fbitcoin_as_hard_money_vs_utility_coins%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fspns3m%2Fbitcoin_as_hard_money_vs_utility_coins%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/spns3m/bitcoin_as_hard_money_vs_utility_coins/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 01:48:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Soon mining on GPU:s will be over! Intel is releasing a blockchain accelerator that will be x1000 faster than GPU:s! Gamechanging tech for crypto!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Digital computing continues to enrich our lives in more ways than we can
imagine. We acquire, consume, and create content and services with a few clicks
or taps of our fingertips. Exponential increases in compute performance, enabled
by Moore’s Law, play a significant role in making these…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sq2srq/soon_mining_on_gpus_will_be_over_intel_is/?score=359&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsq2srq%2Fsoon_mining_on_gpus_will_be_over_intel_is%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsq2srq%2Fsoon_mining_on_gpus_will_be_over_intel_is%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sq2srq/soon_mining_on_gpus_will_be_over_intel_is/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 01:48:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Digital computing continues to enrich our lives in more ways than we  can imagine. We acquire, consume, and create content and services with a  few clicks or taps of our fingertips. Exponential increases in compute  performance, enabled by Moore’s Law, play a significant role in making  these experiences seamless. Moore’s Law is also enabling us to  democratize access to this enormous pool of processing power. Amazing  things happen when a lot of compute is available to a lot of people  without much friction.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We are looking forward to the next set of amazing things.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Blockchain  is a technology that has the potential to enable everyone to own much  of the digital content and services they create. Some even call it an  inflection point in computing, fundamentally disrupting the way we  store, process and transact our digital assets as we usher in the era of  metaverse and Web 3.0. No matter how the future evolves, it is certain  the availability of a lot more compute to everyone will play a central  role.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Today, we at Intel are declaring our intent to contribute to  the development of blockchain technologies, with a roadmap of  energy-efficient accelerators. Intel will engage and promote an open and  secure blockchain ecosystem and will help advance this technology in a  responsible and sustainable way.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We are mindful that some  blockchains require an enormous amount of computing power, which  unfortunately translates to an immense amount of energy. Our customers  are asking for scalable and sustainable solutions, which is why we are  focusing our efforts on realizing the full potential of blockchain by  developing the most energy-efficient computing technologies at scale.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our  blockchain accelerator will ship later this year. We are engaged  directly with customers that share our sustainability goals. Argo  Blockchain, BLOCK (formerly known as Square) and GRIID Infrastructure  are among our first customers for this upcoming product. This  architecture is implemented on a tiny piece of silicon so that it has  minimal impact to the supply of current products.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Intel Labs has  dedicated decades of research into reliable cryptography, hashing  techniques and ultra-low voltage circuits. We expect that our circuit  innovations will deliver a blockchain accelerator that has over 1000x  better performance per watt than mainstream GPUs for SHA-256 based  mining. You will be able to learn more about our circuit innovations at  the International Solid State Circuit Conference (ISSCC) this month.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To  support this, and additional emerging technology, we have formed the  new Custom Compute Group within Intel’s Accelerated Computing Systems  and Graphics business unit. The objective of this team is to build  custom silicon platforms optimized for customers’ workloads, including  blockchain and other custom accelerated supercomputing opportunities at  the edge.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Onward, we aspire to leverage technologies from our  zetta-scale computing initiative to deliver energy-efficient solutions  that make our tomorrow better than our today.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;By Raja M. Koduri&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
 &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Senior vice president and general manager of the Accelerated Computing Systems and Graphics Group at Intel Corporation.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://videocardz.com/press-release/intel-announces-energy-efficient-blockchain-accelerators-and-new-custom-compute-group&quot;&amp;gt;Link to VideoCardz article.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I originally bought crypto as a hedge to the market, but now all crypto does is follow the market]]></title><description><![CDATA[I bought BTC & ETH years ago and have held ever since. Only time I add is during
20%+ corrections, and I have never sold.

When I originally bought cypto, it was as a hedge to the stock market. And it
worked that way for a while.

I'm not sure what happened in the last 2-3 years but now Crypto just…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sq8rzd/i_originally_bought_crypto_as_a_hedge_to_the/?score=447&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsq8rzd%2Fi_originally_bought_crypto_as_a_hedge_to_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsq8rzd%2Fi_originally_bought_crypto_as_a_hedge_to_the%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sq8rzd/i_originally_bought_crypto_as_a_hedge_to_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 00:33:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I bought BTC &amp;amp;amp; ETH years ago and have held ever since. Only time I add is during 20%+ corrections, and I have never sold.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When I originally bought cypto, it was as a hedge to the stock market. And it worked that way for a while.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m not sure what happened in the last 2-3 years but now Crypto just follows the market. If the market is down cyrpto is down. If it&amp;amp;#39;s up, crypto is up. My assumption is cyrpto just got way too big the last few years and it just follows the bigger market.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I thought crypto was suppose to replace a lot of commodities? Turns out it’s just another temperature gauge of the market? Clearly not a hedge.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At this point, why not just buy SPY instead?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[People call this dip Russian FUD and it's fucking disgusting]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm a little drunk rn but I'm pissed off and have to get this off my chest. I've
seen so many comments about the Russian / Ukraine conflict. People brush it off
as FUD, some even asked for Russia to "just fucking do it" so we can get over
with it already. Seriously what the FUCK is wrong with…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqcw3a/people_call_this_dip_russian_fud_and_its_fucking/?score=630&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqcw3a%2Fpeople_call_this_dip_russian_fud_and_its_fucking%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsqcw3a%2Fpeople_call_this_dip_russian_fud_and_its_fucking%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sqcw3a/people_call_this_dip_russian_fud_and_its_fucking/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 00:33:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m a little drunk rn but I&amp;amp;#39;m pissed off and have to get this off my chest. 
I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen so many comments about the Russian / Ukraine conflict. People brush it off as FUD, some even asked for Russia to &amp;amp;quot;just fucking do it&amp;amp;quot; so we can get over with it already. Seriously what the FUCK is wrong with people like you? Wishing for a country to be invaded by one of the most powerful forces in the world just so your favorite shitcoin can start to go up in value again? Be glad you are not on the edge of a war. People in this space have no ethics and are just as bad as your average banker investing in the war industry. I thought embracing authoritarian quasi-dictators like Bukele and Erdogan is bad enough but this crap takes it to a whole new level. Fuck everybody who thinks that way. Rethink your values.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Algorand to Scale Ethereum with Groundbreaking Protocol]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/spzzeg/algorand_to_scale_ethereum_with_groundbreaking/?score=329&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fspzzeg%2Falgorand_to_scale_ethereum_with_groundbreaking%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fspzzeg%2Falgorand_to_scale_ethereum_with_groundbreaking%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/spzzeg/algorand_to_scale_ethereum_with_groundbreaking/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 23:32:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Satoshi Nakamoto disappearing was the biggest masterstroke ever done and the thing that actually made crypto what it is today.]]></title><description><![CDATA[13 Years ago today Satoshi said that trust is the main problem with central
banks. The centralized system needs you to trust all party's included. And athst
very hard to do nowadays.

That probably also was the reason why Satoshi Nakamoto disappeared. Crypto is
about being anonymous, it's about…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sq5b1o/satoshi_nakamoto_disappearing_was_the_biggest/?score=574&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsq5b1o%2Fsatoshi_nakamoto_disappearing_was_the_biggest%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsq5b1o%2Fsatoshi_nakamoto_disappearing_was_the_biggest%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sq5b1o/satoshi_nakamoto_disappearing_was_the_biggest/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 23:32:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;13 Years ago today Satoshi said that trust is the main problem with central banks. The centralized system needs you to trust all party&amp;amp;#39;s included. And athst very hard to do nowadays.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That probably also was the reason why Satoshi Nakamoto disappeared. Crypto is about being anonymous, it&amp;amp;#39;s about having a decentralized system where you don&amp;amp;#39;t have to trust anyone (obviously that does even today not happen everywhere in crypto).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If Satoshi would have still been here and available to everyone. He would be seen as the big CEO of Crypto by some people that do not have real knowledge about crypto. And that would have been another argument for them to call it a &amp;amp;quot;scam&amp;amp;quot;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Him not being here makes crypto what it was always meant to be: decentralized. No one is up there, we just don&amp;amp;#39;t know who made it. It&amp;amp;#39;s anonymous.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Satoshi Nakamoto played the game and he set off the fire that is still burning, brighter than ever.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My Fiance's Employer Wants to See My Holdings]]></title><description><![CDATA[My fiance's company is requiring it's employees and anyone who lives with said
employees to disclose their crypto holdings. Am I legally obligated to do so?
They already have access to my Fidelity account and now they want my bitcoin
too? Apparently they have some "Blacklist" and "Bitcoin will…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sq2kq3/my_fiances_employer_wants_to_see_my_holdings/?score=357&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsq2kq3%2Fmy_fiances_employer_wants_to_see_my_holdings%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsq2kq3%2Fmy_fiances_employer_wants_to_see_my_holdings%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sq2kq3/my_fiances_employer_wants_to_see_my_holdings/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 20:36:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My fiance&amp;amp;#39;s company is requiring it&amp;amp;#39;s employees and anyone who lives with said employees to disclose their crypto holdings.  Am I legally obligated to do so?  They already have access to my Fidelity account and now they want my bitcoin too?  Apparently they have some &amp;amp;quot;Blacklist&amp;amp;quot; and &amp;amp;quot;Bitcoin will never be on it.&amp;amp;quot;  At this point I might just transfer what I have in Coinbase to my cold storage and tell them I have nothing.  Anyone have a similar situation or ways to get around this?  Thanks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: Thank you to all who provided insight. I think I’ll transfer what I have on the exchange to my cold storage and be done with it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[On this day 13 years ago, Satoshi posted this message, “The root problem with conventional currency is all the trust that's required to make it work. The central bank must be trusted not to debase the currency, but the history of fiat currencies is full of breaches of that trust.”]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sq1j6w/on_this_day_13_years_ago_satoshi_posted_this/?score=525&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsq1j6w%2Fon_this_day_13_years_ago_satoshi_posted_this%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsq1j6w%2Fon_this_day_13_years_ago_satoshi_posted_this%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sq1j6w/on_this_day_13_years_ago_satoshi_posted_this/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 20:36:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ontario court freezes access to funds to truckers from GiveSendGo]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.cp24.com/mobile/news/ontario-court-freezes-access-to-donations-for-truckers-protest-from-givesendgo-1.5776665

This is what happens when governments have control over the money supply. This
is a modern day example of what occurs when the powers that be don't agree with
your views. This…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/spmjzc/ontario_court_freezes_access_to_funds_to_truckers/?score=321&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fspmjzc%2Fontario_court_freezes_access_to_funds_to_truckers%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fspmjzc%2Fontario_court_freezes_access_to_funds_to_truckers%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/spmjzc/ontario_court_freezes_access_to_funds_to_truckers/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 20:36:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cp24.com/mobile/news/ontario-court-freezes-access-to-donations-for-truckers-protest-from-givesendgo-1.5776665&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.cp24.com/mobile/news/ontario-court-freezes-access-to-donations-for-truckers-protest-from-givesendgo-1.5776665&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is what happens when governments have control over the money supply. This is a modern day example of what occurs when the powers that be don&amp;amp;#39;t agree with your views. This is the perfect example of why bitcoin is needed in the world and why we must fight tooth and nail to prevent government regulation over the asset.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Satoshi Nakamoto published this thirteen years ago today.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/spznij/satoshi_nakamoto_published_this_thirteen_years/?score=538&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fspznij%2Fsatoshi_nakamoto_published_this_thirteen_years%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fspznij%2Fsatoshi_nakamoto_published_this_thirteen_years%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/spznij/satoshi_nakamoto_published_this_thirteen_years/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 17:31:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Baby Musk Meme Coin Drops 100% After Rug Pull]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/spx9sm/baby_musk_meme_coin_drops_100_after_rug_pull/?score=461&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fspx9sm%2Fbaby_musk_meme_coin_drops_100_after_rug_pull%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fspx9sm%2Fbaby_musk_meme_coin_drops_100_after_rug_pull%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/spx9sm/baby_musk_meme_coin_drops_100_after_rug_pull/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 14:34:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Yesterday was an historical moment for #tether 
In ~3 weeks you'll understand why 🍫

(Yes yes, announcement-ception)]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492070462268088338/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492070462268088338/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 11:37:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Melania Trump sold her NFT to herself for $170,000]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/splxww/melania_trump_sold_her_nft_to_herself_for_170000/?score=325&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsplxww%2Fmelania_trump_sold_her_nft_to_herself_for_170000%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsplxww%2Fmelania_trump_sold_her_nft_to_herself_for_170000%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/splxww/melania_trump_sold_her_nft_to_herself_for_170000/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 10:38:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[nO oNe SaW iNfLaTiOn cOmInG https://t.co/xLAlHFRprh]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492053758406180883/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492053758406180883/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 08:47:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wow! 10 minutes ago someone donated 5 #Bitcoin to the Bitcoin for Truckers fund 🤯 https://t.co/7FiB7ZXYAU]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492050789816221742/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492050789816221742/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 08:47:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[After long lying that #NaturalImmunity is weak and inferior, the #CDC has finally admitted it offers better protection than #COVID19 #vaccines.
https://t.co/sClKFSMKlw]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492050411716493324/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1492050411716493324/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 08:47:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoins true value is somewhere between $500k to $10m. And it will get there faster than anyone could possibly imagine.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Microstrategy bought bitcoin in 2020. Two years later an institutional wave of
money is now entering.

El Salvador bought bitcoin in 2021, by 2023 a wave of sovereign nations will be
buying bitcoin to hold as reserves.

Bitcoins fair value is somewhere between gold and global debt which is…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/spjhxz/bitcoins_true_value_is_somewhere_between_500k_to/?score=313&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fspjhxz%2Fbitcoins_true_value_is_somewhere_between_500k_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fspjhxz%2Fbitcoins_true_value_is_somewhere_between_500k_to%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/spjhxz/bitcoins_true_value_is_somewhere_between_500k_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 06:39:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Microstrategy bought bitcoin in 2020. Two years later an institutional wave of money is now entering.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;El Salvador bought bitcoin in 2021, by 2023 a wave of sovereign nations will be buying bitcoin to hold as reserves.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoins fair value is somewhere between gold and global debt which is between $10 trillion and $200 trillion ($500k to  $10 million per coin).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;New tech is always overvalued before it is fully adopted just like the dot com bubble in the 90s getting way ahead of itself before most people even had a home internet connection.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin will not rise slowly. It will not give people the chance to take their time. It will melt faces off as it leaves everyone behind. A million dollar bitcoin will not take another 10 years, and it doesn&amp;amp;#39;t need to be held by five billion people to get there. It will be overvalued well before mainstream adoption takes place. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Once institutional fomo is well underway and sovereign nation fomo is heating up the price will rise by $100k in a month. It took 12 years to go from zero to a one trillion dollar market cap and once we are solidly above one trillion it could reach two trillion in a matter of months.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin will find its true value somewhere between $500k and $10 million per coin and it will happen faster than anyone on earth could possibly imagine.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Inflation rises 7.5% over the past year, even more than expected]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sp6qb1/inflation_rises_75_over_the_past_year_even_more/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsp6qb1%2Finflation_rises_75_over_the_past_year_even_more%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsp6qb1%2Finflation_rises_75_over_the_past_year_even_more%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sp6qb1/inflation_rises_75_over_the_past_year_even_more/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 06:39:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Texas is becoming the world capital for Bitcoin mining. In two years, the Lone Star state is on course to become the worlds largest producer, dwarfing any foreign nation and the combined output for the rest of the U.S.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/spnb4q/texas_is_becoming_the_world_capital_for_bitcoin/?score=355&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fspnb4q%2Ftexas_is_becoming_the_world_capital_for_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fspnb4q%2Ftexas_is_becoming_the_world_capital_for_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/spnb4q/texas_is_becoming_the_world_capital_for_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 06:39:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>