<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing on Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 06:39:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Let's be honest, how many of you actually held your coins through the last bear run?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I see a lot of people talking about how those who hold through the bear run will
be rewarded, but I rarely see people stating that they're the ones who went
through that.

Are any of you the ones that supposedly held through the insane crypto winter of
a couple years back? And if so, how much did…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ukeaw0/lets_be_honest_how_many_of_you_actually_held_your/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fukeaw0%2Flets_be_honest_how_many_of_you_actually_held_your%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fukeaw0%2Flets_be_honest_how_many_of_you_actually_held_your%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ukeaw0/lets_be_honest_how_many_of_you_actually_held_your/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 05:31:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I see a lot of people talking about how those who hold through the bear run will be rewarded, but I rarely see people stating that they&amp;amp;#39;re the ones who went through that.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Are any of you the ones that supposedly held through the insane crypto winter of a couple years back? And if so, how much did you gain back? How much were you rewarded by your faith in crypto?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I guess this could be survivorship bias. Maybe the people who did hold through that bear run made so much money that they don&amp;amp;#39;t need to be in this sub, but who knows. I&amp;amp;#39;m just curious.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[When Bitcoin dips 10%]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ukiasz/when_bitcoin_dips_10/?score=362&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fukiasz%2Fwhen_bitcoin_dips_10%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fukiasz%2Fwhen_bitcoin_dips_10%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ukiasz/when_bitcoin_dips_10/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 22:37:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[May 22 Bitcoin pizza day .]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ukkckm/may_22_bitcoin_pizza_day/?score=524&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fukkckm%2Fmay_22_bitcoin_pizza_day%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fukkckm%2Fmay_22_bitcoin_pizza_day%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ukkckm/may_22_bitcoin_pizza_day/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 21:37:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Safemoon CEO John Karony squanders $150,000 of Investor funds on a shitcoin, now worth $5,000 - a 96.6% loss]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is one of those truly remarkable things which I personally think elevates
Safemoon to #1 Crypto scam, far above Bitconnect.

In the latest Coffeezilla video [https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kIUrE7Ovm5k],
our intrepid investigator finally confirmed that John Karony, the CEO of
Safemoon,…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujypgz/safemoon_ceo_john_karony_squanders_150000_of/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujypgz%2Fsafemoon_ceo_john_karony_squanders_150000_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujypgz%2Fsafemoon_ceo_john_karony_squanders_150000_of%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujypgz/safemoon_ceo_john_karony_squanders_150000_of/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:39:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is one of those truly remarkable things which I personally think elevates Safemoon to #1 Crypto scam, far above Bitconnect.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kIUrE7Ovm5k&quot;&amp;gt;In the latest Coffeezilla video&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, our intrepid investigator finally confirmed that John Karony, the CEO of Safemoon, definitively owns the infamous &amp;amp;quot;Gabe&amp;amp;quot; wallet - the BSC wallet that ends in &amp;amp;quot;6abe&amp;amp;quot;  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I might make a future post about this, but a quick summary is that the Gabe wallet bought a &amp;amp;quot;Moondog&amp;amp;quot; NFT, which John then tweeted about, and also wrote an instagram post about moving it. He also attended Austin SXSW and received an exclusive NFT that is transferred to your wallet for attendees only.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This (among other evidence) was the smoking gun and confirmed John&amp;amp;#39;s ownership of said wallet, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;which was previously highlighted as problematic as it has been receiving millions of dollars from Bitmart which was supposed to be sent to the liquidity pool&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, and yet these funds are being withdrawn as cash or spent on frivolous items.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;hr/&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With that out the way, we know that Karony owns this wallet, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/6zSJko3&quot;&amp;gt;and he received a tip off from the slimy Ben Phillips&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; to buy some shitcoin called &amp;amp;quot;Stonks&amp;amp;quot;.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://bscscan.com/token/0xb966150c7a0150ed4ea979e04f18d109301aab95?a=0xd51d1d5503dcff819e214faa66c3b6f0ebb06abe&quot;&amp;gt;On that same day, Karony bought $150,000 worth of Stonks&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, becoming the 2nd largest token holder.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Unfortunately, John&amp;amp;#39;s investing savvy is secondly only to his FUD-fighting savvy, and his FUD-fighting savvy is fucking awful, and so I regret to say that his $150,000 worth of Stonks tokens are now... alas...  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;$5,107.46..&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;That&amp;amp;#39;s a 96.6% loss.&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;hr/&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If this was his own money, who gives a shit. But to actually misuse taxed funds from investors which was supposed to go into the liquidity pool to help secure price stability of Safemoon, in order to buy cringey worthless NFT&amp;amp;#39;s and hundreds of thousands of dollars of shit tokens is a new low.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Especially considering Safemoon currently has a very serious liquidity issue. With just over $6m in BNB liquidity left, it only takes a couple whales to drain the LP and slam the door shut on everyone else.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A bank run is a comin&amp;amp;#39;!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["Buy Bitcoin and Hold for retirement" - Senator Cynthia Lummis]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uk3mos/buy_bitcoin_and_hold_for_retirement_senator/?score=334&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuk3mos%2Fbuy_bitcoin_and_hold_for_retirement_senator%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuk3mos%2Fbuy_bitcoin_and_hold_for_retirement_senator%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uk3mos/buy_bitcoin_and_hold_for_retirement_senator/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:35:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[People in here treat NFTs like the rest of Reddit treats crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'ts so strange to watch the crytonatives in here shit talking NFTs on exactly
the same way and people on the rest of Reddit shit talk crypto in general. I'm
sure I'm going to get downvoted into oblivion but shouldn't we embrace NFTs if
it leads to wider mass adoption of the underlying blockchain…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uke7on/people_in_here_treat_nfts_like_the_rest_of_reddit/?score=521&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuke7on%2Fpeople_in_here_treat_nfts_like_the_rest_of_reddit%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuke7on%2Fpeople_in_here_treat_nfts_like_the_rest_of_reddit%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uke7on/people_in_here_treat_nfts_like_the_rest_of_reddit/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:35:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ts so strange to watch the crytonatives in here shit talking NFTs on exactly the same way and people on the rest of Reddit shit talk crypto in general. I&amp;amp;#39;m sure I&amp;amp;#39;m going to get downvoted into oblivion but shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t we embrace NFTs if it leads to wider mass adoption of the underlying blockchain tech? Content creators entering a tech space has never ended badly. Keen to hear why folks are so critical on the technology in general and wonder if those are the same responses that non crytonatives say about cryptocurrency in general.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A casual reminder]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uk0n23/a_casual_reminder/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuk0n23%2Fa_casual_reminder%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuk0n23%2Fa_casual_reminder%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uk0n23/a_casual_reminder/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 15:44:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[It's not a rose bed]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uk3ejl/its_not_a_rose_bed/?score=337&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuk3ejl%2Fits_not_a_rose_bed%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuk3ejl%2Fits_not_a_rose_bed%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uk3ejl/its_not_a_rose_bed/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 15:44:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Getting pretty tired of the crypto market]]></title><description><![CDATA[I've been here for a while now and I've gotta say ... I'm getting pretty tired
of our little market. There's so much that is just so rediculous.

For starters, wasn't the whole point to get away from the mainstream markets and
banks? Now here we are, directly correlated to the moves of the stock…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujz328/getting_pretty_tired_of_the_crypto_market/?score=319&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujz328%2Fgetting_pretty_tired_of_the_crypto_market%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujz328%2Fgetting_pretty_tired_of_the_crypto_market%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujz328/getting_pretty_tired_of_the_crypto_market/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 11:32:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ve been here for a while now and I&amp;amp;#39;ve gotta say ... I&amp;amp;#39;m getting pretty tired of our little market. There&amp;amp;#39;s so much that is just so rediculous.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For starters, wasn&amp;amp;#39;t the whole point to get away from the mainstream markets and banks? Now here we are, directly correlated to the moves of the stock market, driven by bots, Wall Street bankers and big finance whales.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And while we have such a tiny market cap, so much money is diverted into an entirely seperate market that recently blew up, NFT&amp;amp;#39;s. How much retail interest that otherwise would have gone into crypto&amp;amp;#39;s longer term was wasted on the NFT market by buying shitty JPG&amp;amp;#39;s of monkeys and rocks with laser eyes? What the hell were crypto people thinking promoting that BS other than trying to make a quick buck off the backs of ignorant retailers? If people had any forsight, that interest and limited funds would have been much better used in crypto projects. And that new retail would have been much better off for it too. Sure, many would have left with the market downturn, but many would have held too. But now all that new interest has been wasted by getting burned by a (so far) shitty use case in a side-market that&amp;amp;#39;s &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/nft-sales-plummet-92-market-133403653.html&quot;&amp;gt;down over 90%&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. A large percentage of whom never entered the crypto market itself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And then there&amp;amp;#39;s all the news driven BS and shitty meme coins. Doge coin? Shiba inu? Are you f*cking kidding me? Meme BS like that does nothing but damage the markets credibility, and again ... divert limited funds away from legitimate projects.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And we&amp;amp;#39;re entirely dependent on people like Elon Musk (who I like, but that doesn&amp;amp;#39;t change the fact that the market depending on his involvement is rediclulous), that something-something-Miller guy, Saylor, Kwon, ... Since when do we care what a few rich folks do? As retail we have the power to move the market. Too many people are just wasting their money on shitty NFT&amp;amp;#39;s and futures trading, rather than buying spot.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s sad to see this market turn into such a joke and be entirely at the behest of Wall Street ...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hell I still remember back in 2018 everyone was bemoaning the fact that the entire market was tied to the price of Bitcoin. Now here we are, not only still tied to Bitcoin but to the stock market too. What a sad joke.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Grow up. Be the change you want to see. See people about to waste their money on NFT&amp;amp;#39;s? Slap them. Thinking about participating in the futures market? Stick with spot. Thinking about shorting? Don&amp;amp;#39;t, just buy the dips. See news about Elon, Saylor or Kwon? Don&amp;amp;#39;t give a f*. Just DCA, stake, build, whatever it takes. Invest only what you can afford to miss for the long run and ignore the short term noise. This is the only place a lot of us see as an alternative to the old world. A potential for escape from all the control and restrictions. The endless boomer politicians sticking their grubby paws into everything. And however small we are as individuals, as a whole, we &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;can&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; move markets and change things. In more ways than one. We need an alternative system and so far, this is the best one we&amp;amp;#39;ve got. Don&amp;amp;#39;t waste it or let the old world shake you out and undermine it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Don't be in denial that your $500 to $100k token turned out to be the $1000 to $0.01.]]></title><description><![CDATA[There's a common reason people get extremely hostile and defensive, and it's
because they do not handle acceptance well. Don't believe me, then sort by
controversial on a popular post.

If you've made a bad decision, and have to accept a negative outcome it's worth
aknowledging that to move on.…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uk3sw0/dont_be_in_denial_that_your_500_to_100k_token/?score=341&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuk3sw0%2Fdont_be_in_denial_that_your_500_to_100k_token%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuk3sw0%2Fdont_be_in_denial_that_your_500_to_100k_token%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uk3sw0/dont_be_in_denial_that_your_500_to_100k_token/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 09:46:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s a common reason people get extremely hostile and defensive, and it&amp;amp;#39;s because they do not handle acceptance well. Don&amp;amp;#39;t believe me, then sort by controversial on a popular post.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you&amp;amp;#39;ve made a bad decision, and have to accept a negative outcome it&amp;amp;#39;s worth aknowledging that to move on. Alot of people struggle with this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;No more blaming outside parties, or us against them. Blocking out all criticism. Putting more and more faith into delusional utopian outcomes. Going into the whole &amp;amp;quot;well at least we aren&amp;amp;#39;t X project&amp;amp;quot; and so, so much more.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;No one likes being made a fool of, and no one likes to admit they were ignorant in their choices. Yet it is something that needs to be done to wake up to the reality of the situation and make the decisions that need to be done. Dwelling on a dead or dying project is only going to hold you back.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As stated numerous times on this subreddit. Everyone wants to be the $500 to $100k holder as that&amp;amp;#39;s what everyone hears about. No one wants to be the $1000 to $0.01 holder, yet a majority of us will be and we will need to accept that when it happens.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is your call to make as you are the person who holds yourself back or pushes yourself forward. Choose wisely.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin falls $40k and crypto continuous plunge … Is it time to sell ?]]></title><description><![CDATA[If you are new in crypto you may fear and panic because of this prices and I
can’t blame you, but I just want to tell you about Bitcoin price history

In 2014 … Bitcoin went below $400 and everyone thought that the Digital Gold is
gone forever

Then in 2018 … Bitcoin went below $4K and everyone…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uk4icb/bitcoin_falls_40k_and_crypto_continuous_plunge_is/?score=435&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuk4icb%2Fbitcoin_falls_40k_and_crypto_continuous_plunge_is%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuk4icb%2Fbitcoin_falls_40k_and_crypto_continuous_plunge_is%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uk4icb/bitcoin_falls_40k_and_crypto_continuous_plunge_is/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 08:42:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you are new in crypto you may fear and panic because of this prices and I can’t blame you, but I just want to tell you about Bitcoin price history&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In 2014 … Bitcoin went below $400 and everyone thought that the Digital Gold is gone forever&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then in  2018 … Bitcoin went below $4K and everyone thought that the Digital Gold is gone forever&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then in 2022 … Bitcoin went below $40K and everyone thought that the Digital Gold is gone forever&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I am not telling you to buy or sell, I am not telling how much to invest or or what to invest in, I am just telling you the history and don’t worry if you are true believer of crypto and the project you choose to invest in&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, I can‘t wait to buy more cheap Bitcoin in 2026 when it goes below $400K and everyone is thinking it’s gone forever&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/2g4jrwrv0zx81.jpg?width=895&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=b08d617cd85c4468ac950eec2767a764faf516ec&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/2g4jrwrv0zx81.jpg?width=895&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=b08d617cd85c4468ac950eec2767a764faf516ec&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Community in past few days]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uk4adf/bitcoin_community_in_past_few_days/?score=421&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuk4adf%2Fbitcoin_community_in_past_few_days%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuk4adf%2Fbitcoin_community_in_past_few_days%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uk4adf/bitcoin_community_in_past_few_days/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 07:36:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["Bitcoin is rat poison, " says Munger. He's right. All the rats in our financial system are in trouble.]]></title><description><![CDATA[For the longest time I disliked the statement Charlie said. But it finally
clicked today when I re-watched that clip. So, thanks Charlie. The rats better
start to scatter!]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujx99l/bitcoin_is_rat_poison_says_munger_hes_right_all/?score=343&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujx99l%2Fbitcoin_is_rat_poison_says_munger_hes_right_all%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujx99l%2Fbitcoin_is_rat_poison_says_munger_hes_right_all%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujx99l/bitcoin_is_rat_poison_says_munger_hes_right_all/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 02:57:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For the longest time I disliked the statement Charlie said. But it finally clicked today when I re-watched that clip. So, thanks Charlie. The rats better start to scatter!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Today in 2014, Bill Gates defends Bitcoin at $400: "It's a techno tour de force."]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujov02/today_in_2014_bill_gates_defends_bitcoin_at_400/?score=336&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujov02%2Ftoday_in_2014_bill_gates_defends_bitcoin_at_400%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujov02%2Ftoday_in_2014_bill_gates_defends_bitcoin_at_400%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujov02/today_in_2014_bill_gates_defends_bitcoin_at_400/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 02:57:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[just a reminder: we are all going to die at some point.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujmges/just_a_reminder_we_are_all_going_to_die_at_some/?score=318&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujmges%2Fjust_a_reminder_we_are_all_going_to_die_at_some%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujmges%2Fjust_a_reminder_we_are_all_going_to_die_at_some%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujmges/just_a_reminder_we_are_all_going_to_die_at_some/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 02:57:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Argentina Bows to IMF, Gets 45B Loan but have to ban Crypto to prevent money laundering - A good ol' financial gangster extorting third world country]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujqlhw/argentina_bows_to_imf_gets_45b_loan_but_have_to/?score=327&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujqlhw%2Fargentina_bows_to_imf_gets_45b_loan_but_have_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujqlhw%2Fargentina_bows_to_imf_gets_45b_loan_but_have_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujqlhw/argentina_bows_to_imf_gets_45b_loan_but_have_to/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 01:54:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My dinner after buying the dip.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujn0qo/my_dinner_after_buying_the_dip/?score=324&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujn0qo%2Fmy_dinner_after_buying_the_dip%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujn0qo%2Fmy_dinner_after_buying_the_dip%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujn0qo/my_dinner_after_buying_the_dip/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 01:54:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[IMF is threatening countries looking to adopt Bitcoin with no economic support unless they take tough anti-cryptocurrency stance. It's time for emancipation from economic slavery.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujns3q/imf_is_threatening_countries_looking_to_adopt/?score=310&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujns3q%2Fimf_is_threatening_countries_looking_to_adopt%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujns3q%2Fimf_is_threatening_countries_looking_to_adopt%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujns3q/imf_is_threatening_countries_looking_to_adopt/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 21:36:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[For the first time, a home in Portugal was sold today for bitcoin without the conversion back to fiat]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujohns/for_the_first_time_a_home_in_portugal_was_sold/?score=446&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujohns%2Ffor_the_first_time_a_home_in_portugal_was_sold%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujohns%2Ffor_the_first_time_a_home_in_portugal_was_sold%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujohns/for_the_first_time_a_home_in_portugal_was_sold/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 20:34:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2026: Bitcoin falls below $400'000]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujmu8r/2026_bitcoin_falls_below_400000/?score=352&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujmu8r%2F2026_bitcoin_falls_below_400000%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujmu8r%2F2026_bitcoin_falls_below_400000%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujmu8r/2026_bitcoin_falls_below_400000/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 18:43:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[House Sold In Portugal For 3 Bitcoin In Country’s First-Ever Direct Transaction]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujogkf/house_sold_in_portugal_for_3_bitcoin_in_countrys/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujogkf%2Fhouse_sold_in_portugal_for_3_bitcoin_in_countrys%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujogkf%2Fhouse_sold_in_portugal_for_3_bitcoin_in_countrys%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujogkf/house_sold_in_portugal_for_3_bitcoin_in_countrys/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 18:43:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I really don't like dollars anymore]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujgkb9/i_really_dont_like_dollars_anymore/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujgkb9%2Fi_really_dont_like_dollars_anymore%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujgkb9%2Fi_really_dont_like_dollars_anymore%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujgkb9/i_really_dont_like_dollars_anymore/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 18:43:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[r/CryptoCurrency Predictions Tournament ]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujr4h0/rcryptocurrency_predictions_tournament/?score=680&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujr4h0%2Frcryptocurrency_predictions_tournament%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujr4h0%2Frcryptocurrency_predictions_tournament%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujr4h0/rcryptocurrency_predictions_tournament/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 17:33:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why does everyone care about virtual real estate NFTs when there’s real life real estate being sold as NFTs?]]></title><description><![CDATA[The hype around Yuga Labs’ Otherside mint has started a new wave of discussion
around virtual real estate. Minting their “Otherdeeds” cost 305 APE and
generated over $550 million in sales in the first day all on the hope that
they’re going to do something interesting with virtual real estate. I…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujl5tb/why_does_everyone_care_about_virtual_real_estate/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujl5tb%2Fwhy_does_everyone_care_about_virtual_real_estate%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujl5tb%2Fwhy_does_everyone_care_about_virtual_real_estate%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujl5tb/why_does_everyone_care_about_virtual_real_estate/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 16:37:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The hype around Yuga Labs’ Otherside mint has started a new wave of discussion around virtual real estate. Minting their “Otherdeeds” cost 305 APE and generated over $550 million in sales in the first day all on the hope that they’re going to do something interesting with virtual real estate. I don’t get why the vast majority of the hype is around virtual real estate NFTs when there are several projects already doing stuff with &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;real life&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; real estate via NFTs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I learned about these Web3 real estate projects recently and they seem so much more tangible than most metaverse projects. It’s not like Web3 real estate projects are immune to issues. Balcony DAO, Propy, CitaDAO, etc. all have their issues and I’m not going to pretend like they don’t. DeFi is the future but there are a lot of kinks that will have to be worked out. But I continue to be surprised that so much hype and money goes towards virtual real estate on the expectation that &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;maybe someday&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; these virtual spaces will have enough users rather than going towards projects focused on real buildings that people really need to live in and can produce income from.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If anyone is curious, here’s some of the real estate NFT projects that seem most interesting (in alphabetical order):&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.balconydao.com/&quot;&amp;gt;Balcony DAO&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;: This is in the early stages but they’re one of the most interesting ones.  Their goal is to take major real estate investment opportunities (think residential skyscrapers) that are normally inaccessible to the average investor and turn them into investing opportunities for regular people via NFTs. They have a fully doxxed team with founders who are well known and respected in the real estate space.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://citadao.io/&quot;&amp;gt;CitaDAO&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;: They want real estate to be tokenized and transacted on chain. One of their focal points is steady rental income from their projects. They’re starting with property in England and their process involves staking USDC in a pool. Their initial fundraising effort failed to capture enough revenue, falling about 30% short of the total they needed, but still felt like a good proof of concept for the DAO. They still have future plans to pursue another IRO (Introducing Real Estate On-chain) round.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lofty.ai/&quot;&amp;gt;Lofty AI&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;: They’re a startup where you can buy shares in tokenized rental properties. Shares can go as low as $50 so the ceiling for involvement is very low. They’re similar to existing projects like Fundrise and Roofstock but they have a lower bar for entry.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://propy.com/&quot;&amp;gt;Propy&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;: Propy is maybe the most well known player in this space. Their focus is on normal real estate transactions in the Web3 world. Instead of buying or selling your house through normal means, you can trade it like an NFT. They claim to have sold the world’s first real estate NFT.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zoom out and stack]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujlu0i/zoom_out_and_stack/?score=386&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujlu0i%2Fzoom_out_and_stack%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujlu0i%2Fzoom_out_and_stack%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujlu0i/zoom_out_and_stack/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 16:37:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I'm out.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Over the past few years I have gained a good bit and i have lost a (really) good
bit.

I can safely say that i am certainly sure I have addiction issues with crypto.
As it is, quite literally like gambling.

I loved the highs, but frankly I have only begun to dig my own grave by the
amount of lows…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujli2g/im_out/?score=318&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujli2g%2Fim_out%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujli2g%2Fim_out%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujli2g/im_out/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 13:42:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Over the past few years I have gained a good bit and i have lost a (really) good bit.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I can safely say that i am certainly sure I have addiction issues with crypto. As it is, quite literally like gambling.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I loved the highs, but frankly I have only begun to dig my own grave by the amount of lows I&amp;amp;#39;ve been through. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bad decision making, thinking &amp;amp;quot;yeah this&amp;amp;#39;ll work out&amp;amp;quot; and being a fucking gambling addicted idiot.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I have sold the last but of my crypto, and I am genuinely done. I&amp;amp;#39;ve gone through to many sleepless nights of uncertainty, too many days of overthinking. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I am out. Goodbye fellas.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;PS: Don&amp;amp;#39;t get into crypto if you have:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A) an addictive personality
B) have mental health issues
C) think it&amp;amp;#39;s smart to invest money you actually need&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Time for this classic?]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujja17/time_for_this_classic/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujja17%2Ftime_for_this_classic%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujja17%2Ftime_for_this_classic%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujja17/time_for_this_classic/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 12:39:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin drops to $35.5K as 1,000 point Dow correction marks the worst trading day since 2020]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujhp3x/bitcoin_drops_to_355k_as_1000_point_dow/?score=335&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujhp3x%2Fbitcoin_drops_to_355k_as_1000_point_dow%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujhp3x%2Fbitcoin_drops_to_355k_as_1000_point_dow%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujhp3x/bitcoin_drops_to_355k_as_1000_point_dow/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 10:41:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I hate Dogecoin because of its fanbase.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I had nothing against Dogecoin. To be honest, I liked it because it was the most
popular meme coin these last years and the community seemed really cool - until
Elon Musk started to talk about it (at least, that's why I think it became so
annoying).

EVERY POST involving crypto (in some cases not…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uj3vfe/i_hate_dogecoin_because_of_its_fanbase/?score=322&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuj3vfe%2Fi_hate_dogecoin_because_of_its_fanbase%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuj3vfe%2Fi_hate_dogecoin_because_of_its_fanbase%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uj3vfe/i_hate_dogecoin_because_of_its_fanbase/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 09:40:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I had nothing against Dogecoin. To be honest, I liked it because it was the most popular meme coin these last years and the community seemed really cool - until Elon Musk started to talk about it (at least, that&amp;amp;#39;s why I think it became so annoying).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;EVERY POST&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; involving crypto (in some cases not even involving it), especially posts by Elon Musk, there are these people spamming dumb shit about this doggy coin.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One of the most famous figures I&amp;amp;#39;ve noticed is &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MattWallace888&quot;&amp;gt;Matt Wallece&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. Just take a look at his tweets history and you will understand what I&amp;amp;#39;m saying - and he is just one of them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m annoyed of Dogecoin because of these people. How can your life be resumed by &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;convincing people all the time&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; that there&amp;amp;#39;s a crypto out there that is worth paying for?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: Yeah, hate is a strong word. I don&amp;amp;#39;t hate it, but I&amp;amp;#39;m sick of reading Dogecoin everywhere.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/pitnyb9i9px81.png?width=602&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=266b2d50b90bf2cbc2f61148f8fbbcb9f1d28ff7&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/pitnyb9i9px81.png?width=602&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=266b2d50b90bf2cbc2f61148f8fbbcb9f1d28ff7&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Important conversations are taking place on the Joe Rogan show, and the world is beginning to understand that bitcoin is freedom money.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uizk33/important_conversations_are_taking_place_on_the/?score=322&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuizk33%2Fimportant_conversations_are_taking_place_on_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuizk33%2Fimportant_conversations_are_taking_place_on_the%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uizk33/important_conversations_are_taking_place_on_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 08:32:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto has been taken over by the same people it was invented to untether from….]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m not the first person to notice this on this sub, but the last couple years
the crypto market seems to really move with the regular stock markets. Case in
point, the last couple of days the two big swings in the NASDAQ I’m literally
coincided with the same swing of all my crypto. This tells me…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uj0x8x/crypto_has_been_taken_over_by_the_same_people_it/?score=319&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuj0x8x%2Fcrypto_has_been_taken_over_by_the_same_people_it%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuj0x8x%2Fcrypto_has_been_taken_over_by_the_same_people_it%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uj0x8x/crypto_has_been_taken_over_by_the_same_people_it/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 05:41:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m not the first person to notice this on this sub, but the last couple years the crypto market seems to really move with the regular stock markets. Case in point, the last couple of days the two big swings in the NASDAQ I’m literally coincided with the same swing of all my crypto. This tells me that main stream adoption amongst the big fish, (meaning the banks not some monopoly man) Seems to have taken hold. I don’t really see what the future holds because if the way they handled unfettered capitalism is any indication, crypto will have a bad end as well&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Well balls deep long ago :’)]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uj4zi4/well_balls_deep_long_ago/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuj4zi4%2Fwell_balls_deep_long_ago%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuj4zi4%2Fwell_balls_deep_long_ago%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uj4zi4/well_balls_deep_long_ago/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 05:41:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[You can't]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uj9ua4/you_cant/?score=353&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuj9ua4%2Fyou_cant%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuj9ua4%2Fyou_cant%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uj9ua4/you_cant/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 05:41:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Over 95% of the resources intended to “save” Greece ended up in the hands of national and international banks]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uisfgr/over_95_of_the_resources_intended_to_save_greece/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuisfgr%2Fover_95_of_the_resources_intended_to_save_greece%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuisfgr%2Fover_95_of_the_resources_intended_to_save_greece%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uisfgr/over_95_of_the_resources_intended_to_save_greece/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 04:36:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren's obsession with crypto continues: "Investing in cryptocurrencies is a risky and speculative gamble, and we are concerned that Fidelity would take these risks with millions of Americans’ retirement savings" Now she is FUDding about Fidelity accepting crypto for 401k plans]]></title><description><![CDATA[She seems to be trying the throw everything at the wall and see what sticks
approach this time.

Called it a gamble —

> “Investing in cryptocurrencies is a risky and speculative gamble, and we are
> concerned that Fidelity would take these risks with millions of Americans’
> retirement…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uj4z6g/elizabeth_warrens_obsession_with_crypto_continues/?score=344&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuj4z6g%2Felizabeth_warrens_obsession_with_crypto_continues%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuj4z6g%2Felizabeth_warrens_obsession_with_crypto_continues%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uj4z6g/elizabeth_warrens_obsession_with_crypto_continues/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 02:26:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;She seems to be trying the throw everything at the wall and see what sticks approach this time. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Called it a gamble — &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“Investing in cryptocurrencies is a risky and speculative gamble, and we are concerned that Fidelity would take these risks with millions of Americans’ retirement savings,”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Claimed that Elon single handedly pumped BTC by 8% —&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“Bitcoin’s volatility is compounded by its susceptibility to the whims of just a handful of influencers. Elon Musk’s tweets alone have led to Bitcoin value fluctuations as high as 8%.&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Call BTC dangerously centralized —&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;The high concentration of Bitcoin ownership and mining exacerbates these volatility risks. One study estimates that just 10% of Bitcoin miners are responsible for processing 90% of Bitcoin transactions and that 1,000 individuals control 3 million Bitcoins – about 15% of the current Bitcoin supply.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;All this was written as &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/22/05/27030896/sen-elizabeth-warren-questions-fidelity-on-crypto-401-k-product-what-you-need-to-know&quot;&amp;gt;part of a letter&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; by Warren (and senator Tina Smith) to Fidelity&amp;amp;#39;s CEO. The senators gave Fidelity until May 18 to answer questions regarding risks related to cryptocurrency and whether this offering posed a conflict of interest.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I think the fact that we can now send thousands of dollars for less than $1 in fees is what will make crypto go mainstream eventually.]]></title><description><![CDATA[There are a lot of features that give crypto an edge over fiat currency. There’s
the fact that some cryptos have a limited supply just like Bitcoin. Other coins
are untraceable like Monero and are great for privacy and DeFi is decentralized
and safe from government interference.

But out of all…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uiv32d/i_think_the_fact_that_we_can_now_send_thousands/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuiv32d%2Fi_think_the_fact_that_we_can_now_send_thousands%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuiv32d%2Fi_think_the_fact_that_we_can_now_send_thousands%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uiv32d/i_think_the_fact_that_we_can_now_send_thousands/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 23:36:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are a lot of features that give crypto an edge over fiat currency. There’s the fact that some cryptos have a limited supply just like Bitcoin. Other coins are untraceable like Monero and are great for privacy and DeFi is decentralized and safe from government interference.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But out of all features that will later prove crypto more superior than fiat, I think that low transfer fees is what will bring in new people initially and make crypto go mainstream.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The reason I’m saying this is cause I’m seeing it in my own eyes. I live in a country where a lot of young people live abroad and help their families out with extra cash end of month.
Western Union here is HELLA EXPENSIVE so I’m seeing a lot of people who have never had any encounter with crypto before open a wallet and start using platforms like Binance and E-Money cause of the ultra low fees and fast transfers.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m not saying other features in crypto aren’t important. In fact I think limited supply and decentralization are much more important features. I’m just saying that low fees is what will most likely attract the largest number of people.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[We are exactly halfway the current halving! Last halving: 630,000 ; Current block: 735,000 ; Next halving: 840,000 | Ready for the next halving]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uiy1g3/we_are_exactly_halfway_the_current_halving_last/?score=332&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuiy1g3%2Fwe_are_exactly_halfway_the_current_halving_last%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuiy1g3%2Fwe_are_exactly_halfway_the_current_halving_last%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uiy1g3/we_are_exactly_halfway_the_current_halving_last/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 23:36:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren penned a letter to Fidelity today, begging them not to accept Bitcoin in 401k accounts]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uj0ej8/elizabeth_warren_penned_a_letter_to_fidelity/?score=338&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuj0ej8%2Felizabeth_warren_penned_a_letter_to_fidelity%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuj0ej8%2Felizabeth_warren_penned_a_letter_to_fidelity%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uj0ej8/elizabeth_warren_penned_a_letter_to_fidelity/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 20:44:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto.com just announced some further changes in another attempt to claw back the millions of people they screwed over last week.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Via the CEO, Kris, Crypto.com has just announced that they have VERY SLIGHTLY
increased the cashback rewards based on community feedback.

Essentially, this has allowed them to tank the price for a week and continue to
throw tiny breadcrumbs in the hope most users will forgive them.

I am…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uixqda/cryptocom_just_announced_some_further_changes_in/?score=327&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuixqda%2Fcryptocom_just_announced_some_further_changes_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuixqda%2Fcryptocom_just_announced_some_further_changes_in%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uixqda/cryptocom_just_announced_some_further_changes_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 19:36:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Via the CEO, Kris, Crypto.com has just announced that they have VERY SLIGHTLY increased the cashback rewards based on community feedback. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Essentially, this has allowed them to tank the price for a week and continue to throw tiny breadcrumbs in the hope most users will forgive them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I am particularly fascinated by the introduction to re-stake before June 1 and keep all existing offers - because to be honest, I think most people were counting down the days until the they were free from their stake - and the peak of investors wads about to expire over the next three weeks. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The problem with that, is most people are down so they will have to invest more to re-stake at the ongoing rate. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source from Twitter quoted below for reference. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;We&amp;amp;#39;ve been engaging with the community all week about card rewards, and we&amp;amp;#39;re making a few more updates based on your feedback&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The process has been far from ideal, but it&amp;amp;#39;s important to take your feedback into account, and deliver an attractive yet balanced offering.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;✅ Ruby Steel cashback is increasing from .5% to 1%&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;✅ Jade &amp;amp;amp; Indigo cashback is increasing from 1.5% to 2%&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;✅ Current card rewards will be locked-in for six months if you re-stake before June 1, 2022&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;✅ We will waive the card upgrade fee ($50) until further notice&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Once again, thank you to everyone who provided feedback 🙏&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/kris/status/1522204322955935751?s=20&amp;amp;amp;t=S7yM62K7yKZByz_s99NKDA&quot;&amp;gt;https://twitter.com/kris/status/1522204322955935751?s=20&amp;amp;amp;t=S7yM62K7yKZByz_s99NKDA&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[concretely proposing to activate anything on #bitcoin without technical and ecosystem consensus is defacto an attack on bitcoin's change process, that protects immutability and security. the anti-fragility is people who defend those principles.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1522285133600014336/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1522285133600014336/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 18:46:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Yet again, US markets open, entire crypto market dumps]]></title><description><![CDATA[I've seen this like 20 times in the last year. Everything goes well the entire
day in the Asia/Europe markets, but the moment US markets open, everything
tanks.

I've had alts doing +15% today, total portfolio was up like 6-7%, all wiped in a
matter of 2hrs. Sure, it is related to alts being…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uj00j2/yet_again_us_markets_open_entire_crypto_market/?score=397&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuj00j2%2Fyet_again_us_markets_open_entire_crypto_market%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuj00j2%2Fyet_again_us_markets_open_entire_crypto_market%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uj00j2/yet_again_us_markets_open_entire_crypto_market/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 18:46:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen this like 20 times in the last year. Everything goes well the entire day in the Asia/Europe markets, but the moment US markets open, everything tanks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ve had alts doing +15% today, total portfolio was up like 6-7%, all wiped in a matter of 2hrs. Sure, it is related to alts being correlated to BTC. But still. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What is up with that, US? Why don&amp;amp;#39;t you like profits? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Could it be the blatant market manipulation with options and future? Is it the stock/bonds markets influencing BTC? Is it the interest hike somehow? What gives?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gucci will accept 10 cryptocurrencies including Bitcoin, Ether, and Dogecoin]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uivufb/gucci_will_accept_10_cryptocurrencies_including/?score=325&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuivufb%2Fgucci_will_accept_10_cryptocurrencies_including%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuivufb%2Fgucci_will_accept_10_cryptocurrencies_including%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uivufb/gucci_will_accept_10_cryptocurrencies_including/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:35:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[weeeeeee]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uizp5g/weeeeeee/?score=377&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuizp5g%2Fweeeeeee%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuizp5g%2Fweeeeeee%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uizp5g/weeeeeee/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 16:51:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Algorand Founder Silvio Micali Makes 10-Year Prediction On Crypto Markets: "The few blockchains that are really capable of transacting at a very low cost, they’re going to emerge"]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uiq0gy/algorand_founder_silvio_micali_makes_10year/?score=323&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuiq0gy%2Falgorand_founder_silvio_micali_makes_10year%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuiq0gy%2Falgorand_founder_silvio_micali_makes_10year%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uiq0gy/algorand_founder_silvio_micali_makes_10year/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:49:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Restaurants in Singapore started accepting Bitcoin, ignoring government resistance]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uiukny/restaurants_in_singapore_started_accepting/?score=404&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuiukny%2Frestaurants_in_singapore_started_accepting%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuiukny%2Frestaurants_in_singapore_started_accepting%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uiukny/restaurants_in_singapore_started_accepting/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:49:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[IMF is concerned by Bitcoin adoption by Central African Republic]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uih1m1/imf_is_concerned_by_bitcoin_adoption_by_central/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuih1m1%2Fimf_is_concerned_by_bitcoin_adoption_by_central%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuih1m1%2Fimf_is_concerned_by_bitcoin_adoption_by_central%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uih1m1/imf_is_concerned_by_bitcoin_adoption_by_central/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 14:33:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SEC documents show that Binance is contributing upto $500m towards Elon Musk's Twitter takeover]]></title><description><![CDATA[Binance seems to be interested in commiting funds to Elon for his Twitter
takeover. In a letter filed with SEC, Elon has disclosed backing for upto $7 BN
for his proposed takeover of Twitter, from big names such as Brookfield,
Fidelity, Qatar, Sequoia and now Binance too!

As per the filing,…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uiumqx/sec_documents_show_that_binance_is_contributing/?score=460&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuiumqx%2Fsec_documents_show_that_binance_is_contributing%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuiumqx%2Fsec_documents_show_that_binance_is_contributing%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uiumqx/sec_documents_show_that_binance_is_contributing/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 13:11:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Binance seems to be interested in commiting funds to Elon for his Twitter takeover. In a letter filed with SEC, Elon has disclosed backing for upto $7 BN for his proposed takeover of Twitter, from big names such as Brookfield, Fidelity, Qatar, Sequoia and now Binance too!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As per the filing, Binance the largest cryptocurrency exchange has commited upto $500,000,000 in cash towards Musk&amp;amp;#39;s takeover and aquistition of Twitter. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The deal would mark Binance&amp;amp;#39;s entry into the big league of investors who are willing to contribute towards deals outside the traditional crypto space. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/0001494730/000110465922056055/tm2214608-1_sc13da.htm&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.sec.gov/Archives/edgar/data/0001494730/000110465922056055/tm2214608-1_sc13da.htm&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitstamp BLOCKED my account because I'm from Russia!?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sorry if I posted in the wrong section, but I don't know where else to post. I
already wrote in the Bitstamp thread, but the post was blocked without comments.

So 2 weeks ago I saw that my account is blocked, they don't let me trade and
also withdraw my funds. I wrote to their support and here is…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uijimr/bitstamp_blocked_my_account_because_im_from_russia/?score=332&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuijimr%2Fbitstamp_blocked_my_account_because_im_from_russia%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuijimr%2Fbitstamp_blocked_my_account_because_im_from_russia%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uijimr/bitstamp_blocked_my_account_because_im_from_russia/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 12:33:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sorry if I posted in the wrong section, but I don&amp;amp;#39;t know where else to post. I already wrote in the Bitstamp thread, but the post was blocked without comments.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So 2 weeks ago I saw that my account is blocked, they don&amp;amp;#39;t let me trade and also withdraw my funds. I wrote to their support and here is their reply - &amp;amp;quot; in the light of the current events in Ukraine and the consequent regulatory directives, we’ve been required to disable your account’s deposit, trading and withdrawal options&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I asked for an official notice that all Russian citizens should be blocked, without the possibility of withdrawal.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I am a simple person, not connected in any way and not supporting the war in Ukraine. I created an account in 2019, verified it, confirmed the legal origin of the funds.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And now the exchange just wants to appropriate my money, referring to what is happening in Ukraine.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/u/BitStampOfficial/&quot;&amp;gt;u/BitStampOfficial&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; I ask you to provide legal notice on what basis you completely blocked my account, as well as many other accounts from Russia.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why is no other exchange taking measures like yours?? Two weeks later, your support team cannot give me an answer, but is just playing for time. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TICKET #BIT-1438832&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I really hope that you are mistaken and the reliability of the oldest European stock exchange is beyond doubt.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/nkj7hoefmjx81.jpg?width=1580&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=a8059f5d04b1912fb2709cd586cfff2c814c05c0&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/nkj7hoefmjx81.jpg?width=1580&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=a8059f5d04b1912fb2709cd586cfff2c814c05c0&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cardano retail interest is rapidly increasing, on-chain data shows]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uia2qc/cardano_retail_interest_is_rapidly_increasing/?score=310&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuia2qc%2Fcardano_retail_interest_is_rapidly_increasing%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuia2qc%2Fcardano_retail_interest_is_rapidly_increasing%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uia2qc/cardano_retail_interest_is_rapidly_increasing/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 10:36:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Safemoon liquidity has been consistently dropping and has less than two months until it reaches zero.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The liquidity pool for everyone’s favourite scam token has been dropping
significantly. It is losing approximately a million dollars each week it
currently has less than $7m.

If the liquidity pool is no longer able to support the swapping of tokens
between Safemoon and Binance coin, it will have…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uintxh/safemoon_liquidity_has_been_consistently_dropping/?score=355&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuintxh%2Fsafemoon_liquidity_has_been_consistently_dropping%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuintxh%2Fsafemoon_liquidity_has_been_consistently_dropping%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uintxh/safemoon_liquidity_has_been_consistently_dropping/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 10:36:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The liquidity pool for everyone’s favourite scam token has been dropping significantly. It is losing approximately a million dollars each week it currently has less than $7m. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If the liquidity pool is no longer able to support the swapping of tokens between Safemoon and Binance coin, it will have to be disabled. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyone who still holds Safemoon at that point will no longer be able to sell it. Effectively rendering it worth nothing. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Holding at this point is literally the most risky strategy for you poor old Safemoon victims.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I would say this is not financial advice, but being invested in Safemoon means you probably won’t listen anyway. Good luck to you all.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>