<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing on Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 12:50:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Influencers are getting paid to scam you. They are not your friends. If you lose money listening to them it is your fault and nobody feels bad for you.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The things is, they started being bad for many things, not just crypto.

They are getting paid to scam their fans, and they are scumbags on this planet.

How many times we saw videos on youtube, tiktok or any other platform with coins
or tokens that are going to skyrocket and you should get in…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/tatv8p/influencers_are_getting_paid_to_scam_you_they_are/?score=1051&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftatv8p%2Finfluencers_are_getting_paid_to_scam_you_they_are%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftatv8p%2Finfluencers_are_getting_paid_to_scam_you_they_are%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/tatv8p/influencers_are_getting_paid_to_scam_you_they_are/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 11:33:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The things is, they started being bad for many things, not just crypto.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They are getting paid to scam their fans, and they are scumbags on this planet.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How many times we saw videos on youtube, tiktok or any other platform with coins or tokens that are going to skyrocket and you should get in ASAP?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How many of those same youtubers, tiktokers etc. got rich because their tehnical analysis is amazing and they share knowledge that we should be thankfull about?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They are promoting risky, or sometimes even non existent coins and tokens.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;People who are just getting into crypto are sometimes listening to them, investing blindly in what they say and lose money. And later they may think that crypto is a scam, right?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;THEY SHOULD ALL GET SUED!&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Examples:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://decrypt.co/73601/kim-kardashian-is-shilling-ethereum-max-too-what-is-it&quot;&amp;gt;Kim Kardashain promoting EthereumMax&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. Of course, one of the highest payed athlete Floyd Mayweather needed more money so &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://edition.cnn.com/2022/01/12/business/kim-kardashian-floyd-mayweather-crypto-lawsuit/index.html&quot;&amp;gt;he jumped right in to do the same thing&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. Something (I don&amp;amp;#39;t even know what the hell it is) that was even without whitepaper&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.benzinga.com/markets/cryptocurrency/21/05/21337044/soulja-boy-accidentally-reveals-how-much-he-got-paid-to-promote-crypto-project&quot;&amp;gt;Soulja Boy&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; did the same thing to his fans, while revealing how much money he would get for promoting it&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;- &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businessinsider.in/cryptocurrency/news/faze-clan-pump-and-dump-crypto-scam-gets-kay-kicked-off-and-three-others-suspended/articleshow/84063180.cms&quot;&amp;gt;FaZe clan doing pump and dump&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Moon, Mars, NFTs, we are all going to be rich, we are all going to be millionaires.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Get out of here.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ethereum Co-Founder Vitalik Buterin Urges Compassion For Russians, Belarusians Resisting Putin's 'Z-ombie Regime']]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/tapzi5/ethereum_cofounder_vitalik_buterin_urges/?score=365&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftapzi5%2Fethereum_cofounder_vitalik_buterin_urges%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftapzi5%2Fethereum_cofounder_vitalik_buterin_urges%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/tapzi5/ethereum_cofounder_vitalik_buterin_urges/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 08:36:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["Algorand has experienced zero downtime since launch"]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/tamlka/algorand_has_experienced_zero_downtime_since/?score=309&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftamlka%2Falgorand_has_experienced_zero_downtime_since%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftamlka%2Falgorand_has_experienced_zero_downtime_since%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/tamlka/algorand_has_experienced_zero_downtime_since/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 07:35:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ukraine has received almost $100,000,000 in crypto donations]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/taew0c/ukraine_has_received_almost_100000000_in_crypto/?score=397&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftaew0c%2Fukraine_has_received_almost_100000000_in_crypto%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftaew0c%2Fukraine_has_received_almost_100000000_in_crypto%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/taew0c/ukraine_has_received_almost_100000000_in_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 06:37:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[El Salvador's tourism rises 30% after Bitcoin became legal tender]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/taa1eb/el_salvadors_tourism_rises_30_after_bitcoin/?score=310&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftaa1eb%2Fel_salvadors_tourism_rises_30_after_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftaa1eb%2Fel_salvadors_tourism_rises_30_after_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/taa1eb/el_salvadors_tourism_rises_30_after_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 04:31:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A degen's summary of Biden's crypto executive order]]></title><description><![CDATA[Today Joe Biden signed into effect an executive order directing federal agencies
to coordinate their efforts at drafting crypto regulations. This is a first of
its kinds executive order, and its going to take a while for these separate
government agencies to draft their regulations.

You're…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ta93g8/a_degens_summary_of_bidens_crypto_executive_order/?score=320&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fta93g8%2Fa_degens_summary_of_bidens_crypto_executive_order%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fta93g8%2Fa_degens_summary_of_bidens_crypto_executive_order%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ta93g8/a_degens_summary_of_bidens_crypto_executive_order/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 03:30:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Today Joe Biden signed into effect an executive order directing federal agencies to coordinate their efforts at drafting crypto regulations. This is a first of its kinds executive order, and its going to take a while for these separate government agencies to draft their regulations.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You&amp;amp;#39;re probably already sick of reading by now so lets get into the meat of the EO (executive order).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Preface:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;this EO will not outline specific positions that Biden wants, such as directing the SEC to take harsher penalties on rugging. He doesn&amp;amp;#39;t want to seem pro or against crypto even though this EO is pretty pro crypto.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;One part of this EO is that it will direct the US Treasury department to create a report on the &amp;amp;quot;future of money&amp;amp;quot; including how the current financial system may not be right for some current consumer needs.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;THE EXECUTIVE ORDER FOCUSES ON GROWING THE DIGIAL ASSET SECTOR SAFELY FOR CONSUMERS&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;This executive order doesn&amp;amp;#39;t create any laws or regulations. It simply forces government agencies who has been ignoring crypto to stop ignoring crypto.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;The EO is regarded as a &amp;amp;quot;whole government&amp;amp;quot; effort to regulate crypto and it focuses on 6 main goals:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Consumer protection&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: This is the chief goal of the EO and part will go to understanding the technology as well as the volatile micro and macro-economics of the crypto industry. A better understanding on the governments end will help the government better understand where the current popular financial system is failing some consumers. My opinion on this is that the government will plan on helping government agencies aid businesses in crypto adoption as an effort to lessen the massive volatility in crypto that has rekt so many people.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;financial stability&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: this plays into the consumer protection part of the Executive Order. The president wants the financial sector to be less volatile. quoting the price pre-covid (10,300), November 2021 (70,000) and currently (38,000). Using this as a benchmark he wants government agencies to educate more people including themselves on why this volatility happens and how to help prevent this kind of instability through encouraged adoption.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;illicit uses&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: I mean its a bunch of boomers. Did you expect them not to be scared of criminals using crypto LMAO. I&amp;amp;#39;m sure they&amp;amp;#39;re going to enact some laws that crack down on criminals using crypto which will then never be used, because they inherently cant. The EO also states that the DOJ and FBI each have their own crypto investigation units that need more funding. &amp;amp;quot;The insufficiency of international implementation of anti-money laundering networks and frameworks with digital assets is the greatest vulnerability of these ecosystems the criminals are currently exploiting.&amp;amp;quot; I mean c&amp;amp;#39;mon this senior advisor to the president is basically saying that crypto&amp;amp;#39;s worst problem is money laundering? that&amp;amp;#39;s bullish AF.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;promoting responsible innovation&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: senior advisors have said that crypto is creating thousands of jobs in a brand new industry. Innovation is a pivotal role in the American economy and the government does not want to be left behind when it comes to innovation.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;financial inclusion&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: This exact thing has not really been defined but I can define it, because I want to. I&amp;amp;#39;m assuming this aspect is related to the &amp;amp;quot;future of money&amp;amp;quot; publication by the Treasury as well as the future plans to evaluate the necessity of a &amp;amp;quot;digital dollar&amp;amp;quot; issued by the central banks. This will undoubtedly increase financial inclusion and level the playing field because some consumers are either scared or confused by crypto and less likely to adopt.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;U.S. Leadership&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: This is more of an all encompassing part of the EO that is basically saying &amp;amp;quot;we need all government agencies leadership to get on the bandwagon or we as a country will fail at the innovation we have whored ourselves out for since the reconstruction era.&amp;amp;quot; The senior advisor was quoted saying, &amp;amp;quot;We remain committed to working with allies in the broader digital asset community to shape the future of digital assets systems in a manner thats&amp;amp;#39; inclusive, consistent with our Democratic values, and safeguard the integrity of the global financial system.&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TL;DR: Biden signed a bullish ass executive order that begs every government agencies to stop ignoring crypto and create legislation/regulations that will protect the consumer, level the volatility, and create a level playing field for the average consumer. Citing the need for innovation as well as adoption. Digital dollar issuance is mentioned as well as a &amp;amp;quot;future of Money&amp;amp;quot; report by the US Treasury that will surely outline how other government agencies should look at crypto regulation standards.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;edit: thanks to &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/u/ZER0SE7ENONETH&quot;&amp;gt;u/ZER0SE7ENONETH&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; if anyone wants to read the full version &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/presidential-actions/2022/03/09/executive-order-on-ensuring-responsible-development-of-digital-assets/&quot;&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; is a link he provided in the comments&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[As a cripple, crypto currencies have changed my life for the better.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I don't know if this kind of post has been done before, if its over done, I
apologize. Simply put, I want to express my gratitude to crypto, and how its
changed my life for the better.

Also, I'd like to note that I'm not sharing this story for pity points or some
other shit like that, simply put,…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ta2bbq/as_a_cripple_crypto_currencies_have_changed_my/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fta2bbq%2Fas_a_cripple_crypto_currencies_have_changed_my%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fta2bbq%2Fas_a_cripple_crypto_currencies_have_changed_my%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ta2bbq/as_a_cripple_crypto_currencies_have_changed_my/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 03:30:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I don&amp;amp;#39;t know if this kind of post has been done before, if its over done, I apologize. Simply put, I want to express my gratitude to crypto, and how its changed my life for the better.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, I&amp;amp;#39;d like to note that I&amp;amp;#39;m not sharing this story for pity points or some other shit like that, simply put, I want to give a small view into the life of a stranger who had some misfortunate things happen in their lives, but were able to make the best of it with the assistance of crypto.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For context, I was crippled when I was 15, I was involved in a pretty bad collision with a vehicle, the injuries had left me unable to walk for more then a few minutes, and barely even being able to lift my arms over my shoulder height, I could barely even grip more then a few pounds. I could thankfully still stand, but daily life had greatly changed for me, and anxieties set in.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Because of my accident, to no ones surprise, companies far and wide just didn&amp;amp;#39;t want to hire me. Eventually, I had gotten reviewed and eventually accepted into a disability program. Although if I ever start working again, they&amp;amp;#39;ll remove my disability permanently, which just greatly increased my anxieties of not being able to find work I was comfortable in doing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Fast forward to my early 20s, I&amp;amp;#39;ve been on disability for quite some time. I was always very interested in crypto, but never had the chance to buy in or start with it. My medical related bills always drained what little money I had. And then a big pandemic hit, and Canada had given everyone a few thousand if they needed it for emergency aid.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now of course, right away I used stimulus checks to secure food, pay off all my bills, and even bought some equipment to start exercising in hopes to repair the damage in my arms and legs to eventually get back to work. After everything was said and done, I had roughly 2.2k left over, and bought a few GPUs after really thinking about crypto and how it could benefit me in the long run.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thankfully, this was the thing that would really help me both mentally, physically, and financially. I bought the cards and power supply, already had ram and a motherboard, put it all together and started mining with HiveOS. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let me just say, as someone who lived off of 1100$ Canadian a month, for almost 7 years, this was a major game changer for me. Suddenly, I was able to afford better food, lots more meat! I was able to pay all my bills on time, and no longer slowly came into debt, and I was, for the first time, able to lower my financial worries of being homeless if a payment suddenly didn&amp;amp;#39;t come in. The amount of joy that I had for just a few hundred extra a month was unmeasurable.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The best part for me was that the cards paid themselves off in a few months due to the boom.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Fast forward to now, and even though I&amp;amp;#39;m still technically in extreme poverty, my little mining rig gives me just enough breathing room in my income that I can focus on my mental well being, and my physical well being. I cannot express my gratitude to how mining has positively effected my life.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sure, to most people getting an extra 200$-300$ a month would be effectively worthless, but that kind of money is enough to cover the power bill, my phone bill, and internet. It lets me have just enough breathing room to actually have a savings account, to be able to put money aside for my future.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Right now, I&amp;amp;#39;m planning to put some money aside to hopefully expand and get a few more cards, so I can completely get off disability, and maybe finally be able to live alone. I&amp;amp;#39;ve been doing better physically, to the point that I can even walk for over 20 minutes now! I&amp;amp;#39;m still struggling on grip and shoulder stuff, but progress is progress.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin and crypto friendly politician Yoon Suk-yeol was elected the next President of South Korea]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/takuyd/bitcoin_and_crypto_friendly_politician_yoon/?score=490&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ftakuyd%2Fbitcoin_and_crypto_friendly_politician_yoon%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ftakuyd%2Fbitcoin_and_crypto_friendly_politician_yoon%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/takuyd/bitcoin_and_crypto_friendly_politician_yoon/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 03:30:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[No, Russia will not "disconnect from global Internet", Russians will still be able to access crypto. For a community saying DYOR every two seconds, you don't do a ton of research!]]></title><description><![CDATA[What's the deal here? You will question every well-researched article if it's
coming from any "MSM" with a good reputation, but as soon as "TweakTown" does
some dodgy story you'll just upvote it?

So that story is currently the most popular…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/tah0s2/no_russia_will_not_disconnect_from_global/?score=334&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftah0s2%2Fno_russia_will_not_disconnect_from_global%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftah0s2%2Fno_russia_will_not_disconnect_from_global%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/tah0s2/no_russia_will_not_disconnect_from_global/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 03:30:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What&amp;amp;#39;s the deal here? You will question every well-researched article if it&amp;amp;#39;s coming from any &amp;amp;quot;MSM&amp;amp;quot; with a good reputation, but as soon as &amp;amp;quot;TweakTown&amp;amp;quot; does some dodgy story you&amp;amp;#39;ll just upvote it? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So that story is currently the most &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ta5eqx/russia_to_disconnect_from_global_internet_from/&quot;&amp;gt;popular post&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; with over 5,000 upvotes, it states, that Russia is planning to disconnect from the global internet - two days from now!!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Yeah, so that won&amp;amp;#39;t happen. This is based on a misinterpretation of some documents, and it has been debunked &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vice.com/en/article/88gevb/russia-is-preparing-to-cut-itself-off-from-the-global-internet&quot;&amp;gt;again&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://fortune.com/2022/03/07/russia-runet-disconnect-ukraine-dns-chernenko-letter/&quot;&amp;gt;again&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/shakirov2036/status/1500584933491982341&quot;&amp;gt;again&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Soooo DYOR before you upvote a misleading, sensationalist headline I guess?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto friendly Presidential candidate of South Korea becomes President. Had vowed to deregulate crypto and easy crypto tax burden.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/tag55g/crypto_friendly_presidential_candidate_of_south/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftag55g%2Fcrypto_friendly_presidential_candidate_of_south%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftag55g%2Fcrypto_friendly_presidential_candidate_of_south%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/tag55g/crypto_friendly_presidential_candidate_of_south/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 02:35:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What if we’re being played by exchanges?]]></title><description><![CDATA[What if… Coinbase/Kraken/Crypto.com, etc.

Don’t buy the coins when you “buy” on their site

Don’t sell the coins when you “sell” on their site

What if these sites take your order and adjust your ledger but don’t make the
actual purchase/sell orders?

What if they waited for a backlog of orders so…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/tae0oz/what_if_were_being_played_by_exchanges/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftae0oz%2Fwhat_if_were_being_played_by_exchanges%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftae0oz%2Fwhat_if_were_being_played_by_exchanges%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/tae0oz/what_if_were_being_played_by_exchanges/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 01:19:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What if…
Coinbase/Kraken/Crypto.com, etc. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Don’t buy the coins when you “buy” on their site&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Don’t sell the coins when you “sell” on their site&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What if these sites take your order and adjust your ledger but don’t make the actual purchase/sell orders?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What if they waited for a backlog of orders so they could intentionally manipulate the price?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What keeps them from intentionally liquidating leveraged positions by their own movements?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What if the biggest whales are these exchanges?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What if the whales are the ones who manipulate the price the most?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What if the call is coming from inside the house?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Would we create a squeeze if everyone moved coins to wallets?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This thought hit me last night snd kept me up for a while.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[USA and Dubai have each announced their intentions to become world leaders in Bitcoin and Crypto. Everything has changed in just 24hrs]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/taf1ui/usa_and_dubai_have_each_announced_their/?score=331&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftaf1ui%2Fusa_and_dubai_have_each_announced_their%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ftaf1ui%2Fusa_and_dubai_have_each_announced_their%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/taf1ui/usa_and_dubai_have_each_announced_their/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 23:42:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Yoon Suk-Yeol, a conservative candidate who campaigned on promises to deregulate South Korea’s crypto industry, has won that country’s closely-contested presidential election.
@cheyenneligon reports
https://t.co/R3Z2yFvfsi]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501680999092129797/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501680999092129797/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 22:36:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Factsheet on President Biden’s Digital Asset Executive order. It largely promotes studies and oversight but also aims to support innovation and strategic leadership to further the national interest. Seems net positive for the industry. 💪🚀 Source: https://t.co/w2cZJb5pon]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501532267096817671/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501532267096817671/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 22:36:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[White House Exec Order and U.S. Government Strategy for Digital Assets -- a thread with thoughts; TLDR = this is a watershed moment for crypto, digital assets, and Web 3, akin to the 1996/1997 whole of government wakeup to the commercial internet. (1/7)]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501648712313065474/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501648712313065474/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 22:36:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Joe Biden Officially Releases Crypto Executive Order, Promises to Support Technological Advances in Digital Assets]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ta69az/joe_biden_officially_releases_crypto_executive/?score=338&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fta69az%2Fjoe_biden_officially_releases_crypto_executive%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fta69az%2Fjoe_biden_officially_releases_crypto_executive%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ta69az/joe_biden_officially_releases_crypto_executive/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 20:34:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Congressman @Jim_Jordan During A Select Subcommittee...

You Might Want To Hear This... https://t.co/Zng7qv6fSM]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501634423703363586/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501634423703363586/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 19:36:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kraken exchange is gifting $1,000 in Bitcoin to every user in Ukraine 🇺🇦]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ta69de/kraken_exchange_is_gifting_1000_in_bitcoin_to/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fta69de%2Fkraken_exchange_is_gifting_1000_in_bitcoin_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fta69de%2Fkraken_exchange_is_gifting_1000_in_bitcoin_to%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ta69de/kraken_exchange_is_gifting_1000_in_bitcoin_to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 19:31:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin just reached an all-time high ... in Russia]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ta55i6/bitcoin_just_reached_an_alltime_high_in_russia/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fta55i6%2Fbitcoin_just_reached_an_alltime_high_in_russia%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fta55i6%2Fbitcoin_just_reached_an_alltime_high_in_russia%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ta55i6/bitcoin_just_reached_an_alltime_high_in_russia/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 17:31:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[#Bitcoin and realized cap/price (average on-chain price of all ~19M BTC). Note color indicates distance to ATH. The 3 times BTC turned blue (-70% below ATH):
- 2011 after MtGox hack, only exchange at the time
- 2014 after Bitstamp hack, fear of next MtGox
- 2018 after BSV fork https://t.co/tS470uFPvu]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501584039223963653/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501584039223963653/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 16:45:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[المستقبل ملك لمن يصممه .. واليوم من خلال قانون الأصول الافتراضية نسعى لنشارك في تصميم هذا القطاع العالمي الجديد والمتنامي بشكل سريع .. خطوتنا هي قفزة نحو المستقبل هدفها تنمية هذا القطاع وحماية جميع المستثمرين فيه .. والقادم أجمل .. وأشمل .. وأفضل بإذن الله https://t.co/ZQr0fJ6p2N]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501592313352568839/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501592313352568839/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 16:45:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stop bitchin about it]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ta7ojo/stop_bitchin_about_it/?score=324&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fta7ojo%2Fstop_bitchin_about_it%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fta7ojo%2Fstop_bitchin_about_it%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ta7ojo/stop_bitchin_about_it/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 16:45:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[You remember when Solana was the next big thing and it turned out the team were just massive liars and were committing fraud? A lesson in doing your own research and not buying into hype.]]></title><description><![CDATA[For those of you who may be new to the whole crypto thing, Solana was all the
rage last year. People and VCs were incredibly high on this chain like it was
the next best thing since sliced bread. Well surprise surprise. Not only did
Solana turn out to be INCREDIBLY centralized, the team lied about…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ta7anv/you_remember_when_solana_was_the_next_big_thing/?score=392&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fta7anv%2Fyou_remember_when_solana_was_the_next_big_thing%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fta7anv%2Fyou_remember_when_solana_was_the_next_big_thing%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ta7anv/you_remember_when_solana_was_the_next_big_thing/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 15:44:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For those of you who may be new to the whole crypto thing, Solana was all the rage last year. People and VCs were incredibly high on this chain like it was the next best thing since sliced bread. Well surprise surprise. Not only did Solana turn out to be INCREDIBLY centralized, the team lied about their circulating supply twice and were caught committing fraud. That&amp;amp;#39;s a big yikes from me.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I have literally sold all my SOL,  I&amp;amp;#39;ve bought a bag of MATIC and I&amp;amp;#39;m never going back. It&amp;amp;#39;s more  decentralized (SOL has proven to be extremely centralized), The team can  actually be trusted and it&amp;amp;#39;s just an overall better chain IN MY  OPINION. I know a lot of you apes are pretty much gambling and will invest into anything even if it&amp;amp;#39;s a shitcoin. That&amp;amp;#39;s not me though and that shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t be you either.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This chain CANNOT compete with the likes of Ethereum and L2s like Polygon. Especially when Solana is a project that has literally lied to you and disrespected you straight to your face. A real shame that people will still invest in this because y&amp;amp;#39;all have no self respect lmao.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyway I went off on a bit of a rant but the point of my post is this. Do your own research, do consistent research and tune out all the noise you&amp;amp;#39;re going to be hearing. Forget about marketing and hype. You will avoid most of this game&amp;amp;#39;s pitfalls by doing your own research. The most important skill you&amp;amp;#39;re ever going to use is tuning out noise and research.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[⚠️My account is under attack by spam bots!
Every tweet &amp; comment is bombarded by giveaway scam comments. People are blocking me to get rid of the spam.  @TwitterSupport HELP! Also many "send me DM" impersonator scammers. If my account is down pls follow my COO @100trillionEur https://t.co/7H6K3kZQFR]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501560740301479948/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501560740301479948/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 14:39:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jake Paul Exposed as $2.2M Serial Crypto Scammer]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ta5loq/jake_paul_exposed_as_22m_serial_crypto_scammer/?score=386&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fta5loq%2Fjake_paul_exposed_as_22m_serial_crypto_scammer%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fta5loq%2Fjake_paul_exposed_as_22m_serial_crypto_scammer%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ta5loq/jake_paul_exposed_as_22m_serial_crypto_scammer/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 14:38:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kraken just announced they would donate the money the make from trading fees from Russian accounts to Ukraine - and I think that's an incredibly smart move]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is only part of the announcement
[https://blog.kraken.com/post/13215/kraken-to-distribute-over-10-million-in-aid-to-clients-impacted-by-ukraine-crisis/]
- they are also donating 10 million independent from those trading fees - but I
want to focus on the part mentioned in the title - I think…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ta5ivw/kraken_just_announced_they_would_donate_the_money/?score=315&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fta5ivw%2Fkraken_just_announced_they_would_donate_the_money%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fta5ivw%2Fkraken_just_announced_they_would_donate_the_money%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ta5ivw/kraken_just_announced_they_would_donate_the_money/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 13:32:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is only part of the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.kraken.com/post/13215/kraken-to-distribute-over-10-million-in-aid-to-clients-impacted-by-ukraine-crisis/&quot;&amp;gt;announcement&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; - they are also donating 10 million independent from those trading fees - but I want to focus on the part mentioned in the title - I think that&amp;amp;#39;s an incredibly smart move.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Personally, I am more on the &amp;amp;quot;block Russians wherever possible&amp;amp;quot; side - I don&amp;amp;#39;t like that &amp;amp;quot;regular people&amp;amp;quot; are being affected by that either, but it&amp;amp;#39;s how sanctions work and crypto exchanges doing it is really no different from other companies stopping to operate in Russia. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;However:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; I know that Kraken&amp;amp;#39;s CEO is a super-libertarian, so sure, that&amp;amp;#39;s not an option. I think it&amp;amp;#39;s the smartest thing they could have done. Even if I&amp;amp;#39;m against not blocking the accounts, they can now say &amp;amp;quot;but see, we are generating donations for Ukraine by doing this, do you not want us to do that?&amp;amp;quot;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I personally would handle the situation differently, but I applaud them for this move. While I ideologically often disagree with their CEO, Kraken is a great exchange.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Russia to "disconnect from global Internet" from March 11th. Is this the end of crypto for the average Russian citizen?]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ta5eqx/russia_to_disconnect_from_global_internet_from/?score=355&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fta5eqx%2Frussia_to_disconnect_from_global_internet_from%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fta5eqx%2Frussia_to_disconnect_from_global_internet_from%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ta5eqx/russia_to_disconnect_from_global_internet_from/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 13:32:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[#Bitcoin https://t.co/xKEGzai6MY]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501533762227691523/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501533762227691523/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 12:51:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin Price Soars Above $41K on Biden's Crypto Administrative Order Leak]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ta3r7r/bitcoin_price_soars_above_41k_on_bidens_crypto/?score=617&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fta3r7r%2Fbitcoin_price_soars_above_41k_on_bidens_crypto%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fta3r7r%2Fbitcoin_price_soars_above_41k_on_bidens_crypto%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ta3r7r/bitcoin_price_soars_above_41k_on_bidens_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 12:50:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Getting rich can’t be this easy can it?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Everyone says that bear markets make millionaires. Simply buy the dip, keep
buying when it dips lower, and when it completely flatlines buy more. Then, hold
until the bull market comes and reap massive gains.

It can’t be this easy can it?… can it? I’m pretty happy with the projects I’m
invested…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9thxs/getting_rich_cant_be_this_easy_can_it/?score=322&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9thxs%2Fgetting_rich_cant_be_this_easy_can_it%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9thxs%2Fgetting_rich_cant_be_this_easy_can_it%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9thxs/getting_rich_cant_be_this_easy_can_it/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 12:50:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Everyone says that bear markets make millionaires. Simply buy the dip, keep buying when it dips lower, and when it completely flatlines buy more. Then, hold until the bull market comes and reap massive gains. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It can’t be this easy can it?… can it? 
I’m pretty happy with the projects I’m invested in, and my average buy ins are pretty far from all time highs. If I keep accumulating when it dips, will I just be rich if I hold? Seems way too good to be true. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m hoping it is this easy though. Knowing my luck crypto will never recover, but of course most likely it will one day. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What do you think? Is it really that easy as buying low, and holding?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pure GOLD from @thecryptomonk]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ta3bz5/pure_gold_from_thecryptomonk/?score=694&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fta3bz5%2Fpure_gold_from_thecryptomonk%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fta3bz5%2Fpure_gold_from_thecryptomonk%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ta3bz5/pure_gold_from_thecryptomonk/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 12:50:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Ruble is now worth less than toilet paper]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Ruble is sitting at 0.00769235 USD. According to my last order, my toilet
paper cost 26.49 for 1950 sheets or 0.013584 per sheet. This means it would be
cheaper to wipe your ass with Rubles but probably less comfortable.

If this isn't an endorsement for BTC, I don't know what is.]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ta1cx0/the_ruble_is_now_worth_less_than_toilet_paper/?score=310&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fta1cx0%2Fthe_ruble_is_now_worth_less_than_toilet_paper%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fta1cx0%2Fthe_ruble_is_now_worth_less_than_toilet_paper%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ta1cx0/the_ruble_is_now_worth_less_than_toilet_paper/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 12:50:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Ruble is sitting at 0.00769235 USD.  According to my last order, my toilet paper cost 26.49 for 1950 sheets or 0.013584 per sheet.  This means it would be cheaper to wipe your ass with Rubles but probably less comfortable.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If this isn&amp;amp;#39;t an endorsement for BTC, I don&amp;amp;#39;t know what is.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[To all weak hand sellers: thank you for your contribution
https://t.co/CxtLNncfvV]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501513440095002629/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501513440095002629/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 11:43:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[⚡️Russia suspends sale of foreign currency.

Customers will be able to withdraw a maximum of $10,000 in foreign currency from their accounts. All other funds will now be paid in rubles.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501505049213784066/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501505049213784066/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 10:50:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How was the decision made to ignore immunity from prior infection? 

In this clip, Paul Offit describes how he and another person advised in favor of accepting natural immunity, while two others voted against it.

A🧵 on why that was possibly the worst decision of the pandemic: https://t.co/OAM3TvNuhY]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501508671511093249/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501508671511093249/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 10:50:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Looks like Yellen's comments on tomorrow's Executive Order were accidentally posted a day early (now removed). https://t.co/k9jZJcPhS4 got them, though - https://t.co/EtOq1eNHRI]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501486824958705672/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501486824958705672/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 09:40:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[50 Lessons I learned trading crypto for the past 5 years]]></title><description><![CDATA[1 - Everyone’s a genius in a bull market. Real traders can survive and even
thrive in bear markets or highly volatile markets.

2 - Don’t be a blind bull. ALL markets are cyclical. Don’t be afraid of
pullbacks or market crashes – that’s where you can make the most money.

3 - There’s a big…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9yujw/50_lessons_i_learned_trading_crypto_for_the_past/?score=431&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9yujw%2F50_lessons_i_learned_trading_crypto_for_the_past%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9yujw%2F50_lessons_i_learned_trading_crypto_for_the_past%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9yujw/50_lessons_i_learned_trading_crypto_for_the_past/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 08:39:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;1 - Everyone’s a genius in a bull market. Real traders can survive and even thrive in bear markets or highly volatile markets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;2 - Don’t be a blind bull. ALL markets are cyclical. Don’t be afraid of pullbacks or market crashes – that’s where you can make the most money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;3 - There’s a big difference between a trade and an investment.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;4 - Fully plan your trade before you pull the trigger on the entry.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;5 - Entries are important, but risk &amp;amp;amp; money management is where you make or lose money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;6 - Beware of get-rich-quick gurus hopping on the crypto bandwagon over the past year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;7 - Decide which types of trade setups or investments you’ll take and ignore everything else.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;8 - Don’t assume just because you’ve made a lot of money in crypto that you can just as easily make money in other financial markets. 95%+ of stock market traders LOSE money. The game is rigged. Stick to what you know works for you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;9 - The best way to day trade cryptocurrencies is – DON’T!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;10 - The best way to profit in any market is to find something you think has big potential early (before the general public catches on), and invest assuming you’re going to lose 100% of your capital. It’s the “angel investor” approach.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;11 - You can’t control the market. The only thing you can control is your entries, trade size, and exits.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;12 - One market participant can completely destroy “good technical analysis”.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;13 - Don’t blindly follow trade alerts from ANYONE, especially random people on social media or chat rooms.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;14 - All financial networking marketing projects are ponzi schemes, period.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;15 - If you make a life-changing amount of money, do NOTHING for at least 30 days.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;16 - Trading isn’t about picking exact tops and bottoms in a market – it’s about catching the meat of a move.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;17 - Don’t turn a small losing trade into a massive losing investment.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;18 - Don’t set daily profit target goals – set long-term performance goals.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;19 - Learn to survive, then thrive.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;20 - The best charting indicators are price action and volume. You can use others, but it won’t necessarily make you a more profitable trader.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;21 - Trends can go way past what seems rational.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;22 - Don’t try to pick tops in a market. Wait for the market to tell you when the trend is over.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;23 - Don’t trade in front of big news events – it’s impossible to predict how markets will react.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;24 - The biggest challenge for most traders is their ego, or the need to be right.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;25 - You can lose 50% of your trades and still be profitable if you manage risk properly.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;26 - The best entrepreneurs and CEO’s typically make the worst traders and investors.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;27 - People with the best mindset for investing typically have a career in high-risk situations like firefighters, pilots, police.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;28 - Avoid pump and dump groups like the plague they are.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;29 - You WILL make every mistake in the book. Don’t beat yourself up when you make mistakes, just learn and try not to make the same mistake twice.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;30 - Don’t treat crypto exchanges like bank accounts. You don’t own the coins unless you control the private keys.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;31 - Crypto is a 24/7/365 market. You can’t catch every trade. If you miss one, don’t worry – there’s ALWAYS another trade.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;32 - Don’t invest in a coin unless you understand it inside out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;33 - You can make money trading the momentum and hype in shitcoins, just don’t invest long-term.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;34 - Stay away from coins with low trading volume and low market caps. They are easily manipulated and you can get stuck in a position.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;35 - Don’t trade with money you need for living expenses. It’s called “risk capital” for a reason.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;36 - Think of yourself as a hunter – save your ammo for the big game.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;37 - Crypocurrency exchanges go down when there’s high volatility. If price hits a major target or buy zone, it might make sense to place some orders BEFORE everyone else.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;38 - Trading and investing brings all your emotions to the forefront – fear, greed, hesitation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;39 - The hardest thing to do in trading is… NOTHING. This can also be the most profitable thing to do.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;40 - Just because a market is in a “bubble” doesn’t mean it’s going to die. Bitcoin has been through over half a dozen big bubbles and increased in price after each one.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;41 - Manage your trades in a way that would leave you with no regrets no matter what the market does.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;42 - Learn to think like a contrarian. If you’re someone who needs to have your opinion validated by everyone around you, then trading and investing isn’t for you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;43 - The shorter the chart time frame, the less reliable the chart patterns are. The longer the time frame, the more variables affect price action and the harder it becomes to predict price. My sweet spot in the daily chart for trade setups and 60-minute chart for entries.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;44 - Some market conditions are great for pushing the gas on every trade setup you can find, where other market conditions call for you to slam on the brakes and step away from the markets altogether.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;45 - 90%+ of cryptocurrencies will eventually go to zero. Invest accordingly.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;46 - The mental side of trading is the hardest to master, the most under-appreciated skill, and will cause you to make or lose the biggest amounts of money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;47 - The 3 biggest problems for traders are over-trading, hesitating on entries, and closing positions prior to profit targets when the trade is still intact.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;48 - You can make a career’s worth of profit in one year or one trade – don’t feel like every day has to be a home run. Play the long game. Be patient and wait for the best plays.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;49 - Don’t trust anyone else to trade for you. Manage your own high-risk investments (like crypto trading) or don’t participate at all.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;50 - Take the news for what it is – they’re trying to get views and clicks. They’re NOT looking out for your best interests or trying to help you make money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[EU rejects plans to ban Bitcoin, removes whole Passage out of planned Law]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t9s7n6/eu_rejects_plans_to_ban_bitcoin_removes_whole/?score=335&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft9s7n6%2Feu_rejects_plans_to_ban_bitcoin_removes_whole%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft9s7n6%2Feu_rejects_plans_to_ban_bitcoin_removes_whole%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t9s7n6/eu_rejects_plans_to_ban_bitcoin_removes_whole/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 08:39:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[London Metal Exchange (LME) artificially halted nickel trading as prices double, to stop a short squeeze play squeezing a Chinese company who shorted heavily on nickel. How is this fair for traders who took a long position? A call for people to adopt decentralization on commodity exchanges.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9wksw/london_metal_exchange_lme_artificially_halted/?score=383&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9wksw%2Flondon_metal_exchange_lme_artificially_halted%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9wksw%2Flondon_metal_exchange_lme_artificially_halted%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9wksw/london_metal_exchange_lme_artificially_halted/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 08:39:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The “it’s solid team and project” argument doesn’t work anymore.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I used to think it did, it has been the reason I’ve invested in specific
projects, but you know what, it doesn’t work. Not in an unregulated space where
you can just develop a coin out of thin air and list it on random exchanges.

You can have all the roadmaps and genius developers in the world,…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9v25p/the_its_solid_team_and_project_argument_doesnt/?score=333&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9v25p%2Fthe_its_solid_team_and_project_argument_doesnt%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9v25p%2Fthe_its_solid_team_and_project_argument_doesnt%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9v25p/the_its_solid_team_and_project_argument_doesnt/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 08:39:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I used to think it did, it has been the reason I’ve invested in specific projects, but you know what, it doesn’t work. Not in an unregulated space where you can just develop a coin out of thin air and list it on random exchanges.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can have all the roadmaps and genius developers in the world, but the second you don’t deliver on those promises or the second your lead dev quits; the project tanks so far into the depths it could take years to recover, if ever. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Look at ADA, such high hopes for Cardano, so many promises, institutional backing, hype, devs..... trees in Africa. And now, the face of the company is accused of lying about his degree, among other questionable activities.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Look at FTM, Andre, and Anton just deciding to peace out, closing 25 apps and services, dragging some of its projects down over 64%. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just to name a few.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know we all tout “DYOR, make sure it’s a good team, and they have a solid roadmap,” but in the end, we’re all still just gambling.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I bought $1k of the Top 10 Cryptos on January 1st, 2022 (FEB Update/Month 2)]]></title><description><![CDATA[EXPERIMENT - Tracking Top 10 Cryptos Of 2022 - Month Two – Down -14%
[https://preview.redd.it/9zbq2e5ok8m81.png?width=666&format=png&auto=webp&s=9fd17e5639d8094cb97b0482dd062727054dcdef]

Find the full blog post with all the tables here
[https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2022-top-10…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9syee/i_bought_1k_of_the_top_10_cryptos_on_january_1st/?score=339&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9syee%2Fi_bought_1k_of_the_top_10_cryptos_on_january_1st%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9syee%2Fi_bought_1k_of_the_top_10_cryptos_on_january_1st%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9syee/i_bought_1k_of_the_top_10_cryptos_on_january_1st/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 06:34:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/9zbq2e5ok8m81.png?width=666&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9fd17e5639d8094cb97b0482dd062727054dcdef&quot;&amp;gt;EXPERIMENT - Tracking Top 10 Cryptos Of 2022 - Month Two – Down -14&amp;amp;#37;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Find the full blog post with all the tables&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2022-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-2/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Welcome to your monthly no-shill data dump: Here&amp;amp;#39;s the second monthly report for the 2022 Top Ten Experiment featuring &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BTC, ETH, BNB, SOL, ADA, USDC, XRP, LUNA, DOT, and AVAX.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;tl;dr&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What&amp;amp;#39;s this all about?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; I purchased $100 of each of Top 10 Cryptos in Jan. 2018, haven&amp;amp;#39;t sold or traded, reporting monthly for over four years. Did the same in 2019, 2020, 2021, and 2022. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Learn more about the history and rules of the Experiments&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;(including why in the world I would include stablecoins)&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/about/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Learn more about the new features in the 2022 Top Ten Experiment&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/announcing-top-10-2022/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;February Highlights:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Crypto bounces back after a tough start to 2022, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;LUNA&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; dominates.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;New features:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; easy +23% on &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;USDC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and Top Ten outperforms &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/cryptex/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TCAP&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; this month winning the second round of my friendly TCAP vs. Top Ten comparison&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;2018+2019+2020+2021+2022 Combined Top Ten Portfolios are returning 247% vs. S&amp;amp;amp;P&amp;amp;#39;s 34%.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Month Two – Down -14%&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/43jxuvc2m8m81.jpg?width=942&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=de6a5648a8aa8246b73485e5334394efcfb3442c&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/43jxuvc2m8m81.jpg?width=942&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=de6a5648a8aa8246b73485e5334394efcfb3442c&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The 2022 Top Ten Crypto Index Fund Portfolio is &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BTC, ETH, BNB, Solana, ADA, USDC, XRP, LUNA, DOT, AVAX.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;February highlights for the 2022 Top Ten Portfolio:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;After a &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2022-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-1&quot;&amp;gt;rough January&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, the 2022 Top Ten Portfolio saw a nice rebound this month.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Luna&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; was easily the best performing Top Ten crypto in February while &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;SOL&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ADA&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; struggled.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;February Ranking and Dropouts&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here’s a look at the movement in the ranks two months into the 2022 Top Ten Index Fund Experiment:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/t7camdk4m8m81.jpg?width=298&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=7e6b626057b2092958acce78f12b6a8d365137f0&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/t7camdk4m8m81.jpg?width=298&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=7e6b626057b2092958acce78f12b6a8d365137f0&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;February Winners and Losers&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;February Winners&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; – &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;LUNA&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; easily outperformed the pack this month, gaining an impressive +73% this month. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;XRP&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; finished a distant second place, +27% in February.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;February Losers&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; –  &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;SOL&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ADA&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; struggled to keep up with their peers this month, dropping -12% and -10% respectively.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Overall Update – 80% of 2022 Top Ten in the red, LUNA  with early lead, SOL worst performing&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;LUNA’s&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; had a wild ride this year already.  Down -41% &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2022-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-1&quot;&amp;gt;last month&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, it roared back in February and is now the only crypto (besides &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;USDC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;) in positive territory.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At the bottom is &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;SOL&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, down -43% since the beginning of the year.  The initial $100 invested in &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;SOL&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; sixty days ago is worth $57 today.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Factoring in USDC Gains&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;New feature this year!&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; – In past Experiment years, I have not included stablecoin gains in the monthly reports. These days, there are many ways to earn ROI using stables alone. I figure this may be especially interesting this year, depending on how the crypto market performs. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For the 2022 Top Ten Experiment, I am detailing ways to build on the $100 USDC, starting with the most straightforward strategies.  As we go along in the year, I will share increasingly advanced methods to increase USDC. My goal of this little side quest will be to beat the ROI of as many of the non-stablecoin cryptos in the Experiment as possible. A simple task if 2022 ends up being a bear year, a bit more difficult if the crypto market moons.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;February&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; – One of the easiest methods to capitalize on stables (or any crypto for that matter) is to take advantage of sign up bonuses of different platforms, which are all competing for your business.  Many of which can be triggered with a small initial investment.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This month I took advantage of Nexo’s sign up bonus.  Using a promo code I transferred my current balance of USDC and after 30 days was given $25 in BTC, which I immediately exchanged to USDC.  These promo codes are everywhere online (or just ask a friend).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt; A very easy 23% monthly gain.  I am now &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+37% on USDC in two months&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/bwbbc42dm8m81.jpg?width=711&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=98126300f6bb85a5ecd98bfba9abd6a231a9dbdc&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/bwbbc42dm8m81.jpg?width=711&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=98126300f6bb85a5ecd98bfba9abd6a231a9dbdc&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Something to be aware of:&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; If you&amp;amp;#39;re considering taking advantage of this bonus, there have been complaints that Nexo doesn’t pay the $25 bonus if the value of the crypto you transfer is worth under $100 at the end of 30 days, as per the terms and conditions.  Lucky for us we’re using USDC, so I had no problem with the bonus. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;2022 Top Ten Portfolio vs. Total Crypto Market Cap Token (TCAP)&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Another new feature this year!&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; – The first Top Ten Crypto Experiment was started on 1 February 2018 in an attempt to capture the gains of the entire market. Much has changed in the last four+ years, including innovative Decentralized Finance (DeFi) projects that have created index tokens to capture segments of the crypto market (DeFi, the Metaverse, Blue Chips, etc.) instead of manually buying coins and tokens, like I do for my Experiments.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A project of particular interest to the Top Ten Experiments is the Total Crypto Market Cap (&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptex.finance/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TCAP&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;) token, created by &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/cryptex/&quot;&amp;gt;Cryptex&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, which tracks the entire crypto market – exactly what my Top Ten Portfolios have been trying to recreate from the start.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I thought it would be interesting to compare my homemade 2022 Top Ten Crypto Index Fund Experiment to &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TCAP&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; for a bit of a friendly competition. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here’s the question I’ll be tracking this year: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;would I have been better off with $1,000 of TCAP instead of going through the effort of creating a homemade $1,000 Top Ten Index Fund?&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;February:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Thanks to a strong month, both the &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TCAP&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; token and the 2022 Top Ten Portfolio gained in value.  The February monthly victory goes to the 2022 Top Top Portfolio (+14%) which edged out &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TCAP’s&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; +11% gain&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Overall: TCAP&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; leads the 2022 Top Ten Portfolio.  Visual below:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/xw94c0clm8m81.jpg?width=748&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=492aa178b7d38195810fbe1b153ce766e953c078&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/xw94c0clm8m81.jpg?width=748&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=492aa178b7d38195810fbe1b153ce766e953c078&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Bitcoin Dominance:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;BitDom continued to tick up this month, ending February at 43.3%. For context, it was at 40.2% at the beginning of the year. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/yg7nxffmm8m81.png?width=522&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=33db401369c2187254280cc9699c035b3e27d3ab&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/yg7nxffmm8m81.png?width=522&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=33db401369c2187254280cc9699c035b3e27d3ab&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For those just getting into crypto, it’s worth paying attention to the &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Bitcoin&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; dominance figure, as it signals the appetite for altcoins vs. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BTC.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Overall return on $1,000 investment since January 1st, 2022:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/zmawxsdnm8m81.jpg?width=307&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=3dc8c9cadbb40a3f84bb7f5e0701e002a6b0e313&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/zmawxsdnm8m81.jpg?width=307&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=3dc8c9cadbb40a3f84bb7f5e0701e002a6b0e313&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The 2022 Top Ten Portfolio gained $100 in February.  The initial $1000 investment on New Year’s Day 2022 is now worth &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$862&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, down -14%. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here’s a visual summary of the progress so far:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/vxon9wcom8m81.jpg?width=199&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e2d8469c7b584b83223dbea2fdb94a51347856c3&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/vxon9wcom8m81.jpg?width=199&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e2d8469c7b584b83223dbea2fdb94a51347856c3&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The 2022 Top Ten Cryptos are currently the worst performing of the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/&quot;&amp;gt;five Portfolios&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Combining the 2018, 2019, 2020, 2021, and 2022 Top Ten Crypto Portfolios&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, where do we stand if we combine five years of the Top Ten Crypto Index Fund Experiments?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;2018 Top Ten Experiment: up +10% (total value $1,099)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2019-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-38&quot;&amp;gt;2019 Top Ten Experiment&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;: up +401% (total value $5,014)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;2020 Top Ten Experiment: up +625% (total value $7,248)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;2021 Top Ten Experiment: up +211% (total value $3,110)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;2022 Top Ten Experiment: down -14% (total value $861)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Taking the five portfolios together, here’s the bottom bottom bottom bottom &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;bottom&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; line: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;After a $5,000 investment in the 2018, 2019, 2020, and 2021 Top Ten Cryptocurrencies,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; the combined portfolios are worth &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$17,332.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;That’s up +247%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; on the combined portfolios, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;down from&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2021-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-11/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;November 2021’s all time high&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for the Top Ten Index Fund Experiments of &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+533%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.  Here’s the combined monthly ROI since I started tracking the metric in January 2020:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/g0u37h8qm8m81.jpg?width=729&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=aaeb1f74755c494c502b1f9a843619e893239625&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/g0u37h8qm8m81.jpg?width=729&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=aaeb1f74755c494c502b1f9a843619e893239625&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In summary: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;That’s a +247% gain by investing $1k on whichever cryptos happened to be in the Top Ten on January 1st (including stablecoins) for five straight years&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Comparison to S&amp;amp;amp;P 500&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m also tracking the S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 as part of my Experiment to have a comparison point to traditional markets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/cy48e5ksm8m81.png?width=538&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=5cc3d19dbf5097551542659c2e249fa461a5db7a&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/cy48e5ksm8m81.png?width=538&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=5cc3d19dbf5097551542659c2e249fa461a5db7a&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 is down -10% so far in 2022, so the initial $1k investment into crypto on New Year’s Day would be worth $900 had it been redirected to the S&amp;amp;amp;P.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Taking the same invest-$1,000-on-February-1st-of-each-year approach with the S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 that I’ve been documenting through the Top Ten Crypto Experiments, the yields are the following:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2018 = $1,610 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2019 = $1,720 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2020 = $1,330 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2021 = $1,150 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2022 = $900 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Taken together, here’s the bottom bottom bottom bottom &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;bottom&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; line for a similar approach with the S&amp;amp;amp;P: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;After five $1,000 investments into an S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 index fund in January 2018, 2019, 2020, and 2021, my portfolio would be worth $6,710.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That is up &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+34%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-ten-month-one/&quot;&amp;gt;since January 2018&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; compared to a &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+247%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; gain of the combined Top Ten Crypto Experiment Portfolios.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here’s a fancy new chart showing a combined ROI comparison between a Top Ten Crypto approach and the S&amp;amp;amp;P as per the rules of the Top Ten Experiments: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/0oiwrzyzm8m81.png?width=697&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=8c321167623161b8d061d9920c1548324daef7d2&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/0oiwrzyzm8m81.png?width=697&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=8c321167623161b8d061d9920c1548324daef7d2&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Conclusion:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To the long time followers of the Top Ten Experiments, thank you so much for sticking around so long. For those just getting into crypto, I hope these reports will help prepare you for the highs and lows that await on your crypto adventures.  Buckle up, go with the flow, think long term, don’t invest what you can’t afford to lose, and most importantly, try to enjoy the ride!  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A reporting note: I’ll focus on 2022 Top Ten Portfolio reports + one other portfolio on a rotating basis this year, so expect only two reports from me per month.  February’s extended report was on the 2019 Top Ten Portfolio, which you can access &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2019-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-38&quot;&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.  You can check out the latest &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-49&quot;&amp;gt;2018 Top Ten&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; (the OG Experiment), &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2020-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-24&quot;&amp;gt;2020 Top Ten&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2021-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-12&quot;&amp;gt;2021 Top Ten&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; reports as well.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Treasury leaks Sec. Yellen’s press release on Biden’s Bitcoin Executive Order.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t9xdct/treasury_leaks_sec_yellens_press_release_on/?score=420&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft9xdct%2Ftreasury_leaks_sec_yellens_press_release_on%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft9xdct%2Ftreasury_leaks_sec_yellens_press_release_on%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t9xdct/treasury_leaks_sec_yellens_press_release_on/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 06:34:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A redditor lost $120k worth of crypto when he mistakenly clicked a malicious link.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9f0nu/a_redditor_lost_120k_worth_of_crypto_when_he/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9f0nu%2Fa_redditor_lost_120k_worth_of_crypto_when_he%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9f0nu%2Fa_redditor_lost_120k_worth_of_crypto_when_he%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9f0nu/a_redditor_lost_120k_worth_of_crypto_when_he/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 04:47:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[IMO BTC's first dip from 60k to 30k in 2021 was caused by China's mining ban. The second dip from 60k to 30k in 2021 was caused by inflation combined with possible rate hikes &amp; QE ending. Currently the odds of rate hikes &amp; QE ending seem low.. https://t.co/BHLLZQqI8l]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501332293293461504/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1501332293293461504/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 01:19:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coinbase Blocks 25,000 Russian Accounts]]></title><description><![CDATA[Regardless of your opinions on the conflict in Ukraine, I think we can all agree
that Coinbase is a steaming pile of shit. Their actions contradict the very
essence and purpose of cryptocurrency - a completely decentralized financial
solution that is NOT to be governed by any central bank or…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t9fceo/coinbase_blocks_25000_russian_accounts/?score=333&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft9fceo%2Fcoinbase_blocks_25000_russian_accounts%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft9fceo%2Fcoinbase_blocks_25000_russian_accounts%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t9fceo/coinbase_blocks_25000_russian_accounts/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 01:18:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Regardless of your opinions on the conflict in Ukraine, I think we can all agree that Coinbase is a steaming pile of shit. Their actions contradict the very essence and purpose of cryptocurrency - a completely decentralized financial solution that is NOT to be governed by any central bank or monetary authority.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://blockworks.co/coinbase-blocks-25000-accounts-linked-to-russia-to-support-sanctions/&quot;&amp;gt;https://blockworks.co/coinbase-blocks-25000-accounts-linked-to-russia-to-support-sanctions/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jake Paul earned over $2 million by promoting pump and dump crypto schemes]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9kewn/jake_paul_earned_over_2_million_by_promoting_pump/?score=340&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9kewn%2Fjake_paul_earned_over_2_million_by_promoting_pump%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9kewn%2Fjake_paul_earned_over_2_million_by_promoting_pump%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9kewn/jake_paul_earned_over_2_million_by_promoting_pump/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 01:18:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just a week after the ‘Earn’ debacle, Crypto.com fucks up again by announcing that anyone with a Crypto Loan needs to repay it within 7 days – or be forcibly liquidated via funds in their Spot Wallet. What planet are these idiots living on?]]></title><description><![CDATA[EDIT: This post went straight to the top of the CDC sub - then the Mods removed
it. So not only are CDC untrustworthy, but they're now censoring (accurately)
critical posts on their own…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9mcfj/just_a_week_after_the_earn_debacle_cryptocom/?score=383&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9mcfj%2Fjust_a_week_after_the_earn_debacle_cryptocom%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9mcfj%2Fjust_a_week_after_the_earn_debacle_cryptocom%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9mcfj/just_a_week_after_the_earn_debacle_cryptocom/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 01:18:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: This post went straight to the top of the CDC sub - then the Mods removed it. So not only are CDC untrustworthy, but they&amp;amp;#39;re now censoring (accurately) critical posts on their own sub:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/0s83zfynw8m81.png?width=1057&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=dfcfbdf7f17dd829bb9554f2e114b109d9b8e8eb&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/0s83zfynw8m81.png?width=1057&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=dfcfbdf7f17dd829bb9554f2e114b109d9b8e8eb&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Disclaimer: I’ve been a serious cheerleader for CDC for almost two years (check my post history). Until the past week, they could literally do no wrong in my eyes. But I’m starting to see that they are sneaky and becoming more untrustworthy by the day.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As per the title of this thread - Yes, you read that right. Forced Liquidations from your Spot Wallet. Yesterday CDC were happily handing out Crypto loans on their Exchange at a balmy 8% APY. Yet today, they decided they’d rather not – and gave any borrower 7 days to repay their loan(s).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;e.g. if someone had taken out a 10K loan last week (at 8%) and then placed it straight into Earn (USDC 14%) with a three-month stake, they would be absolutely fucked right now because of CDC&amp;amp;#39;s incompetent and ridiculous communication. 7 days to repay a loan that THEY were happy to make just 24 hours ago.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Yes, most us know that they trading on leverage is a bad idea, but it seems many were happy to borrow at 8% and then stake in Earn at 14%. I’m the opposite luckily – USDC staked in Earn and (currently) no borrowing as the market is a mess right now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I think it’s important that we draw as much attention to this as possible as ANY exchange which decides to treat loyal users in this way deserves to be called out and publicly shamed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto.com do a LOT of things right (Cards, Marketing, Sponsorships, Partnerships, PR, etc). But they are starting to seriously wrong foot users and making some very penny-pinching, illogical decisions which make them look shady as fuck.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;End of rant : ))&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Proof (+ it&amp;amp;#39;s all over the CDC sub)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/f2mp7h5q87m81.png?width=813&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=520647f7c1d8b2628efdd54db972aaa5bdd745dc&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/f2mp7h5q87m81.png?width=813&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=520647f7c1d8b2628efdd54db972aaa5bdd745dc&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[So does Elizabeth Warren lie all of the time about crypto or does she just not understand anything about it?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Admittedly I don't really pay much attention to her ramblings on anything, but I
see stuff about her mentioned on here from time to time.

My aunt is visiting, though, and she loves MSNBC so we've had that on quite a
bit for the past few days.

Liz Warren comes on this morning to talk about the war…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9oagp/so_does_elizabeth_warren_lie_all_of_the_time/?score=319&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9oagp%2Fso_does_elizabeth_warren_lie_all_of_the_time%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9oagp%2Fso_does_elizabeth_warren_lie_all_of_the_time%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9oagp/so_does_elizabeth_warren_lie_all_of_the_time/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 01:18:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Admittedly I don&amp;amp;#39;t really pay much attention to her ramblings on anything, but I see stuff about her mentioned on here from time to time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My aunt is visiting, though, and she loves MSNBC so we&amp;amp;#39;ve had that on quite a bit for the past few days.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Liz Warren comes on this morning to talk about the war in Ukraine.  Then the topic turned to crypto and how Russia is using it to bypass sanctions, but...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;...literally EVERY point she made was either flawed or completely false.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How the heck is the crypto community going to achieve true mass adoption when we have people like her in positions of power who are inhibiting progress?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It reminds me of Andreas Antonopoulos mentioning years ago about how people were so against electricity at first because...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;IT&amp;amp;quot;LL CAUSE FIRES!  EVERYONE&amp;amp;#39;S HOUSE WILL BURN DOWN!&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;or&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;WHY SHOULD WE CHANGE?  CANDLES AND OIL LAMPS WORK FINE!&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The mountain of naysayers just seems insurmountable right now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Give me some encouragement, /cc!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Top Senate Democrat Ron Wyden says regulating crypto would be like killing the internet in its infancy.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9jaa4/top_senate_democrat_ron_wyden_says_regulating/?score=337&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9jaa4%2Ftop_senate_democrat_ron_wyden_says_regulating%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft9jaa4%2Ftop_senate_democrat_ron_wyden_says_regulating%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t9jaa4/top_senate_democrat_ron_wyden_says_regulating/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 01:18:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Change my mind]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t9bcbo/change_my_mind/?score=314&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft9bcbo%2Fchange_my_mind%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft9bcbo%2Fchange_my_mind%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t9bcbo/change_my_mind/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 20:42:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>