<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing on Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 11:40:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[1/n

Putin didn’t just invade the Ukraine on 2/24/2022, he officially ended the #petrodollar system. How? Remember, Russians don’t do anything without a plan. They and China have been prepping for this moment for years and are now ready:

https://t.co/b7IYdVYepG]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1498231627058716672/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1498231627058716672/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 10:36:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cheers for the high-court decision and relief from a societal menace.  "Gross violation of human rights" an appropriate description of the offending practice. https://t.co/iXcVTwbi7r]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1498206498496864261/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1498206498496864261/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 08:37:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Russian soldiers surrendering to Ukraine will receive 5 million rubles worth of crypto]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t391pz/russian_soldiers_surrendering_to_ukraine_will/?score=657&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft391pz%2Frussian_soldiers_surrendering_to_ukraine_will%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft391pz%2Frussian_soldiers_surrendering_to_ukraine_will%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t391pz/russian_soldiers_surrendering_to_ukraine_will/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 08:37:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The stock market is more than 200 years old, went through 2 world wars and people STILL make millions off of it. Crypto is only 13 years old…]]></title><description><![CDATA[If people still made millions off of stocks like Facebook, Tesla and Amazon from
a market that’s more than 200 years old, I’m pretty sure that we’re not “too
late”

You have no idea how many people in the world still don’t know what crypto or
Bitcoin even is. We just think that “its too late” cause…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t312c2/the_stock_market_is_more_than_200_years_old_went/?score=307&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft312c2%2Fthe_stock_market_is_more_than_200_years_old_went%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft312c2%2Fthe_stock_market_is_more_than_200_years_old_went%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t312c2/the_stock_market_is_more_than_200_years_old_went/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 06:38:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If people still made millions off of stocks like Facebook, Tesla and Amazon from a market that’s more than 200 years old, I’m pretty sure that we’re not “too late”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You have no idea how many people in the world still don’t know what crypto or Bitcoin even is. We just think that “its too late” cause people like us are constantly exposed to crypto news when in actuality most people either still dont care enough or dont know about it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I think the crypto market will have a really long run from here. Start investing early into projects with actual utility and technology like Ethereum or even MATIC considering they helped people save hundreds of millions of dollars on Ethereum gas fees over this entire period.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Don’t asume that “we’re too late” just cause someone on this sub said so. Zoom out and you’ll see that the crypto market is still a spec on the map compared to other markets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ukraine Government Offering Bounty in crypto currency for Info Leading to Russian Politician Wallet Addresses]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2v8az/ukraine_government_offering_bounty_in_crypto/?score=345&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2v8az%2Fukraine_government_offering_bounty_in_crypto%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2v8az%2Fukraine_government_offering_bounty_in_crypto%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2v8az/ukraine_government_offering_bounty_in_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 06:38:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The fact that you can now transfer thousands of dollars from one country or another for near zero fees should be enough to show you the inefficiency of institutions like Western Union.]]></title><description><![CDATA[A thousand dollars cross country would cost at least $50 through things like
Western Union which we all too as a standard back in the day but now seems
outrageous with projects like e-Money or Tron pressing near zero fees for such
large sums of money transfers.

The only reason Western Union isn’t…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2ykey/the_fact_that_you_can_now_transfer_thousands_of/?score=314&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2ykey%2Fthe_fact_that_you_can_now_transfer_thousands_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2ykey%2Fthe_fact_that_you_can_now_transfer_thousands_of%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2ykey/the_fact_that_you_can_now_transfer_thousands_of/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 04:38:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A thousand dollars cross country would cost at least $50 through things like Western Union which we all too as a standard back in the day but now seems outrageous with projects like e-Money or Tron pressing near zero fees for such large sums of money transfers.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The only reason Western Union isn’t tumbling right now is because crypto is still new to most of the populous and the fact that some countries don’t have internet access to begin with.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But for the most part, once crypto start gaining more and more mainstream traction, companies and financial institutions the likes of Western Union and MoneyGram will start to falter and wi only be used by severely underdeveloped countries with no internet access.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs executive joins Coinbase, says it’s time to embrace crypto economy]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2rnfj/goldman_sachs_executive_joins_coinbase_says_its/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2rnfj%2Fgoldman_sachs_executive_joins_coinbase_says_its%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2rnfj%2Fgoldman_sachs_executive_joins_coinbase_says_its%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2rnfj/goldman_sachs_executive_joins_coinbase_says_its/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 03:31:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Everyone says we need easy and cheap markets for non-KYC BTC... So I have done this.]]></title><description><![CDATA[TL;TR: Bitcoin is slowly being captured by the tight grip on the fiat on/off
ramps. We need convenient, fast and cheap markets for non-KYC bitcoin. I have
worked my ass off for two months to create an easy and private P2P exchange that
uses solely lightning hold invoices. It is called RoboSats and…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t2v44r/everyone_says_we_need_easy_and_cheap_markets_for/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft2v44r%2Feveryone_says_we_need_easy_and_cheap_markets_for%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft2v44r%2Feveryone_says_we_need_easy_and_cheap_markets_for%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t2v44r/everyone_says_we_need_easy_and_cheap_markets_for/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 02:51:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TL;TR:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Bitcoin is slowly being captured by the tight grip on the fiat on/off ramps. We need convenient, fast and cheap markets for non-KYC bitcoin. I have worked my ass off for two months to create an easy and private P2P exchange that uses solely lightning hold invoices. It is called RoboSats and I believe it can potentially rival centralized exchanges in ease of use and fees, while being totally private and having a close to custody-less pipeline. You can use it from your smartphone right now: it is straightforward to use even for the very noob. The platform is fully open source and will always be. It works quite well, but it is experimental: read the info and trade only small amounts. Open it now with Tor Browser: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;http://robosats6tkf3eva7x2voqso3a5wcorsnw34jveyxfqi2fu7oyheasid.onion/&quot;&amp;gt;Onion Link&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Background&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One of the main threats for the Bitcoin network and its users is the ability of a few entities to control the fiat on/off-ramps. The tight grip on them allows for censorship and surveillance by linking funds with identities and strips the freedom away from Bitcoin. While there exists several peer-to-peer alternatives to centralized exchanges, these are rather technical, slow and costly. Most users still prefer the convenience of a centralized exchange at the cost of their privacy and a difficult initial setup (submit passport, selfie-video, etc). Things do not look too well for a truly free Bitcoin ecosystem.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, there are opportunities too. Using the Lightning Network it might very well be possible to create a very user friendly, safe, fast and cheap peer-to-peer market. By using hold invoices as fidelity bonds and trade escrows, trust/security can be maximized. It will never be as secure as an on-chain escrow. But one can dream that an open p2p market like that could rival the ease of use of centralized exchanges and have very low fees too; yet, with minimal privacy invasion and a close to custody-less trade pipeline.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/yvd6dqtpafk81.jpg?width=1200&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=6293fafd6fffffd1b6d792134007e588bdc19dd9&quot;&amp;gt;Wait, is that u/Reckless_Satoshi wearing a hoodie... AGAIN!?. He must have been up to something.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For the last two months I have been locked in my basement, feeding protein shakes and listening to SaylorWaves instead of sleeping... yeah, living the good life. And... I have also built &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;RoboSats&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; during that time :)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;What is RoboSats?&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is a BTC/FIAT peer-to-peer exchange over lightning. It simplifies matchmaking and minimizes the need for trust. RoboSats focuses in privacy, speed and user friendliness. RoboSats is an &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/reckless-satoshi/robosats&quot;&amp;gt;open source project&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;How does it work?&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Alice wants to buy bitcoin privately. She generates an avatar in RoboSats homepage (AnonymousAlice01) and stores her random token safely so she can recover the avatar later. She creates a new buy order. Bob wants to sell bitcoin and takes Alice&amp;amp;#39;s order. Both have to post a small bond using lightning to prove they are &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;real robots&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Then, Bob posts the trade collateral also using a lightning hold invoice. RoboSats locks the invoice until Bob confirms he received the fiat, then the satoshis are released to Alice. Enjoy your satoshis Alice!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At no point, Alice and Bob have to entrust the bitcoin to each other. In case they have a conflict, RoboSats staff will help resolving the dispute. You can find a step-by-step description of the trade pipeline in &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/Reckless-Satoshi/robosats/blob/main/README.md#how-it-works&quot;&amp;gt;How It Works&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Use it now&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Click the link below to start buying/selling non-KYC Bitcoin, no registration or any other BS required. Just visit the site using TOR Browser (Mobile works great). Brave is OK too:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;http://robosats6tkf3eva7x2voqso3a5wcorsnw34jveyxfqi2fu7oyheasid.onion&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;RoboSats&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;6tkf3eva7x2voqso3a5wcorsnw34jveyxfqi2fu7oyheasid.onion&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;... if it does not work, you must download &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.torproject.org/download/&quot;&amp;gt;Tor Browser for your device&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ciii1r5wafk81.png?width=3407&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=ea29fb95e54c4a7c4184675754b8a8f3ff124dfc&quot;&amp;gt;They usually place fancy screenshots of the apps in the play store / apple store. This is just my attempt to conform to expectations. There is more to RoboSats that what can be seen here, make sure to read the how-to-use guide.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;In more details&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Here a full guide with two complete walk-throughs: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/reckless-satoshi/robosats/blob/main/docs/how-to-use.md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;How to Use RoboSats&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You can also read the full list of features in the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/reckless-satoshi/robosats/releases/tag/v0.1.0-mvp&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;RoboSats v0.1.0 stack release&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;What payment methods are accepted?&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Basically all of them as long as they are FAST. You can write down your preferred payment method(s). You will have to match with a peer who also accepts that method as you pay each other directly. The step in the contract to exchange fiat has an expiry time of 24 hours before a dispute is automatically opened. So, I highly recommend using instant fiat payment rails.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Are there trade limits?&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Maximum single trade size is 500,000 satoshis to minimize lightning routing failure. There is no limits to the number of trades per day. A robot can only have one order at a time. However, you can use multiple robots simultaneously in different browsers (remember to back up your robot tokens!). At launch RoboSats is limited to a maximum of 100 public orders at a time (...just a temporary safety measure).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Is RoboSats private?&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;RoboSats will absolutely never ask you for your name, email, phone number, country or ID. RoboSats does not custody your funds and does not care pinch about who you are. For best anonymity use Tor Browser and access the .onion hidden site.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Your trading peer is the only one who can potentially guess anything about you. Keep your chat short and concise. Avoid providing non-essential information other than strictly necessary for the fiat payment. But don&amp;amp;#39;t forget to be polite! :)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;What are the risks?&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is an experimental lightning application, things could go wrong. Trade small amounts! The seller faces the same charge-back risk as with any other peer-to-peer service. I do not recommend using Paypal or credit cards.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;What is the trust model?&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The buyer and the seller never have to trust each other. Some trust on RoboSats is needed since linking the seller&amp;amp;#39;s hold invoice and buyer payment is not atomic (research ongoing). In addition, disputes are solved by the RoboSats staff.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To be totally clear. Trust requirements are minimized. However, there is still one way RoboSats could run away with your satoshis: by not releasing the satoshis to the buyer. It could be argued that such move is not in the platform&amp;amp;#39;s interest as it would badly damage the reputation for a small payout. However, you should hesitate and only trade small quantities at a time. For large amounts use an on-chain escrow service such as Bisq. You can build more trust on RoboSats by inspecting the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/reckless-satoshi/robosats&quot;&amp;gt;source code&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;What are the fees?&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The trading fee is 0.2%. That&amp;amp;#39;s about the same as Binance, yet you will not have to pay a &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;withdrawal fine&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; (that same fee covers for the routing to your wallet). The fidelity bonds are sized 1% with respect the trade amount, these are automatically returned.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;What happens if RoboSats suddenly disappears?&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Your sats will return to you. Any hold invoice that is not settled will automatically return even if RoboSats goes down forever. This is true for both, locked bonds and trading escrows. However, there is a small window between the seller confirms FIAT RECEIVED and the moment the buyer receives the satoshis when the funds could be permanently lost if RoboSats disappears. This window is about 1 second long, so make sure to have enough inbound liquidity to avoid routing failures. If you have any problem, reach out trough the RoboSats public channels (&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://t.me/robosats&quot;&amp;gt;Telegram&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Is RoboSats legal in my country?&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In most countries using RoboSats is no different than using Ebay or Craiglist. Your regulation may vary. It is your responsibility to comply (lmao, sorry but I have to write this). If your country is shitty about p2p commerce start thinking about moving, it will only get worse.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Can I access it without Tor Browser / Brave?&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Not yet, and why should you? Use Tor and improve your privacy! However, the site &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;robosats.com&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; will be accessible at some point. It will be a simple web2tor bridge to widen the access to any browser and improve URL memorability... It comes with a huge set of caveats for privacy and security: so you should always use the .onion site and Tor Browser if possible!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;You make RoboSats a great place&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you like what you see, there is a lot of ways you can become part of this open project. The most needed contributions are: develop code (funding might be possible, ask); create tutorials and guides; open outbound LN channels towards &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://1ml.com/node/0282eb467bc073833a039940392592bf10cf338a830ba4e392c1667d7697654c7e&quot;&amp;gt;RoboSats node (1ML)&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;; create art (logo, banners, they are shitty rn); and help newbies in our community groups (Telegram: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://t.me/robosats&quot;&amp;gt;English&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://t.me/robosats_es&quot;&amp;gt;Spanish&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;). Needless to say, simply using the platform, telling a friend or sharing your idea/criticism is a huge help!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Give it a try now and contribute to make this open source project glorious!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cheers, &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Reckless_Satoshi&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[oof, this ain’t it chief.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t2xd1t/oof_this_aint_it_chief/?score=317&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft2xd1t%2Foof_this_aint_it_chief%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft2xd1t%2Foof_this_aint_it_chief%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t2xd1t/oof_this_aint_it_chief/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 02:51:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I made a document you can give to your family which explains what to do after you die]]></title><description><![CDATA[So as some can figure out, I've been preparing a few things for when I die. (No
I'm not expecting. But it is better to get this out of the way now)

Anyways, I made a template for anyone to mess…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2y6r4/i_made_a_document_you_can_give_to_your_family/?score=374&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2y6r4%2Fi_made_a_document_you_can_give_to_your_family%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2y6r4%2Fi_made_a_document_you_can_give_to_your_family%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2y6r4/i_made_a_document_you_can_give_to_your_family/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 01:47:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So as some can figure out, I&amp;amp;#39;ve been preparing a few things for when I die. (No I&amp;amp;#39;m not expecting. But it is better to get this out of the way now)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyways, I made a template for anyone to mess with. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/document/d/13se29qf7V6V12VHdnaOXyQAu3wkbRf3xYeRrg7r7XXs/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&amp;gt;https://docs.google.com/document/d/13se29qf7V6V12VHdnaOXyQAu3wkbRf3xYeRrg7r7XXs/edit?usp=sharing&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;MAKE YOUR OWN COPY SO YOU CAN EDIT IT&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/1v4pspjdzfk81.png?width=920&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e01d5b5ce50cea60eefdac76524614ab2984664b&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/1v4pspjdzfk81.png?width=920&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e01d5b5ce50cea60eefdac76524614ab2984664b&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Obviously you would want to heavily edit this, but this should help you get started.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Big things to note is taxes, and how people will find out where your crypto is stored. I&amp;amp;#39;m using Koinly anyways to track everything for taxes. So I might as well make that in a way family can find whatever crypto and where it is.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Note I wouldn&amp;amp;#39;t put seed phrases or other things in this. To be blunt, I don&amp;amp;#39;t trust Google.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;NOTE I heavily use last pass to just give people my passwords in this time. This allows them to take whatever from my exchanges, and it allows them to bypass horrible support they most likely would get from &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://Binance.US&quot;&amp;gt;Binance.US&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. Plus since I even have a hard time remember which exchange has a KYC and what doesn&amp;amp;#39;t. This bypasses if the exchange even could do this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Prime Minister of Ukraine is now asking the exchanges to block all Russian users out. No matter the politics but this is a great reminder to take your coin out of any exchange. One day, your country could be on the list too. Not your keys, not your sats!]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t2w9hd/the_prime_minister_of_ukraine_is_now_asking_the/?score=498&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft2w9hd%2Fthe_prime_minister_of_ukraine_is_now_asking_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft2w9hd%2Fthe_prime_minister_of_ukraine_is_now_asking_the%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t2w9hd/the_prime_minister_of_ukraine_is_now_asking_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 01:47:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ruble is set to fall by 50% crypto markets have not yet realized this]]></title><description><![CDATA[According to unofficial over the weekend exchange rates Russian ruble is down by
about 50%.

Analysis by Paul Sonne from Washington Post.

"Russian bank Tinkoff now offering to exchange rubles for dollars at a rate of
171 rubles per dollar. It was 83 before the European/US announcement…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2vtvd/ruble_is_set_to_fall_by_50_crypto_markets_have/?score=609&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2vtvd%2Fruble_is_set_to_fall_by_50_crypto_markets_have%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2vtvd%2Fruble_is_set_to_fall_by_50_crypto_markets_have%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2vtvd/ruble_is_set_to_fall_by_50_crypto_markets_have/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 22:39:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;According to unofficial over the weekend exchange rates Russian ruble is down by about 50%.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Analysis by Paul Sonne from Washington Post.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Russian bank Tinkoff now offering to exchange rubles for dollars at a rate of 171 rubles per dollar. It was 83 before the European/US announcement about targeting the Russian central bank. Currency market formally opens tomorrow. This is brutal. &amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/8wljxfeqgfk81.png?width=1101&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=0552cc2b01039c7aeb560c96cd9e3acc7053fe55&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/8wljxfeqgfk81.png?width=1101&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=0552cc2b01039c7aeb560c96cd9e3acc7053fe55&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;According to coinmarketcap crypto has not yet realized this, and Bitcoin trades at the same price to RUB as usual. Even as Tether shows the drop.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/frh8m7hsgfk81.png?width=1445&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=b6e0b523b745652fb1dfa6123085d03c14012397&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/frh8m7hsgfk81.png?width=1445&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=b6e0b523b745652fb1dfa6123085d03c14012397&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Of course CMC can just be broken and not show the actual ruble/BTC rate. But be careful out there, and selling any crypto for ruble might be a really bad idea.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Of course if you have Rubles and any exchange still takes them, it might be a really good idea to switch to crypto, before the market wakes up :)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin pools should NOT block Russian users. The entire point of the network is to be decentralized regardless of current situation.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Miners are what keep the network alive. Regardless of the current situation the
network should not be degraded or disconnected for Russian users.

Russian civilian's don't want a war. It's unlikely Russia government is using
the BTC network anyway.

I too take Ukraine side in this disgusting act by…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t2rdpx/bitcoin_pools_should_not_block_russian_users_the/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft2rdpx%2Fbitcoin_pools_should_not_block_russian_users_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft2rdpx%2Fbitcoin_pools_should_not_block_russian_users_the%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t2rdpx/bitcoin_pools_should_not_block_russian_users_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 21:34:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Miners are what keep the network alive. Regardless of the current situation the network should not be degraded or disconnected for Russian users.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Russian civilian&amp;amp;#39;s don&amp;amp;#39;t want a war. It&amp;amp;#39;s unlikely Russia government is using the BTC network anyway.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I too take Ukraine side in this disgusting act by Putin but we must maintain integrity of the Bitcoin network.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Edit&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To clarify it has been reported that some cryptocurrency pools are blocking access to Russia. This is not solely limited to just BTC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Edit 2&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just to be clear. I know exactly how the network works. I&amp;amp;#39;m stating freely and clearly that all pools should remain online and active for everyone and not to impose any restrictions as to retain the integrity of crypto currency.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a pool owner you should NOT be making choices based of political decisions that may deliberately prevent end users from using the service.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Binance Donates $10 Million to Ukraine and Launches Charity Fund]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2qo4c/binance_donates_10_million_to_ukraine_and/?score=512&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2qo4c%2Fbinance_donates_10_million_to_ukraine_and%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2qo4c%2Fbinance_donates_10_million_to_ukraine_and%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2qo4c/binance_donates_10_million_to_ukraine_and/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 20:38:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Polkadot founder Gavin Wood: If Ukraine releases the Polkadot address, I will donate $5 million]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2toco/polkadot_founder_gavin_wood_if_ukraine_releases/?score=342&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2toco%2Fpolkadot_founder_gavin_wood_if_ukraine_releases%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2toco%2Fpolkadot_founder_gavin_wood_if_ukraine_releases%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2toco/polkadot_founder_gavin_wood_if_ukraine_releases/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 20:38:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ukrainian govt offering rewards for Russian politicians’ crypto info]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2l5zg/ukrainian_govt_offering_rewards_for_russian/?score=314&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2l5zg%2Fukrainian_govt_offering_rewards_for_russian%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2l5zg%2Fukrainian_govt_offering_rewards_for_russian%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2l5zg/ukrainian_govt_offering_rewards_for_russian/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 20:38:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto Donations to Ukraine Exceed $13 Million]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2n2hv/crypto_donations_to_ukraine_exceed_13_million/?score=355&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2n2hv%2Fcrypto_donations_to_ukraine_exceed_13_million%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2n2hv%2Fcrypto_donations_to_ukraine_exceed_13_million%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2n2hv/crypto_donations_to_ukraine_exceed_13_million/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 16:33:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Most disgusting scam yet: dude comments on all posts pretending to post the official crypto address for helping the Ukrainian government. Please report u/substantialsummer634 to Reddit]]></title><description><![CDATA[That's pretty much all there is to say to it. u/substantialsummer634
[/u/substantialsummer634] is mass replying to posts, saying "Ukraine’s official
Twitter account tweeted out a call for donations through bitcoin, Ethereum, and
stablecoin tether on Saturday." and then adds an Ethereum address for…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2pttl/most_disgusting_scam_yet_dude_comments_on_all/?score=612&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2pttl%2Fmost_disgusting_scam_yet_dude_comments_on_all%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2pttl%2Fmost_disgusting_scam_yet_dude_comments_on_all%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2pttl/most_disgusting_scam_yet_dude_comments_on_all/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 16:33:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That&amp;amp;#39;s pretty much all there is to say to it. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/u/substantialsummer634&quot;&amp;gt;u/substantialsummer634&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; is mass replying to posts, saying &amp;amp;quot;Ukraine’s official Twitter account tweeted out a call for donations through bitcoin, Ethereum, and stablecoin tether on Saturday.&amp;amp;quot; and then adds an Ethereum address for donations. The first part is true, you can find the real addresses in &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t26b00/im_uvladimirputin_and_im_asking_you_to_donate/&quot;&amp;gt;this very popular post&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. The address is fake though. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Fortunately nobody fell for it yet, the last transfer to that address was 47 days ago, but please report the scammer to Reddit - I have done that already. Thanks!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: just in case their account indeed gets suspended, their posts look like this: &amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Ukraine Update: Ukraine’s official Twitter account tweeted out a call for donations through bitcoin, Ethereum, and stablecoin tether on Saturday. I just sent what I could, wish I could do more . Have a. Heart Stand with Ukraine . Here’s the wallet address if you guys wanna donate anything to help. [Wallet address]&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you see something like that, check if it&amp;amp;#39;s the real address and if not, report the account&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Apology to Charles (Hoskinson) and r/cc]]></title><description><![CDATA[I made a few sensationalist posts over the past week alleging that Charles was
involved with the front-running of Sundae Swap.

In one of the posts, I showed that IOHK’s wallet could be traced to a huge,
unstaked wallet that funded another wallet used in the alleged front-running of
Sundae. The…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2cdhj/apology_to_charles_hoskinson_and_rcc/?score=329&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2cdhj%2Fapology_to_charles_hoskinson_and_rcc%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2cdhj%2Fapology_to_charles_hoskinson_and_rcc%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2cdhj/apology_to_charles_hoskinson_and_rcc/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 15:36:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I made a few sensationalist posts over the past week alleging that Charles was involved with the front-running of Sundae Swap.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In one of the posts, I showed that IOHK’s wallet could be traced to a huge, unstaked wallet that funded another wallet used in the alleged front-running of Sundae. The connection between IOHK’s wallet and the huge, unstaked wallet was made in about a dozen transfers, each with over 25 million ADA transfers with most transfers involving over a billion ADA.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I had said in a previous post that I did not believe this address &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cardanoscan.io/address/addr1q8g77agasft90nnrln487665tf4nz9tt0z9df0l5z637yavnfrlkaatu28n0qzmqh7f2cpksxhpc9jefx3wrl0a2wu8qu5g9nq&quot;&amp;gt;https://cardanoscan.io/address/addr1q8g77agasft90nnrln487665tf4nz9tt0z9df0l5z637yavnfrlkaatu28n0qzmqh7f2cpksxhpc9jefx3wrl0a2wu8qu5g9nq&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; was an exchange account since it was unstaked and had nearly a billion ADA. My thinking was that if exchanges are willing to screw over customers by withholding withdrawals for a few days to make it to the next reward epoch, then they would not leave a billion unstaked. Based on that and given that this huge, unstaked wallet was tied to IOHK in a dozen large transactions, I made the claim that Charles was involved in the front-running of Sundae.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I apologize to Charles for jumping to that conclusion. I hope that IOHK will confirm that &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cardanoscan.io/address/addr1q8g77agasft90nnrln487665tf4nz9tt0z9df0l5z637yavnfrlkaatu28n0qzmqh7f2cpksxhpc9jefx3wrl0a2wu8qu5g9nq&quot;&amp;gt;https://cardanoscan.io/address/addr1q8g77agasft90nnrln487665tf4nz9tt0z9df0l5z637yavnfrlkaatu28n0qzmqh7f2cpksxhpc9jefx3wrl0a2wu8qu5g9nq&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; is indeed a Coinbase address. I would ask IOHK to also consider stating whether IOHK funds are being held at this address, as was done in 2017 when IOHK disclosed its original address (&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://iohk.io/en/blog/posts/2017/10/17/statement-on-iohks-ada-holdings/&quot;&amp;gt;https://iohk.io/en/blog/posts/2017/10/17/statement-on-iohks-ada-holdings/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;). That would explain the transaction path that led from IOHK’s 2017 address to the billion ADA unstaked wallet.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Secondly, I would also like to apologize to anyone who read and engaged with any of the posts I had made. Some of you spent time wrestling with the decision of whether to sell your ADA  based on the allegations I made. Some of you spent time debating with me as to whether the transactions were IOHK’s. Some of you spent time correcting my misunderstanding of reading UTXO’s. I’ve fixed the mistakes in the edited post regarding change addresses, but you spent more time than you would have had to if I had just made sure I had understood how to read UTXOs properly before posting what I posted. I apologize for wasting all of your time and causing a scare to those who considered selling.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Whether I end up being correct regarding the transactions being IOHK’s transactions is irrelevant. I made these posts in bad faith and without doing my due diligence. I was not trying to make anything up. When writing the post, I genuinely believed that the transactions listed were IOHK’s/Charles’ transactions and I genuinely believed that large, unstaked address could not have been an exchange wallet. I still believe that the transactions are IOHK’s, and I believe that when IOHK comes out with a statement, then that address will be a Coinbase address with IOHK funds. However, the post was in bad faith. My intention was never to save people from a scam coin or point out some wrong I felt had been committed. It was to reduce people’s trust in Cardano. I had not participated in the SundaeSwap launch, so I was not affected by any front-running or even cared to know who was involved in it. Those of you who called me out on bad faith motivations were correct on that point.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If IOHK confirms that the large, unstaked address is a Coinbase address, then some good may come out of this. If it becomes public knowledge that either Ae2tdPwUPEZ6xYrxCgRDM2NQFM5oajHEoJN3i9ZVV2AbsbvxoJBjVu3yP7W or addr1q8g77agasft90nnrln487665tf4nz9tt0z9df0l5z637yavnfrlkaatu28n0qzmqh7f2cpksxhpc9jefx3wrl0a2wu8qu5g9nq is a Coinbase address, then that allows some victims of scammers to report ADA scams to the authorities and/or Coinbase knowing that this is a Coinbase address. For example, here are some reports of scams with that address: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://forum.cardano.org/t/report-a-youtube-fraud-give-away-scam-video/41265/64?page=4&quot;&amp;gt;https://forum.cardano.org/t/report-a-youtube-fraud-give-away-scam-video/41265/64?page=4&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/monivong_eth/status/1448744468417441819&quot;&amp;gt;https://twitter.com/monivong_eth/status/1448744468417441819&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/cardano/comments/sp8e96/what_happened_to_my_ada/&quot;&amp;gt;https://np.reddit.com/r/cardano/comments/sp8e96/what_happened_to_my_ada/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; (&amp;lt;a href=&quot;/u/zujizu&quot;&amp;gt;u/zujizu&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you’re a victim of a scam and you see your money going to the Coinbase address, you’ll now be able to contact Coinbase as well as the FBI’s new crypto unit (&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/technology/fbi-form-new-digital-currency-unit-justice-dept-taps-new-crypto-czar-2022-02-17/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.reuters.com/technology/fbi-form-new-digital-currency-unit-justice-dept-taps-new-crypto-czar-2022-02-17/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;) knowing that Coinbase would be able to KYC the scammers and hopefully get your ADA back.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, anyone who was concerned about the Sundae Swap front-running transaction can report it to the SEC knowing that Coinbase would be able to KYC it as well. The transactions to look at are &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cardanoscan.io/transaction/5e495b9d447d180f5748f9c660c71f16ec993e0fd9afbdaef3ce33e357cb85ae&quot;&amp;gt;https://cardanoscan.io/transaction/5e495b9d447d180f5748f9c660c71f16ec993e0fd9afbdaef3ce33e357cb85ae&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cardanoscan.io/transaction/b7418577cb7265c7a986595d57b9ae9b355b4e51dfda400e1bb0732ae6cca48f&quot;&amp;gt;https://cardanoscan.io/transaction/b7418577cb7265c7a986595d57b9ae9b355b4e51dfda400e1bb0732ae6cca48f&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. The addresses in question are addr1qxu7ja9hduaqllh08qddamckewlhxf06vaansaacgcw864qwq3wh8ycd3n4ulgmjsd7yg99dexmrjn5jvq02zndyl53sgu4pen and addr1qxw876l6pafu63z25muwvzt7fgjf9l7qtfmh4j5dq0v44xhtj5fxf9czefjucs9nkmlyrkuguj0rdll0knagj9wull7qh79w83, with the second one being directly tied to the front-running. If Coinbase owns the address ending in 5g9nq, then they can figure out who sent transfers to either the address ending in u4pen or 79w83. Coinbase isn’t going to investigate this without a formal official inquiry, so if you care about finding out who it is, you’ll have to submit a tip to probably the SEC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This will be my last post on Cardano. Again, I apologize for wasting everyone&amp;amp;#39;s time this past week.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TLDR: I apologize to Charles and anyone who was scared, angered, or frustrated by my sensationalist posts regarding Charles’ alleged involvement in the front running of Sundae Swap.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The entire Moscow exchange is offline.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The entire Moscow exchange is offline.

They halted all trades within. Even there main portal is completely offline.
Probably also targeted by Anonymous in their effort to DDOS all state websites.
https://www.moex.com/en/

We are witnissing the greatest downfall in the history of the russian…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2oit3/the_entire_moscow_exchange_is_offline/?score=1558&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2oit3%2Fthe_entire_moscow_exchange_is_offline%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2oit3%2Fthe_entire_moscow_exchange_is_offline%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2oit3/the_entire_moscow_exchange_is_offline/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 15:36:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The entire Moscow exchange is offline.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They halted all trades within. Even there main portal is completely offline. Probably also targeted by Anonymous in their effort to DDOS all state websites.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.moex.com/en/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.moex.com/en/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We are witnissing the greatest downfall in the history of the russian economy. They just don&amp;amp;#39;t know it yet.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;People in Moscow are running for the bank. They placed a maximum withdrawel of $20 to not loose solvency. The russian population is starting to see what&amp;amp;#39;s happening.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Putin played stupid games and won stupid prizes.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Think twice ...everything is not what it seems to be on tv https://t.co/NvoqviokYK]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1497885178936672258/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1497885178936672258/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 12:46:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Disappointed to see that Bitcoin has been plotted on the left vs. right paradigm. Guess this is what happens when we hit the mainstream stage of adoption.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t2inba/disappointed_to_see_that_bitcoin_has_been_plotted/?score=379&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft2inba%2Fdisappointed_to_see_that_bitcoin_has_been_plotted%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft2inba%2Fdisappointed_to_see_that_bitcoin_has_been_plotted%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t2inba/disappointed_to_see_that_bitcoin_has_been_plotted/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 12:45:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Russians have found out about the sanctions and the SWIFT ban. A Bank Run seems to have begun.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t2lj0r/russians_have_found_out_about_the_sanctions_and/?score=752&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft2lj0r%2Frussians_have_found_out_about_the_sanctions_and%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft2lj0r%2Frussians_have_found_out_about_the_sanctions_and%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t2lj0r/russians_have_found_out_about_the_sanctions_and/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 12:45:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Don’t underestimate stablecoins. Those 20% APYs hit pile up fast.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I see a lot of people (especially beginners) disregard stablecoins as a good
investment just cause the price doesn’t change.

This couldn't be farther away from the truth as the true power in stablecoins in
yield farming. Some platforms like Nacho [https://nachoxyz.com/] and…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2gry8/dont_underestimate_stablecoins_those_20_apys_hit/?score=342&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2gry8%2Fdont_underestimate_stablecoins_those_20_apys_hit%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2gry8%2Fdont_underestimate_stablecoins_those_20_apys_hit%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2gry8/dont_underestimate_stablecoins_those_20_apys_hit/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 11:32:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I see a lot of people (especially beginners) disregard stablecoins as a good investment just cause the price doesn’t change.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This couldn&amp;amp;#39;t be farther away from the truth as the true power in stablecoins in yield farming. Some platforms like &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://nachoxyz.com/&quot;&amp;gt;Nacho&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://beefy.finance/&quot;&amp;gt;Beefy&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; offer very high APYs. Some even like Yield App offer near 20% on USDC and USDT.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I think stable and sustainable profits always defeat improbable ones for a memecoin where the probability of actually making profit is very low compared to that of DeFi where profits are ensured even if the whole market dips.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kyiv: full consensus for disconnecting Russia from SWIFT has been achieved, the process has begun]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t25byw/kyiv_full_consensus_for_disconnecting_russia_from/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft25byw%2Fkyiv_full_consensus_for_disconnecting_russia_from%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft25byw%2Fkyiv_full_consensus_for_disconnecting_russia_from%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t25byw/kyiv_full_consensus_for_disconnecting_russia_from/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 10:39:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ukraine Tweeted Its Crypto Wallet, And Got $4 Million In Donations To Help Fight Russia]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2dqbx/ukraine_tweeted_its_crypto_wallet_and_got_4/?score=378&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2dqbx%2Fukraine_tweeted_its_crypto_wallet_and_got_4%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2dqbx%2Fukraine_tweeted_its_crypto_wallet_and_got_4%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2dqbx/ukraine_tweeted_its_crypto_wallet_and_got_4/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 10:39:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cash transactions in person are 100% decentralized, and are not on a public ledger. That's why drug dealers, and criminals use it over CC, debit, or cash app. Crypto is on a public ledger, and you can track it. Yet somehow, crypto is the bad guy.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Read all of it because it makes one good point here that everyone should
realize.

You can track Bitcoin on a public ledger. That's why when someone who got a few
million stolen from them can call the FBI, and they track the wallet waiting for
a transaction to pop up, and when it does...the person…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t27wfy/cash_transactions_in_person_are_100_decentralized/?score=325&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft27wfy%2Fcash_transactions_in_person_are_100_decentralized%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft27wfy%2Fcash_transactions_in_person_are_100_decentralized%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t27wfy/cash_transactions_in_person_are_100_decentralized/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 06:31:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Read all of it because it makes one good point here that everyone should realize. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can track Bitcoin on a public ledger.  That&amp;amp;#39;s why when someone who got a few million stolen from them can call the FBI, and they track the wallet waiting for a transaction to pop up, and when it does...the person gets nailed.        &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can&amp;amp;#39;t call the FBI, tell them 2M in cash was stolen from your safe, and have them wait for the criminal to spend some of it so they know his location. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Only dumb criminals get caught...like when someone is paying  $25,000,000 all cash for new condo complex in Hawaii.  That&amp;amp;#39;s when someone gets suspicious and calls the FBI.    That&amp;amp;#39;s pretty much the only time they can catch you in cash transaction....when someone calls them on you. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With a Bitcoin transaction, the probability of you being caught after stealing a wallet they are now keeping track of actually goes up.     Yeah, there&amp;amp;#39;s ways to unload it into different cryptos using an encrypted throwaway mobile that&amp;amp;#39;s not connected to you or anyone you know but it&amp;amp;#39;s actually a tedious process if you don&amp;amp;#39;t want to get caught.     Using &amp;amp;quot;stolen cash&amp;amp;quot; or using cash from illegal earnings is much much easier than using a stolen BTC wallet. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You use just $10 in Bitcoin from that wallet, and you can get nailed.       If you use a couple of $100 cash at a random store..  nobody is calling the FBI on you.  Because it&amp;amp;#39;s a normal everyday transaction. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So you can have 2M in stolen cash and just sit on that for life using little by little, doing lightweight money laundering that doesn&amp;amp;#39;t look too suspicious and nobody will suspect anything.     You can&amp;amp;#39;t sit on a stolen BTC wallet for life and use it little by little without jumping through fire hoops or paranoid about being caught everytime you use it. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That&amp;amp;#39;s the point I&amp;amp;#39;m trying to make.   They are lying to everyone about how dangerous BTC usage is.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My kid sucks at art. What’s the cheapest and easiest way to mint his art as NFTs?]]></title><description><![CDATA[My kid is a year and a half old. He sucks at art. Well, I mean his art looks
like a toddler made it. Which he kind of is, so it actually may be good for his
age. Fuck if I know.

The point is; I figure I’m sitting on a goldmine.

All the recent “art” looks like something I drew in Mario Paint over…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2d7r3/my_kid_sucks_at_art_whats_the_cheapest_and/?score=401&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2d7r3%2Fmy_kid_sucks_at_art_whats_the_cheapest_and%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft2d7r3%2Fmy_kid_sucks_at_art_whats_the_cheapest_and%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t2d7r3/my_kid_sucks_at_art_whats_the_cheapest_and/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 06:31:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My kid is a year and a half old. He sucks at art. Well, I mean his art looks like a toddler made it. Which he kind of is, so it actually may be good for his age. Fuck if I know. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The point is; I figure I’m sitting on a goldmine. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;All the recent “art” looks like something I drew in Mario Paint over two decades ago. I figure I mint my kid’s “art”, sell it as an NFT and retire next week. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m bullish on ETH so I figure that even if I set a floor price of 0.05 ETH, I’ll be rich down the road. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What’s the cheapest and best way to do this? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;I will only accept not financial advice&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Runs on Russian banks likely to start on Monday morning if SWIFT sanctions pass.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The solvency of most Russian banks will be at grave risk. The Ruble is in a
historic collapse, and their MOEX stocks can't sustain a drop further; it's down
60% in 90-days, all while Brent tops $100, which is crazy considering most of
the exchange is made of gas giants. Gold is acting…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t23jum/runs_on_russian_banks_likely_to_start_on_monday/?score=309&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft23jum%2Fruns_on_russian_banks_likely_to_start_on_monday%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft23jum%2Fruns_on_russian_banks_likely_to_start_on_monday%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t23jum/runs_on_russian_banks_likely_to_start_on_monday/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 06:31:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The solvency of most Russian banks will be at grave risk. The Ruble is in a historic collapse, and their MOEX stocks can&amp;amp;#39;t sustain a drop further; it&amp;amp;#39;s down 60% in 90-days, all while Brent tops $100, which is crazy considering most of the exchange is made of gas giants. Gold is acting counterintuitively as well, retreating from a feel-good faux spike. Russia&amp;amp;#39;s largest bank limited withdrawals to $20 yesterday. Apple Pay doesn&amp;amp;#39;t work after Apple removed banking support in Russia. Reports on the ground that most debit cards have been suspended. Reports credit cards have had their limits slashed 50% or more. And it&amp;amp;#39;s only been 24 hours...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What happens in the next 72-hours will in my opinion lay the groundwork for bitcoin&amp;amp;#39;s next violent uptrend.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BBC NEWS: Millions in Bitcoin pouring into Ukraine from donors. At least $11m (£8.2m) has so far been donated to the Ukrainian war effort through anonymous Bitcoin donations. More than 4,000 donations have been made so far, with one unknown donor gifting Bitcoin worth $3m to an NGO.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t298o8/bbc_news_millions_in_bitcoin_pouring_into_ukraine/?score=307&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft298o8%2Fbbc_news_millions_in_bitcoin_pouring_into_ukraine%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft298o8%2Fbbc_news_millions_in_bitcoin_pouring_into_ukraine%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t298o8/bbc_news_millions_in_bitcoin_pouring_into_ukraine/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 04:44:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[No one can stop Bitcoin]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t2bgle/no_one_can_stop_bitcoin/?score=390&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft2bgle%2Fno_one_can_stop_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft2bgle%2Fno_one_can_stop_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t2bgle/no_one_can_stop_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 04:44:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[There is no way to stop Bitcoin!]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t246dw/there_is_no_way_to_stop_bitcoin/?score=322&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft246dw%2Fthere_is_no_way_to_stop_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft246dw%2Fthere_is_no_way_to_stop_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t246dw/there_is_no_way_to_stop_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 02:43:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Woops. turns out the RNA from Pfizer vaccine is rapidly reverse transcribed into DNA in as fast as 6 hours! But don't worry, it's in vitro, I'm sure in vivo they must have studied it and everything's just fine ... right? 🤨 https://t.co/ThP87iIUTl]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1497733849111044105/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1497733849111044105/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 01:06:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I'm u/vladimir-putin, and I'm asking you to donate your crypto to Ukraine if you can.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ukraine has published official addresses
[https://twitter.com/Ukraine/status/1497594592438497282?s=20&t=qrsqUrPZKkiucJYWRC54-A]
to accept donations for much needed supplies. Please, I'm asking you all to dig
deep into your wallets and donate whatever you can.

Those of you who've been around the…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t26b00/im_uvladimirputin_and_im_asking_you_to_donate/?score=519&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft26b00%2Fim_uvladimirputin_and_im_asking_you_to_donate%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft26b00%2Fim_uvladimirputin_and_im_asking_you_to_donate%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t26b00/im_uvladimirputin_and_im_asking_you_to_donate/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 23:35:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Ukraine has &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Ukraine/status/1497594592438497282?s=20&amp;amp;amp;t=qrsqUrPZKkiucJYWRC54-A&quot;&amp;gt;published official addresses&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; to accept donations for much needed supplies. Please, I&amp;amp;#39;m asking you all to dig deep into your wallets and donate whatever you can. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Those of you who&amp;amp;#39;ve been around  the crypto space for a long time will remember when donations to good causes were lauded in the community as a way to grow the footprint of cryptocurrency as a way to transfer wealth across borders. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Right now, we should all invoke that same community giving mentality and put our Satoshis where our thoughts and prayers are. Dig deep, send what you can, and lets show the world why cryptocurrency is the future of finance. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you&amp;amp;#39;re a miner, point your rewards to Ukraine, if you&amp;amp;#39;re staking, stake in the name of Ukraine, if you&amp;amp;#39;re a hodler let your grip ease up in the name of a free and independent Ukraine. There is no middle-man here. Ukraine has official wallet addresses to accept donations. This is what crypto was made to be used for-- So lets use it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Note: If you do donate, please send the Transx # in the comments below along with an indication of the country you are from so your fellow crypto enthusiasts can give some love.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Proof of my identity &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/O65vPSy&quot;&amp;gt;can be found here.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ukrainian Government Is Seeking Crypto Donations. The official Twitter accounts of the Ukrainian government provided wallet addresses for donations of bitcoin (BTC), ethereum (ETH) and the stablecoin tether (USDT).]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t22wyg/ukrainian_government_is_seeking_crypto_donations/?score=409&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft22wyg%2Fukrainian_government_is_seeking_crypto_donations%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft22wyg%2Fukrainian_government_is_seeking_crypto_donations%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t22wyg/ukrainian_government_is_seeking_crypto_donations/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 23:35:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WATCH: Bitcoin Can Be Used For Cyber Defense Says Michael Saylor. Meanwhile Ukraine Receives Over $4 Million in Bitcoin For War Defense. Even Putin Can't Stop Bitcoin.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t23rze/watch_bitcoin_can_be_used_for_cyber_defense_says/?score=573&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft23rze%2Fwatch_bitcoin_can_be_used_for_cyber_defense_says%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft23rze%2Fwatch_bitcoin_can_be_used_for_cyber_defense_says%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t23rze/watch_bitcoin_can_be_used_for_cyber_defense_says/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 23:35:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Macro Narrative Of #Bitcoin

@100trillionUSD and @TimmerFidelity cover:

- The next phase of Bitcoin adoption
- Bond market manipulation
- Equity market outlook
- How to value Bitcoin
- Fed’s rate policy

Apple: https://t.co/mJnnMHS37f
Spotify: https://t.co/0lfw5u6vuZ https://t.co/CEFRmu2M8b]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1497177756953628678/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1497177756953628678/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 22:43:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA['50% of transactions were fraudulent' when Steam accepted Bitcoin for payments, says Gabe Newell]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t20rn7/50_of_transactions_were_fraudulent_when_steam/?score=356&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft20rn7%2F50_of_transactions_were_fraudulent_when_steam%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft20rn7%2F50_of_transactions_were_fraudulent_when_steam%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t20rn7/50_of_transactions_were_fraudulent_when_steam/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 21:32:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Vitalik Tweets To Be Careful Donating Crypto Without Verification]]></title><description><![CDATA[UPDATE:

The wallet addresses has been verified and confirmed to be legit, but as always
- Be careful when sending crypto, since transactions are irreversible



https://etherscan.io/address/0x165CD37b4C644C2921454429E7F9358d18A45e14 - The
Wallet Address has also been tagged by Etherscan as…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t20iz5/vitalik_tweets_to_be_careful_donating_crypto/?score=387&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft20iz5%2Fvitalik_tweets_to_be_careful_donating_crypto%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft20iz5%2Fvitalik_tweets_to_be_careful_donating_crypto%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t20iz5/vitalik_tweets_to_be_careful_donating_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 21:32:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;UPDATE:&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The wallet addresses has been verified and confirmed to be legit, but as always - Be careful when sending crypto, since transactions are irreversible&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://etherscan.io/address/0x165CD37b4C644C2921454429E7F9358d18A45e14&quot;&amp;gt;https://etherscan.io/address/0x165CD37b4C644C2921454429E7F9358d18A45e14&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;  - The Wallet Address has also been tagged by Etherscan as legit&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/s3crqk4qi7k81.png?width=596&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=36016d16d45279cab014c4d3f27decb30de26ec4&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/s3crqk4qi7k81.png?width=596&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=36016d16d45279cab014c4d3f27decb30de26ec4&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Transcript:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To follow up on &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/VitalikButerin&quot;&amp;gt;@VitalikButerin&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#39;s tweet, I&amp;amp;#39;ve confirmed directly with Ukrainian Ambassador &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/olex_scherba&quot;&amp;gt;@olex_scherba&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;that the addresses are correct and in the control of the Ukrainian govt. Give!!! Defending free and open societies may be the best thing we ever do with our BTC and ETH...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/zg4y9w88i7k81.png?width=597&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=fa207e2c97d2ec9e77a279aaa65eb89da16db3c5&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/zg4y9w88i7k81.png?width=597&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=fa207e2c97d2ec9e77a279aaa65eb89da16db3c5&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Transcript:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Getting some confirmations from a couple sources that it&amp;amp;#39;s legit. Deleting my warning for now. But continue to be vigilant, and always be slow and careful when sending irreversible crypto transactions.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/5mou191v87k81.png?width=598&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=7a5340f04a138f3d3e7407714a4c5e185de155bb&quot;&amp;gt;TL;DR Don&amp;amp;#39;t Trust, but Verify&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Transcript:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please DO NOT send BTC/ETH/USDT to that address in the tweet from the Ukraine account without verification. There have been *a lot* of hacks alongside this invasion, this could easily be a hack.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This info environment is as hostile as it gets, exercise extreme vigilance.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Looking at this it was obvious Vitalik was pointing on these tweets&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/hcqnk38s97k81.png?width=599&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=81fd17e3822516ed8a040db4cd89bf6e88896dbf&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/hcqnk38s97k81.png?width=599&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=81fd17e3822516ed8a040db4cd89bf6e88896dbf&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/os09vhv2a7k81.png?width=598&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=a71cffb31b79d216e6817bd2d8ed9f53dd1d7203&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/os09vhv2a7k81.png?width=598&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=a71cffb31b79d216e6817bd2d8ed9f53dd1d7203&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Transcript:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Stand with the people of Ukraine. Now accepting cryptocurrency donations. Bitcoin, Ethereum and USDT.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;BTC - &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.blockchain.com/btc/address/357a3So9CbsNfBBgFYACGvxxS6tMaDoa1P&quot;&amp;gt;357a3So9CbsNfBBgFYACGvxxS6tMaDoa1P&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;ETH and USDT (ERC-20) - &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://etherscan.io/address/0x165CD37b4C644C2921454429E7F9358d18A45e14&quot;&amp;gt;0x165CD37b4C644C2921454429E7F9358d18A45e14&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; (and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://bscscan.com/address/0x165CD37b4C644C2921454429E7F9358d18A45e14&quot;&amp;gt;BSC Scan&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As always, be careful when sending donations in crypto, since it&amp;amp;#39;s really hard to verify the owners of crypto wallets without much proof&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Famous porn star compares her NFT scam to Russia invading Ukraine]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t1qnll/famous_porn_star_compares_her_nft_scam_to_russia/?score=313&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft1qnll%2Ffamous_porn_star_compares_her_nft_scam_to_russia%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft1qnll%2Ffamous_porn_star_compares_her_nft_scam_to_russia%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t1qnll/famous_porn_star_compares_her_nft_scam_to_russia/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 19:31:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Official Ukraine Twitter just tweeted this]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t21gof/official_ukraine_twitter_just_tweeted_this/?score=1028&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft21gof%2Fofficial_ukraine_twitter_just_tweeted_this%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft21gof%2Fofficial_ukraine_twitter_just_tweeted_this%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t21gof/official_ukraine_twitter_just_tweeted_this/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 19:31:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[An NFTs game project Pixelmon raised over $70 Million at 3 ETH per mint just to reveal NFTs that look like they were designed by a 5 year old. Currently it's trending on Twitter hashtag "3 ETH"]]></title><description><![CDATA[This whole project was a cash grab. They tweeted their NFT project will be 3D
characters which will be interactable. Well take a look at 3D modeled NFTs.

Worth 3 ETH
[https://preview.redd.it/ym536tcv46k81.jpg?width=976&format=pjpg&auto=webp&s=f137a96c705061038f7e94ae94c7ece89a05da9b]

Bored…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t1vs4y/an_nfts_game_project_pixelmon_raised_over_70/?score=418&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft1vs4y%2Fan_nfts_game_project_pixelmon_raised_over_70%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft1vs4y%2Fan_nfts_game_project_pixelmon_raised_over_70%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t1vs4y/an_nfts_game_project_pixelmon_raised_over_70/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 18:30:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This whole project was a cash grab. They tweeted their NFT project will be 3D characters which will be interactable. Well take a look at 3D modeled NFTs.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ym536tcv46k81.jpg?width=976&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=f137a96c705061038f7e94ae94c7ece89a05da9b&quot;&amp;gt;Worth 3 ETH&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/cs7qnuux46k81.jpg?width=975&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=82d5ba9abddbd5b9489fa00f17e0f88dc3a300f3&quot;&amp;gt;Bored ape?&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/um9w30g056k81.jpg?width=482&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=be179530458fc92856ce2f76561506eb314bdd63&quot;&amp;gt;I don&amp;amp;#39;t know what the hell is this.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/f4b9hb5w56k81.jpg?width=482&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9fb3f177a91f83ced9892349ec4944a58179c7a9&quot;&amp;gt;I wouldn&amp;amp;#39;t pay 1 penny for this. &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;People on Discord mentioned one of the devs wallet went on buying spree of other NFTs after receiving 400 ETH from multisig.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/sr7sgzih56k81.jpg?width=2184&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9d570ce768925fb5783d98712a943b1a2f621a24&quot;&amp;gt;Dev Wallet&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here&amp;amp;#39;s their twitter handle: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Pixelmon&quot;&amp;gt;https://twitter.com/Pixelmon&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Whole thread if you want to read more: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1497370216690503687&quot;&amp;gt;https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1497370216690503687&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I have told them to buy Bitcoin but a few of them listen to me that time]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t1vjxp/i_have_told_them_to_buy_bitcoin_but_a_few_of_them/?score=328&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft1vjxp%2Fi_have_told_them_to_buy_bitcoin_but_a_few_of_them%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft1vjxp%2Fi_have_told_them_to_buy_bitcoin_but_a_few_of_them%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t1vjxp/i_have_told_them_to_buy_bitcoin_but_a_few_of_them/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 18:30:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[''China Will Sentence Over 10 Years In Prison For Crypto Traders'' - This news shows us how afraid of crypto dictator countries are.]]></title><description><![CDATA[They're shitting their pants. They are afraid of losing their power over their
citizens. They are afraid of crypto because they know crypto gives freedom to
the people. So they ban it.

Whenever I see a news about a dictator country banning crypto, I feel so bullish
because if dictator countries…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t1cr4u/china_will_sentence_over_10_years_in_prison_for/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft1cr4u%2Fchina_will_sentence_over_10_years_in_prison_for%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft1cr4u%2Fchina_will_sentence_over_10_years_in_prison_for%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t1cr4u/china_will_sentence_over_10_years_in_prison_for/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 16:31:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They&amp;amp;#39;re shitting their pants. They are afraid of losing their power over their citizens. They are afraid of crypto because they know crypto gives freedom to the people. So they ban it. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Whenever I see a news about a dictator country banning crypto, I feel so bullish because if dictator countries hate crypto that means Crypto works as it should. Because they can&amp;amp;#39;t control it. They are afraid of losing their power on their citizens. This is exactly what crypto is supposed to be, giving 100% control to people. Peer 2 peer. There is no middle man. There is no control freak authority. This is what decentralization is supposed to be and dictators hate that. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If a dictatorial country is trying to ban crypto, know that Crypto is on the right track.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;No matter how much those dictators try to ban it, Crypto is INEVITABLE.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Price at which all ~19M #Bitcoin last transacted.

3 cluster:
- Current cycle: 9M BTC &gt;$20K
- 2017 ATH &amp; aftermath: 5.5M BTC &lt; $20K
- Early BTC history (2009-2016): 4.5M BTC &lt; $2K (most probably lost, incl 1M Satoshi coins) https://t.co/CYakNX6XH2]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1497582404554219524/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1497582404554219524/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 15:43:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bitcoin is up - Gold is down]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t1jksp/bitcoin_is_up_gold_is_down/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft1jksp%2Fbitcoin_is_up_gold_is_down%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft1jksp%2Fbitcoin_is_up_gold_is_down%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t1jksp/bitcoin_is_up_gold_is_down/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 15:43:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[You can’t cry for decentralization and then cry that Russia is leaning on crypto to bypass sanctions.]]></title><description><![CDATA[It just doesn’t work like that. It’s either decentralized or it’s not. You don’t
get to pick and choose when or why it’s decentralized just because you don’t
agree with the use case.

Obviously, it sucks that psychopaths take to crypto to hide illicit activity,
and that it gets publicized in a way…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t1x698/you_cant_cry_for_decentralization_and_then_cry/?score=467&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft1x698%2Fyou_cant_cry_for_decentralization_and_then_cry%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft1x698%2Fyou_cant_cry_for_decentralization_and_then_cry%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t1x698/you_cant_cry_for_decentralization_and_then_cry/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 15:43:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It just doesn’t work like that. It’s either decentralized or it’s not. You don’t get to pick and choose when or why it’s decentralized just because you don’t agree with the use case. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Obviously, it sucks that psychopaths take to crypto to hide illicit activity, and that it gets publicized in a way that paints crypto in a bad light. But if we want crypto to maintain its autonomous decentralization, we have to accept all of its shortcomings. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto scares the shit out of the powers that be for all the reasons we love it. It gives power back to the people, unfortunately there&amp;amp;#39;s bad people out there and fear sells, so the media likes to focus on it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I don’t agree with anything that’s going on in Russia right now, but I do believe in crypto maintaining its decentralization.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a 100x here then you’re searching in the wrong place. Once you’ve read about it here, your 100x is long gone.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Almost all 100x picks are by complete luck. It doesn’t matter how good or
technically advanced the project is (as we’ve seen with zero utility coins like
Doge and Shib).

Once a project has already gained popularity on subreddits like this one, it’s
almost certain that you already missed out on a…]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t1us43/if_youre_looking_for_a_100x_here_then_youre/?score=328&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft1us43%2Fif_youre_looking_for_a_100x_here_then_youre%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft1us43%2Fif_youre_looking_for_a_100x_here_then_youre%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t1us43/if_youre_looking_for_a_100x_here_then_youre/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 14:38:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Almost all 100x picks are by complete luck. It doesn’t matter how good or technically advanced the project is (as we’ve seen with zero utility coins like Doge and Shib).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Once a project has already gained popularity on subreddits like this one, it’s almost certain that you already missed out on a 100x&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This doesn’t mean you still can’t profit from popular coins on this sub. But don’t expect 4 digit % gains.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The problem is that investing in still unpopular startups could be very risky. You risk rug pulls or scams since this market is completely unregulated.
And while there are exceptions with projects with insurance backing like Solanaprime and others that can mitigate such risks, for the most part it will be risky otherwise.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The important thing is to not get impulsive and let FOMO take control over you. Always make educated guesses and well thought out investments. This is the only reliable way to make profit long term.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What could be more powerful than this? Kudos to Bitcoin!]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t1vx50/what_could_be_more_powerful_than_this_kudos_to/?score=662&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft1vx50%2Fwhat_could_be_more_powerful_than_this_kudos_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft1vx50%2Fwhat_could_be_more_powerful_than_this_kudos_to%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t1vx50/what_could_be_more_powerful_than_this_kudos_to/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 14:38:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The first city in the world to be heated by #bitcoin mining.

North Vancouver's local energy utility company announced it was partnering with MintGreen to create heat for the city using renewable energy and #bitcoin mining. ♻️

https://t.co/ocycRy3GxH]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1497563137985458179/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/en/tweet/1497563137985458179/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 13:43:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>