<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[加密货币国外热门讨论]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 13:59:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[#比特币月度RSI低于50，且低于ATH（绿色）~50% https://t.co/dcIwfvFiIa]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1523628585616953346/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1523628585616953346/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 12:44:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[再次重申我在2022年底2023年初的40万美元的价格目标。这里是我如此坚持的真正原因。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在几周前写了这篇文章，讨论为什么改变2,100万的硬上限
在未来是完全不相关的。其原因是，假设
比特币成功地成为诚实透明的基础层，而我们非常需要
来取代不诚实的法币/债务基础层--...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uli4dc/reiterating_my_400k_late_2022_early_2023_price/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuli4dc%2Freiterating_my_400k_late_2022_early_2023_price%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuli4dc%2Freiterating_my_400k_late_2022_early_2023_price%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uli4dc/reiterating_my_400k_late_2022_early_2023_price/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 12:44:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I authored this post a few weeks back discussing why changing the 21M hard cap is completely irrelevant in the future. The reason for that is because assuming bitcoin successfully becomes the honest transparent base layer that we need so desperately to replace the dishonest fiat/debt base layer--which nothing built over can ever achieve honesty--then changing the 21M hard cap would simply cause everything outside the money (products, services, credit markets) to adjust to the new block subsidy and BTC float. Thusly, the incentive to change it doesn&amp;amp;#39;t exist. This was really more of a refutation of FUD &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;(But the limit can be changed!)&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; and thought experiment than it was any probability.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I based this on economics 101, and more closely, on bitcoin mining. If for example, bitcoin spiked to $100k tomorrow, what would happen? Would an ASIC stay at the price it is today, which is about $10k for an S19j? No. It would increase roughly by whatever the BTC price increase is and then price itself with the next difficulty adjustment and current hashpower, along with the price entropy associated with an always approaching halving. I&amp;amp;#39;ve noticed that when you include this stuff, mining has actually consistently beaten my spot BTC buys over the long run by a few percent.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So this all figures into my $400k price call. If you got a $100k spike tomorrow, would BTC maintain itself there? Absolutely not, because that would be at odds with everything rational to do with money. Why? Because efficient miners would be sitting there making $80k per BTC. Their BTC stockpiles would be worth a tremendous amount. ASIC owners would be sitting there with insane hardware appreciation. What do you think happens here? Same thing that eventually happens in every commodity market over time--the gap would get closed, arbitraged, miners would do huge share offerings, even I&amp;amp;#39;d sell my S19&amp;amp;#39;s, the difficulty adjustment would rocket, every student with a laptop would be syphoning their dorm and library&amp;amp;#39;s free electricity to mine. The price would drawdown, because we are very early in BTC&amp;amp;#39;s monetization phase.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But before you freak out, here&amp;amp;#39;s what bears always forget:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are two sides to that. This holds true for not just the move up, but the move down as well. So when you have baseload energy prices along the lines of &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;$8 per cubic foot&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; or &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;$110 per barrel&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;, you have hashpower increasing relentlessly, difficulty adjustments going up, constrained supply chains and miners HODLing, how long can the price stay depressed? Not long. That would be at odds with everything rational to do with money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Look at the major miners. Are they selling? Nope. Decreasing their hashpower. Nope. Read their 10k&amp;amp;#39;s. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/u/Riotblockchain&quot;&amp;gt;u/Riotblockchain&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; is active on this sub and they just announced in a post last week a 1GW expansion, literally at the same moment the press dropped elsewhere. Here&amp;amp;#39;s all the US majors plans 2022:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/rgxttjcv6dy81.png?width=649&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=193bcf52457e106096140dccb78ea17488189685&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/rgxttjcv6dy81.png?width=649&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=193bcf52457e106096140dccb78ea17488189685&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;THAT. IS. JAW-DROPPING.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; This to me says a 10x is likely the peak which also happens to be about gold&amp;amp;#39;s market capitalization give or take. Will it hold? Absolutely not, probably a drawdown of 50%-60% like we see currently. Bitcoin doesn&amp;amp;#39;t target a stable price, it targets a variable price. It can control the supply and issuance, then the market determines what the price is. That&amp;amp;#39;s what a free market looks like. Bitcoin is in the long, difficult, and organic process of absorbing the world&amp;amp;#39;s trust (and thus its value). When it&amp;amp;#39;s absorbed enough, the confidence curve (and thus its volatility) will flatten. Many projects think they can magically skip this step. There&amp;amp;#39;s only one crypto category that can: stablecoins. That&amp;amp;#39;s why nothing inside altcoin protocols have ever established themselves as money, except stablecoins. Which is why 85% of all altcoin volume is from stablecoins--a percentage that is growing monthly. You ever look at the graph of stablecoin growth? At this rate it&amp;amp;#39;ll be bitcoin at #1 and stablecoins making up the next 4 spots in 5 years. If you add bitcoin&amp;amp;#39;s mkt cap dominance with the mkt caps of stablecoins, you get 74%. But there are 15,000 altcoins... Talk about an example of &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Gresham&amp;amp;#39;s Law.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; This is why you don&amp;amp;#39;t touch anything but bitcoin, because here&amp;amp;#39;s another prediction:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Fiat trouble is climbing the ladder from small to mid, and might now be just reaching the Japanese Yen already. There are many currencies which are more volatile than BTC. This WILL reach the USD&amp;amp;#39;s rung in the next 24 months. When that happens a credit market will rapidly develop around BTC, and also, stablecoins are in a world of trouble in the shadow of BTC&amp;amp;#39;s next halving, and altcoins are in even more trouble. Entire protocols can get completely de-collateralized when stablecoins wobble on their pegs and arbitrageurs are nowhere to be found, because volume spikes will make transactions unaffordable, and because bitcoin will emerge as collateral. And collateral is money, as we&amp;amp;#39;re starting to rapidly learn with the Ukraine crisis and commodities. This more than regulation in my opinion, will be the s-curve adoption shakeout we&amp;amp;#39;ve been waiting for, much to the chagrin of the web 3 shills--apologies if you&amp;amp;#39;re a holder of these things with mega-lottery environments built around them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This post is written as a chicken-noodle soup of sorts for the BTC holder&amp;amp;#39;s soul, because volatility is hard to digest especially for noobs, but counterintuitively, it proves BTC is working, and it makes hedging quite expensive, which brings its own protective benefits in this free market. So you HODL, buy, repeat. You listen to the heartbeat of the only truly free market asset in existence, and ignore the mainstream talking points. Bitcoin&amp;amp;#39;s longterm chart is a tale of highs and lows. But between that is a relentless and healthy uptrend. Why is that? Thanks for reading.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;--Mallardshead 🦆&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[解放思想 https://t.co/Jg0qNDePXX]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1522301647493414912/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1522301647493414912/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 10:45:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[最后在0.01个硬币的]]></title><description><![CDATA[一直在享受浸泡，使我的平均水平下降。终于达到了1/100
的硬币。我知道这不是一个大数目，但对我来说是一个很大的里程碑。

只是想分享一下 :)]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uli5dl/finally_at_001_of_a_coin/?score=394&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuli5dl%2Ffinally_at_001_of_a_coin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuli5dl%2Ffinally_at_001_of_a_coin%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uli5dl/finally_at_001_of_a_coin/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 10:45:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Been enjoying the dip and bringing my average down. Finally made it to 1/100th of a coin. I know it’s not a huge amount, but it’s a big milestone for me.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just wanted to share :)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币跌至2.7美元一个。很高兴我没有买入那场混乱。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1523579725364740096/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1523579725364740096/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 08:40:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在全球范围内，实际上有大量未使用的绿色电力过剩，它实际上并不稀缺。而#比特币可以在任何地方被开采。如果他们接受这项业务，他们可以再投资建设更多的绿色电力，或者再投资于当地的经济发展。https://t.co/Oco1w7AVeR]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1523565043115192320/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1523565043115192320/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 08:40:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果我在神秘的情况下死去，很高兴认识你。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1523573303616884736/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1523573303616884736/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 08:40:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[每个人都有这样的朋友...]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ul4hat/everyone_has_this_friend/?score=307&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ful4hat%2Feveryone_has_this_friend%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ful4hat%2Feveryone_has_this_friend%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ul4hat/everyone_has_this_friend/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 08:39:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一位前熊市参与者的一些建议]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在2016年很随意地进入了加密货币。以900美元买了2个BTC，以1000美元卖出
1000美元，并认为我是个天才。没有太认真地对待它。

在交易了一段时间后，做了更多的研究，我开始认为加密货币
可能有一个非常光明的未来。然后我在2017年的某一天醒来，BTC...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ulg72c/some_advice_from_a_previous_bear_market/?score=532&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fulg72c%2Fsome_advice_from_a_previous_bear_market%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fulg72c%2Fsome_advice_from_a_previous_bear_market%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ulg72c/some_advice_from_a_previous_bear_market/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 06:47:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I got into crypto in 2016 pretty casually. Bought 2 BTC for $900, sold them for $1000 and thought I was a genius. Didn’t take it too seriously. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After trading them for awhile and doing more research I started thinking crypto could have a really bright future. Then I woke up one day in 2017 and BTC was jumping to 2k. I frantically bought that morning with all the money I could spare. I could feel the FOMO coursing through the investment community. Bitcoin was national news and on CNBC everyday after being mostly ignored for years.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Shortly thereafter, it went to 19k and I was walking around town like a God amongst mortals. I told all my friends and family to buy some crypto. I begged them. I was so cocky I put 100% of my IRA account into GBTC at $29/share. Why not? BTC was going to the moon and there would be no detours along the way. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then I went to lunch a few days later, checked the price and it had dropped to 17k. No biggie, I thought, of course there needs to be a correction after this run up, it’ll bounce back. A few days later it was 15k. Okay, I thought, just some more profit taking by short term investors, this’ll stop soon and we’ll be at 30k in a month. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The next two months we’re a torturous gauntlet of small bounces of hope followed by spirit crushing dips, sleepless nights and poor mental health. I capitulated and sold half of my stack at 6k/BTC just so I could take a break from thinking about it and “get my old life back.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For the next 2 years I kept advocating for crypto and wishing it would rise as it became less and less relevant in the news once again. It bounced around 10k again for awhile and finally landed down at 3k during the Covid crash in March 2020. My GBTC position and my IRA was down 95% to $3/ share. I laughed to myself looking at the account balance on my screen and said out loud “Ha! Space cash?…What the fuck was I thinking?”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Of course we all know that was the start of the next bull market and we ended up at 68k. I DCA’ed every chance I could over that 2 year period and I ended up with about 50% more crypto as I had before I sold half in 2017. I still DCA today as we have drifted back down to 34k, a 50% drop from ATHs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The message and point of this story is:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Allowing myself to feel depressed or super excited about the price over the last 6 years has been a complete waste of my time. I could’ve just set an automatic recurring buy order my exchange account and gotten drunk or been in a coma and I’d be elated with the results right now if I had never checked the price. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The drop allowed me to increase my crypto position. Dollars or euros don’t matter, what matters is increasing your crypto stack. We all know it’s just a matter of time until it’s $680k/BTC. Guess what? It’ll probably drop to 340k then too. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is the crypto game. My story is not unique. Losing 50%+ of your money is a right of OG crypto hodler passage, so welcome to the club of this is your first time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hang in there.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币方舟]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ul3vuz/bitcoin_ark/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ful3vuz%2Fbitcoin_ark%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ful3vuz%2Fbitcoin_ark%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ul3vuz/bitcoin_ark/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 03:15:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我为比特币感到自豪。]]></title><description><![CDATA[听着，我在6.9万买入，我的投资组合至少可以说是下降了很多。但是
听听这个。

看看我们现在吧。我们现在的价格是每枚硬币3.5万。我们已经向世界证明了
去中心化货币的价值。看看其他每一次比特币达到顶峰，然后
然后它又下跌了。这也是一样的...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ul5yo7/im_proud_of_bitcoin/?score=317&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ful5yo7%2Fim_proud_of_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ful5yo7%2Fim_proud_of_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ul5yo7/im_proud_of_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 03:15:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Listen , I bought at 69k , and my portfolio is down a lot to say the least . But hear this :&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Look at us now . We are at 35 thousand per coin. We have proven to the world the value of decentralised money . Look at every other time bitcoin peaked , and then it went down after . This is just the same . However if our low this time is 35k , or even 30k , or even 20k .... how high do you think this thing is going to shoot up to if that&amp;amp;#39;s what we start from ?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Take it from me , i&amp;amp;#39;m at a major loss . Just be patient . Well done BTC , i&amp;amp;#39;m proud of you . Thank you for teaching me life lessons via this ride .&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[彼得得到了它!]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ul1ah6/peter_gets_it/?score=313&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ful1ah6%2Fpeter_gets_it%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ful1ah6%2Fpeter_gets_it%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ul1ah6/peter_gets_it/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 03:15:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[对于从2017年开始进入加密货币的人来说，我对它取得的成绩有点失望。]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好。

我真的以为我们现在至少会遇到一些更大的真实世界的使用情况。
但现在我们只有像DeFi Apps和NFT这样的庞氏骗局，它们吸走了所有的 "使用量"
和到处都是的模仿者。我真的以为加密货币会有更好的
影响力，或至少有一些有用的用途，有点......]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ul8z4r/for_being_into_crypto_since_2017_im_kinda/?score=473&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ful8z4r%2Ffor_being_into_crypto_since_2017_im_kinda%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ful8z4r%2Ffor_being_into_crypto_since_2017_im_kinda%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ul8z4r/for_being_into_crypto_since_2017_im_kinda/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 01:49:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hello all,&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I really thought we would encounter at least some greater real world usage by now, but atm we only have ponzi like DeFi Apps, NFT that suck all the &amp;amp;quot;usage&amp;amp;quot; and copycats all over the place. I seriously thought crypto would have a better impact by now or at least some useful usage, kinda disappointed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Most tokens feel so useless, a lot are just made for governance, but really how is that decentralized? A centralized system where everyone can only vote once is way more fair than a decentralized governance where the biggest whales dictate everything.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And if they are not only made for governance, they are made for staking/farming aka ponzi like tactics, which is very short term. Most of the DeFi apps can function well without the token and just use the native token they operate on, but the team behind it just wants to milk as much as possible so they create a token and give high APY to make it &amp;amp;quot;useful&amp;amp;quot;. High APY where they give the same token you stake is never going to end well. Don&amp;amp;#39;t ever hold these tokens long term.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then we have all the copycats. If you have one dApp or chain that&amp;amp;#39;s &amp;amp;quot;successful&amp;amp;quot;, everyone is copycatting it. Just look at the amount of EVM compatible smart contract chains, it&amp;amp;#39;s getting out of hand. Or STEPN which attracted a decent chunk of users, got copied straight after and so many more examples...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Pretty much all smart contact chains have the same dApps trying to milk every DeFi user there is. Most unique dApps still come from Ethereum and they all get copied to the cheaper chains.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto projects like STEPN are P2E games, all these games are made for short term. Enjoy the gains while it lasts, because the unlimited high emission is going to kill every P2E game. They also attract a TON of bots, so you pretty much are competing with perfect human like players.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then we have countries that are pretty much dictatorships that &amp;amp;quot;adopt&amp;amp;quot; bitcoin, while in reality they just buy bitcoin with the money they steal from their country. Statistics already show these countries aren&amp;amp;#39;t adopting bitcoin in anyway. Also very funny how you see a posts here in front page about some house being sold for BTC for the first time in a country. Like really? Bitcoin has been around for so long and we are proud because of one single private transaction? Lmao.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So really, what did crypto achieve that&amp;amp;#39;s really something to show off with? Curious to see others opinion.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[市场 rn]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ul8y4b/market_rn/?score=477&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ful8y4b%2Fmarket_rn%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ful8y4b%2Fmarket_rn%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ul8y4b/market_rn/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 01:49:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[什么是恶性通货膨胀？]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ulbijn/what_is_hyperinflation/?score=366&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fulbijn%2Fwhat_is_hyperinflation%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fulbijn%2Fwhat_is_hyperinflation%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ulbijn/what_is_hyperinflation/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 01:49:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BTC正式从历史最高点下降50%]]></title><description><![CDATA[比特币已从其ATH值下跌了50%。

对我来说，这是一个简单的买点，不一定是目前，但无论何时我买入，我都知道
随着时间的推移，我的钱将在未来翻倍，任何低于这个价格的购买
价格。很多替代币看起来也很诱人，但有一件事我已经学会了。
我学到的一点是，我宁愿...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ul6unv/btc_is_officially_down_50_from_all_time_high/?score=372&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ful6unv%2Fbtc_is_officially_down_50_from_all_time_high%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ful6unv%2Fbtc_is_officially_down_50_from_all_time_high%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ul6unv/btc_is_officially_down_50_from_all_time_high/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 22:30:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin has dropped 50% from its ATH&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For me this is an easy buy not necessarily currently but anytime I buy I know that with in time my money will double in the future on any buy below this price. Lots of altcoins out there looking very tempting as well, but one thing I have learned is Id rather have a large portion of my portfolio in BTC when things are on there way down. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is a time were you hold solid projects that you truly believe will succeed long term because it will take time for the market to recover. Fill your bags now&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[只是把这个留在这里]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ul4kgg/just_leaving_this_here/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ful4kgg%2Fjust_leaving_this_here%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ful4kgg%2Fjust_leaving_this_here%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ul4kgg/just_leaving_this_here/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 22:30:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你还在这里，还在购买，那么恭喜你，因为你是真正能通过加密货币获胜的一小部分人的一部分!]]></title><description><![CDATA[无论我们是继续上涨还是下跌（或只是吃几只螃蟹），我们都会有机会。
我们目前正处于市场阶段，在下一轮牛市中，所有的
新手都会看着图表说："如果我当时就知道了
币"。我自己在一开始就是这些人之一...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ul42ma/if_you_are_still_here_and_still_buying/?score=354&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ful42ma%2Fif_you_are_still_here_and_still_buying%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ful42ma%2Fif_you_are_still_here_and_still_buying%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ul42ma/if_you_are_still_here_and_still_buying/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 18:36:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Regardless of if we continue up or down from here ( or just crab for a couple years) we are currently in the market phase where during the next bull run all the newbies will look at the charts and say &amp;amp;quot;if only I would have know about crypto back then&amp;amp;quot;. I myself was one of those people at the start of the last bull run, and despite being late to the game my portfolio is still ~3x what it was when I started.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you are here now, and buying now, you have figured out the biggest trick in crypto, which is to buy when everyone says it&amp;amp;#39;s dead. Truly only a tiny fraction of people actually do this, so Pat yourself on the back for being one of them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That is all, see y&amp;amp;#39;all when the snakes are back from hibernation!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[到目前为止，你最糟糕的加密货币投资是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在夏天的时候被卷入了太多的代理，我已经留下了一些需要三倍才能接近他们的ATH的代理。
剩了一些需要用高音喇叭才能接近他们的ATH。我削减了一个
我在年初削减了一些，以购买一些BTC，这被证明是一个不错的主意。
考虑到大多数盟友的资金流向，这是一个不错的主意......]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uklsdj/what_is_your_worst_crypto_investment_to_date/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuklsdj%2Fwhat_is_your_worst_crypto_investment_to_date%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuklsdj%2Fwhat_is_your_worst_crypto_investment_to_date%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uklsdj/what_is_your_worst_crypto_investment_to_date/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 18:36:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I got caught up in one too many alts during the run up in the summer and I’ve been left with some that would need to treble to get close to their ATH. I cut a few at the beginning of the year to buy some BTC, which turned out to be a decent idea considering how much more most alts have bled in comparison, but realistically cash and gradual buys would have been the better option. I didn’t anticipate a crash like this, maybe that was naive, but here we are. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So yeah, was just wondering what has been the worst for people here. Maybe we got caught up in the same projects.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[下跌是暂时的，通货膨胀是永远的]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ul1wjb/dip_is_temporary_inflation_is_forever/?score=398&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ful1wjb%2Fdip_is_temporary_inflation_is_forever%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ful1wjb%2Fdip_is_temporary_inflation_is_forever%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ul1wjb/dip_is_temporary_inflation_is_forever/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:43:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[五个月前，我梳理了这里的所有帖子，以找到最被人看不起的次品硬币。我将其合并为一个可怕的对开本。这是对 "憎恨的对开本 "的更新。你有多想让它失败？它还会让你生气吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家早上好。

我们正处于熊市。糟透了。但这并不意味着我们不能仍然有
一些乐趣，对吗？

对于那些在今年年初的人，你可能记得
我创建了这个。憎恨的文件夹。我投资了（Yolo'd？）100美元到这个子的最
讨厌的硬币。有些钱币...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ul10rr/five_months_ago_i_combed_through_all_the_posts/?score=316&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ful10rr%2Ffive_months_ago_i_combed_through_all_the_posts%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ful10rr%2Ffive_months_ago_i_combed_through_all_the_posts%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ul10rr/five_months_ago_i_combed_through_all_the_posts/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:43:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Good morning all,&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We&amp;amp;#39;re in a bear market. Shit sucks. But that doesn&amp;amp;#39;t mean we can&amp;amp;#39;t still have some fun right?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For those that were around at the beginning of the year, you might remember that I created this. The FOLIO OF HATE. I invested (yolo&amp;amp;#39;d?) $100 into this subs most hated coins. Some coins are hated because of utility, some because of corruption, some because of the the shills. Whatever the reason, I decided to act on the theory that this sub can actually pick winners by investing into the ones that we all hate the most.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, $100 was invested on the same day to each of the ten coins/tokens. Here is how it fared.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/nfz7ezwmz8y81.png?width=991&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d0ac739a8375280fe14e47eb7564c5a1d6d7fc0e&quot;&amp;gt;Folio of Hate&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Down 46% or $460 in five months.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What about the individual results? Surely they&amp;amp;#39;re not all bad? Right?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Best performer:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; USDT -0.01 %&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Worst performer:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; LRC -70.13 %&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Surprise Performer:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; DOGE -31.01%&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/mbx8ck2j09y81.png?width=1007&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=87d85fccc2bb402f75ac9b570a37b9cd73b866ec&quot;&amp;gt;Folio of Hate Individual Performance&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Personal points of interest:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Investing in Dogecoin - yes Dogecoin - was a better investment than Solana, Cardano, Ripple and Binance.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Safemoon was not the predicted worst performer ...yet.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Tether - FUCKING TETHER - was the folios best performer. Props to &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/u/entschida&quot;&amp;gt;u/entschida&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for getting that one right.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I am aware that perceptions and opinions shift over time, so it is of course possible that we hate these coins more than ever. Oh, and fuck you Crypto.com&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Original post from &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rng996/here_it_is_the_subs_most_despised_coins_combined/&quot;&amp;gt;five months ago&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Well after a long and exhaustive battle of coins being shilled in just a couple of hours, I have found the list of the subs most hated coins. There was definitely a lot of hate out there. I put $100 into each and stored it on a seperate group of wallets to my real bags. To make it easier to track, I create the folio of hate using coinmarketcap to track them more easily. I&amp;amp;#39;ll post the updates every month and hope to see some big gains going against us all (even my most hated coin is in this group).  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There was a lot of hate from users, towards some coins more so than others. The two most hated were the most hated by a very long way. Merry Christmas everyone!  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The final list in order of most votes and comments is listed in the comment below because the filter won&amp;amp;#39;t let me create a post with that many coin names in it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[本杰明-考文认为他的 "延长周期 "理论不再有效了]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你仍然不认为我们处于熊市，我不知道该对你说什么。
你。你不能把比特币在过去4个月里经历的不断下跌和疲软的泵送联系在一起
在过去4个月中经历的牛市。

本杰明-考文是我关注的少数人之一，我喜欢他的内容。这很
悲哀的是，他说...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ukzwtu/benjamin_cowen_believes_his_lengthening_cycles/?score=405&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fukzwtu%2Fbenjamin_cowen_believes_his_lengthening_cycles%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fukzwtu%2Fbenjamin_cowen_believes_his_lengthening_cycles%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ukzwtu/benjamin_cowen_believes_his_lengthening_cycles/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 15:48:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you still don&amp;amp;#39;t think we&amp;amp;#39;re in a bear market, I&amp;amp;#39;m not sure what to say to you. You can&amp;amp;#39;t associate constant dumps and weak pumps Bitcoin has been going through for the last 4 months as a bull market.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Benjamin Cowen is one of the few people I follow and I enjoy his content. It&amp;amp;#39;s sad to him say his theory of lengthening cycles is dead, because it made the most sense. As an asset gets bigger, it obviously takes more money to move it up hence more time. Also, every Bitcoin cycle has seemed like it was progressively getting longer if you measure it from cycle bottoms.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ym1kycwyl8y81.png?width=595&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=77e259cb883425ccc915974eb75452c90cf84073&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/ym1kycwyl8y81.png?width=595&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=77e259cb883425ccc915974eb75452c90cf84073&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/mc0c80fwm8y81.png?width=589&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=0560ebfc99b268861e9bc617644a307749ff8417&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/mc0c80fwm8y81.png?width=589&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=0560ebfc99b268861e9bc617644a307749ff8417&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What he says makes sense, even if we were to somehow pump up from here it wouldn&amp;amp;#39;t erase all this downwards movement we had to go through. It would be hard to classify the past 2 years as part of the bull market. If the high inflation numbers and the situation with the FED wasn&amp;amp;#39;t a thing, I think his theory would have been correct. What do you think?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[当BTC达到历史最高点时，很多人都会急于进入加密货币。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ukgshj/alot_of_folks_are_going_to_rush_into_crypto_when/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fukgshj%2Falot_of_folks_are_going_to_rush_into_crypto_when%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fukgshj%2Falot_of_folks_are_going_to_rush_into_crypto_when%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ukgshj/alot_of_folks_are_going_to_rush_into_crypto_when/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 14:38:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我一直在等待的积极信号，在我堆积一些sats之前👇]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ukyb32/the_positive_signal_i_have_been_waiting_for/?score=530&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fukyb32%2Fthe_positive_signal_i_have_been_waiting_for%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fukyb32%2Fthe_positive_signal_i_have_been_waiting_for%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ukyb32/the_positive_signal_i_have_been_waiting_for/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 14:38:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币的流血事件将变得更加严重。这很好。]]></title><description><![CDATA[目前的加密货币市场大屠杀可能会变得更糟，但不要把你的目光从大局上移开。
但不要把目光从大局上移开。

外面的情况越来越糟糕了。比特币本周下跌超过8%，并从去年的历史最高点下跌了
从去年的历史高点下跌了近50%。情况也没有好多少
以太坊，本周下跌了5%，...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ukn5tx/the_bitcoin_bloodbath_will_get_worse_this_is_fine/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fukn5tx%2Fthe_bitcoin_bloodbath_will_get_worse_this_is_fine%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fukn5tx%2Fthe_bitcoin_bloodbath_will_get_worse_this_is_fine%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ukn5tx/the_bitcoin_bloodbath_will_get_worse_this_is_fine/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 13:40:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The current crypto market carnage will probably get worse—but don&amp;amp;#39;t take your eyes off the big picture.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s getting ugly out there.
Bitcoin is down over 8% this week and has fallen nearly 50% from last year&amp;amp;#39;s all-time-high. The situation isn&amp;amp;#39;t much better for Ethereum, down 5% over the week, while newer best-of-breed coins like Solana (SOL), Terra (LUNA), and Avalanche (AVAX) fell over 10% this week. Things haven&amp;amp;#39;t looked this bad in a while, and it&amp;amp;#39;s going to get worse before it gets better.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But don&amp;amp;#39;t be alarmed. Like the meme of the dog in a bowler hat sitting in a house on fire: This is fine.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Before getting into why things will be (mostly) fine, let&amp;amp;#39;s take a look at what&amp;amp;#39;s causing crypto to melt down in the first place.
The primary culprit is the global macroeconomy. Governments around the world are being walloped by inflation levels not seen in 40 years, and central banks are finally taking measures—like jacking interest rates and shrinking their balance sheets—to fix this. Unfortunately, this has meant taking away the cheap money punchbowl that has powered decades of surging stock and real estate prices.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The result has been a wipeout in both stocks and crypto (Bitcoin is more closely correlated with the Nasdaq than it&amp;amp;#39;s been in ages) and fear among investors. Meanwhile, other global events—from the war in Ukraine to new Covid lockdowns in China—are fueling further sell-offs and adding to the sense of unease. 
In these circumstances, is it any surprise people are flushing their Shiba Inu tokens? Many crypto enthusiasts, and Bitcoiners in particular, like to believe blockchains will supply an alternative financial reality when the world goes to hell, but it&amp;amp;#39;s clear that&amp;amp;#39;s not (yet) the case. Crypto is as prone to macroeconomic shocks as everything else.
Meanwhile, the crypto industry itself has become a bubble waiting to pop. Pick your example—from the glut of worthless Layer 1 chains to fly-by-night NFTs to Floyd Mayweather&amp;amp;#39;s latest pump-and-dump. There&amp;amp;#39;s a lot money being squandered in stupid ways. That&amp;amp;#39;s fine as long as there are enough &amp;amp;quot;greater fools&amp;amp;quot; out there to buy that garbage, but when the music stops, it&amp;amp;#39;s going to look a lot like the ICO fallout of 2018.
We might be at that stage again now. Paradoxically, though, the current carnage we&amp;amp;#39;re seeing should be cause for optimism.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Since the birth of Bitcoin, the crypto industry has been marked by spectacular booms followed by painful crashes. If history repeats itself—and I&amp;amp;#39;m betting it will—the impending downturn will serve as a healthy cleanse and reboot for the industry.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That&amp;amp;#39;s what happened in 2013 when the price of Bitcoin brushed the once jaw-dropping figure of $1,200, only to plummet afterward. It took years to reach that level again, but in the interim, something remarkable happened: dedicated teams put their heads down and built a series of innovations that transformed the industry. By the time the next boom rolled around in 2016, crypto had gone from being just Bitcoin and a handful of altcoins like Litecoin and XRP to encompass smart contracts, utility tokens, and a multi-chain future.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A similar thing happened after the bust of 2018. When crypto came roaring back in 2021, the technology had changed profoundly. A series of stylish NFT platforms had eclipsed the primitive CryptoKitties of the previous boom, DAOs took off for real, and the entire plumbing of the industry had become far more sophisticated.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s going to happen again. Just as in the past, the dilettantes and hustlers will move to some other shiny thing, while the real crypto believers will stick around to lay the groundwork for the next era of Web3.
It&amp;amp;#39;s hard to predict exactly what this next era will look like, but a good bet is that it will feature low gas fees, easy-to-use Layer 2 options, and NFTs moving to the core of the music and entertainment industries. It&amp;amp;#39;s a
fun future to imagine—provided you have the stomach to get through another Crypto Winter.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;*Source
This is Roberts on Crypto, a weekend column from Decrypt&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币恐惧和贪婪指数深陷 "极度恐惧"，BTC被抛至34K美元]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ukwr4y/bitcoin_fear_and_greed_index_deep_in_extreme_fear/?score=486&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fukwr4y%2Fbitcoin_fear_and_greed_index_deep_in_extreme_fear%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fukwr4y%2Fbitcoin_fear_and_greed_index_deep_in_extreme_fear%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ukwr4y/bitcoin_fear_and_greed_index_deep_in_extreme_fear/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 12:54:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[泰国btc商业]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uks9zo/thailand_btc_commercial/?score=329&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuks9zo%2Fthailand_btc_commercial%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuks9zo%2Fthailand_btc_commercial%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uks9zo/thailand_btc_commercial/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 12:54:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1,000 BTC（交易时为34,382,646美元）从Gemini转到Binance，收费4.39美元。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uksvr4/1000_btc_34382646_at_the_time_of_transaction_were/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuksvr4%2F1000_btc_34382646_at_the_time_of_transaction_were%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuksvr4%2F1000_btc_34382646_at_the_time_of_transaction_were%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uksvr4/1000_btc_34382646_at_the_time_of_transaction_were/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 11:34:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[终于达到了1 BTC !]]></title><description><![CDATA[今天对此感到欣喜若狂。

终于达到了我的目标，即1个BTC。

从2009年起就听说过比特币，以为是农场村的钱。我有一个GPU
但我宁愿用它来玩《使命召唤》。
但我宁愿用它来玩《使命召唤》。直到2021年，我对比特币是什么都不关心，但现在它
是...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ukuzsu/finally_made_it_to_1_btc/?score=328&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fukuzsu%2Ffinally_made_it_to_1_btc%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fukuzsu%2Ffinally_made_it_to_1_btc%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ukuzsu/finally_made_it_to_1_btc/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 11:34:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Overjoyed at this today.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Finally hit my goal of 1 BTC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Been hearing about Bitcoin since 2009, Thought it&amp;amp;#39;s farmville money. I had a GPU that could mine hundeds of Bitcoin a week in 2011 but I rather played Call of Duty with it. Till 2021, I didn&amp;amp;#39;t give a damn about what Bitcoin is but now it is all I research about (watching Greg Foss for Hopium, What Bitcoin Did for philosophy and money Benjamin Cowen for TA)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Started stacking sats from Jan 2021, flipped some shitcoins, DCA&amp;amp;#39;ed monthly into stacking via the lightning network and finally arrived here.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Used to hold it in a single account ledger wallet, but did not feel safe because of dictionary attacks. So, now HODLing into sparrow multi sig wallet (2 of 2 both Ledger Nano X). Stored my seed phrase safely burned underground in my backyard in a layer of concrete. HODL mode on!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Best of all, its KYC free.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Well, on to the next goal of 2 BTC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/d3lyakg2u6y81.png?width=987&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=41b1e652a7462d7fc87036157b01dca4319f6129&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/d3lyakg2u6y81.png?width=987&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=41b1e652a7462d7fc87036157b01dca4319f6129&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[德州当地的Newswest9电台报道了比特币开采的好处 | "与其把气体送到火炬上，不如把它送到发动机上，创造出电力，然后我们就可以从中开采比特币。所以这是一个减少油田排放的真正机会，"]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ukj9ze/local_texas_station_newswest9_reports_on_the/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fukj9ze%2Flocal_texas_station_newswest9_reports_on_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fukj9ze%2Flocal_texas_station_newswest9_reports_on_the%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ukj9ze/local_texas_station_newswest9_reports_on_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 09:38:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[大约一年前，Dogecoin达到0.70美元。现在它降低了约80%。表明获利回吐有时也是没有错的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[回到一年前。随着纪念币的兴起，加密货币正处于全面 "狂热 "阶段。
纪念币的兴起，由纪念币教父Dogecoin本身引领。多格币达到
0.70左右，超过了神奇的0.69大关。互联网上到处都是对狗币的炒作。
互联网上的炒作。投资者已经看到了1美元的大关，在...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ukm6l2/about_one_year_ago_dogecoin_hit_070_usd_now_its/?score=324&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fukm6l2%2Fabout_one_year_ago_dogecoin_hit_070_usd_now_its%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fukm6l2%2Fabout_one_year_ago_dogecoin_hit_070_usd_now_its%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ukm6l2/about_one_year_ago_dogecoin_hit_070_usd_now_its/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 08:32:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Going back one year. Crypto is in it full &amp;amp;quot;mania&amp;amp;quot; stage as the rise of meme coins takes place lead by the godfather of memes, Dogecoin itself. Dogecoin hits about 0.70 crossing the magical 0.69 mark. It&amp;amp;#39;s just complete doge hype all over the internet. Investors are already seeing the 1$ mark in front of their eyes.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here we are one year later. Since then DOGE only was in a downtrend from 0.70$ to 0.12$. Reasons are the overall Crypto dump but also fading interest and hype in the crypto itself. Which they are even trying to tackle right now with actual development and a roadmap. But this is not about doge. This is about not being too overconfident with your investment.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Being to overconfident will lead you to the blinded HODL. While holding may be a very good strategy in crypto its not always. Some cryptos rise others disappear you have to look into the market to know where your investments are heading.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If your crypto look weak over the longterm you should take the profit or if your crypto has done an unsustainable pump you should take a profit. Taking profit is not bad, it&amp;amp;#39;s smart and wise, also you always have the option to buy low afterwards.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[具有讽刺意味的是，比特币最近比股票更稳定]]></title><description><![CDATA[股票市场的人总是取笑加密货币，说它的波动性有多大。他们
他们是对的，直到最近。最受欢迎的增长型股票已经比
波动性比比特币大。这证明了比特币比一些
最受欢迎的股票。

以下是图表

比特币价格，过去6...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ukj53q/ironically_bitcoin_has_been_more_stable_than/?score=321&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fukj53q%2Fironically_bitcoin_has_been_more_stable_than%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fukj53q%2Fironically_bitcoin_has_been_more_stable_than%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ukj53q/ironically_bitcoin_has_been_more_stable_than/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 08:32:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Stock market people always made fun of crypto about how volatile it is. They were right until recently. The most popular growth stocks have been more volatile than Bitcoin. This proves that Bitcoin is more stable than some of the most popular stocks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here is the charts&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Bitcoin price, past 6 months; (down 43%)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ax1j5lk6h3y81.png?width=603&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=867b29d9075eca60e6c4345971feac212e50e7a4&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/ax1j5lk6h3y81.png?width=603&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=867b29d9075eca60e6c4345971feac212e50e7a4&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin&amp;amp;#39;s price has dropped 43% over 6 months.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here are the some most popular growth stocks&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Netflix (down 72%)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/8b4xzineh3y81.png?width=628&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=c83c6f07305d5ec733e34bfd2ec85daf2018f586&quot;&amp;gt;Netflix&amp;amp;#39;s share price is down 72&amp;amp;#37; in last 6 months&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Spotify (down 63%)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/rfss0x5mh3y81.png?width=620&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=61f76baf145131eedaeb2a42546488e9e801edaa&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/rfss0x5mh3y81.png?width=620&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=61f76baf145131eedaeb2a42546488e9e801edaa&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Here are the other growth stocks;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/uws4e0dzh3y81.jpg?width=960&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=984f2166746b910b27300fbe6b2c3a67dcc14bf8&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/uws4e0dzh3y81.jpg?width=960&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=984f2166746b910b27300fbe6b2c3a67dcc14bf8&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Tl;dr&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Bitcoin has been more stable than stocks recently. For example; Netflix is down 72% in past 6 months meanwhile Bitcoin is down 43%.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Of course that doesn&amp;amp;#39;t make Bitcoin a stable asset but it&amp;amp;#39;s clear that Bitcoin has been more stable than stocks recently.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[说实话，你们有多少人真正持有你们的硬币度过了上一次熊市？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看到很多人都在谈论那些在熊市中坚守的人将会得到回报。
得到回报，但我很少看到有人说他们是那些经历了
经历过这种情况。

你们当中有谁是那些据说在几年前的疯狂的加密货币冬天中持有的人吗？
几年前的那个疯狂的加密货币冬天？如果是的话，有多少是...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ukeaw0/lets_be_honest_how_many_of_you_actually_held_your/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fukeaw0%2Flets_be_honest_how_many_of_you_actually_held_your%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fukeaw0%2Flets_be_honest_how_many_of_you_actually_held_your%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ukeaw0/lets_be_honest_how_many_of_you_actually_held_your/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 05:31:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I see a lot of people talking about how those who hold through the bear run will be rewarded, but I rarely see people stating that they&amp;amp;#39;re the ones who went through that.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Are any of you the ones that supposedly held through the insane crypto winter of a couple years back? And if so, how much did you gain back? How much were you rewarded by your faith in crypto?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I guess this could be survivorship bias. Maybe the people who did hold through that bear run made so much money that they don&amp;amp;#39;t need to be in this sub, but who knows. I&amp;amp;#39;m just curious.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[当比特币下挫10%时]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ukiasz/when_bitcoin_dips_10/?score=362&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fukiasz%2Fwhen_bitcoin_dips_10%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fukiasz%2Fwhen_bitcoin_dips_10%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ukiasz/when_bitcoin_dips_10/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 22:37:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[5月22日比特币披萨日.]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ukkckm/may_22_bitcoin_pizza_day/?score=524&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fukkckm%2Fmay_22_bitcoin_pizza_day%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fukkckm%2Fmay_22_bitcoin_pizza_day%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ukkckm/may_22_bitcoin_pizza_day/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 21:37:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Safemoon首席执行官John Karony将投资者的15万美元资金挥霍在一个狗屎币上，现在价值5,000美元--损失96.6%。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是那些真正了不起的事情之一，我个人认为它提升了
Safemoon成为排名第一的加密货币骗局，远远高于Bitconnect。

在最新的Coffeezilla视频中[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kIUrE7Ovm5k]。
我们无畏的调查员终于证实，约翰-卡洛尼，Safemoon的CEO，...
Safemoon，...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujypgz/safemoon_ceo_john_karony_squanders_150000_of/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujypgz%2Fsafemoon_ceo_john_karony_squanders_150000_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujypgz%2Fsafemoon_ceo_john_karony_squanders_150000_of%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujypgz/safemoon_ceo_john_karony_squanders_150000_of/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 18:39:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is one of those truly remarkable things which I personally think elevates Safemoon to #1 Crypto scam, far above Bitconnect.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kIUrE7Ovm5k&quot;&amp;gt;In the latest Coffeezilla video&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, our intrepid investigator finally confirmed that John Karony, the CEO of Safemoon, definitively owns the infamous &amp;amp;quot;Gabe&amp;amp;quot; wallet - the BSC wallet that ends in &amp;amp;quot;6abe&amp;amp;quot;  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I might make a future post about this, but a quick summary is that the Gabe wallet bought a &amp;amp;quot;Moondog&amp;amp;quot; NFT, which John then tweeted about, and also wrote an instagram post about moving it. He also attended Austin SXSW and received an exclusive NFT that is transferred to your wallet for attendees only.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This (among other evidence) was the smoking gun and confirmed John&amp;amp;#39;s ownership of said wallet, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;which was previously highlighted as problematic as it has been receiving millions of dollars from Bitmart which was supposed to be sent to the liquidity pool&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, and yet these funds are being withdrawn as cash or spent on frivolous items.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;hr/&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With that out the way, we know that Karony owns this wallet, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/6zSJko3&quot;&amp;gt;and he received a tip off from the slimy Ben Phillips&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; to buy some shitcoin called &amp;amp;quot;Stonks&amp;amp;quot;.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://bscscan.com/token/0xb966150c7a0150ed4ea979e04f18d109301aab95?a=0xd51d1d5503dcff819e214faa66c3b6f0ebb06abe&quot;&amp;gt;On that same day, Karony bought $150,000 worth of Stonks&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, becoming the 2nd largest token holder.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Unfortunately, John&amp;amp;#39;s investing savvy is secondly only to his FUD-fighting savvy, and his FUD-fighting savvy is fucking awful, and so I regret to say that his $150,000 worth of Stonks tokens are now... alas...  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;$5,107.46..&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;That&amp;amp;#39;s a 96.6% loss.&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;hr/&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If this was his own money, who gives a shit. But to actually misuse taxed funds from investors which was supposed to go into the liquidity pool to help secure price stability of Safemoon, in order to buy cringey worthless NFT&amp;amp;#39;s and hundreds of thousands of dollars of shit tokens is a new low.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Especially considering Safemoon currently has a very serious liquidity issue. With just over $6m in BNB liquidity left, it only takes a couple whales to drain the LP and slam the door shut on everyone else.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A bank run is a comin&amp;amp;#39;!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["购买比特币并持有用于退休" - 参议员辛西娅-卢米斯]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uk3mos/buy_bitcoin_and_hold_for_retirement_senator/?score=334&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuk3mos%2Fbuy_bitcoin_and_hold_for_retirement_senator%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuk3mos%2Fbuy_bitcoin_and_hold_for_retirement_senator%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uk3mos/buy_bitcoin_and_hold_for_retirement_senator/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:35:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这里的人对待NFT就像Reddit的其他人对待加密货币一样。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我很奇怪，看着这里的加密货币者以完全相同的方式谈论NFTs，而Reddit上的其他人则以一般的方式谈论加密货币。
和Reddit其他地方的人以同样的方式谈论加密货币。我
我确信我将会被降权，但我们不应该接受NFTs吗？
导致更广泛地大规模采用底层区块链......]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uke7on/people_in_here_treat_nfts_like_the_rest_of_reddit/?score=521&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuke7on%2Fpeople_in_here_treat_nfts_like_the_rest_of_reddit%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuke7on%2Fpeople_in_here_treat_nfts_like_the_rest_of_reddit%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uke7on/people_in_here_treat_nfts_like_the_rest_of_reddit/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 17:35:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ts so strange to watch the crytonatives in here shit talking NFTs on exactly the same way and people on the rest of Reddit shit talk crypto in general. I&amp;amp;#39;m sure I&amp;amp;#39;m going to get downvoted into oblivion but shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t we embrace NFTs if it leads to wider mass adoption of the underlying blockchain tech? Content creators entering a tech space has never ended badly. Keen to hear why folks are so critical on the technology in general and wonder if those are the same responses that non crytonatives say about cryptocurrency in general.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[随便提醒一下]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uk0n23/a_casual_reminder/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuk0n23%2Fa_casual_reminder%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuk0n23%2Fa_casual_reminder%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uk0n23/a_casual_reminder/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 15:44:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[这不是一个玫瑰花坛]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uk3ejl/its_not_a_rose_bed/?score=337&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuk3ejl%2Fits_not_a_rose_bed%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuk3ejl%2Fits_not_a_rose_bed%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uk3ejl/its_not_a_rose_bed/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 15:44:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[对加密货币市场感到相当厌倦]]></title><description><![CDATA[我已经在这里呆了一段时间了，我不得不说...... 我已经很厌倦
我们的小市场。有太多的东西是如此的荒谬。

首先，我们的目的不就是要远离主流市场和银行吗？
银行吗？现在我们在这里，与股票的走势直接相关...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujz328/getting_pretty_tired_of_the_crypto_market/?score=319&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujz328%2Fgetting_pretty_tired_of_the_crypto_market%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujz328%2Fgetting_pretty_tired_of_the_crypto_market%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujz328/getting_pretty_tired_of_the_crypto_market/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 11:32:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ve been here for a while now and I&amp;amp;#39;ve gotta say ... I&amp;amp;#39;m getting pretty tired of our little market. There&amp;amp;#39;s so much that is just so rediculous.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For starters, wasn&amp;amp;#39;t the whole point to get away from the mainstream markets and banks? Now here we are, directly correlated to the moves of the stock market, driven by bots, Wall Street bankers and big finance whales.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And while we have such a tiny market cap, so much money is diverted into an entirely seperate market that recently blew up, NFT&amp;amp;#39;s. How much retail interest that otherwise would have gone into crypto&amp;amp;#39;s longer term was wasted on the NFT market by buying shitty JPG&amp;amp;#39;s of monkeys and rocks with laser eyes? What the hell were crypto people thinking promoting that BS other than trying to make a quick buck off the backs of ignorant retailers? If people had any forsight, that interest and limited funds would have been much better used in crypto projects. And that new retail would have been much better off for it too. Sure, many would have left with the market downturn, but many would have held too. But now all that new interest has been wasted by getting burned by a (so far) shitty use case in a side-market that&amp;amp;#39;s &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/nft-sales-plummet-92-market-133403653.html&quot;&amp;gt;down over 90%&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. A large percentage of whom never entered the crypto market itself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And then there&amp;amp;#39;s all the news driven BS and shitty meme coins. Doge coin? Shiba inu? Are you f*cking kidding me? Meme BS like that does nothing but damage the markets credibility, and again ... divert limited funds away from legitimate projects.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And we&amp;amp;#39;re entirely dependent on people like Elon Musk (who I like, but that doesn&amp;amp;#39;t change the fact that the market depending on his involvement is rediclulous), that something-something-Miller guy, Saylor, Kwon, ... Since when do we care what a few rich folks do? As retail we have the power to move the market. Too many people are just wasting their money on shitty NFT&amp;amp;#39;s and futures trading, rather than buying spot.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s sad to see this market turn into such a joke and be entirely at the behest of Wall Street ...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hell I still remember back in 2018 everyone was bemoaning the fact that the entire market was tied to the price of Bitcoin. Now here we are, not only still tied to Bitcoin but to the stock market too. What a sad joke.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Grow up. Be the change you want to see. See people about to waste their money on NFT&amp;amp;#39;s? Slap them. Thinking about participating in the futures market? Stick with spot. Thinking about shorting? Don&amp;amp;#39;t, just buy the dips. See news about Elon, Saylor or Kwon? Don&amp;amp;#39;t give a f*. Just DCA, stake, build, whatever it takes. Invest only what you can afford to miss for the long run and ignore the short term noise. This is the only place a lot of us see as an alternative to the old world. A potential for escape from all the control and restrictions. The endless boomer politicians sticking their grubby paws into everything. And however small we are as individuals, as a whole, we &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;can&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; move markets and change things. In more ways than one. We need an alternative system and so far, this is the best one we&amp;amp;#39;ve got. Don&amp;amp;#39;t waste it or let the old world shake you out and undermine it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不要否认你的500美元到10万美元的代币变成了1000美元到0.01美元。]]></title><description><![CDATA[人们变得极度敌视和防卫有一个共同的原因，那就是
因为他们不善于处理接受问题。不相信我，那就按
热门帖子上的争议。

如果你做了一个错误的决定，并且不得不接受一个负面的结果，那就值得
认识到这一点才能继续前进....]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uk3sw0/dont_be_in_denial_that_your_500_to_100k_token/?score=341&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuk3sw0%2Fdont_be_in_denial_that_your_500_to_100k_token%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuk3sw0%2Fdont_be_in_denial_that_your_500_to_100k_token%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uk3sw0/dont_be_in_denial_that_your_500_to_100k_token/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 09:46:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s a common reason people get extremely hostile and defensive, and it&amp;amp;#39;s because they do not handle acceptance well. Don&amp;amp;#39;t believe me, then sort by controversial on a popular post.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you&amp;amp;#39;ve made a bad decision, and have to accept a negative outcome it&amp;amp;#39;s worth aknowledging that to move on. Alot of people struggle with this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;No more blaming outside parties, or us against them. Blocking out all criticism. Putting more and more faith into delusional utopian outcomes. Going into the whole &amp;amp;quot;well at least we aren&amp;amp;#39;t X project&amp;amp;quot; and so, so much more.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;No one likes being made a fool of, and no one likes to admit they were ignorant in their choices. Yet it is something that needs to be done to wake up to the reality of the situation and make the decisions that need to be done. Dwelling on a dead or dying project is only going to hold you back.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As stated numerous times on this subreddit. Everyone wants to be the $500 to $100k holder as that&amp;amp;#39;s what everyone hears about. No one wants to be the $1000 to $0.01 holder, yet a majority of us will be and we will need to accept that when it happens.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is your call to make as you are the person who holds yourself back or pushes yourself forward. Choose wisely.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币下跌4万美元，加密货币连续暴跌......是时候出售了吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你是加密货币的新手，你可能会因为这个价格而感到害怕和恐慌。
我不能怪你，但我只想告诉你比特币的价格历史

在2014年......比特币跌到了400美元以下，大家都认为数字黄金已经
永远消失了

然后在2018年......比特币跌破4千美元，每个人......。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uk4icb/bitcoin_falls_40k_and_crypto_continuous_plunge_is/?score=435&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuk4icb%2Fbitcoin_falls_40k_and_crypto_continuous_plunge_is%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fuk4icb%2Fbitcoin_falls_40k_and_crypto_continuous_plunge_is%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/uk4icb/bitcoin_falls_40k_and_crypto_continuous_plunge_is/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 08:42:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you are new in crypto you may fear and panic because of this prices and I can’t blame you, but I just want to tell you about Bitcoin price history&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In 2014 … Bitcoin went below $400 and everyone thought that the Digital Gold is gone forever&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then in  2018 … Bitcoin went below $4K and everyone thought that the Digital Gold is gone forever&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then in 2022 … Bitcoin went below $40K and everyone thought that the Digital Gold is gone forever&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I am not telling you to buy or sell, I am not telling how much to invest or or what to invest in, I am just telling you the history and don’t worry if you are true believer of crypto and the project you choose to invest in&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, I can‘t wait to buy more cheap Bitcoin in 2026 when it goes below $400K and everyone is thinking it’s gone forever&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/2g4jrwrv0zx81.jpg?width=895&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=b08d617cd85c4468ac950eec2767a764faf516ec&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/2g4jrwrv0zx81.jpg?width=895&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=b08d617cd85c4468ac950eec2767a764faf516ec&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[过去几天的比特币社区]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uk4adf/bitcoin_community_in_past_few_days/?score=421&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuk4adf%2Fbitcoin_community_in_past_few_days%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fuk4adf%2Fbitcoin_community_in_past_few_days%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/uk4adf/bitcoin_community_in_past_few_days/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 07:36:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["比特币是老鼠药，"芒格说。他是对的。我们金融系统中的所有老鼠都有麻烦了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在很长一段时间里，我不喜欢查理说的那句话。但今天当我重新观看那段视频时，我终于
今天，当我重新观看那段视频时，我终于明白了。所以，谢谢查理。老鼠们最好
开始散开!]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujx99l/bitcoin_is_rat_poison_says_munger_hes_right_all/?score=343&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujx99l%2Fbitcoin_is_rat_poison_says_munger_hes_right_all%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujx99l%2Fbitcoin_is_rat_poison_says_munger_hes_right_all%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujx99l/bitcoin_is_rat_poison_says_munger_hes_right_all/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 02:57:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For the longest time I disliked the statement Charlie said. But it finally clicked today when I re-watched that clip. So, thanks Charlie. The rats better start to scatter!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[2014年的今天，比尔-盖茨以400美元的价格为比特币辩护："它是一个技术性的巡回演出"。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujov02/today_in_2014_bill_gates_defends_bitcoin_at_400/?score=336&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujov02%2Ftoday_in_2014_bill_gates_defends_bitcoin_at_400%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujov02%2Ftoday_in_2014_bill_gates_defends_bitcoin_at_400%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujov02/today_in_2014_bill_gates_defends_bitcoin_at_400/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 02:57:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[只是提醒大家：我们都会在某个时刻死去。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujmges/just_a_reminder_we_are_all_going_to_die_at_some/?score=318&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujmges%2Fjust_a_reminder_we_are_all_going_to_die_at_some%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujmges%2Fjust_a_reminder_we_are_all_going_to_die_at_some%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujmges/just_a_reminder_we_are_all_going_to_die_at_some/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 02:57:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿根廷向IMF低头，获得450亿贷款，但不得不禁止加密货币以防止洗钱 - 一个好的老金融黑帮敲诈第三世界国家]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujqlhw/argentina_bows_to_imf_gets_45b_loan_but_have_to/?score=327&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujqlhw%2Fargentina_bows_to_imf_gets_45b_loan_but_have_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fujqlhw%2Fargentina_bows_to_imf_gets_45b_loan_but_have_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ujqlhw/argentina_bows_to_imf_gets_45b_loan_but_have_to/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 01:54:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我买完蘸酱后的晚餐。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujn0qo/my_dinner_after_buying_the_dip/?score=324&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujn0qo%2Fmy_dinner_after_buying_the_dip%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujn0qo%2Fmy_dinner_after_buying_the_dip%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujn0qo/my_dinner_after_buying_the_dip/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 01:54:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[国际货币基金组织正在威胁那些希望采用比特币的国家，除非他们采取强硬的反加密货币立场，否则不会给予经济支持。是时候从经济奴役中解放出来了。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujns3q/imf_is_threatening_countries_looking_to_adopt/?score=310&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujns3q%2Fimf_is_threatening_countries_looking_to_adopt%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fujns3q%2Fimf_is_threatening_countries_looking_to_adopt%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/ujns3q/imf_is_threatening_countries_looking_to_adopt/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 21:36:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>