<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[加密货币国外热门讨论]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 13:05:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[我们已经有了一个完整的零售湮灭。
简单地说：所有的供应现在都由LTH持有，没有销售压力，但也--没有更多的东西可拿。工作已经完成。这意味着未来的蓝天。

#Bitcoin #BTC #BTCUSDT #Supply 
🧵👇👇https://t.co/jTaYfaelnU]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491703074351685634/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491703074351685634/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 11:36:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[非随机住院数据由于差异化测试、缺乏裁决和对暴露的确认不足而无效。 然而，先前的感染在数据中一直坚如磐石，最终投降也近在眼前。 那些遭受痛苦的人应该恢复正常。https://t.co/ZVzUpundo7]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491700787927519238/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491700787927519238/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 11:36:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯这次抽水。这里没有熊的空间。#比特币]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sowh3o/russia_pump_this_time_no_space_for_bears_here/?score=327&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsowh3o%2Frussia_pump_this_time_no_space_for_bears_here%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsowh3o%2Frussia_pump_this_time_no_space_for_bears_here%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sowh3o/russia_pump_this_time_no_space_for_bears_here/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 11:31:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[停止过度利用你的投资组合为卡的CRO]]></title><description><![CDATA[不受欢迎的意见。CRO在你的投资组合中不应该超过10-15％。

最近，我注意到这里有很多人在CRO中严重地过度使用杠杆，试图
试图获得更高层次的卡。不要误会我的意思，好处是很大的。
但是，仅凭利益是不可能保证将如此高的杠杆率投入的。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soxt6k/stop_over_leveraging_your_portfolio_into_cro_for/?score=423&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoxt6k%2Fstop_over_leveraging_your_portfolio_into_cro_for%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoxt6k%2Fstop_over_leveraging_your_portfolio_into_cro_for%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soxt6k/stop_over_leveraging_your_portfolio_into_cro_for/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:32:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Unpopular Opinion: CRO should not be more than 10-15% of your portfolio.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Lately I’ve noticed lots of people here heavily over leveraged in CRO attempting to obtain the next level of card. Don’t get me wrong, the benefits are great, but BENEFITS ALONE could never warrant putting such a high percentage of your portfolio into a project that has a lot to prove. While CRO is far from a shitcoin, it is also far from a blue chip, and if crypto.com doesn’t flourish, the coin itself really has little to no use. If you’re shooting for the next card up remember, it’s not a race, slowly work your way there as your portfolio grows.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT - First of all, I should have said “over allocating”, not over leveraging. I thought it was obviously enough but that’s on me.   Second, not spreading fud, not scoffing at cro. I’m saying the card and rewards are great, Just a reminder not to over allocate your portfolio for any type of rewards with any company&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[11年前的今天，比特币达到1美元]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/somjed/11_years_ago_today_bitcoin_reached_1/?score=350&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsomjed%2F11_years_ago_today_bitcoin_reached_1%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsomjed%2F11_years_ago_today_bitcoin_reached_1%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/somjed/11_years_ago_today_bitcoin_reached_1/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:44:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto非常善于显示梅拉尼娅的NFT团队购买了她自己的NFT]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soo4wo/crypto_is_very_good_at_showing_melanias_nft_team/?score=346&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoo4wo%2Fcrypto_is_very_good_at_showing_melanias_nft_team%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoo4wo%2Fcrypto_is_very_good_at_showing_melanias_nft_team%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soo4wo/crypto_is_very_good_at_showing_melanias_nft_team/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:44:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[友情提醒。对你在YouTube上看到的新硬币要格外小心，因为取消DISLIKE COUNT后，YouTube就成了骗子的天堂。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在取消 "不喜欢计数 "之前，像我这样的人依靠 "拇指向上 "和 "拇指向下 "之间的比例来发现诈骗和虚假评论。
拇指向上的数量和拇指向下的数量之间的比例来发现诈骗、虚假评论或不良内容。
内容。现在这些日子已经过去了，因为YouTube已经删除了 "不喜欢 "计数。
计数。

现在，骗子们只是在YouTube上诈骗人们，所以...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sotn2r/friendly_reminder_be_extra_careful_with_new_coins/?score=505&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsotn2r%2Ffriendly_reminder_be_extra_careful_with_new_coins%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsotn2r%2Ffriendly_reminder_be_extra_careful_with_new_coins%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sotn2r/friendly_reminder_be_extra_careful_with_new_coins/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:44:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Before the removal of the Dislike Count, people like me rely on the ratio between number of thumb-ups and thumb-downs to spot scams, fake reviews, or bad content overall. Those days are gone now that YouTube has removed the Dislike Count.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now scammers are just out on YouTube and scam people so blatantly because all people see is the number of thumb-ups.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is exactly why I had always told people to avoid finding crypto advice on TikTok in the first place, because all you see is the number of hearts, and many just fall for the scams if the number of hearts is high.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My point is that if you were careful with the content on YouTube before, you have to be extra careful now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[与我当地的国会议员交谈，现在他实际上希望我向他提供有信誉的来源，说明为什么加密货币可以帮助我的国家。]]></title><description><![CDATA[标题说得很清楚，我有一个难得的机会与我的民选代表实际交谈。
我的当选代表，他说他唯一听到的关于
加密货币是 "令人担忧的"。我想寻求帮助，把一个好的
我想寻求帮助，把我可以提供给他的有信誉的来源的清单，以便他可以...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soukpv/spoke_to_my_local_congressman_and_now_he_actually/?score=364&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoukpv%2Fspoke_to_my_local_congressman_and_now_he_actually%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoukpv%2Fspoke_to_my_local_congressman_and_now_he_actually%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soukpv/spoke_to_my_local_congressman_and_now_he_actually/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:44:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The title says it generally, I had a rare opportunity to actually SPEAK to my elected representative, and he said the only things hes heard about cryptocurrency are “concerning”. Im looking for help on putting together a good list of reputable sources that i could provide to him so that he could see the value that the cryptocurrency and blockchain industries could bring to my state. I really would appreciate help on this matter as he really seemed to listen and i dont want to miss my opportunity to potentially put a good word in for cryptocurrency! Thanks!
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
Edit: I live in Connecticut and the representative is a Democrat! Forgot to mention that! Thank you so much to everyone who has replied so far this is exactly why i came to this sub!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究表明，美国人更喜欢加密货币而不是传统的储蓄账户]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sobj4s/americans_prefer_crypto_over_a_traditional/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsobj4s%2Famericans_prefer_crypto_over_a_traditional%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsobj4s%2Famericans_prefer_crypto_over_a_traditional%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sobj4s/americans_prefer_crypto_over_a_traditional/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 06:35:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在加密货币和稳定币上赚取利息：从初级到高级指南，DeFi，LP，赌注，借贷]]></title><description><![CDATA[在加密货币上产生收益是一件繁荣的事情。有很多方法可以提高你的
收益，这包括借贷、押注、提供流动性等。你可以通过
用CeFi和DeFi。这是一个最新的尝试，为初学者提供指南。
但即使是有经验的用户也会发现一些有用的东西......]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soiu05/earn_interest_on_crypto_and_stablecoins_begginer/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoiu05%2Fearn_interest_on_crypto_and_stablecoins_begginer%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoiu05%2Fearn_interest_on_crypto_and_stablecoins_begginer%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soiu05/earn_interest_on_crypto_and_stablecoins_begginer/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 06:35:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Generating yield on crypto is a booming thing. There are many ways to boost your gains, this includes lending, staking, liquidity providing, etc. You can do this with CeFi and DeFi. This is an updated attempt to provide guide for begginers, but even experieneced user might find some useful tips.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;First let get some terms right:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Staking&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - refers to generating income by block generation on Proof of Stake (PoS) blockchains. The term is heavily misused everywhere, so nowadays it can mean anything from staking to liquidity providing&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Lending&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - you lend your crypto and get interest. Counterparty does anything it want with it and hopefully pays back some day.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Liquidity providing (LP)&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - you provide two (sometimes even more) cryptocurrencies to a DEX (decentralized exchange), so people can trade. You get your share of trading fees.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;CeFi&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - centralized companies, you can lend them your coins, they pay you interest.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;DeFi&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - decentralized (well, at least in theory) applications like DEXes, lending apps etc&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Risks&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are obviously risks that come with all this, so beware. CeFi can get hacked, can scam you, can bankrupt. DeFi can get hacked, can scam you and its happening a lot. With staking you can get slashed (happens rarely), but if you delegate your funds to a validator, he can misbehave (depends on specific chain what he can or cant do). When doing LP, you face impermanent loss, in addition to all the DeFi risks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;How to get yield&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now lets get to generating some money, starting from the simplest options.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;CeFi&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Probably easiest thing to do is to lend your coins to a big CeFi lender, like Celsius. They have been around for a while, have $20B in assets under management and among CeFi its as safe as it gets. But their rates are somewhat lower than what competitors can pay you. Rates for different coins are a lot different and every CeFi lender has different rates for the coin, so you can optimize by using several CeFi. When deciding between platforms these are important things to consider: rates, security, jurisdiction, withdrawal fees, how customer support works. Also not every lender will be available in your country.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Where to find best rates:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coinlenders.net/&quot;&amp;gt;https://coinlenders.net&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; - this a is site i put together myself, you can search for rates among several CeFi and DeFi lending platforms. Just select a coin and see what your options are.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Note that most of the CeFi platforms have tiered system, meaning you can get best rate on limited amount - if that affects you, consider splitting funds between multiple platforms to get best value. It also helps with diversification.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
StakingIf you have Proof of Stake coins, than very likely staking will be safest option with great return. Many CeFi providers will just stake the coin for you and take their cut for doing this, so consider doing it yourself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Typical yield for stablecoins is 10-12%, 5-6% on bitcoin and ether.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are services that promise a way bigger yield than this, but i don&amp;amp;#39;t find them trustworthy enough for sharing. But just in case you want to gamble, know that if you look, you can find yields like 15-30% on btc - but dont be suprised if you end up with nothing...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;DeFi&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Moving to DeFi. First of all try to eliminate unnecessary risks by obtaining HW wallet. Ledger or Trezor. Chose wisely according to the chains you wanna use, not all chains are supported. If possible, go for the Nano X or Model T, as these support all the modern stuff. Learn to use Metamask with you HW wallet, it will work well for all the EVM chains.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;DeFi lending&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just like CeFi, you can just lend you coin with some lending protocol like AAVE, Compound etc. Most of the DeFi protocols issue its own token, and sometimes they will give some as incentives to lenders, borrowers or liquidity providers. This is additional yield, sometimes these rewards are locked for some time, so there is a risk of the incentive token losing lot of value before you can sell. Interest rates are usually adjusted to current market situation and change a lot, so you need to monitor it.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Where to find good rates?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coinlenders.net/defi-lending&quot;&amp;gt;https://coinlenders.net/defi-lending&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coindix.com/?kind=single&quot;&amp;gt;https://coindix.com/?kind=single&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;DeFi - liquidity providing&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Liquidity providing is another great way to generate yield. You provide some liquidity to a DEX, in return you get fees and sometimes also incentive tokens. Usually you need to provide two assets in 50:50 ratio, which makes it more complicated. Understand, that by providing liquidity you are basically putting you assets for sale and you no longer have direct exposure to their price, so if the price in the pair changes, you will find that you own different amount of tokens and always, you will own more of the worse one.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
This is called impermanent loss, but there is nothing really impermanent about it, its quite normal loss. To avoid impermanent loss you can chose a pool with currencies of equal or correlated value, like USDC-USDT. Also note that due to the impermanent loss, if one token loses 100% of value, you lose everything in the pool not just half - because you will be left with with 100% of the worthless one, due to arbitrage. Sometimes with the LP pools you will see ridiculous APYs like 1000000%, that does not mean you are getting rich. The reason for these crazy APYs is usually one of these:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;its a new platform and it will go down quickly as more liquidity is added&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You need to but hyperinflating token which will lose a lot of value over time, negating the gains&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Its very unsecure/untrustworthy platform with high risk of getting robbed&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Where to find the best pools? Here are some resources to help:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coindix.com/&quot;&amp;gt;https://coindix.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://kingdata.com/&quot;&amp;gt;https://kingdata.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://app.apy.vision/liquidity-pools&quot;&amp;gt;https://app.apy.vision/liquidity-pools&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;How to handle incentive tokens/rewards&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
You usually will want to sell it and add to your lending/LP positions to get compounding effects. These incentive tokens are normally very inflationary and are losing value quickly, especially when the protocol is new. Claiming the rewards and swapping it on DEX are transactions which can cost you tx fees, so if this is on expensive chain like Ethereum, this is only profitable for whales basically. Solution is to use automatic compounders, like Autofarm, more on this later. When the reward is locked for some time, it may go down a lot during this period, and your yield will be smaller than expected. Be sure to include this in your risk assessment.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Advanced strategies&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When you get familiar with DeFi, you might want to try some advanced stuff, combining multiple protocols together to boost your yields even further. These come with more risk and usually involve some kind of leverage, so be careful. There are plenty of options, lets check some usual or popular options.Some of these strategies:  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Recursive lending&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is when you lend your asset to a DeFi protocol and borrow it right back, then supply it into the same protocol. You can do the loop several time until limit is reached, the limit is a function of collateral factor. So lets say you deposit $1k and collateral factor is 80%, you can max you position to 1/(1-CF), so to $5k deposit and $4k borrow position. There will be a lot of transactions doing this, so you need cheap chain or big deposit to be worthy. This strategy is profitable if deposit interest is bigger than borrow interest, which is possible when incentive token rewards are high. But you will need to do constant compounding to avoid liquidation (without it your debt grows). You need to monitor the incentive token price and the APYs, so you can recognize when its no longer profitable.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tranquil.finance/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.tranquil.finance/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; is one place this is possible at this moment&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Lend and borrow, then put into LP&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some protocols do not allow recursive lending, you can maybe circumvent this with multiple accounts, or you can do something else, like deposit USDT, borrow USDC, sell half of the USDC for USDT and put it in LP pool. Again, you need high incentive token rewards to make it profitable.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Automated compounding&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As compounding on some platforms is costly due to blockchain fees, solution is to use automated compounder, like Autofarm, which does all the work for you in optimal way. You add some risk by doing this, if the auto compounding protocol gets compromised, you also lose your deposit.Examples:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Autofarm: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://autofarm.network/&quot;&amp;gt;https://autofarm.network/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Beefy: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://beefy.finance/&quot;&amp;gt;https://beefy.finance/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Leveraged yield farming&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Basically you provide liquidity, while borrowing additional money to get more yield. You pay interest to lenders, but you earn more of the incentive tokens and fees. You put your money as collateral. Examples: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Alpaca: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://app.alpacafinance.org/farm&quot;&amp;gt;https://app.alpacafinance.org/farm&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Tulip: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://tulip.garden/leverage&quot;&amp;gt;https://tulip.garden/leverage&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Anchor+Mirror&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anchor protocol is one of the most favorite places to earn interest on stablecoins, with stable 19.5% its a no brainer. But you can get more when combining with Mirror protocol. This is covered in depth in many articles, so i am not going to repeat it: just google Anchor Mirror delta neutral strategy.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anchorprotocol.com/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.anchorprotocol.com/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://mirrorprotocol.app&quot;&amp;gt;https://mirrorprotocol.app&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Anchor+MIM leverage&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Another thing people have been doing is basically leveraging your position. You borrow MIM against your aUST tokens (representing your deposit), sell MIM for UST, deposit again. I have never done this though, &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anchorprotocol.com/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.anchorprotocol.com/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Nexus&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Next generation of these combined strategies is automated. Nexus Protocol is a great example: you deposit LUNA or ETH(PoS version) to nexus, it uses it as collateral in Anchor to borrow UST, deposits the UST to Anchor for additional yield, it monitors and maintains your LTV to ensure you are not liquidated, sell you profits for LUNA/ETH and it results in safer and higher yield. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Check it out: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://nexusprotocol.app/&quot;&amp;gt;https://nexusprotocol.app/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Moving funds between chains&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you are going the DeFi way, you may need to move funds between chains a lot. Especially valid for stablecoins and WBTC. Some tips to do this effectively:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Register on exchanges which support withdrawals and depostits to multiple chains: Binance, Bitfinex, Crypto. com - you can deposit with one chain, withdraw with other, usually paying some withdrawal fees&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;For swapping one stablecoin for another, use Binance rather than DEX, as fees are way lower. (if low cost is a priority, understandably for some of you priorites might be different, or you dont have binance available etc.)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Learn how to use multichain router: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://app.multichain.org/#/router&quot;&amp;gt;https://app.multichain.org/#/router&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for cheap cross chain transfers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;For larger amounts, avoid services which charge percentual fees&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Swapping to one crypto and than back for cross chain transafers is sometimes possible, but usually not very cheap and might trigger taxable event. Sometimes it might be only option though.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ethereum bridges are usually the most expensive way to do this, unless you are handling very large amounts&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Some additional tips:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;If you just starting with few hundreds dollars, don&amp;amp;#39;t bother with DeFi. You will get crushed by blockchain fees. Use some CeFi lender with free withdrawals to accumulate, when you have more, you can start with DeFi. Also these CeFis will often give you nice sign-up bonuses, which will probably be worth a lot more than the interest, so be sure to get it. You can even jump between several CeFis to collect more of it. If still want to do DeFi, use a cheap chain. Harmony and Solana come to mind. Avoid Ethereum.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Don&amp;amp;#39;t get attached to a specific chain, good opportunities appear on different chains every time, it does not make sense to limit yourself to one favorite. Of course, if you are hodling SOL token, you will probably find best opportunities on Solana network, but with universal assets like stablecoins or BTC, it can be anywhere.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Always monitor your gains. If something doesn&amp;amp;#39;t add up, investigate and be prepared to move your funds.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Depending on your jurisdiction, you might have to pay taxes on your lending/staking/LP gains. &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My favorite CeFi products:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Hodlnaut.com&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ledn.io&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Celsius&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;FTX&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Less known, but very promising: Vauld&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My favorite DeFi products:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Anchor Protocol - note that Anchor Yield reserve is bleeding rapidly, its possible that yield will go down. &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Tranquil.finance on Harmony (+Mimas clone from the same team on Cronos)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;TraderJoe on Avalanche&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Sovryn on RSK&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Note: this is an updated post from January, update includes: some more strategies a tips, more specific examples. Added cross-chain transfers tips.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[实际上我在想，也许Facebook/Meta会这样做。杰克："我告诉迪姆他们做错了。你们应该使用闪电。"]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/som20p/i_actually_was_thinking_that_maybe_facebook_meta/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsom20p%2Fi_actually_was_thinking_that_maybe_facebook_meta%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsom20p%2Fi_actually_was_thinking_that_maybe_facebook_meta%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/som20p/i_actually_was_thinking_that_maybe_facebook_meta/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 06:35:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1997年的互联网用户：1.3亿。今天的BTC用户。130M]]></title><description><![CDATA[1997年的互联网用户：1.3亿。

今天的BTC用户。130M

1997年互联网有14年的历史，而BTC今年有13年（?）的历史。

看起来我们的增长速度比互联网当年的增长速度快，但我知道这不是所有的黑色和白色，还有很多因素在起作用。
并非都是黑白分明的，这里还有很多因素在起作用。
技术...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soljnd/internet_users_in_1997_130m_btc_users_today_130m/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoljnd%2Finternet_users_in_1997_130m_btc_users_today_130m%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoljnd%2Finternet_users_in_1997_130m_btc_users_today_130m%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soljnd/internet_users_in_1997_130m_btc_users_today_130m/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 03:39:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Internet users in 1997: 130M. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;BTC users today: 130M&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Internet was 14 years old in 1997 while BTC is 13 (?) years old this year. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Looks like we&amp;amp;#39;re growing faster than internet did way back when but I know it&amp;amp;#39;s not all so black and white and there&amp;amp;#39;s many more factors at play here: technological literacy, avaliability of said technology, nearly 2 billion people more on the planet today compared to 1997 etc ...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just felt like sharing this here and maybe starting a discussion since somebody mentioned the numbers Bitcoin sub.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天几乎从一个骗子那里得到了10亿泰铢。就差那么一点点。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sonz2c/almost_got_1btc_out_of_a_scammer_today_so_close/?score=367&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsonz2c%2Falmost_got_1btc_out_of_a_scammer_today_so_close%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsonz2c%2Falmost_got_1btc_out_of_a_scammer_today_so_close%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sonz2c/almost_got_1btc_out_of_a_scammer_today_so_close/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 02:42:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[是否还有其他即将推出的 "玩赚 "游戏，你认为会有价值？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想尽早投资于P2E游戏，这样我就能快速获得投资回报。
而且，在价格不高的时候。(我不会把它作为我的主要收入来源。
总之，以下是我发现的一些游戏。
发现的一些游戏。
1. 元气大伤
我认为我没有那么早接触这个....。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soc2jj/are_there_any_other_upcoming_play_to_earn_games/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoc2jj%2Fare_there_any_other_upcoming_play_to_earn_games%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoc2jj%2Fare_there_any_other_upcoming_play_to_earn_games%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soc2jj/are_there_any_other_upcoming_play_to_earn_games/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 02:42:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I want to invest in P2E games as early as possible so I can have my ROI fast, and also, while the prices aren’t high. (I’m not gonna use it as my main source of income so don’t come at me) Anyways, Here are some of the games that I have found.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;1. Metawars&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
I don&amp;amp;#39;t think I&amp;amp;#39;m that early with this one. I was hoping for phase one, but I think this will be enough. I&amp;amp;#39;m hoping the graphics aren&amp;amp;#39;t too bad considering we will be exploring planets and battling other players. (It’s kinda like star atlas? lol) I’m wondering how much the planets will cost alsoooooo, it’s a multiplayer game which is kinda intriguing but still kinda skeptic about this.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;2. Wrejects&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
I’m looking forward to this one too. Wrestling and aliens are the perfect combination for me. Still thinking if the graphics when wrestling will be good. I’m really realllyyy looking forward to the gameplay but It’s still on Q1 so there’s nothing much info out there. Every fighter, like in other PVP games, has their own backstory and unique special move. Also, unlike in Metawars, the team is doxxed.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;3. My Neighbor Alice&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Not early enough with this one too but this is a pretty wholesome game. It’s an open world game kinda like animal crossing? I wasn’t able to join the pre-alpha access but seeing the gameplay was enough for me. I can see myself spending hours playing this, just like I did with AC also, It’s on steam which is a plus for me.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Any thoughts about the games that I mentioned?&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Ps. still new to this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[佩洛西放弃反对，国会着手禁止议员交易股票]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sorx7h/congress_moves_to_ban_members_from_trading_stocks/?score=522&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsorx7h%2Fcongress_moves_to_ban_members_from_trading_stocks%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsorx7h%2Fcongress_moves_to_ban_members_from_trading_stocks%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sorx7h/congress_moves_to_ban_members_from_trading_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 02:42:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我把0.003 BTC的钥匙放在保险库里100年。]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，不完全是我把它放在那里，我居住的城市档案馆将存储
信件100年。他们将在2122年打开它们。我写了一封信，也
把价值100美元的私钥放在BTC中。你认为有多大的机会
网络还能继续运行吗？什么会是区块链？]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/soknl2/i_put_keys_to_0003_btc_in_a_vault_for_100_years/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsoknl2%2Fi_put_keys_to_0003_btc_in_a_vault_for_100_years%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsoknl2%2Fi_put_keys_to_0003_btc_in_a_vault_for_100_years%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/soknl2/i_put_keys_to_0003_btc_in_a_vault_for_100_years/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 01:36:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Well not exactly I put it there, the city archive where I live will store letters for 100 years. They will open them in 2122. I wrote a letter and also put the private keys for 100 $ worth in BTC. What do you think are the chances the network will be still up and running? What would be the block reward by then if so? What would you put in an envelope for 100 years?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[很快，由于区块链的存在，二手车商将无法扭曲汽车里程数。阿尔法-罗密欧推出一款新的SUV，利用NFT和区块链追踪汽车的生命周期]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sohm0r/soon_used_car_dealers_will_not_be_able_to_twist/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsohm0r%2Fsoon_used_car_dealers_will_not_be_able_to_twist%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsohm0r%2Fsoon_used_car_dealers_will_not_be_able_to_twist%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sohm0r/soon_used_car_dealers_will_not_be_able_to_twist/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 01:36:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[十年前，我曾预言Reddit将把其因果报应系统变成加密货币。这是我下一个十年的预测。]]></title><description><![CDATA[区块链技术正处于构建一个无信任的全球投票机的早期阶段。
的机器，人类将用它来快速达成对当前事件的大众共识。
事件达成共识。VR头盔或AR眼镜中的生物统计学和面部识别将被用来验证用户的特定钱包地址。
用来验证用户的特定钱包地址，...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sohd28/ten_years_ago_i_predicted_that_reddit_would_turn/?score=339&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsohd28%2Ften_years_ago_i_predicted_that_reddit_would_turn%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsohd28%2Ften_years_ago_i_predicted_that_reddit_would_turn%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sohd28/ten_years_ago_i_predicted_that_reddit_would_turn/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 21:38:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Blockchain tech is in the early stages of constructing a trustless global voting machine that humanity will use to quickly reach popular consensus on current events. Biometrics and facial recognition in VR headsets or AR glasses will be used to authenticate users to a specific wallet address, guaranteeing that no user votes twice. This will lead to an informal global democracy. Ignoring or acting against the will of global consensus will be considered political taboo in many countries. Over time, this voting mechanism will fundamentally transform the way in which humanity governs itself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thank you for reading my silly prediction. Obligatory, this is not financial advice but entertainment only. Proof of my last prediction is noted in the subreddit&amp;amp;#39;s wiki under the crypto history section.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国政府现在持有40亿美元的比特币，是特斯拉堆积的两倍]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sogujw/us_government_now_holds_4_billion_in_bitcoin/?score=343&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsogujw%2Fus_government_now_holds_4_billion_in_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsogujw%2Fus_government_now_holds_4_billion_in_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sogujw/us_government_now_holds_4_billion_in_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 21:38:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[现金是垃圾]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sojhsr/cash_is_trash/?score=390&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsojhsr%2Fcash_is_trash%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsojhsr%2Fcash_is_trash%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sojhsr/cash_is_trash/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 20:39:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[梅拉尼娅-特朗普的NFT以17万美元卖给了....herself。]]></title><description><![CDATA[铸造NFT的地址（又称1号地址）将473,657.64美元发送到一个中介地址（2号）。
中介地址(#2)。中介地址将其中一些USDC换成了
1,816.08 SOL。然后，2号地址向第三个地址发送了1800个SOL。

第三个地址出价，以1800 SOL赢得了NFT。这1800SOL...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sohojt/melania_trumps_nft_was_sold_for_170000_toherself/?score=470&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsohojt%2Fmelania_trumps_nft_was_sold_for_170000_toherself%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsohojt%2Fmelania_trumps_nft_was_sold_for_170000_toherself%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sohojt/melania_trumps_nft_was_sold_for_170000_toherself/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 20:39:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The address (aka address #1) that minted the NFT sent 473,657.64 USDC to an intermediary address (#2). The intermediary address swaps some of that USDC for 1,816.08 SOL. Then Address #2 sends 1800 SOL to a 3rd address.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The third address makes a bid and wins the NFT for 1800 SOL. That 1800 SOL goes to address #1 (the one that minted the NFT). Then address #1 sends the 1800 to the intermediary Address #2. The intermediary address swaps the 1800 SOL to USDC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Blockchains, amirite?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Credit to user @zachxbt on twitter did the digging here.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here it is on the solana explorer: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://explorer.solana.com/address/JB21HTccXiiyZUYpdWxoy1nSu6zbMBVKBQz1if85d7ud&quot;&amp;gt;https://explorer.solana.com/address/JB21HTccXiiyZUYpdWxoy1nSu6zbMBVKBQz1if85d7ud&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here is an article on it: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7vpx8/analyzing-the-very-bizarre-sale-of-melania-trumps-dollar170000-nft&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7vpx8/analyzing-the-very-bizarre-sale-of-melania-trumps-dollar170000-nft&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[人们说投资加密货币的风险太大，然而结婚却被社会美化和接受。为什么呢？婚姻是风险更大的投资。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在美国，一场婚礼的平均费用大约是20,000美元。这还只是
的婚礼。随着离婚率的稳步上升，婚姻是
一个人在他/她的一生中可能做出的最有风险、最不利的投资。

那么，假设你和你的另一半决定离婚....。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sojzqo/people_say_investing_in_crypto_is_too_risky_yet/?score=344&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsojzqo%2Fpeople_say_investing_in_crypto_is_too_risky_yet%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsojzqo%2Fpeople_say_investing_in_crypto_is_too_risky_yet%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sojzqo/people_say_investing_in_crypto_is_too_risky_yet/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 20:39:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The average cost of a wedding is roughly $20,000 here in the USA. That’s just for the wedding. With the divorce rate steadily increasing, a marriage is the most risky, unfavorable investment one could make in his/her entire life. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then, let’s say you and your significant other decides to divorce. Attorney fees, and divorce filings can well exceed $10k (If you’re lucky) and that’s not even taking into account your significant other taking half of your shit + child support if you have children. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Society is programmed into thinking getting married and having children is happiness. Don’t get me wrong, of course there’s happiness and love involved, but almost 65% of men and women find out the hard way there is A LOT of financial suffering involved too. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In conclusion, investing in Crypto is a risk, but so is living the blueprint model of happiness and success. Investing in crypto seems a lot safer than getting married to one person for the rest of your life. I’m just saying.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto.com宣布成为一级方程式Crypto.com迈阿密大奖赛的官方冠名合作伙伴]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soenkl/cryptocom_announced_as_official_title_partner_of/?score=395&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoenkl%2Fcryptocom_announced_as_official_title_partner_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoenkl%2Fcryptocom_announced_as_official_title_partner_of%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soenkl/cryptocom_announced_as_official_title_partner_of/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 18:47:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爆炸性新闻：俄罗斯将把#比特币作为一种货币对待! 😱]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491437217608507393/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491437217608507393/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 16:36:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BBC和加密货币媒体。"20岁的年轻人通过交易加密货币将50美元变成了800万美元，他设立的代币已经为慈善机构募集了25万美元的资金😍" 他们没有报道的是，那个代币在10月关闭了，似乎是一个骗局？]]></title><description><![CDATA[今天，英国广播公司(BBC)有一个健康的故事，并得到一些加密货币 "媒体 "的响应。
"媒体 "报道了一个年轻的加密货币百万富翁，在几个月内将50美元变成了数百万美元。
几个月内交易加密货币。好吧，这听起来有点难以置信，但还有更多的
的故事。

他们报告说，他正在回馈给...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sobivz/bbc_and_crypto_media_20yearold_turned_50_into_8m/?score=315&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsobivz%2Fbbc_and_crypto_media_20yearold_turned_50_into_8m%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsobivz%2Fbbc_and_crypto_media_20yearold_turned_50_into_8m%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sobivz/bbc_and_crypto_media_20yearold_turned_50_into_8m/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 16:36:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There is a wholesome story going around by the BBC today, echoed by some crypto &amp;amp;quot;media&amp;amp;quot; about a young crypto millionaire that turned $50 into millions within months trading crypto. Okay, this sound somewhat unbelievable, but there&amp;amp;#39;s more to the story.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They report, he is giving back to the community and &amp;amp;quot;A cryptocurrency he set up to support charity has already seen more than £200,000 spent on causes, and he is looking to use further funds raised by his currency to realise his foodbank plans for his home town of Birmingham.&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The problem is: that token shut down in October, as a &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/jimwaterson/status/1491361991541538817&quot;&amp;gt;Twitter user&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; found out through a short search. If you look at their &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/Orfano/&quot;&amp;gt;subreddit&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; it&amp;amp;#39;s dead and people don&amp;amp;#39;t seem very happy - it seemingly was a scam.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What the fuck? I know crypto reporting in mainstream media is often bad, and crypto media is always awful, but how can such a big medium publish such a story without the most basic research?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Edit: seems like the BBC article was taken down! You can find an archived version &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sobivz/bbc_and_crypto_media_20yearold_turned_50_into_8m/hw7ofvc/&quot;&amp;gt;in my reply here&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; (I don&amp;amp;#39;t want to link it directly as my post couldn&amp;amp;#39;t be posted with the link originally)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爆炸：首相鲍里斯-约翰逊宣布，政府将提前一个月取消英格兰的所有Covid限制，包括自我隔离的法律要求。

 https://t.co/xWwAM6JF6x]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491431981531680768/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491431981531680768/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 15:37:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coinbase窃取了我的Eth存款，并无视我与他们的通信。快速搜索一下他们的支持子，发现他们经常这样做，而且显然他们是在逃避。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我把ETH从一个我用过很多次的地址存入我的CB地址，我已经用过很多次了。
我已经使用了很多次，没有任何问题。存款是在2021年圣诞节那天进行的。

我收到了通常的CB电子邮件，说他们收到了我的存款，并且Tx是
在Etherscan上确认。

这些硬币从未被放入我的投资组合。

I...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sode68/coinbase_have_stolen_my_eth_deposit_and_ignored/?score=855&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsode68%2Fcoinbase_have_stolen_my_eth_deposit_and_ignored%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsode68%2Fcoinbase_have_stolen_my_eth_deposit_and_ignored%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sode68/coinbase_have_stolen_my_eth_deposit_and_ignored/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 15:37:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I deposited ETH, from an address I have used many times, to my CB address I have used many times without issues. Deposit made on Christmas day 2021.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I got the usual CB email saying they&amp;amp;#39;d received my deposit, and the tx is confirmed on etherscan.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The coins were never put into my portfolio.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I opened a support ticket, and got a vague non-answer by reply (we&amp;amp;#39;re looking into it). It was promptly closed without explanation. I have since opened another 3 tickets which have all been met with similar vague responses, and then the tickets are closed without explanation. My requests to make a complaint have been ignored. I posted on their subreddit 2 weeks ago and got another vague response, no DMs etc.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ve posted there again today but don&amp;amp;#39;t expect much.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My account is not suspended etc., I am still able to transact with existing funds and deposit fiat. I tested this yesterday.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The funny thing is I trade high volume and had I continued using CBP, I would have paid them multiples of the value of this deposit in fees over the next 12 months. Congrats, you played yourselves.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I was able to live with CBP constantly going down during periods of volatility (sus AF!) but this is crossing the line.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;I am purely posting to encourage others to stay away from coinbase and CBP.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; I am not the first person this has happened to. There are literally hundreds of posts like mine on their support sub where people have had funds vanish and the support team just ignores them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Aside from this their fee structure sucks anyway. People seem think CBP is the cheapest for fees but they&amp;amp;#39;re only the cheapest if you trade over $100k per month. I only used them because it was a quick cash onramp from my Revolut account. I&amp;amp;#39;ll be sticking with Binance and Kraken from here on out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Be careful where you leave your funds.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: Lots of people doubting the legitimacy of my post which I guess is healthy skepticism. When I get home from work I will redact my personal details and edit in links to my (very one sided) correspondence with Coinbase.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯将承认比特币为货币]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sob3c0/russia_to_recognize_bitcoin_as_currency/?score=554&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsob3c0%2Frussia_to_recognize_bitcoin_as_currency%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsob3c0%2Frussia_to_recognize_bitcoin_as_currency%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sob3c0/russia_to_recognize_bitcoin_as_currency/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 15:37:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[拖车公司拒绝拖走堵塞渥太华的大卡车 
https://t.co/0uo4EI7XMX]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491400537606361088/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491400537606361088/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 14:37:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[法官命令渥太华警方将没收的燃料归还给卡车司机。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491399794778341379/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491399794778341379/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 14:37:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯不会禁止加密货币，而是对其进行监管并将其作为货币对待]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/so8ys0/russia_wont_ban_cryptocurrencies_will_regulate/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fso8ys0%2Frussia_wont_ban_cryptocurrencies_will_regulate%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fso8ys0%2Frussia_wont_ban_cryptocurrencies_will_regulate%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/so8ys0/russia_wont_ban_cryptocurrencies_will_regulate/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 14:31:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯政府和俄罗斯银行已同意像监管货币一样监管加密货币，而不是资产]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯银行希望俄罗斯政府宣布使用
加密货币在俄罗斯是非法的，但不是禁止使用
但俄罗斯政府和俄罗斯银行并没有禁止使用加密货币，而是同意
加密货币在俄罗斯将被视为货币的一种类似物
和...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/so7ru7/the_russian_government_and_the_bank_of_russia/?score=374&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fso7ru7%2Fthe_russian_government_and_the_bank_of_russia%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fso7ru7%2Fthe_russian_government_and_the_bank_of_russia%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/so7ru7/the_russian_government_and_the_bank_of_russia/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 14:31:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Bank of Russia wanted the Russian government to declare the use of cryptocurrencies illegal in Russia, but instead of banning the use cryptocurrencies, the Russian government and the Bank of Russian have agreed that cryptocurrencies will be recognized as an analogue of currencies in Russia and they will be regulated as such.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;From this newspaper that is nationally distributed in Russia: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kommersant.ru/doc/5206307&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.kommersant.ru/doc/5206307&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The government and the Bank of Russia have agreed on a future regime for the circulation of cryptocurrencies in Russia: before February 18, they will prepare a draft law on the circulation of digital currencies in the Russian Federation, in which cryptocurrencies are recognized as an analogue of currencies, and not digital financial assets (DFA). Their circulation in the legal sector will be possible only with full identification, through the banking system or licensed intermediaries. Operations equivalent to more than 600 thousand rubles must be declared, transactions outside the legal sector for such amounts will become a criminal offense and an aggravating circumstance under the Criminal Code, fines will be introduced for the illegal acceptance of cryptocurrencies as a means of payment. Mining and related issues of DFA are not affected by the concept within which the project is being prepared.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The government, after meetings with Deputy Prime Minister, Chief of Staff of the White House Dmitry Grigorenko, published the approved &amp;amp;quot;Concept for regulating the mechanisms for organizing the circulation of digital currencies.&amp;amp;quot; Recall that the White House has been discussing the new status of cryptocurrencies and digital currencies in the Russian Federation since the summer of 2021, in January 2021 a road map was created on this issue, the Bank of Russia made a consultative report proposing to ban the circulation of cryptocurrencies in the Russian Federation, the Ministry of Finance - with its own development on this topic. The final concept is mainly based on the positions of the Ministry of Finance.Until February 18, the ministry and the Bank of Russia must formulate either a separate bill or amendments to the law on the CFA and other laws for its implementation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The details of the &amp;amp;quot;transition period&amp;amp;quot;, as well as mining, are not discussed by the concept. Meanwhile, they are quite important: the regulation of turnover will require quick decisions from cryptocurrency owners - whether they should move into the emerging legal market segment, get rid of such assets, or stay in the illegal sector. The main difference between the concept, which, in fact, implements the Central Bank&amp;amp;#39;s strong distrust of cryptocurrency, is the proposal to develop amendments to the Criminal Code and the Code of Criminal Procedure, according to which evasion of declaring transactions with cryptocurrency will become a criminal offense, and its use will become an aggravating circumstance in other offenses.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The possession of cryptocurrency in the jurisdiction of the Russian Federation and transactions with it (as well as with the dollar) are not prohibited - but only through the &amp;amp;quot;organizer of the digital currency exchange system&amp;amp;quot; (a bank with a universal license) or a p2p exchanger legalized in the Russian Federation. The mode of operation of the legal segment involves the full identification of the client according to banking rules, work taking into account AML / CFT requirements, all information about transactions through the Transparent Blockchain system of Rosfinmonitoring will be available for state control in the same way as transactions with non-cash rubles or foreign currency on bank accounts. The mode of control over transactions with the cryptocurrency of natural persons, however, is described by the concept as not too different from the mode of control over cash transactions with any currency. Most likely, the main argument “for” was that in the USA, the EU and Japan they are inclined to the same or to strict bans, as in China, which was also proposed by the Bank of Russia.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So far, the most intriguing is the organization of the legalization of the existing undeclared cryptocurrency, which is not described in the concept. Market participants have no doubts that the possibilities of working with &amp;amp;quot;legal crypto&amp;amp;quot; in the implementation of the concept are adequate. The same part of the owners who prefer to remain in the sector illegal for the jurisdiction of the Russian Federation depends on the future taxation of operations with cryptocurrencies (from the meaning of the concept it follows that it should not differ from the principles of holding foreign currency) and on the rules of legalization. The Ministry of Finance&amp;amp;#39;s estimate of the total amount of crypto assets in the Russian Federation has not changed - it is 12 million crypto wallets with assets worth 2 trillion rubles. It is decidedly unknown whether this figure takes into account the cryptocurrency used in the criminal sector, obviously.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[最有趣的时间线是俄罗斯在美国之前就有一个现货#比特币ETF，而斯诺登一直在抨击美国，认为它仍然是全球自由的领导者。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491374635161878532/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491374635161878532/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币是全球性的]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/so4azf/bitcoin_is_global/?score=414&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fso4azf%2Fbitcoin_is_global%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fso4azf%2Fbitcoin_is_global%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/so4azf/bitcoin_is_global/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 12:46:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我们怎么能诚实地相信这样一个荒谬的想法：一个有能力入侵10万个BTC的人决定将2000个私钥保存在......云存储中？又如，联邦调查局如何执行历史上最大的金融扣押，以获得36亿美元的BTC。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/snxzp1/how_can_we_honestly_believe_the_absurd_notion/?score=341&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsnxzp1%2Fhow_can_we_honestly_believe_the_absurd_notion%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsnxzp1%2Fhow_can_we_honestly_believe_the_absurd_notion%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/snxzp1/how_can_we_honestly_believe_the_absurd_notion/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 12:46:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你要犯大错，Metamask应该警告你，就像你的反病毒软件或网络浏览器会警告你一样--这与集中化或分散化没有关系。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这不是一个关于分权或集权的问题。这也是
也不仅仅是一个简单的 "好 "的功能。想象一下，你浏览的网站
故意将你的I.P.地址和其他信息卖给黑客和其他
恶意行为者可以公开看到你在做什么和你的...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snrvt9/metamask_should_warn_you_if_you_are_about_to_make/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnrvt9%2Fmetamask_should_warn_you_if_you_are_about_to_make%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnrvt9%2Fmetamask_should_warn_you_if_you_are_about_to_make%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snrvt9/metamask_should_warn_you_if_you_are_about_to_make/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 12:46:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This isn&amp;amp;#39;t a question about about decentralization or centralization. This is also more than just a simple nice-to-have feature. Imagine you browse websites that knowingly sell your I.P. address and other information to hackers and other malicious actors can openly see what you&amp;amp;#39;re doing and your physical location on a map. Isn&amp;amp;#39;t that dangerous? Don&amp;amp;#39;t our Anti-virus softwares and web browsers stop us from doing these things? Don&amp;amp;#39;t all windows machines have these installed by default?               &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It feels like this is one of those topics that 5 or 10 years down the road, none of us will be discussing because it&amp;amp;#39;s already been implemented for a long long time. If you guys used the first iterations of the internet where you had to memorize I.P. Addresses because there were no DNS names to get to some places online, then pretty much everyone here would agree that no one would use the internet of the late 80s and early 90s today if it were still the same way.                  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To the people who say, &amp;amp;quot;If you have lots of money in ETH or BTC and you are sending it to an address by mistake, it&amp;amp;#39;s your fuck up and you deserve to lose your money.&amp;amp;quot; You&amp;amp;#39;re missing the point completely. The point is that your antivirus warns you when you are about to make a massive mistake that could lead to something like ransomware, spyware, or trojans getting installed to your PC. I think it would be great to have Metamask fire off an audible warning and a message that says, &amp;amp;quot;The wallet address you are sending funds to is a known contract address and not a hot wallet. The funds you send will not be used by any human being and will be lost forever. Do you wish to continue?&amp;amp;quot; seems fine. Maybe stack it with, something like, &amp;amp;quot;This address is to a known wallet address of an Exchange that suffered a security breach and has ended service to their customers. The funds you send to this wallet address will likely be lost forever.&amp;amp;quot; Not bad...              &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But what if we have someone whose account on an exchange was terminated and then all of the exchanges got together and said, &amp;amp;quot;Let&amp;amp;#39;s make a database of irrecoverable wallet addresses where terminated / irretrievable 0x addresses exist so that users don&amp;amp;#39;t send funds to them by mistake, and let the people at Metamask know this as well.&amp;amp;quot; Sounds like an interesting value proposition.                  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Finally, by improving the way wallets function we are increasing adoption by eliminating one route where users can screw up simply by stopping them from making a mistake and making them double check an address they send funds to.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;                &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;And I almost forgot: To be clear, I am NOT advocating that wallets block transactions at all. If the user is fully aware of what they are doing, then the opus is on them.&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[人们想回到过去购买BTC，然而他们现在正在睡觉。]]></title><description><![CDATA[每个人都在谈论错过的机会，但有时机会就在他们面前，他们却没有利用，没有认识到。
机会就在他们面前，但他们却没有利用，没有认识到。
人们还在 "在这里插入你最喜欢的硬币 "上睡觉。如果你想
买入BTC或ETH，现在就去做吧! 如果你想买ADA，NANO，DOT，...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snuhg5/people_wants_to_go_back_in_time_to_buy_btc_yet/?score=314&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnuhg5%2Fpeople_wants_to_go_back_in_time_to_buy_btc_yet%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnuhg5%2Fpeople_wants_to_go_back_in_time_to_buy_btc_yet%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snuhg5/people_wants_to_go_back_in_time_to_buy_btc_yet/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 12:46:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Everyone talks about missed opportunities, but sometimes the opportunities are right in front of them and they fail to take advantage, to recognise them. People are still sleeping on &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;”insert your favourite coin here”&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;. If you want to buy BTC or ETH, do it now! If you want to buy ADA, NANO, DOT, MONERO, ETH, MATIC, AAVE, ALGO, UNI, LTC or any from the 11,000~ cryptos, do it now !&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sometimes, luck is when opportunity meets preparation. The opportunity of a lifetime has been in front of people for a months if not years now! Many people dismiss crypto because they don’t understand it. Instead of giving an hour of their time to begin learning about the problems that crypto solves.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Stop listening to good ol’ banks. They don’t care about you. Be aware, and have clear frame of mind.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Born too late to explore the Earth. Born too early to explore the stars. But born just in time to invest in Cryptocurrency. Don’t hesitate to take opportunities. It’s your time now !&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[给我的荷兰追随者

紧急：签署请愿书，要求立即废除荷兰的科罗纳票。

1) 填写：姓名、电子邮件、城市
2) 通过你将收到的电子邮件确认

已经有80万个签名了!

服务器再次上线
请转发🙏
https://t.co/2aUGK1VK2A]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491369870889713672/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491369870889713672/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 11:42:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爆炸性新闻：据俄罗斯《生意人报》报道，俄罗斯政府和中央银行刚刚就加密货币达成协议。

两个组织将把比特币和加密资产作为货币对待。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491372730901725184/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491372730901725184/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 11:42:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[JUST IN - 加拿大。艾伯塔省省长杰森-肯尼宣布，将于今晚午夜取消疫苗护照计划。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491371515085934593/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491371515085934593/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 11:42:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[找到我2013年的钱包]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以当我13岁的时候，我了解了比特币并开始在我的游戏电脑上挖矿。
电脑上挖。一段时间后失去了兴趣，比特币爆炸了，我感叹年轻的我的错误。
等等

通过我以前的谷歌硬盘，找到了我的钱包，问题是--我完全不知道如何访问它/。
我完全不知道如何访问它/如果我能访问它。这是个...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/so8dlp/found_my_wallet_from_2013/?score=504&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fso8dlp%2Ffound_my_wallet_from_2013%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fso8dlp%2Ffound_my_wallet_from_2013%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/so8dlp/found_my_wallet_from_2013/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 10:44:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So when I was 13, I learned about bitcoin and starting mining it on my gaming PC. Lost interest after a while, bitcoin blows up, I lament young me’s error, etc&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Went through my old google drive and found my wallet, problem is - I have absolutely no idea how to access it / if I can access it. It’s a text file with .aes.json file extension at the end of the title. I know it’s my wallet since that’s what the document is titled.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Any advice here or is this just a lost cause? I know absolutely nothing about crypto besides surface level knowledge.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit - Rip DM’s&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[对于每个使用Brave浏览器的人来说]]></title><description><![CDATA[一个本月获得12.25个BAT的人最近的帖子获得了相当多的关注。
牵引力。我注意到，许多人在评论中提到他们
每小时只收到1或2个添加。

如果你的Brave已经更新，你可以导航到奖励设置（在Brave的
奖励窗口），并从那里...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snh7rs/for_everyone_using_the_brave_browser/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnh7rs%2Ffor_everyone_using_the_brave_browser%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnh7rs%2Ffor_everyone_using_the_brave_browser%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snh7rs/for_everyone_using_the_brave_browser/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 09:32:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Recent post from a person gaining 12.25 BAT this month gained quite some traction. I noticed that many people mentioned in the comments that they are only receiving 1 or 2 adds per hour.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If your Brave is updated you can navigate to Reward Settings (in the Brave Rewards window), and from there click on the icon on the right of Brave Private Ads. This will bring up a menu that lets you specify how many adds per hour you are limited do.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now, I don&amp;amp;#39;t know how it possible to get 12.25 BAT, but I was previously getting close to 1 with being locked to 5 ads per hour. Being locked to 10 should net you close to 2 or even 3 if you are browsing a lot.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Welcome!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯将承认加密货币为一种货币形式]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/so5z5p/russia_set_to_recognize_crypto_as_a_form_of/?score=447&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fso5z5p%2Frussia_set_to_recognize_crypto_as_a_form_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fso5z5p%2Frussia_set_to_recognize_crypto_as_a_form_of%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/so5z5p/russia_set_to_recognize_crypto_as_a_form_of/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 09:32:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我读了凯西-伍德的方舟投资公司的132页 "2022年大想法 "报告。所以你不必这样做]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你不认识她，凯西-伍德是一位基金经理（Ark Invest），她在2020/21年因一系列非常成功的投资/市场押注而崛起。
在一系列非常成功的投资/市场赌注之后，她在2020/21年崭露头角。

她是颠覆性技术的坚定信仰者。

认为机器人技术、明天的电池和基因组学以及erm.....。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snx7rw/i_read_cathie_woods_ark_invests_132_page_big/?score=338&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnx7rw%2Fi_read_cathie_woods_ark_invests_132_page_big%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnx7rw%2Fi_read_cathie_woods_ark_invests_132_page_big%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snx7rw/i_read_cathie_woods_ark_invests_132_page_big/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 08:35:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you don’t know her, Cathie Wood is a fund manager (Ark Invest) who rose to prominence in 2020/21 after a series of very successful investments/market bets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;She is a strong believer in disruptive technologies.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Think robotics, tomorrow’s batteries and genomics as well as erm.. blockchain technology and is perhaps &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;the most bullish person&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; on crypto.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;She recently predicted that BTC will be worth &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;over $1M by 2030&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, making her perhaps the most bullish person I know.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Allow me to summarize the report’s highlights on the future of Bitcoin..&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Ark Invest analysts predict that the market capitalization of blockchain technology will reach $49T in 2030.&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That’s roughly &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;half&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; what the global equities market is worth today ($106T).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cathie Wood predicts that &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;more than half (57%)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; of that market cap will come from Bitcoin alone; believing Bitcoin’s market cap will climb to &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$28T by 2030.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Currently, Bitcoin&amp;amp;#39;s market cap stands at $815B, down from an ATH of around $1.2T.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And this is where she gets her $1M/BTC price point from (more details on that at the end of this post).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;According to Cathie Wood, El Salvador’s Bitcoin “experiment” is already a resounding success.&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Why?&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; The data &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;speaks volumes.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;# of people in El Salvador with a Bitcoin wallet = &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;3.8 million&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;# of people in El Salvador with a traditional bank account = &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;1.9 million&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The % of eligible citizens with a Bitcoin wallet in El Salvador is 84% as of December 2021, versus 42% with a traditional bank account.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What’s more bullish is people are actually using these wallets!&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Bitcoin wallets in El Salvador settled (on average) &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$2M worth of transactions in remittances DAILY&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; as of October 2021.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;On an annual basis, this accounts for roughly &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;12% of ALL remittances sent&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; to El Salvador (total = $6B annually, or &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;2% of El Salvador’s overall GDP&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Reader’s Note I — Remittances are money transfers sent from one party who works abroad to another in their home country (typically family).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;And El Salvador is not alone..&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;2021 was the year that Bitcoin’s annual settlement volume &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;surpassed that of Visa’s.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin’s total came to a whopping &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$13.1T, or ~120% of Visa’s.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is effectively a &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;5x increase&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; on the previous year ($2.3T in 2020, ~24% of the Visa network’s).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, is the Bitcoin network becoming more dominated by larger investors with deeper pockets?!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&amp;gt;Well.. probably.&amp;lt;/span&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The average value of each individual transaction in 2021 was $136,555. This is up from $21,590 in 2020, significantly more than the increase in Bitcoin’s price over the same period.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This makes sense as ETFs, countries and companies have all increased their BTC holdings in 2021 and now hold roughly 1.5 million BTC. Or, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;8% of the total circulating supply.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The 5 largest publicly disclosed bitcoin wallets belong to the (1) Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (2) Block One (3) Microstrategy (4) CoinShares and (5) Tesla.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;But what about me, you and the annoying Karen you avoid on the school run?&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Believe it or not, most Bitcoin investors in 2021 were not speculators.&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The number of BTC long term holders has been steadily increasing since 2011, except for a substantial “blip” back in 2018. Understandable.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This trend has continued throughout the most recent bull run in 2020/21.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Long term investors now collectively hold &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;13.5m Bitcoin&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, or more than half of all BTC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Reader’s Note II — A “long term investor” is defined by Ark Invest as someone who has held their BTC for more than 155 days.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Reader’s Note III — Yes, they removed any wallets with “dust” BTC from the data.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;So how does Cathie Wood arrive at the $28T BTC market cap by 2030?&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Is she, like all of us, drunk on hopium?&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ll give you the figures and let you make your mind up:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Reader’s Note IV — Important For Context..  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Gold’s market capitalization is $10T (2021)  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The global equities market has an overall market capitalization of $106T (2021)  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In their analysis, Ark Invest chose to project BTC’s 2030 market cap using 2021 data rather than “&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;projected&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;” 2030 data/guesswork.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now For The Juice:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;BTC will become the new “digital gold” and account for a whopping 50% of gold’s market cap by 2030 — or, $5.5T.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;More S&amp;amp;amp;P companies will keep BTC on their balance sheets (like Tesla). Ark Invest estimates 5% of balance sheets will be kept in BTC — adding another $4.2T.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Institutions are not far behind and will keep 2.55% of assets in BTC — accounting for $4.1T.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;High Net Worth Individuals will dedicate 5% of their portfolios to BTC — that’s another $4.0T right there.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Nation-states will keep 1% of their reserves in BTC — providing a further $3.8T in “value” to the market.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;US Banks will get in on the action too and use BTC for 25% of all inter-bank settlements — that’s another $3.8T.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;BTC will have replaced fiat currencies in emerging markets at a rate of around 10% by 2030 — or, $2.8T.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Finally, BTC will account for 50% of all global remittances — adding a relatively meagre $0.3T.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&amp;gt;Grand Total = $28.5T (equal to $1.36M/BTC)&amp;lt;/span&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Reader’s Note V — For those interested, I personally think some of these numbers are actually conservative especially as (mentioned earlier) they’re based on 2021 market capitalization rather than “projected” 2030 market caps.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Obv there is so much more in the report about blockchain tech and DeFi, but I chose to focus on BTC in this post because I, honestly, already doubt anyone will read this considering its length so it doesn’t need to be any longer.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyway, I’m sorry if I bored you and you’re most welcome if you happened to read and appreciate this post :)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我们又开始了对中国的疑虑]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sns6yu/here_we_go_with_the_china_fud_again/?score=319&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsns6yu%2Fhere_we_go_with_the_china_fud_again%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsns6yu%2Fhere_we_go_with_the_china_fud_again%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sns6yu/here_we_go_with_the_china_fud_again/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 06:35:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[招聘人员说，随着工人们逃离谷歌和亚马逊，转而投向加密货币和Web3创业公司，硅谷不再是前卫的科技前沿阵地。"他们的飞跃部分是为了尽早兑现他们所认为的行业的未来。"]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/so0fg9/silicon_valley_is_no_longer_the_edgy_tech/?score=408&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fso0fg9%2Fsilicon_valley_is_no_longer_the_edgy_tech%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fso0fg9%2Fsilicon_valley_is_no_longer_the_edgy_tech%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/so0fg9/silicon_valley_is_no_longer_the_edgy_tech/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 06:35:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[确保在超级碗广告中寻找复活节彩蛋，这可能是值得的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们一直听说在即将到来的超级碗LVI中，将有一堆传闻中的加密市场的商业广告。
传闻中来自加密市场的广告，包括来自crypto.com
[https://crypto.com]，coinbase，甚至可能是dogecoin。对于crypto.com
[https://crypto.com] 最有可能的是，马特-达蒙将再次出现。但是...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snxksz/make_sure_to_look_for_easter_eggs_during_super/?score=353&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnxksz%2Fmake_sure_to_look_for_easter_eggs_during_super%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnxksz%2Fmake_sure_to_look_for_easter_eggs_during_super%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snxksz/make_sure_to_look_for_easter_eggs_during_super/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 05:38:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We been hearing that the coming  Super Bowl LVI there is going to be a bunch of rumored commercial from the cryptomarket including one from &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://crypto.com&quot;&amp;gt;crypto.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, coinbase and may be even dogecoin .  For &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://crypto.com&quot;&amp;gt;crypto.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; most likely Matt Damon is going to appear again.  But did you know that in the last commercial there was a hidden Easter egg, hidden to the side, below is the image&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/j9tdy8pybog81.png?width=686&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=f528560f443709228ff4478efd79ef796e8f732d&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/j9tdy8pybog81.png?width=686&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=f528560f443709228ff4478efd79ef796e8f732d&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;you see that QR code hidden to the side? Well had you scan that code; it would had taken you to a website which you can register and then get a free airdrop.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyways, this super bow, the entire US is going to be watching and I think speculate that buried in those commercials might be some other hidden easter eggs, may be not QR codes but something else.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I don&amp;amp;#39;t think its going to be much even if there are easter eggs but hey free money and the chance to brag that you found it on your own.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let the hunt begin.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国司法部刚刚扣押了36亿美元的加密货币，并逮捕了与2016年Bitfinex黑客攻击有关的两人。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snoqjp/the_us_doj_just_seized_36_billion_in_crypto_and/?score=349&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnoqjp%2Fthe_us_doj_just_seized_36_billion_in_crypto_and%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnoqjp%2Fthe_us_doj_just_seized_36_billion_in_crypto_and%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snoqjp/the_us_doj_just_seized_36_billion_in_crypto_and/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 22:42:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美国官员查获2016年Bitfinex黑客攻击的比特币 | 联邦官员周二查获价值约36亿美元的比特币，与2016年加密货币交易所Bitfinex被黑有关。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/snosgv/us_officials_seize_bitcoin_from_2016_bitfinex/?score=316&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsnosgv%2Fus_officials_seize_bitcoin_from_2016_bitfinex%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsnosgv%2Fus_officials_seize_bitcoin_from_2016_bitfinex%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/snosgv/us_officials_seize_bitcoin_from_2016_bitfinex/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 22:42:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[第三次是个好机会？https://t.co/tCacirJO9v]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491157645805617152/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1491157645805617152/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 21:40:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>