<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[加密货币国外热门讨论]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 22:45:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[亿万富翁对冲基金创始人Ken Griffin软化了他的反加密立场："我在这个电话上并不正确]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5tmhf/billionaire_hedge_fund_founder_ken_griffin/?score=323&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5tmhf%2Fbillionaire_hedge_fund_founder_ken_griffin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5tmhf%2Fbillionaire_hedge_fund_founder_ken_griffin%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5tmhf/billionaire_hedge_fund_founder_ken_griffin/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 21:36:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币将在卢加诺成为合法货币!]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t5vygy/bitcoin_will_become_legal_tender_in_lugano/?score=309&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft5vygy%2Fbitcoin_will_become_legal_tender_in_lugano%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft5vygy%2Fbitcoin_will_become_legal_tender_in_lugano%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t5vygy/bitcoin_will_become_legal_tender_in_lugano/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 21:36:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你这样说的时候，多么有趣。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t5qrad/how_funny_when_you_say_it_like_this/?score=323&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft5qrad%2Fhow_funny_when_you_say_it_like_this%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft5qrad%2Fhow_funny_when_you_say_it_like_this%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t5qrad/how_funny_when_you_say_it_like_this/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 21:36:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Algorand状态证明在这里! 这是个大问题! Algorand状态证明是一种新的互操作性标准，可以安全地将区块链与外部世界连接起来，而不需要信任中介。所有的权益证明链都可以实施状态证明，以便从跨链的方程式中消除信任。]]></title><description><![CDATA[区块链生态系统就像城市：每个城市都提供价值，吸引人们
的价值--从商业机会、社区、娱乐。
基础设施、地方治理，以及普通的个人偏好。随着这个行业的
随着行业的成熟，人们将有更多理由访问不同的...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5wcvx/algorand_state_proofs_are_here_this_is_huge/?score=338&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5wcvx%2Falgorand_state_proofs_are_here_this_is_huge%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5wcvx%2Falgorand_state_proofs_are_here_this_is_huge%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5wcvx/algorand_state_proofs_are_here_this_is_huge/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 20:34:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Blockchain ecosystems are like cities: each one provides value that draws people to visit — ranging from business opportunities, community, entertainment, infrastructure, local governance, to plain personal preference. As the industry matures, people will have more reasons to visit different ecosystems, driving more value into cross-chain applications.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In order to access your source blockchain in new ecosystems, you need a reliable way to verify its “state” (a snapshot of account balances and transactions) in the new environment. This trustless infrastructure is currently missing from the market, so people have turned to trusted intermediaries, like centralized bridges and validator networks, to handle their assets. Layer-1 blockchains share a responsibility to reduce this trust threshold in order to protect on-chain value.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Algorand State Proofs (ASPs) are a new interoperability standard that extends trustless interactions beyond a blockchain’s native ecosystem. Through &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/codechain/blockchain-light-client-1171dfa1269a&quot;&amp;gt;light clients&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; (efficient software that tracks blockchain state), they provide a simple, trustless interface to build powerful applications conditioned by multiple blockchains’ events. State Proofs can be implemented on all Proof of Stake chains, and will accelerate our collective path towards true decentralization.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Algorand State Proofs fortify cross-chain applications with Post-Quantum security. By using advanced cryptography, ASPs can withstand attacks by powerful quantum computers that try to alter the reported state of the blockchain, providing a robust, portable source of truth about on-chain data.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;From trustless bridges that move assets across blockchains to decentralized oracles that export valuable on-chain data, people will be able to leverage Algorand’s fast, cheap, and reliable protocol in new ecosystems without trust in an intermediary–they only need to trust the security of the underlying blockchain itself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Interoperability Problem&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;2021 was an exciting year for the blockchain industry, with a 1,200% growth¹ in the Total Value Locked (TVL) in global DeFi smart contracts, the rise of NFTs, and a diversification across many Layer-1 chains. The promise of a thriving, decentralized blockchain ecosystem is nearly here — yet, most dApps are constrained by the very platform they are built upon.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Blockchain communities are looking for reliable ways to use their favorite dApps without paying expensive gas fees, dealing with network outages, or trusting intermediaries with their valued assets.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Developers want to build on fast and inexpensive blockchains like Algorand, and want immediate access to an expanded user base and liquidity scattered across several ecosystems.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Investors seek exciting opportunities on multiple platforms without switching chains or turning to more centralized alternatives.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;People want to send basic transactions across blockchains in a trustless manner.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Developers, creators, and investors are looking for interoperability solutions that break them out of their walled gardens. ASPs remove these boundaries and open the doors to cross-chain applications and liquidity.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Bridging Solution&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To solve these interoperability problems, many companies have built bridges that move assets across blockchains. These “bridged” assets can be freely used in the target chain’s ecosystem: lent out as collateral for a loan, traded for another asset, or simply held in a wallet.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;While bridges show promise, most solutions require people to trust the bridge operator or a set of delegates to store and move their assets in a secure, timely manner. With over $32 billion worth of assets already held in cross-chain bridges (up from $670 million at the start of 2021)², the industry has created a new, centralized attack surface with a large target.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We have an opportunity to eliminate trust from the interoperability equation, creating a new breed of trustless bridges and cross-chain applications that don’t compromise on cost, reliability, or security.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Algorand State Proofs&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Introducing Algorand State Proofs: new blockchain infrastructure that connects Algorand to the broader world. ASPs are an &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://people.csail.mit.edu/nickolai/papers/micali-compactcert-eprint.pdf&quot;&amp;gt;immutable chain of proofs&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; that attest to the state of the Algorand blockchain. They let anyone track Algorand transactions, balances, and application data in low-power environments like a phone, smartwatch, and even inside a blockchain smart contract, without compromising on security — each ASP is produced by the same decentralized network that reaches &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.algorand.com/technology/pure-proof-of-stake&quot;&amp;gt;consensus&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; on new blocks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Due to their lightweight, portable nature, ASPs can be used to update Algorand light clients in other ecosystems. To lower costs in fee-constrained environments like Ethereum, Algorand will also produce even more compact zk-SNARK proofs that can be used to keep light clients up to date.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Applications like bridges, oracles, and wallets can query these light clients to cryptographically verify Algorand state in a simple, trustless manner. For example, say Alice wants to send Bob 10 AliceCoins from Algorand to Ethereum. AliceCoins are extremely valuable, so they want to make sure the tokens arrive quickly, safely, and without permission from or trust in an intermediary. Alice can send these tokens directly to Bob’s Ethereum wallet via a trustless bridge whose code-base is open to the public.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/99totm7qa7l81.png?width=1400&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=00cdb402e5b39e1072c564816ad169fa54b9e575&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/99totm7qa7l81.png?width=1400&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=00cdb402e5b39e1072c564816ad169fa54b9e575&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Behind the scenes, Alice would “lock” the tokens in the trustless bridge’s &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.algorand.com/smart-contracts-defi&quot;&amp;gt;Algorand smart contract&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, which prevents her from creating duplicate tokens out of thin air. The bridge’s Ethereum smart contract would simply ask the Algorand light client (kept up-to-date by State Proofs) if Alice did, in fact, lock the tokens. Once verified, the bridge would mint and release an equivalent amount on Ethereum to Bob’s chosen wallet.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Similarly, the bridge can trustlessly mint and release bridged Ethereum assets into the Algorand ecosystem using Ethereum light clients. Bridge operators can create Algorand smart contracts that ask these light clients to validate Ethereum transactions (e.g. depositing ETH in an Ethereum smart contract) via Algorand’s &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/algorand/hello-contract-calling-abff8fc00939&quot;&amp;gt;Contract to Contract calls&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. These light client pairs complete the import/export flow for bi-directional bridging.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;The Big Picture&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Algorand State Proofs fortify cross-chain applications with Post-Quantum security. By using advanced cryptography, ASPs can withstand attacks by powerful quantum computers that try to alter the reported state of the blockchain, providing a robust, portable source of truth about on-chain data.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;From trustless bridges that move assets across blockchains to decentralized oracles that export valuable on-chain data, people will be able to leverage Algorand’s fast, cheap, and reliable protocol in new ecosystems without trust in an intermediary–they only need to trust the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.algorand.com/technology/security&quot;&amp;gt;security&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; of the underlying blockchain itself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Roadmap&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Algorand State Proofs will be available soon, with our first milestone going live this month (March 2022). After next week’s consensus upgrade, the Algorand network will start registering the Post-Quantum secure voting keys used to generate ASPs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;link: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/algorand/algorand-state-proofs-707d64038e35&quot;&amp;gt;https://medium.com/algorand/algorand-state-proofs-707d64038e35&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在是否限制俄罗斯账户的问题上，加密货币交易所处于道德两难境地]]></title><description><![CDATA[CZ、Binance和加密货币是否存在？
[https://swapzone.io/currencies?utm_source=reddit&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=promo]
的人难道没有责任站出来，与群众一起平定
经济制裁？他们是否为俄罗斯提供了规避金融制裁的手段？
制裁？是否...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5o5dz/crypto_exchanges_in_moral_dilemma_over_whether_to/?score=328&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5o5dz%2Fcrypto_exchanges_in_moral_dilemma_over_whether_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5o5dz%2Fcrypto_exchanges_in_moral_dilemma_over_whether_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5o5dz/crypto_exchanges_in_moral_dilemma_over_whether_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 20:34:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Does CZ, Binance and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://swapzone.io/currencies?utm_source=reddit&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=social&amp;amp;amp;utm_campaign=promo&quot;&amp;gt;cryptocurrency&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; at large not have a responsibility to stand up and join the masses in levelling economic sanctions? Are they providing Russia a means to circumvent financial sanctions? Are Binance thereby indirectly inhibiting what are, at heart, measures designed to prevent a war and the deaths of countless innocent people?&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
I think we should separate the politicians to the normal people, but the Ukrainian Vice President Mykhailo Fedorov’s appeal to crypto exchanges asking them to sabotage not only politicians accounts, but also ordinary users, what&amp;amp;#39;s your point of view?  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/3y89cyxo55l81.png?width=590&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=06553ff735270781c5c62b84592a70966b73a92c&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/3y89cyxo55l81.png?width=590&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=06553ff735270781c5c62b84592a70966b73a92c&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[安大略省男子上当受骗26万美元，耗尽毕生积蓄后一蹶不振]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5g6em/ontario_man_devastated_after_falling_for_260000/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5g6em%2Fontario_man_devastated_after_falling_for_260000%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5g6em%2Fontario_man_devastated_after_falling_for_260000%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5g6em/ontario_man_devastated_after_falling_for_260000/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 20:34:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[伊丽莎白-沃伦又来了。她现在敦促监管机构 "加强对加密货币的审查，因为它有可能破坏对俄罗斯的制裁"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不明白她对加密货币的痴迷。首先，她开始在推特上谈论如何
监管机构需要加强对加密货币的审查

https://news.bitcoin.com/us-senator-urges-regulators-to-increase-scrutiny-on-crypto-as-it-risks-undermining-sanctions-against-russia/

> 由于世界各国政府正在将...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5uwgg/elizabeth_warren_is_at_it_again_she_is_now_urging/?score=626&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5uwgg%2Felizabeth_warren_is_at_it_again_she_is_now_urging%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5uwgg%2Felizabeth_warren_is_at_it_again_she_is_now_urging%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5uwgg/elizabeth_warren_is_at_it_again_she_is_now_urging/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 18:33:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I dont get her obsession with crypto. First she starts tweeting about how regulators need to increase scrutiny of crypto&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://news.bitcoin.com/us-senator-urges-regulators-to-increase-scrutiny-on-crypto-as-it-risks-undermining-sanctions-against-russia/&quot;&amp;gt;https://news.bitcoin.com/us-senator-urges-regulators-to-increase-scrutiny-on-crypto-as-it-risks-undermining-sanctions-against-russia/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As governments worldwide are placing sanctions on Russia following its invasion of Ukraine, U.S. Senator Elizabeth Warren is worried that cryptocurrency could give Russia a way to evade sanctions. The senator from Massachusetts tweeted Monday:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Cryptocurrencies risk undermining sanctions against Russia, allowing Putin and his cronies to evade economic pain.&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“U.S. financial regulators need to take this threat seriously and increase their scrutiny of digital assets,” she added.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then on wednesday she and three other senators write a letter to Janet Yellen of all people telling her to &amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.warren.senate.gov/oversight/letters/senators-warren-warner-brown-reed-express-concerns-to-treasury-regarding-potential-use-of-cryptocurrency-to-evade-sanctions&quot;&amp;gt;enforce sanctions compliance&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot; in the crypto industry &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;All of this out of a supposed fear that Putin is going to use crypto to bypass sanctions even though its been known for a while now that Russia has been sanction-proofing itself by building up gold and Chinese Yuan reserves. As well as crypto&amp;amp;#39;s marketcap and volatility making it an unsuitable medium for country-scale transactions.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;See why &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://mobile.twitter.com/jchervinsky/status/1498786025438650369&quot;&amp;gt;Russia wont be using crypto to bypass sanctions&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Tired of these politicians pushing their own agendas.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[立法者已经从欧盟最新版本的加密货币立法中删除了 "比特币禁令"。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5opry/lawmakers_have_removed_the_bitcoin_ban_from/?score=360&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5opry%2Flawmakers_have_removed_the_bitcoin_ban_from%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5opry%2Flawmakers_have_removed_the_bitcoin_ban_from%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5opry/lawmakers_have_removed_the_bitcoin_ban_from/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 18:33:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界各国政府是否就这样无视辉瑞公司的不良事件审查？]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1499377654365147138/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1499377654365147138/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 15:43:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[难道只有我不喜欢越来越多的人试图将加密货币和政治混为一谈？]]></title><description><![CDATA[当人们在谈论法规时将加密货币和政治混为一谈，我表示理解。
因为我相信，为了实现大规模的采用，加密货币法规是需要的。
采用。然而，我认为最近事情已经走得太远了。

在过去的几周里（尤其是乌克兰-俄罗斯战争进入了...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5afmp/am_i_the_only_one_who_doesnt_like_how_more_and/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5afmp%2Fam_i_the_only_one_who_doesnt_like_how_more_and%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5afmp%2Fam_i_the_only_one_who_doesnt_like_how_more_and%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5afmp/am_i_the_only_one_who_doesnt_like_how_more_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 14:31:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I understand when people mix crypto and politics when talking about regulations. Since I believe that crypto regulations are needed in order to achieve mass adoption. However, I think that things have gone too far recently. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;During last weeks (especially since the Ukraine-Russian war got into the mainstream) I’m seeing more and more comments of people mixing crypto and politics, and I don’t think this benefits the crypto space nor is it necessary.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto has nothing to do with politics, I understand that personalities like Vitalik, CEO’s of exchanges or other famous crypto personalities talk about politics, they have all the right to do so. But we shouldn’t make the mistake to mix crypto with politics.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[S. 韩国加密货币交易所冻结了约20个俄罗斯账户]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5jpbm/s_korean_crypto_exchange_freezes_around_20/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5jpbm%2Fs_korean_crypto_exchange_freezes_around_20%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5jpbm%2Fs_korean_crypto_exchange_freezes_around_20%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5jpbm/s_korean_crypto_exchange_freezes_around_20/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 14:31:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[将比特币从加密货币仇视者手中解放出来!]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t5mf1m/free_bitcoin_from_crypto_haters/?score=347&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft5mf1m%2Ffree_bitcoin_from_crypto_haters%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft5mf1m%2Ffree_bitcoin_from_crypto_haters%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t5mf1m/free_bitcoin_from_crypto_haters/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 12:49:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[刚刚设置了我的新硬件钱包👍]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t5pbcm/just_set_up_my_new_hardware_wallet/?score=394&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft5pbcm%2Fjust_set_up_my_new_hardware_wallet%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft5pbcm%2Fjust_set_up_my_new_hardware_wallet%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t5pbcm/just_set_up_my_new_hardware_wallet/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 12:49:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我们不都希望能把所有的钱都预支给自己吗？]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t5lpjp/dont_we_all_wish_we_could_premine_all_the_money/?score=371&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft5lpjp%2Fdont_we_all_wish_we_could_premine_all_the_money%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft5lpjp%2Fdont_we_all_wish_we_could_premine_all_the_money%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t5lpjp/dont_we_all_wish_we_could_premine_all_the_money/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 11:33:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Binance首席执行官称全面禁止俄罗斯用户是不道德的]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5izcm/binance_ceo_calls_total_ban_on_russian_users/?score=348&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5izcm%2Fbinance_ceo_calls_total_ban_on_russian_users%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5izcm%2Fbinance_ceo_calls_total_ban_on_russian_users%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5izcm/binance_ceo_calls_total_ban_on_russian_users/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 10:39:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[匿名者将为每辆坦克向俄罗斯军队支付52,000美元的BTC费用]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5kkrf/anonymous_will_pay_russian_troops_52000_in_btc/?score=419&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5kkrf%2Fanonymous_will_pay_russian_troops_52000_in_btc%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5kkrf%2Fanonymous_will_pay_russian_troops_52000_in_btc%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5kkrf/anonymous_will_pay_russian_troops_52000_in_btc/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 07:32:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[乌克兰国旗NFT以2258ETH售出，价值约675万美元]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5h5kz/ukrainian_flag_nft_sold_for_2258_eth_worth/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5h5kz%2Fukrainian_flag_nft_sold_for_2258_eth_worth%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5h5kz%2Fukrainian_flag_nft_sold_for_2258_eth_worth%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5h5kz/ukrainian_flag_nft_sold_for_2258_eth_worth/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 07:32:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["'帮助乌克兰'的骗局出现了，因为该国寻求加密货币捐款。" 在发送任何金额之前，请小心并核实接收者。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5bbgf/help_ukraine_scams_appear_as_country_seeks_crypto/?score=320&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5bbgf%2Fhelp_ukraine_scams_appear_as_country_seeks_crypto%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5bbgf%2Fhelp_ukraine_scams_appear_as_country_seeks_crypto%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5bbgf/help_ukraine_scams_appear_as_country_seeks_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 06:36:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Robinhood终于允许我在平台外转移我的ETH，但每次只允许我发送2000美元，每笔交易要花费大约125美元的汽油费!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想还有比拥有太多ETH更大的问题，但这是
荒唐。显然，"为了我的安全"，我不能转移超过2000美元的ETH
每小时。现在以太坊的气体费用高得惊人，显然
最好避免不必要的交易。没问题，我是个好手......]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5hx7m/robinhood_finally_lets_me_transfer_my_eth/?score=478&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5hx7m%2Frobinhood_finally_lets_me_transfer_my_eth%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5hx7m%2Frobinhood_finally_lets_me_transfer_my_eth%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5hx7m/robinhood_finally_lets_me_transfer_my_eth/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 06:36:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I guess there are bigger problems than having too much ETH, but this is ridiculous. Apparently, &amp;amp;quot;for my safety&amp;amp;quot; I cannot transfer more than $2000 in ETH per hour. With incredibly high-gas fees on Ethereum right now, it&amp;amp;#39;s obviously best to avoid unnecessary transactions. No problem, I&amp;amp;#39;m a hodlr anyway, but if I&amp;amp;#39;m gonna hodl I figured that I might as well earn some decent interest on my coins. I thought I&amp;amp;#39;d stake them on Coinbase or lend to a liquidity pool or something, but if I have to pay $1000s in transaction fees, then what amount of APY will be worth it? Is this it? Am I stuck in  Robinhood&amp;amp;#39;s interest-less purgatory while the rest of the industry offers 4.5-8.5% APY?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Congratulations Robinhood, you figured out how to prevent the crypto-exodus we all know you were fearing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果银行冻结了我们的账户，如果我们不能从中获得任何法币，那么加密货币有什么帮助？]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果我错过了一些明显的东西，请原谅，但这并不符合事实。每个人都在说
但当你卖掉你的加密货币时，你从哪里获得了
法币来生存？

大多数国家和地方还不接受加密货币作为支付手段。大多数人不是
在交易所出售他们的加密货币......]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t51f4s/if_banks_freeze_our_accounts_how_does_crypto_help/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft51f4s%2Fif_banks_freeze_our_accounts_how_does_crypto_help%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft51f4s%2Fif_banks_freeze_our_accounts_how_does_crypto_help%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t51f4s/if_banks_freeze_our_accounts_how_does_crypto_help/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 04:33:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sorry if I’m missing something obvious here, but it doesn’t add up. Everyone is saying unbank yourself, but when you sell your crypto, where are you getting the fiat from to survive? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Most countries and places don’t accept crypto as payment yet. Don’t most people sell their crypto on the exchange and then send it to their bank for fiat? If your account is frozen, then how do you take out your crypto profits?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Again, my apologies if I’m missing something obvious here but it doesn’t make sense to me.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今天是Safemoon的第一个生日。让我们看看他们在这一里程碑事件中取得了哪些成就。]]></title><description><![CDATA[什么也没有。

哈，只是开玩笑。但这与事实相差不大。

 *Safemoon于2021年3月2日发布，此前核心开发人员
   "Safemoondev "逐行复制了BEE合同，将总体税收从5%改为10%。
   整体税率从5%提高到10%[https://editor.mergely.com/tNAqXd2g/]。

 *Safemoon到...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5bdwz/today_is_safemoons_1st_birthday_lets_look_at_what/?score=368&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5bdwz%2Ftoday_is_safemoons_1st_birthday_lets_look_at_what%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft5bdwz%2Ftoday_is_safemoons_1st_birthday_lets_look_at_what%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t5bdwz/today_is_safemoons_1st_birthday_lets_look_at_what/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 04:33:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;NOTHING.&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hah, just kidding. But it&amp;amp;#39;s not &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;too&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; far off from the mark.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Safemoon was released on the 2nd March 2021, after core developer &amp;amp;quot;Safemoondev&amp;amp;quot; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://editor.mergely.com/tNAqXd2g/&quot;&amp;gt;copy-pasted the BEE contract line for line, changing the overall tax from 5% to 10%&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Safemoon to this day claim there was a &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;fair launch&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;, however in reality, Safemoon launched with zero announcements on March 2nd 2021, where immediately, several wallets purchased hundreds and thousands of dollars worth of a token listed at less than $0.00000000002 (10 zeroes, meaning one hundred bucks would buy you 5 Trillion Tokens &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;This price is correct as of March 5th, I have no earlier price entries&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;). &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Public availability was then on the 8th March, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://currency.com/safemoon-price-prediction&quot;&amp;gt;where the token price had already raised significantly to $0.000000001&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. At this point, new entrants were still getting billions of tokens for relatively small sums, but of course, the people selling got very lucky - these original wallets are widely speculated to be Developers &amp;amp;amp; Friends/Family of developers, with investigation to confirm proof of this currently underway. Whoever bought between March 2nd and March 8th could&amp;amp;#39;ve earned up to 4,900%&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Safemoon enlists the help of several prominent influencers to keep the volume high and price pumping. Names such as Soulja Boy, Jake Paul, etc. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fxstreet.com/cryptocurrencies/news/safemoon-price-plunges-in-response-to-class-action-lawsuit-against-jake-paul-nick-carter-and-souja-boy-202202220843&quot;&amp;gt;There is currently an ongoing Class-Action lawsuit alleging these influencers, and Safemoon dev team pumped and dumped Safemoon&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;An &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/invnefpcizq61.png&quot;&amp;gt;original roadmap is published&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. This lays out a year&amp;amp;#39;s worth of activity. To this day, most items have been abandoned, or were released months late.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In May 2021, Safemoon reaches the All-Time-High of $0.00001094. If any Pre &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;fair-launch&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; wallets held, they are up 54,699,900%. A $100 investment at the start of launch would therefore yield $54.7m. Currently, the price is &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;-87.27% down from ATH&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.certik.com/projects/safemoon&quot;&amp;gt;The Certik Audit is complete&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and notes several major security flaws. Chief of which;  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a result, overtime the _owner address will accumulate a significant portion of LP tokens&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Remember this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/p0i6kr/safemoons_performance_of_mental_gymnastics_in_the/&quot;&amp;gt;The Wallet was supposed to launch at the end of June&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. In early July, with no wallet in sight, the devs &amp;amp;amp; moderators on the Safemoon subreddit &amp;amp;amp; discord &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;pretend they have a beta wallet to test and claim to have distributed it to 500 people who signed an NDA to keep it secret&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;. It&amp;amp;#39;s now 8 months later and not one person has ever confirmed this wallet existed. At all. No redacted screenshots, no download logs. There is no proof of its existence.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Wallet is now scheduled for end of August. A date has been set. Safemooners are utterly convinced it will bring them legitimacy and respect in the Crypto community. Finally, their first real and tangible product. August 28th rolls round and Billboards appear in London &amp;amp;amp; New York advertising the wallet. CEO John Karony is hyping the launch 10 minutes before it is due to be released at 4pm. 4pm rolls around. No wallet. Nothing. Links to Google Play and iOS store redirect to the homepage. A whale sells trillions upon trillions of tokens 30 minutes before launch, causing a huge cascade of price over the next weeks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://db70102c-bf65-41f3-abcf-4a0026b2dbdd.filesusr.com/ugd/8fd214_665d75779cd440389a8367fe209e307a.pdf&quot;&amp;gt;An independent company called Doxxlocker audits Safemoon&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. They use the previous flaw stated in the Certik audit as their jumping-off point. They discover that via the very same SwapAndLiquify function, an address did indeed accumulate significant quantities of tokens from the LiquidityPool. Those tokens were then wash-traded and sold on the open market. In total, over $68.4m in BNB &amp;amp;amp; Safemoon were sold.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/l8g6xio5aom71.jpg?width=345&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=19083c375455a7e18fac74415e37b67b53bbea8a&quot;&amp;gt;Three team members simultaneously quit.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; The Chief Operating Officer, Chief Blockchain officer and Chief Technology Officer. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sq5vlh/this_is_how_the_exsafemoon_coo_lives_after_a/&quot;&amp;gt;Jack is now living a life of abject luxury&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; despite &amp;amp;quot;never owning any Safemoon&amp;amp;quot;. Prior to this, he worked as a part time DJ and twitch streamer. Kay.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/plait6/last_call_for_safemoon_the_curtains_are_drawing/&quot;&amp;gt;The Wallet is finally released&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. It has a non-functioning calculator, and many Safemooners notice it looks strangely familiar. It appears to have been built from the open source code of Trust Wallet. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/54q7q8dde0g71.jpg?width=320&amp;amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=dca1610ebffeaeb78b6f08734fa6dc1531a37bc8&quot;&amp;gt;[1]&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/lakkh7dde0g71.jpg?width=320&amp;amp;amp;crop=smart&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=6d5b521e8583ad6d441dc34aaf10cc77d472da44&quot;&amp;gt;[2]&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After several updates, to give them credit, in a short amount of time the wallet was more of less functional. It was missing some features from the Roadmap. &amp;amp;quot;Military-grade&amp;amp;quot; encryption was nowhere to be found... and there was no buy button.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The &amp;amp;quot;direct-buy&amp;amp;quot; functionality finally arrives, brought to Safemooners via Wyre. Now you can buy Safemoon with just a 3.9% fee. That means if you buy 1 million Safemoon, you get 900,000 because of the 10% tax and it costs you 3.9% more. When you sell, you are taxed another 10%, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/YRB3nYo.jpg&quot;&amp;gt;so buying Safemoon direct has a whopping 23.9% tax added on top. &amp;amp;quot;ThE eVOlutION!&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/r6utx4/history_repeats_itself_another_highranking/&quot;&amp;gt;Thomas leaves.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; The man they called &amp;amp;quot;Papa&amp;amp;quot;. The &amp;amp;quot;Blockchain Wizard&amp;amp;quot;. He had no proven experience coding a single material thing and helped pepretate a story that he rejected a $2,000,000 job offer from Ripple. Thomas originally handed in his notice, then was convinced to stay. He didn&amp;amp;#39;t last long.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitmart is hacked and 28 Trillion Safemoon tokens are stolen and sold on the open market, crashing the price. Moonboys speculate this is only a good thing, as Bitmart will buy back the tokens at a higher price than the market sells, therefore the price will go up. Two months later, it appears Safemoon CEO John Karony has transferred Bitmart Billions of V2 tokens under the counter, profiting, while Safemoon investors are left holding the shit. They didn&amp;amp;#39;t even get reflections from the transfers.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On Halo Infinite&amp;amp;#39;s release day, investors start to demand updates to Roadmap items. Many things were promised before the end of the year, such as the Blockchain and Exchange. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/3v4pwgymsk481.jpg&quot;&amp;gt;CEO Karony tells them &amp;amp;quot;Hush, Halo time&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. Not once. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/bwfzctbyek481.jpg&quot;&amp;gt;Twice.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now it&amp;amp;#39;s time to upgrade the contract! Apparently, the reason there is no Safemoon Blockchain, Safemoon Exchange or major Exchange listings are because this token has too many decimals (quick, nobody mention Shib!) so a reverse-split happens, where Safemoon tokens are traded 1000:1 for Safemoon V2.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The &amp;amp;quot;upgrade&amp;amp;quot; is botched. V2 trades at a higher price, and major arbitrage happens. People sell V2, re-buy V1, trade it for V2 tokens and sell, repeating the process to profit. V2 wallets aren&amp;amp;#39;t receiving reflections properly. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/ri4iam/amidst_a_botched_upgrade_943_of_safemoon_holders/&quot;&amp;gt;The community is furious and turns on itself&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Safemoon puts their best minds together and comes up with a plan &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/3lpq6vj3uh881.jpg?width=354&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=c335b14faf664baf24e66a5f2ec34beddc1a9499&quot;&amp;gt;to implement a 100% tax on the V1 token&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, confiscating any funds transacted into the liquidity pool. They signal intention to do this just 1.5 hours before implementing the 100% tax. Many, many, many investors lose thousands and thousands of dollars. Safemoon has not mentioned any plan to reimburse these folks. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/SafeMoonCase/comments/sztaht/the_wheels_are_in_full_motion_safemoon_class/&quot;&amp;gt;Currently, a second Class-Action lawsuit&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; is brewing because people rightfully feel like Safemoon has stolen their money.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P9jSoXYhv8g&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Operation Pheonix&amp;amp;quot; &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;[sic]&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; has been revealed.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; Safemoon is now a &amp;amp;quot;Human-focused technology company&amp;amp;quot; who are spraying Rain-X onto wind turbines built by a third party, in order to generate energy in The Gambia, where a portion of the energy generated will convert into Safemoon. None of the mechanics are clear. The benefits of application of &amp;amp;quot;nanotechnology&amp;amp;quot; &amp;amp;quot;hydrophilic&amp;amp;quot; particles are not clear. How this ties into a Cryptocurrency is not clear. It&amp;amp;#39;s alleged people can have ownership of these wind turbines via an NFT - how that works is not clear. Safemoon community continues to confuse Windmills with Wind Turbines. Windmills mill wheat into flour. That has always been clear.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Safemoon opens their headquarters in Utah. A large office section of a building on a business estate is leased. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/jahvltsfkjk71.png?width=1029&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=00ed93b57be316342f4dff35b05c9e07e7666ce8&quot;&amp;gt;Safemoon claim to have 90 employees&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, but only about 5 of them have ever been seen.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FIEzAcmWYAEl0vv?format=jpg&amp;amp;amp;name=large&quot;&amp;gt;Advertisements go up in Times Square&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. These play for 15 seconds per hour, every hour of every day, for an entire year. Looking at Advertisement companies in Times Square, one of these billboards would cost between $6-15m dollars for a year. Safemoon has 4 large ones. These billboards have not materially increased the token holders, price or volume.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Mandala exchange, a tiny offshoot of Binance with one of the lowest CEX volume rankings &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/0sujr5x6i2f81.jpg&quot;&amp;gt;announces they are officially adding Safemoon&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. Mandala does not allow trading in the US. The launch is set for Feb 17th. The 17th Arrives. Mandala releases a statement saying they are having issues implementing Safemoon, but to hang tight. A few days later, they release another statement saying they are having unforeseen issues and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/qkalxm2nplj81.jpg?width=622&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d86c46cc03881e880099916a4aa57b60fff598e2&quot;&amp;gt;advise to withdraw all Safemoon deposited onto Mandala&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;3 months after V2 launch, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://bscscan.com/token/0x42981d0bfbAf196529376EE702F2a9Eb9092fcB5&quot;&amp;gt;only 626,000 of the 3 million Safemoon V1 wallets&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; have migrated. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/lnajequunw981.jpg?width=568&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=147320ca26f3d862f6b9eaf61a9d93834c080f9a&quot;&amp;gt;Of the 626,000 wallets, 79% of these holders have less than $600&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s now today, March 2nd 2022. A full year after Safemoon was released. Safemoon teases a month of surprises, and kicks the celebrations off by changing the domain of Safemoon.net website to Safemoon.com, and changing the logo. There are no other changes.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Happy Birthday, Safemoon.&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币节点的数量已经达到15,000个。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t4vz7l/the_number_of_bitcoin_nodes_has_reached_15000/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft4vz7l%2Fthe_number_of_bitcoin_nodes_has_reached_15000%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft4vz7l%2Fthe_number_of_bitcoin_nodes_has_reached_15000%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t4vz7l/the_number_of_bitcoin_nodes_has_reached_15000/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 02:18:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是那个航班预测了三次比特币价格的人，我将在星期六飞行]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不知道你是否记得我，但我在大约两个月前发布了关于我的
航班与比特币价格的突然大幅下跌有关。I
这次我想事先让社区知道，我将在星期六飞往
周六撤离我现在的国家，与我的家人团聚。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t515jk/i_am_the_guy_whose_flights_have_predicted_the/?score=310&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft515jk%2Fi_am_the_guy_whose_flights_have_predicted_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft515jk%2Fi_am_the_guy_whose_flights_have_predicted_the%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t515jk/i_am_the_guy_whose_flights_have_predicted_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 23:33:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I don&amp;amp;#39;t know if you remember me but I posted about two months ago about how my flights have correlated with a sudden severe drop in the price in Bitcoin. I wanted to let the community know this time beforehand that I will be flying on Saturday to evacuate my current country and reunite with my girlfriend. The price drops always happened on my first flight and the first flight should be about noon central standard time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I also want to include in this post that I am a young American who has been living in Eastern Europe for well over two years now. I have many friends in Ukraine and I was a business consultant at Skolkovo while I was a student in Moscow. I may have some interesting perspectives on the situation and how it relates to the price changes in the price of Bitcoin if you want to ask.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Previous post: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rr5745/my_flights_have_predicted_the_price_of_bitcoin/&quot;&amp;gt;https://np.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rr5745/my_flights_have_predicted_the_price_of_bitcoin/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我的女儿采访了Jack Mallers（Strike的CEO）关于比特币的问题 🙃]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t5777a/my_daughter_interviewed_jack_mallers_ceo_of/?score=385&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft5777a%2Fmy_daughter_interviewed_jack_mallers_ceo_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft5777a%2Fmy_daughter_interviewed_jack_mallers_ceo_of%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t5777a/my_daughter_interviewed_jack_mallers_ceo_of/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 23:33:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不言自明]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t5ah0o/speaks_for_itself/?score=314&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft5ah0o%2Fspeaks_for_itself%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft5ah0o%2Fspeaks_for_itself%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t5ah0o/speaks_for_itself/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 23:33:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[欧盟不再禁止比特币和其他基于PoW的资产了]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t56bjf/the_european_union_is_no_longer_banning_bitcoin/?score=352&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft56bjf%2Fthe_european_union_is_no_longer_banning_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft56bjf%2Fthe_european_union_is_no_longer_banning_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t56bjf/the_european_union_is_no_longer_banning_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 23:33:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么大多是30岁以下的男性在交易比特币？]]></title><description><![CDATA[根据一个专注于比特币的交易应用程序，拥有数万名用户。
女性和年长的投资者在很大程度上没有参与加密货币的热潮，留下的主要是年轻男性成为加密货币反弹和上涨的动力。
主要是年轻男性成为加密货币上涨和下跌背后的驱动力。

绝大多数使用该应用程序进行比特币交易的人...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t4zh3j/why_is_it_mostly_men_who_are_under_30_trading/?score=321&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft4zh3j%2Fwhy_is_it_mostly_men_who_are_under_30_trading%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft4zh3j%2Fwhy_is_it_mostly_men_who_are_under_30_trading%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t4zh3j/why_is_it_mostly_men_who_are_under_30_trading/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 23:33:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;According to a bitcoin-focused trading app, with tens of thousands of users, women and older investors are largely staying out of the crypto craze, leaving mainly young men to be the driving force behind crypto rallies and lows.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The overwhelming majority of people using the app to trade in bitcoin are men, making up 79% of users to just 21% women. Compared with the most recent data from the U.K.’s Office for National Statistics, or ONS, this makes the gender divide among bitcoin holders even wider than with other investments.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;So, is it overconfidence?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Barber and Odean found that men trade stocks 45% more frequently than women, which is a symptom of overconfidence because overconfident investors trade excessively&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If we see from that research study that men are, on average, more inclined to be overconfident, that overconfidence could be helping to drive the heavier representation of men in these much more speculative markets. It really takes a bit of a hope and a prayer to believe that these assets are going to be long-term, reliable investment performers.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币的价值超过了俄罗斯所有的流通货币。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t52xoo/bitcoin_is_worth_more_than_all_of_russias/?score=575&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft52xoo%2Fbitcoin_is_worth_more_than_all_of_russias%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft52xoo%2Fbitcoin_is_worth_more_than_all_of_russias%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t52xoo/bitcoin_is_worth_more_than_all_of_russias/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 21:37:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密货币市值再次超过2万亿美元（祝贺所有霍德人！）。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t53u84/crypto_market_cap_is_once_again_above_2_trillion/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft53u84%2Fcrypto_market_cap_is_once_again_above_2_trillion%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft53u84%2Fcrypto_market_cap_is_once_again_above_2_trillion%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t53u84/crypto_market_cap_is_once_again_above_2_trillion/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 21:37:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Binance首席执行官称阻止所有俄罗斯人进入加密货币交易所是 "不道德的]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t51q81/binance_ceo_says_blocking_all_russians_from/?score=355&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft51q81%2Fbinance_ceo_says_blocking_all_russians_from%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft51q81%2Fbinance_ceo_says_blocking_all_russians_from%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t51q81/binance_ceo_says_blocking_all_russians_from/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 19:37:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[勇敢的浏览器的BAT奖励是一场灾难，团队未能解决发生的问题，并且在r/BATPROJECT上没有反应。]]></title><description><![CDATA[广告商向Brave支付购买BAT的费用，以便在浏览器上开展广告活动。用户可以
用户可以通过观看这些广告来赚取BAT，而Brave则保留一部分（30%）来运行他们的
运营。这个过程一直在稳步退步，这个月的问题越来越多。
这个月，似乎是...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4u5vj/brave_browsers_bat_rewards_are_a_disaster_and_the/?score=319&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4u5vj%2Fbrave_browsers_bat_rewards_are_a_disaster_and_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4u5vj%2Fbrave_browsers_bat_rewards_are_a_disaster_and_the%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4u5vj/brave_browsers_bat_rewards_are_a_disaster_and_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 16:35:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Advertisers pay Brave to buy BAT to run ad campaigns on the Browser. Users can earn BAT by viewing these ads, and Brave keeps a cut (30%) to run their operations. This process has been steadily regressing, with more and more issues this month and seems to be capitulating.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://community.brave.com/c/brave-rewards/71&quot;&amp;gt;https://community.brave.com/c/brave-rewards/71&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Their community forum is full of people experiencing Brave&amp;amp;#39;s terrible payout system. Basically, Brave tells you you&amp;amp;#39;ll get paid the 5-7th, but that isn&amp;amp;#39;t happening. Your rewards seem to disappear, and then you hope one day you get paid. The Brave Team seems to expect their millions of users to individually PM them to get it resolved on a wallet-by wallet basis, and as you can imagine, they aren&amp;amp;#39;t able to keep up. Now they&amp;amp;#39;re rolling people&amp;amp;#39;s rewards over to the next month, essentially just holding people&amp;amp;#39;s money until they look into it more.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bravebat.info/brave_initiated_bat_purchase&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.bravebat.info/brave_initiated_bat_purchase&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;
Brave touts 54 million active monthly users, but has failed to convert those numbers into revenue. The link above shows that for 54MM users, they&amp;amp;#39;ve never done more than $3MM in monthly BAT sales, which they only keep 30% of. This is pennies a month per user, and means that Brave is massively cash flow negative, as they claim hundreds of employees. They have completely failed to effectively monetize their massive user base, and now we&amp;amp;#39;re seeing they&amp;amp;#39;re completely in over their head.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you head over to &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/r/batproject&quot;&amp;gt;r/batproject&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, you&amp;amp;#39;ll see that the Brave Team has stopped engaging their users, unless they have a very canned response. Their &amp;amp;quot;Director of Engagement&amp;amp;quot; posts very rarely, and they refuse to respond to questions of users. The red flags are adding up, and my guess is that Brave is failing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Investing in BAT I&amp;amp;#39;m realizing is like investing in a private company, and is actually a regressive way to invest. They don&amp;amp;#39;t disclose their runrate, revenue, all revenue sources, executive compensation and many other key metrics that you can see at any publicly traded company. However, Brave touts &amp;amp;quot;transparency&amp;amp;quot; every chance they get, while being about as transparent as milk when it comes to any issues with the payouts.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Perhaps the most damming metric is the 0 growth in ad campaigns in the US. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bravebat.info/brave_ads_campaigns?country=United%20States&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.bravebat.info/brave_ads_campaigns?country=United%20States&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Shows 2 years of flat US ad campaigns, so US advertisers don&amp;amp;#39;t want this. plenty of big names have come through, and very few of run repeat campaigns. If you use the browser, the ads you&amp;amp;#39;ll get now are from very low quality companies, similar to when the browser first started.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I think it&amp;amp;#39;s clear that BAT is failing. Most people on here get maybe a couple of quarters a month, after being told how valuable their data is. Most people think the rewards are a complete joke on here, and I guess they are, and the team&amp;amp;#39;s response is certainly telling of a team in complete disarray. The idea of privacy browser that compensates you for your ad viewing is brilliant, but this team&amp;amp;#39;s execution of that concept ain&amp;amp;#39;t it. It&amp;amp;#39;s been years, they won&amp;amp;#39;t talk about what&amp;amp;#39;s going on, and it&amp;amp;#39;s getting worse. Take a look through that first link, it&amp;amp;#39;s not good.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;These issues have gotten worse over the years, and clearly Brave isn&amp;amp;#39;t going to be &amp;amp;quot;transparent&amp;amp;quot; about the problem. I would advise any investors to assume that if the team won&amp;amp;#39;t answer their questions, it&amp;amp;#39;s because the answer is really bad. The Brave Team won&amp;amp;#39;t answer these questions on &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/r/batproject&quot;&amp;gt;r/batproject&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; - go take a look, they&amp;amp;#39;ve been asked for years, the team will engage and then ghost any question they don&amp;amp;#39;t like.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一个平衡的投资组合应该包括至少70%的BTC，60%的ETH，30%的前15名alts，20%的stables，以及10%的low cap。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看到很多人发帖说要在他们的投资组合中加入BTC和ETH，并询问他们应该如何分配他们的投资组合。
并询问他们应该如何分割他们的投资组合。在这个
我将与大家分享我对完美投资组合的经验。

首先，你需要至少70%的BTC。这是所有硬币中的鼻祖，而且
你的...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4yy7f/a_balanced_portfolio_should_consist_of_at_least/?score=686&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4yy7f%2Fa_balanced_portfolio_should_consist_of_at_least%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4yy7f%2Fa_balanced_portfolio_should_consist_of_at_least%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4yy7f/a_balanced_portfolio_should_consist_of_at_least/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 15:40:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve been seeing a lot of people post about adding BTC and ETH to their portfolio and asking questions how they should split up their portfolio. In this thread, I will share my experience on the perfect breakdown. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To start, you want at least 70% in BTC. This is the granddaddy of all coins and your most stable. The higher the percentage of BTC, the better.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Next is ETH, I’ve found 60% is a good level. Even if you just have BTC and ETH, you will have 130% of your portfolio in 2 coins, up for 100% you started with. To instantly have 30% more, you are genius. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Next up is the large-cap alts. I like 30% here. You can LRDYOR (let Redditors do your own research) to decide which coin is best for you, but possible examples are SOL, ADA, DOT, LINK, AVAX, etc. Following advice up to this point, you have at least 160% portfolio. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Keeping 20% stables is key to any portfolio. You can earn interest (up to 20%) on stables, plus any price action. I saw one tik-tok’er predict Tether would go to $5 this year. I think that’s bullish, but I can easily see USDT going to $3. Let’s say you earn 20% interest on your 20% investment, you now have 40% (compounding interest works wonders). Now your portfolio allocation is at 200% and you have doubled your money. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now that you have doubled your money, going for 100% portfolio allocation to 200%, you have freedom to gamble on low cap coins. I’d keep this to 10%. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This strategy will work for everyone. It will instantly turn you into a billionaire overnight. Follow me for more financial advice.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[大多数在历史最高点买入的比特币投资者已经卖出。报告显示，大多数在历史高位买入的比特币投资者已经卖出]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t4mb8n/most_bitcoin_investors_who_bought_at_alltime_high/?score=341&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft4mb8n%2Fmost_bitcoin_investors_who_bought_at_alltime_high%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft4mb8n%2Fmost_bitcoin_investors_who_bought_at_alltime_high%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t4mb8n/most_bitcoin_investors_who_bought_at_alltime_high/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 15:40:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[娜塔莉-布鲁内尔为福克斯新闻的博主们提供了橙色服务]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t4urm7/natalie_brunell_orangepilling_fox_news_boomers/?score=435&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft4urm7%2Fnatalie_brunell_orangepilling_fox_news_boomers%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft4urm7%2Fnatalie_brunell_orangepilling_fox_news_boomers%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t4urm7/natalie_brunell_orangepilling_fox_news_boomers/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 15:40:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[新法令禁止携带超过1万美元的外币离开俄罗斯。加密货币需求将急剧上升]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄罗斯人不再被允许携带超过1万美元的外币离开俄罗斯。
货币。
[https://www.marketwatch.com/story/putin-signs-decree-to-prohibit-leaving-russia-with-more-than-10-000-in-foreign-currency-01646176225]

现在想象一下，你想离开俄罗斯并带着钱。你不...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4x2zz/new_decree_prohibits_leaving_russia_with_more/?score=457&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4x2zz%2Fnew_decree_prohibits_leaving_russia_with_more%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4x2zz%2Fnew_decree_prohibits_leaving_russia_with_more%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4x2zz/new_decree_prohibits_leaving_russia_with_more/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 15:40:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/putin-signs-decree-to-prohibit-leaving-russia-with-more-than-10-000-in-foreign-currency-01646176225&quot;&amp;gt;Russians are no longer allowed to leave Russia with more than $10k in a foreign currency.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now imagine you want to leave Russia and bring money with you. You don&amp;amp;#39;t want to hold Rubles because they&amp;amp;#39;re losing value by the second. You can&amp;amp;#39;t hold foreign currency. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How do you bring money with you? Crypto. You buy lots of BTC and ETH, store your wallet keys safely, and leave the country with no one any the wiser. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Russians will use crypto to get out of the hellhole that is Russia and start a new life, now that they can&amp;amp;#39;t use foreign currencies to do it.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[此外，如果我们要自愿冻结在世界各地不公正地攻击和挑起暴力的国家的居民的金融账户，步骤[一]将是冻结所有美国账户。Kraken首席执行官]]></title><description><![CDATA[继乌克兰部长要求破坏普通用户从
加密货币交易所

Kraken首席执行官Jesse Powell有一个非常好和公平的观点

> 此外，如果我们要自愿冻结一些国家的金融账户
> 不公正地攻击和挑起周围暴力的国家的居民。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4y4v7/besides_if_we_were_going_to_voluntarily_freeze/?score=368&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4y4v7%2Fbesides_if_we_were_going_to_voluntarily_freeze%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4y4v7%2Fbesides_if_we_were_going_to_voluntarily_freeze%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4y4v7/besides_if_we_were_going_to_voluntarily_freeze/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 12:34:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Following the requests from Ukrainian minister to sabotage ordinary users from Crypto exchanges&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Kraken CEO Jesse Powell has a very good and fair point&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Besides, If we were going to voluntarily freeze financial accounts of residents of countries unjustly attacking and provoking violence around the world, Step[One] would be to freeze all the US accounts &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The dude got a point,If citizens should be punished for the actions of their govt, then it should start from freezing accounts of US citizens&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I like this dude, he got some balls and really stands for it, never mince his words,He is one of the right guy to lead Crypto.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[稳定币的赌注在APY中最高达到20%。这可能是目前最安全和最有利的被动收入。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在这次车祸中，我深刻地认识到这一点。P]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4noch/stablecoin_staking_reaches_up_to_20_in_%D0%B0py_its/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4noch%2Fstablecoin_staking_reaches_up_to_20_in_%D0%B0py_its%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4noch%2Fstablecoin_staking_reaches_up_to_20_in_%D0%B0py_its%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4noch/stablecoin_staking_reaches_up_to_20_in_аpy_its/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 11:30:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Learned this the hard way during this crash. People who had big amount of stablecoins staked barely felt a thing and didn&amp;amp;#39;t panic as much as others.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m not gonna go all in on stablecoins but it would be nice to ensure a chunk of my wealth won&amp;amp;#39;t get wiped out each dip. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Although I wouldnt get anywhere near USDT. Who knows when it will come crashing down. Would much safer to go with audited and fully backed stablecoins like USDC, EURST and UST.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some well regarded platforms offer up to 20% AРY for stablecoins. Would be a cool investment to sleeр on for а couple of years and gain passive income from.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[亿万富翁Ken Griffin承认他对比特币和加密货币的看法是错误的 - "在过去的15年里，加密货币是金融领域的一个伟大故事。我要说清楚，在那段时间里，我一直处于反对者的阵营。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4q4ug/billionaire_ken_griffin_admits_he_was_wrong_about/?score=332&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4q4ug%2Fbillionaire_ken_griffin_admits_he_was_wrong_about%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4q4ug%2Fbillionaire_ken_griffin_admits_he_was_wrong_about%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4q4ug/billionaire_ken_griffin_admits_he_was_wrong_about/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 10:39:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[被曝光的国会议员布拉德-谢尔曼试图 "关闭 "加密货币，并从大银行获得最大的捐赠，将在明年2022年重新选举。让我们把他投出去？这里有像我这样的加州人可以帮忙吗？无论明年谁反对他，我都会投票给他。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t4izwn/exposed_congressman_rep_brad_sherman_who_is/?score=313&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft4izwn%2Fexposed_congressman_rep_brad_sherman_who_is%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft4izwn%2Fexposed_congressman_rep_brad_sherman_who_is%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t4izwn/exposed_congressman_rep_brad_sherman_who_is/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 08:43:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特币继续产生一个又一个的交易区块，不管世界上发生了什么。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t4evhn/bitcoin_continues_to_produce_block_after_block/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft4evhn%2Fbitcoin_continues_to_produce_block_after_block%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft4evhn%2Fbitcoin_continues_to_produce_block_after_block%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t4evhn/bitcoin_continues_to_produce_block_after_block/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 06:47:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[由于最近的事件，我不得不做这个:D比特币者都能体会到。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t46wwl/with_the_latest_events_i_had_to_make_this_one_d/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft46wwl%2Fwith_the_latest_events_i_had_to_make_this_one_d%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft46wwl%2Fwith_the_latest_events_i_had_to_make_this_one_d%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t46wwl/with_the_latest_events_i_had_to_make_this_one_d/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 06:47:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[匿名者向俄罗斯军队提供比特币赏金以交出他们的坦克]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4dm4t/anonymous_offers_russian_troops_bitcoin_bounty_to/?score=315&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4dm4t%2Fanonymous_offers_russian_troops_bitcoin_bounty_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4dm4t%2Fanonymous_offers_russian_troops_bitcoin_bounty_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4dm4t/anonymous_offers_russian_troops_bitcoin_bounty_to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 05:34:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[希拉里-克林顿。"我很失望地看到，一些所谓的加密货币交易所，不是所有的交易所，但其中一些交易所为了一些自由主义的哲学或其他东西，拒绝结束与俄罗斯的交易。" 去中心化显然只是什么。]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 美国前总统候选人--希拉里-克林顿批评了那些
> 加密货币交易场所拒绝停止为俄罗斯的
>用户。她再次认为，数字资产应该被置于一个
> 监管框架。
> 
> 在俄罗斯入侵乌克兰的情况下，米哈伊洛...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4p880/hillary_clinton_i_was_disappointed_to_see_that/?score=509&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4p880%2Fhillary_clinton_i_was_disappointed_to_see_that%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4p880%2Fhillary_clinton_i_was_disappointed_to_see_that%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4p880/hillary_clinton_i_was_disappointed_to_see_that/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 04:50:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Former US presidential candidate – Hillary Clinton – criticized those cryptocurrency trading venues that refused to stop servicing Russian-based users. She once again opined that digital assets should be put under a regulatory framework.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Amidst the Russian invasion in Ukraine, Mykhailo Fedorov – the latter’s Vice Prime Minister – asked the leading digital asset platforms to freeze all Russian users’ blockchain addresses. According to the politician, the move would weaken Russia and aid Ukraine’s defense.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In a recent interview for MSNBC, the former first lady Hillary Clinton said she is “disappointed” that some cryptocurrency exchanges still provide services to such users:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Why do these people talk about thinga they have not a single inkling about? And clearly any sort of decentralization is poisoni their eyes&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptopotato.com/hillary-clinton-is-disappointed-that-some-crypto-exchanges-refused-to-stop-servicing-russians/&quot;&amp;gt;https://cryptopotato.com/hillary-clinton-is-disappointed-that-some-crypto-exchanges-refused-to-stop-servicing-russians/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[麦当劳已经为一家在玄幻世界的餐厅申请了商标，该餐厅将真正把食物送到你的家里。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4fx2n/mcdonalds_has_filed_a_trademark_for_a_restaurant/?score=346&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4fx2n%2Fmcdonalds_has_filed_a_trademark_for_a_restaurant%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4fx2n%2Fmcdonalds_has_filed_a_trademark_for_a_restaurant%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4fx2n/mcdonalds_has_filed_a_trademark_for_a_restaurant/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 04:50:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[很少在新闻中看到这种情况......不得不拍了一张照片]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t4jxp0/rarely_see_this_on_the_news_had_to_take_a_photo/?score=351&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft4jxp0%2Frarely_see_this_on_the_news_had_to_take_a_photo%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Ft4jxp0%2Frarely_see_this_on_the_news_had_to_take_a_photo%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/t4jxp0/rarely_see_this_on_the_news_had_to_take_a_photo/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 03:38:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[匿名者向俄罗斯士兵提供价值超过5万美元的比特币以换取每辆上缴的坦克]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4k7sy/anonymous_offers_russian_soldiers_over_50k_worth/?score=325&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4k7sy%2Fanonymous_offers_russian_soldiers_over_50k_worth%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4k7sy%2Fanonymous_offers_russian_soldiers_over_50k_worth%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4k7sy/anonymous_offers_russian_soldiers_over_50k_worth/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 02:26:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[总结一下我今天与@cvpayne的聊天。
 
-#比特币有明确的规则，但没有统治者
- 两个系统正在发生碰撞，旧的系统基于操纵 - 新的系统基于自由和希望
- 人们不想要战争，他们想要经济机会
- #黄金是旧的

谢谢你邀请我！https://t.co/ZrG7gmQsQK]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1498788184213364736/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/tweet/1498788184213364736/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 22:38:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BitConnect创始人在24亿美元的庞氏骗局中被定罪后失踪了]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t44xqb/bitconnect_founder_convicted_in_24b_ponzi_scheme/?score=309&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft44xqb%2Fbitconnect_founder_convicted_in_24b_ponzi_scheme%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft44xqb%2Fbitconnect_founder_convicted_in_24b_ponzi_scheme%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t44xqb/bitconnect_founder_convicted_in_24b_ponzi_scheme/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 22:35:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄罗斯卢布跌至不足0.01美元，比特币需求爆炸性增长]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t48go2/bitcoin_demand_explodes_as_russian_ruble/?score=320&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft48go2%2Fbitcoin_demand_explodes_as_russian_ruble%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft48go2%2Fbitcoin_demand_explodes_as_russian_ruble%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t48go2/bitcoin_demand_explodes_as_russian_ruble/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 22:35:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[到今天为止，我拥有加密货币已经整整6年了，我告诉你一件事，就是我99.99%是为了致富，只有0.01%是为了去中心化。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这是正确的，在这个时代，它是钱。Moola，dinero，现金，这是
我从加密货币中得到的最重要的东西。所有这些隐私
所有这些隐私术语都很酷，但我刚刚听说天然气将在加州的EOY达到10美元。
这意味着它在东海岸将接近7美元。我的税款在美国和欧洲都有。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4e9dl/its_been_exactly_6_years_to_this_day_i_owned/?score=490&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4e9dl%2Fits_been_exactly_6_years_to_this_day_i_owned%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft4e9dl%2Fits_been_exactly_6_years_to_this_day_i_owned%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t4e9dl/its_been_exactly_6_years_to_this_day_i_owned/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 22:35:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That&amp;amp;#39;s right, in this day, it&amp;amp;#39;s money.  The Moola, the dinero, cash that&amp;amp;#39;s the most important thing that I get out of cryptocurrency.   All of that privacy jargon is cool and all, but I just heard Gas will hit $10 by EOY in California which means it will be close to $7 on the east coast.     My taxes on a regular home went up 30% in two years, 2 slices of pizza, and a drink come out to $10, and now the town decided it was the perfect idea to TRIPLE OUR WATER BILL! &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;YES, they actually tripled it.   Turns out the previous mayor didn&amp;amp;#39;t pay the water bill from the other city we get water from for like 8 years!.    Great that I have to pay for the previous home owner&amp;amp;#39;s water bill.  Why not right?    But the absolute worst thing about what we are going through right now is the idea that &amp;amp;quot;crypto is the problem&amp;amp;quot; and it&amp;amp;#39;s being used as one of the scape goats in the Ukraine/Russia war.   God, people are so FKing stupid to believe this shit. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The more we change, the more we stay the same.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>