<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[加密貨幣國外熱門討論]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 03:20:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[在向國稅局報稅時，不要忘記將 "非法活動收入 "與你的加密貨幣收益一起列入。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果計算你的加密貨幣稅收還不夠困難，國稅局現在要我們
包括來自非法活動的收入，以及報告你可能擁有的任何被盜財產。
可能擁有的任何被盜財產，。

根據國稅局出版物17，國稅局希望納稅人
在他們的表格中包括 "來自非法活動的收入"。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5n15p/dont_forget_to_include_income_from_illegal/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5n15p%2Fdont_forget_to_include_income_from_illegal%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5n15p%2Fdont_forget_to_include_income_from_illegal%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5n15p/dont_forget_to_include_income_from_illegal/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 02:32:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As if working out your tax for crypto wasn&amp;amp;#39;t hard enough, the IRS now want us to include income from illegal activities as well as report any stolen property you may have,.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;According to IRS publication 17, the Internal Revenue Service wants taxpayers to include on their forms “income from illegal activities, such as money from dealing illegal drugs.” Make sure you put that on “Schedule 1 (Form 1040) , line 8z, or on Schedule C (Form 1040) if from your self-employment activity”.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They also requests that “if you steal property, you must report its fair market value,” but only if you don’t “return it to its rightful owner in the same year.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you want to read up on this latest nonsense there&amp;amp;#39;s a good article on the NBC News website. I know people can be weary of links so I haven&amp;amp;#39;t included it&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BTC不是匿名的，如果有人發現你的地址，你的整個歷史就會被破壞。]]></title><description><![CDATA[去中心化比使用BTC更有意義

我經常看到這些人，我相信你也是如此。這些人認爲
一旦他們轉而使用BTC，他們就永遠擺脫了稅收。
機構、政府和 "老大哥"。但事實並非如此。
和那些有點...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5g5ue/btc_isnt_anonymous_if_something_finds_your/?score=389&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5g5ue%2Fbtc_isnt_anonymous_if_something_finds_your%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5g5ue%2Fbtc_isnt_anonymous_if_something_finds_your%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5g5ue/btc_isnt_anonymous_if_something_finds_your/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 22:35:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There’s more to decentralization than using BTC&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I see these people all the time, and I’m sure you do as well. People who think that once they’ve moved on to using BTC, they’re forever freed of taxes, institutions, the government, and ‘big brother’. Well it doesn’t work that way, and those a little more experienced in crypto will tend to agree.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin was an experiment, it went well but it still has a long way to go. Bitcoin isn’t anonymous, it’s pseudonymous, anyone who can find one address of yours, can track your entire search history. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Something else Bitcoin has to work on, is the largeholder control. A few whales control the majority of the market. Decentralized organizations have already solved this using DAOs. You see when you use a DAO, take BitDAO for example, you don’t have to put your trust in the hands of a few sketchy men. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Instead, you are given the choice of handing your confidence to the entirety of the public. No honest man is in power, and no power is given to an honest man. You can’t trust humans to control your fortunes. You too, should handle a share of the responsibility of the fortunes of yours as well as others, and that’s how DAOs work. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you only trust politicians to rule and soldiers to fight, then don’t be surprised when war is fought by fools and governments are ruled by cowards.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我要說的是......DOGE不可能有另一個泵。]]></title><description><![CDATA[很多人都會被這句話激怒，但女人撒謊，男人撒謊，數字
並非如此。而現在，數字並不在DOGE一邊。



DOGE的市值高達220億美元，這意味着任何抽水的機會都很渺茫。
的機會是非常小的，而像ELON這樣市值小得多的幣...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5ca41/im_gonna_say_it_doge_is_not_likely_to_have/?score=395&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5ca41%2Fim_gonna_say_it_doge_is_not_likely_to_have%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5ca41%2Fim_gonna_say_it_doge_is_not_likely_to_have%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5ca41/im_gonna_say_it_doge_is_not_likely_to_have/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 22:35:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A lot of people will get triggered by this but women lie, men lie, numbers don’t. And right now the numbers aren’t on the side of DOGE.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;DOGE is sitting at a whopping $22 billion market cap meaning that any chance at a pump is very thin and other coins like ELON with a much small market cap of $700 million will most probably have a much higher chance at multiple pumps.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you’re gonna invest in memecoins then I’m not one to judge but investing in DOGE right now would honestly be a bad move in my personal opinion.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Loopring一直在穩步下跌，看不到底部，沒有人談論它。]]></title><description><![CDATA[似乎很清楚，去年的指數型價格走勢都是基於
圍繞GME傳言的炒作，沒有實際內容，因此價格並不高。
因此，價格並沒有保持下去。市值與TVL的比率仍然很高，爲4.5，所以我不認爲這是個好消息。
所以我不認爲在沒有任何新消息的情況下，這種下降趨勢會很快結束。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5hd3q/loopring_has_been_steadily_dumping_with_no_bottom/?score=484&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5hd3q%2Floopring_has_been_steadily_dumping_with_no_bottom%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5hd3q%2Floopring_has_been_steadily_dumping_with_no_bottom%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5hd3q/loopring_has_been_steadily_dumping_with_no_bottom/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 22:35:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It seems pretty clear the exponential price action last year was all based on hype surrounding GME rumours, there was no actual substance to it therefore the price isn&amp;amp;#39;t holding up. The market cap to TVL ratio is still high at 4.5 so I don&amp;amp;#39;t see this downtrend ending anytime soon without any new catalysts. If you compare this to another hyped coin like CRO, which saw a meteoretic rise and who&amp;amp;#39;s price has stabilized since then (especially if you look at the CRO/BTC pair), you can see that LRC is nowhere near a bottom. I could easily see Loopring dropping below $1 again, assuming no significant BTC movements happen.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And yet, all I see on this sub is more threads shilling the coin and doses of hopium about the long term potential? Nobody is seriously discussing price action over the last two months which is a huge concern to me. I&amp;amp;#39;m not arguing that Loopring is a dead project, far from it, but the short term price prospects are very meagre. Everyone should decide what to do for themselves i.e. risk management, but I don&amp;amp;#39;t see any value in bagholding it when there&amp;amp;#39;s no end in sight for the downwards trend.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Don&amp;amp;#39;t get me wrong, I see huge potential in ZK roll ups and in particular LRC for the next five years eventhough I don&amp;amp;#39;t own it myself. In fact, I&amp;amp;#39;m looking for this downtrend to end so I can buy it when it eventually consolidates. Since Loopring is by far the most shilled coin on this sub , I feel bad for the ones that FOMO&amp;amp;#39;d in after the price rise in early November. These people are seeing their gains evaporate like snow in the sun or are suffering big losses. Maybe an announcement by Gamestop at the end of this month or during the next earnings call will stop this downtrend, but I don&amp;amp;#39;t see it stopping anytime soon before that.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: To anyone commenting that price doesn&amp;amp;#39;t matter, well it does. Let me put it this way, if LRC is $1.35 and you feel like it will move below $1 in the short term: you should absolutely sell because you can increase your holdings for the long term with 35%&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT 2: Obviously DCA&amp;amp;#39;ing is also an option when the price drops, I would wait until the price stabilizes though&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT 3: Since I received the suicide care message from Reddit and multiple threats in my inbox, I will no longer interact with this thread. What a shame that people can&amp;amp;#39;t behave.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有人創建了1100個自己穿着超短裙的NFT，稱其爲DAO，並從絕望的競標者那裏籌集了超過300萬美元。Novograts正在宣傳這個。🤡]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是一個怎樣的時代，你可以點擊自己的照片，稱之爲 "DAO"，並在數小時內籌集數百萬美元。
在幾個小時內籌集數百萬美元。

這就是艾琳所做的。

IreneDAO selling \"Tribe passes\"。花費你寶貴的硬幣來加入她的部落
i.e private...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5kyu4/someone_created_1100_nfts_of_herself_wearing/?score=786&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5kyu4%2Fsomeone_created_1100_nfts_of_herself_wearing%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5kyu4%2Fsomeone_created_1100_nfts_of_herself_wearing%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=true</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5kyu4/someone_created_1100_nfts_of_herself_wearing/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 22:35:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What a time to be living in, you can click pics of yourself, call it a &amp;amp;quot;DAO&amp;amp;quot; and raise millions of dollars in hours.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thats what Irene did.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/uqv9vtep04c81.jpg?width=1030&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=296b0e721c3ac0e23bf6560f1ac292ac28e99eed&quot;&amp;gt;IreneDAO selling \&amp;amp;quot;Tribe passes\&amp;amp;quot;. Spend your valuable coins to join her tribe i.e private group&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/4yzyqmpt04c81.jpg?width=1170&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=83d65d39b3447f24aa5490375161764b8958ce30&quot;&amp;gt;No thanks? The market says otherwise. &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Well.. anything is possible if you get big accounts to back you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/7p8yhjf214c81.jpg?width=1170&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9bbeee30cebb6c8a6ed1ae88172e68973db11376&quot;&amp;gt;She even got Novogratz to shill this \&amp;amp;quot;DAO\&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/t7qjyac424c81.jpg?width=512&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=86e4c293df85a1d9cb2f59d01c31a5a00381e151&quot;&amp;gt;henlo? Novofaps&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This chick be straight up hustling yo, she got plebs to send her their valuable NFTs (which are now trading at $15,000 each! ), in exchange of a 5 minute phone call. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/awjomdzmh4c81.jpg?width=1242&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=8057dfc1b82aa2c28f303b8def7b5bd14a9291a2&quot;&amp;gt;$15,000 for a 5 minute phone call?  Shut up and take my money!&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And then she used those 2 NFTs to get the attention of Su Zhu and Justin Sun &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/wnt2rqtwh4c81.jpg?width=1169&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=2d03022b8a7d8e48b98bb7935cd7546b92fcbf23&quot;&amp;gt;Lmao&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Looks like Bored Apes are gonna become history soon &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[法國🇫🇷
英國🇬🇧
德國🇩🇪 
意大利🇮🇹
澳大利亞🇦🇺
新西蘭🇳🇿
加拿大🇨🇦
美國🇺🇸
西班牙🇪🇸
荷蘭🇳🇱 
瑞士🇨🇭 
奧地利🇦🇹
還有更多。

每週都有數以千計的人抗議疫苗護照。但媒體不會告訴你。這裏有一個提醒。

https://t.co/ym9zDzeTQ7]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1482813539094048768/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1482813539094048768/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 20:48:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[卡達諾在2022年的11種擴展方式：參數調整、改進、增強和其他創新都將在穩步提高卡達諾的容量&amp; 吞吐量方面發揮其作用。]]></title><description><![CDATA[鏈上解決方案

區塊大小增加

區塊越大，它能承載的交易就越多。區塊大小是
最近增加了8KB，達到72KB（增加了12.5%）；進一步的增加將被應用於
將根據持續的系統監測和整體網絡健康狀況，進一步增加。

管道化

改善了...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5bmu2/11_ways_cardano_will_scale_in_2022_parameter/?score=320&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5bmu2%2F11_ways_cardano_will_scale_in_2022_parameter%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5bmu2%2F11_ways_cardano_will_scale_in_2022_parameter%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5bmu2/11_ways_cardano_will_scale_in_2022_parameter/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 20:31:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;On-chain solutions&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Block size increase&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The  bigger the block, the more transactions it can carry. Block size was  recently increased by 8KB to 72KB (a 12.5% increase); further increases  will be applied over time based on ongoing system monitoring and overall  network health.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Pipelining&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Improves block  propagation times by coalescing validation and propagation. The goal is  for blocks to be propagated to at least 95% of peers within five seconds  by reducing the ‘dead time’ between blocks (the block propagation  overhead). This provides the headroom to make more aggressive scaling  changes, such as increasing block size/increasing Plutus parameter limits.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Input Endorsers&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Input endorsers  improve block propagation times and throughput by allowing transactions  to be separated into pre-constructed blocks. This improves the  consistency of block propagation times and allows higher transaction  rates.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Memory /CPU parameters for Plutus&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Memory  usage is more efficient across the chain. Specifically, there are  memory improvements in Unspent Transaction Output (UTXO) handling, stake  distribution, live stake distribution and pools, and hash  representation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Plutus script enhancements&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Even more effective usage of the powerful EUTXO model through smart contract optimization, including: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Reference  inputs (CIP-0031)  – Plutus scripts can inspect transaction inputs  without needing to spend them. This means that it is not necessary to  create UTXOs simply to inspect the information held by an input.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Plutus  Datums (CIP-0032) – Datums can be attached directly to outputs instead  of datum hashes. This simplifies how datums are used, as a user can see  the actual datum rather than having to supply the datum that matches the  given hash.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Script sharing (CIP-0033) – Plutus script  references can be associated with transaction outputs, meaning that they  can be recorded on-chain for subsequent reuse. It will not be necessary  to supply a copy of the script with each transaction, hugely reducing  friction for developers. Reusing scripts in multiple transactions  significantly reduces transaction sizes, improving throughput and  reducing script execution costs.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Node enhancements&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Improvements  will help even distribution of stake and reward computations across the  epochs, thus providing greater headroom for block size increases. Also,  memory usage is now more efficient. Memory compaction reduces RSS  footprint, and memory sharing means we need less data instantiated. Node  version 1.3.3, from January 2022, reduces peak load at critical points,  including the epoch boundary.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;On-disk storage&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;By  storing portions of the protocol state on disk, nodes will need to hold  less in memory, meaning that RAM-constrained systems will be able to  run nodes provided they have sufficient storage, and memory will no  longer be a bottleneck on scalability. This will enable significant  growth in the blockchain state.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Off-chain solutions&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Sidechains&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A sidechain is a separate blockchain connected to a main blockchain (the  &amp;amp;#39;main&amp;amp;#39; chain, also known as parent chain), through a two-way mechanism  (the &amp;amp;#39;bridge&amp;amp;#39;) that enables tokens and other digital assets from one  chain to be used in another and results returned to the original chain.  Assets can be moved between chains as needed. One single parent chain  can have multiple interoperable sidechains connected to it, which may  operate in completely different ways. EVM sidechains coming to Cardano  include dcSpark’s Milkomeda and IOG’s Mamba. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Hydra&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Introduces  isomorphic state channels to maximize throughput, minimize latency,  incur low to no costs, and greatly reduce storage requirements. Hydra  provides a more efficient means to process transactions off-chain while  using the main-chain ledger as the secure settlement layer.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Off-chain computing&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Offloading  some of the computation, for example with Asynchronous Contract  Execution (ACE)  can drive greater core network efficiency. Transactions  occur outside of the blockchain itself, yet can offer fast, cheap  transactions via a trust model.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Mithril&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To  achieve greater scalability, you need to address the complexity of  critical operations that depend logarithmically on the number of  participants. Mithril will improve chain synchronization while  maintaining trust. The result? Multi-signature aggregation that is fast  and efficient without compromising security features.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TL;DR: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://ucarecdn.com/ff38dd08-5947-4c52-af32-15c59cdcdcf8/-/format/webp/-/quality/best/-/progressive/yes/&quot;&amp;gt;All this summarized in one pic&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://iohk.io/en/blog/posts/2022/01/14/how-we-re-scaling-cardano-in-2022/&quot;&amp;gt;https://iohk.io/en/blog/posts/2022/01/14/how-we-re-scaling-cardano-in-2022/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bonus:  Plutus is basically Haskell which is native smart contract language for the Cardano blockchain. Plutus contracts consist of parts that run on the blockchain  (on-chain code) and parts that run on a user’s machine (off-chain or  client code). Both the on-chain and off-chain code are written in Haskell, and Plutus smart contracts are effectively Haskell programs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特幣百萬富翁正在遷往波多黎各，以獲得更低的稅收和島嶼生活]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5e784/bitcoin_millionaires_are_moving_to_puerto_rico/?score=455&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5e784%2Fbitcoin_millionaires_are_moving_to_puerto_rico%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5e784%2Fbitcoin_millionaires_are_moving_to_puerto_rico%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5e784/bitcoin_millionaires_are_moving_to_puerto_rico/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 20:31:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[十三年前的今天，中本聰給了我們所有人一些可能有史以來最重要的建議。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s5gk6s/thirteen_years_ago_today_satoshi_nakamoto_gave_us/?score=421&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs5gk6s%2Fthirteen_years_ago_today_satoshi_nakamoto_gave_us%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs5gk6s%2Fthirteen_years_ago_today_satoshi_nakamoto_gave_us%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s5gk6s/thirteen_years_ago_today_satoshi_nakamoto_gave_us/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 20:31:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[星期三會很有趣。國會宣佈就比特幣的能源使用舉行聽證會]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4ylmb/wednesday_is_gonna_be_interesting_congress/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4ylmb%2Fwednesday_is_gonna_be_interesting_congress%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4ylmb%2Fwednesday_is_gonna_be_interesting_congress%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4ylmb/wednesday_is_gonna_be_interesting_congress/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 20:31:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[昨天，以色列🇮🇱醫學協會呼籲停止大規模測試和隔離，並停止Covid護照。

今天，以色列最大的醫院抨擊衛生部的 "瘋狂政策"。

潮水正在轉向。官方的說法正在瓦解。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1482764186413408263/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1482764186413408263/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 17:49:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼通貨緊縮的貨幣既可以是價值儲存也可以是貨幣]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tl;dr/結論。

從個人的角度來看，通貨緊縮的貨幣形式是
從根本上說，通貨緊縮的貨幣形式比通貨膨脹的貨幣形式更優越。理性的
理性的做法是持有這種通貨緊縮形式的貨幣，並將其轉換爲
通貨膨脹的貨幣。鑑於...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5cvhv/why_deflationary_money_can_be_both_a_store_of/?score=355&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5cvhv%2Fwhy_deflationary_money_can_be_both_a_store_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5cvhv%2Fwhy_deflationary_money_can_be_both_a_store_of%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5cvhv/why_deflationary_money_can_be_both_a_store_of/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 16:32:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Tl;dr/conclusion:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Looking at it from the level of the individual, a deflationary form of money is fundamentally a superior form of money to an inflationary currency. The rational move would be to hold such a deflationary form of currency, and to swap into inflationary currencies as needed. Given the possibility, it would be attractive for merchants and invididuals to accept payment directly in this deflationary form of money.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;While a comparison with gold and the flaws of transacting in gold is often made, these flaws no longer need apply. With the advent of crypto, we have the possibility to create a form of money that has the advantages of gold, without the disadvantages of its physicality.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;----------&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve seen this discussion pop up more often recently, so let’s dive in. In short, the argument goes that currencies need to be inflationary so that people are incentivised to spend. A way to see it is to think of inflationary currency as a hot potato — if you don’t do anything with it and keep it in cash, it’s going to decline in value. Therefore, you might as well spend it or invest it. If you know your food is going to be (ever so slightly) more expensive tomorrow, you might as well buy it today.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/jqt6kkb272c81.png?width=602&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=160fc72058667fe9322a18b346ad8f741c98cf86&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/jqt6kkb272c81.png?width=602&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=160fc72058667fe9322a18b346ad8f741c98cf86&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In a deflationary form of money (for example a currency with a fixed supply) this incentive is absent. Because of this, people will hoard their money, rather than spend it or invest it. With no (or less) money being spent, merchants drop prices to try and entice people to spend. With dropping prices, consumers want to wait longer to purchase stuff, because they expect the item they intend to buy will be cheaper again next month, compared to now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What this has to do with crypto is that people will often make the claim that crypto can be seen as a store of value, rather than a currency. Save your money in a fixed supply asset that you know won’t be debased, spend your inflationary currency. Because of this, crypto won’t be used as money. People will hold (HODL) their crypto that is likely to increase their value, while spending their fiat money that will decrease in value. Because of this, no network effect arises for crypto, it remains just a savings (and speculation) vehicle.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the hope of having represented the argument of those that believe money should be inflationary correctly, I’ll now dive into why I believe this take is in a sense incorrect, and stems from issues with the specific forms of non-inflationary currency we have seen so far rather than a fundamental issue with deflationary forms of money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Why deflationary money is a superior store of value&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When you have the choice between spending in an asset that is likely to appreciate in value (deflationary) or an asset that is likely to depreciate in value (inflationary) the rational move is to spend in the inflationary asset. You’d prefer to pass on the hot potato. However, as in a typical hot potato game, the receiver would then again prefer to pass on the hot potato as quickly as possible, while preferring to hold a harder form of money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The bigger question here is not whether an individual prefers to pay in an inflationary or a deflationary currency. Rather, it’s about why anyone would &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;hold&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; the hot potato, when there is the option of passing it on right away. If I’m a merchant receiving US dollars, and I can convert this into a fixed supply form of money right away, that seems like a smarter course of action. If the friction of doing so is low enough, I’d prefer to hold that harder form of money even if I have to convert back into inflationary currency a few days later.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Run this process through to its conclusion and the question becomes: who is holding the hot potato, and why?&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The current answer to this is that the hot potato has some characteristics that make it attractive to use and to hold at least some of it. It tends to be more stable than the fixed supply money. While the hot potato money might fluctuate 2–30% against other currencies on a yearly basis, the fixed supply asset currently might fluctuate that much in a day. As an individual or business who can’t afford to see 30% of their spending power wiped out in a day, such fluctuations are undesirable. There’s also the fact that governments like to be paid in this hot potato money and it’s commonly accepted in most places, which gives hot potato money a great network effect.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;What about people not wanting to spend deflationary currency?&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I believe this argument assumes a flexibility in humans that is at odds with how people live, and that is at odds with what history has shown us.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Look at how much the average person is making, and at how much the average person is spending. Most people are far more preoccupied with paying their rent, mortgage, buying food and other necessities than they are with the value of their money. As a fun thought experiment — say you need a toothbrush. would you postpone buying a toothbrush if you thought it would be 1% cheaper next month?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are very specific examples we can point to here. Technology (and most things in life) get cheaper over time. Say you were in the market for a television. Specifically, it’s March 29th 2020 and we’re thinking an &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://tweakers.net/pricewatch/1540272/lg-oled55cx6la-zwart.html&quot;&amp;gt;LG OLED55CX6LA&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; would be great to have. It’s top of the market. We check the price, and it turns out it retails at €2099. A bit steep.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We decide to postpone our purchase for three months. On June 29th 2020, it turns out we can already get the TV for €1668! Three months later, on September 29th 2020, it’s €1299. A full year later, we can get this exact same TV for €1098.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/hhlfb2f372c81.png?width=602&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e63ffdb347c51b427ac925bf20e67c7a85a88014&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/hhlfb2f372c81.png?width=602&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e63ffdb347c51b427ac925bf20e67c7a85a88014&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Most people are well aware of this, and know that it holds for televisions, entertainment, computers, fridges, dishwashers, and a plethora of other things. Nearly everything gets cheaper if you keep the quality equal. Yet people do not wait infinitely. They buy what they want to have now, or when they’ve saved up enough money (or even use credit to do so).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is no fluke. A great piece of research on the “&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.frbsf.org/economic-research/files/wp2017-25.pdf&quot;&amp;gt;Rate of Return on Everything, 1870–2015&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;” shows that the real rate of return on government bonds &amp;amp;amp; bills has been positive, taking into account inflation (p17), for most countries in the world. Since the 1980’s it has been on average positive for every country in the world.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/4pvcdf4472c81.png?width=602&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=39df26ee074629812708c7cfbefddc91524bc9b9&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/4pvcdf4472c81.png?width=602&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=39df26ee074629812708c7cfbefddc91524bc9b9&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Data for bank savings accounts are harder to find except for specific countries. When we look at specific countries, bank savings that are insured by a government deposit guarantee tend to offer an even higher interest rate than government bonds &amp;amp;amp; bills.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is commonly stated that people would postpone purchases and investments under a deflationary money system because people’s money would be worth more tomorrow or a year from now. What the above shows is that there is a safe asset that people can already invest into, with small or large amounts, knowing their money will be worth more in a year from now, yet we haven’t seen a deflationary collapse yet. It shows that people can already have “deflation” work in their favor by postponing buying a new TV, or computer, or a myriad of other things, yet we haven’t seen a deflationary collapse yet.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;How could a non-inflationary currency work as currency?&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Earlier in this article I mentioned how inflationary currency can be seen as a hot potato that is constantly passed on. The question turns into who holds the hot potato. An even more important question is &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;why&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, fundamentally, anyone would want to be holding the hot potato.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thinking about it from a fundamental point of view, I would prefer to hold as little as possible in a form of cash that depreciates. In other words, when I receive payment in inflationary currency, I would prefer to exchange it into hard money as quickly as possible. When paying others, I would convert back into inflationary currency as needed, and pay them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However — as this continues and more people think in this way, the step of converting back into inflationary currency makes less sense. If I want to hold my money in a fixed supply currency, and you have a fixed supply currency but are converting to inflationary currency to pay me with, that seems like an inefficient form of exchange.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a merchant, I would gladly take your fixed supply currency, and could let you know that I accept this fixed supply currency for payment. It saves you the hassle of converting fixed supply into inflationary currency, it saves me the hassle of having to swap that inflationary currency back into fixed supply currency.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Full efficiency is gained when we have a form of money that is both a fantastic store of value and a fantastic currency. The two strengthen each other — so why have we not seen this so far?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;The gold standard and its flaws&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At this point you’re probably wondering why I haven’t touched upon the gold standard yet. It’s an example of a relatively fixed supply currency. Yet as we broadly observe, it is not in use today, while gold does serve as a store of value. Why is that?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Many economies have had a direct gold-based exchange system at times. Gold (and silver) coins were widely circulated — the Roman aureus was a gold coin, later replaced by the Byzantine solidus. Italian denari, Spanish dineros and the Florentine florin are well-known examples.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;These currencies were used within countries and internationally. Gold is a base layer asset, the value is in the physical gold itself. Because of this, no trust was needed when transacting. A country having a debt settled by another country preferred this to be done in gold, because once paid it was fully settled. There was no debt claim, no need to trust the counterparty beyond the simple exchange.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, carrying around gold is inconvenient at best. Amongst other issues gold is heavy and can be stolen. To solve this issue, credible parties (which we today think of as banks) offered to store gold in a secure place, giving a paper claim to the deposited gold in exchange. As long as the credible party was credible enough, this paper claim was “as good as gold”, while being far easier to transport, protect and use.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, this also allows banks to lend out this gold to others, in exchange for interest. As long as not everyone comes by at the same time to retrieve their gold, this would work fine, and provides some income for the bank.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the interest of keeping this short, Ray Dalio’s “Principles for Dealing with the Changing World Order: Why Nations Succeed and Fail” is a fantastic read. It goes into the next stages of such a system and why we see ebbs and flows in hard money and fiat money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The important part for this analysis is why we’ve repeatedly seen the move from using gold as a pure medium of exchange to claims on gold and ultimately fiat. It’s not because gold’s (relatively) fixed supply fundamentally makes it unsound to transact with. It is gold’s other characteristics, such as limited portability/transferability and divisibility, and its security costs, that mean it is not ideal for use as a medium of exchange.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Gold is heavy to carry around. It’s expensive to transfer large sums, because the risk of it being stolen increases, so you would need to pay for security. It’s hard to divide it down to small amounts — try paying a few cents in gold. Conversely, try paying very large amounts in gold to someone far away. The transport costs would be large.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Fixing these flaws&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Say we were able to create an asset that had a demonstrably and unchangeably fixed supply, while fixing the flaws with gold. This asset could be carried anywhere easily, and you would be able to transfer 2 cents as easily as you were able to transfer 2 billion. Such a transfer would be confirmed instantly, while the transaction would not cost you any fees. As in gold, it would be paramount that such a transfer happen trustlessly, and that there is no way for people to spend money they do not have.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The idea behind cryptocurrency is largely to offer such a form of money. This is one of the reasons a lot of money is flowing into crypto, and that many people are so enthusiastic about it. Bitcoin was a first version of this, but has some flaws. As an example, transferring Bitcoin is not instant, and it costs a fair bit. It’s not extremely divisible, and most importantly does not ensure security.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin’s security comes from decentralization, from many miners competing for the rewards that come with mining Bitcoin. At the same time, mining Bitcoin comes with economies of scale due to the way Bitcoin is designed. In other words, Bitcoin is designed to encourage centralization and loss of security over time. For more info, see &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://senatus.substack.com/p/why-99-of-cryptocurrencies-centralize&quot;&amp;gt;“&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Why 99% of cryptocurrencies centralize over time”&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That does not mean crypto as a whole has failed at this. Nano is a cryptocurrency that offers instant transfers at zero fees, from anywhere in the world to anywhere. It is a fixed supply, and almost limitlessly divisible (up to 30 decimals). As opposed to Bitcoin, Nano does not centralize over time, instead decentralizing ever further.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the interest of not making this article even longer, I would link to “&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://senatus.substack.com/p/why-nano-is-the-ultimate-store-of-value-and-reserve-currency-3b0318844bc8&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;crypto as a store of value&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;”&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://senatus.substack.com/p/on-crypto-as-a-store-of-value-bitcoins&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;“the long-term future of crypto”&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for those interested in the ways that certain cryptocurrencies have solved these issues.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Conclusion&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Looking at it from the level of the individual, a deflationary form of money is fundamentally a superior form of money to an inflationary currency. The rational move would be to hold such a deflationary form of currency, and to swap into inflationary currencies as needed. Given the possibility, it would be attractive for merchants and invididuals to accept payment directly in this deflationary form of money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;While a comparison with gold and the flaws of transacting in gold is often made, these flaws no longer need apply. With the advent of crypto, we have the possibility to create a form of money that has the advantages of gold, without the disadvantages of its physicality.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;If this article interests you, I would first and foremost recommend the article&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://senatus.substack.com/p/on-crypto-as-a-store-of-value-bitcoins&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;“On crypto as a store of value, Bitcoin’s incentives, and the long-term future of crypto”&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;. I would also recommend this analysis of&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://senatus.substack.com/p/creating-the-theoretical-best-possible&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;“The theoretical best form of money”&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Mostly, I would love to hear comments and feedback. I’ve written this down to improve my own thinking, and am open to hearing where this is plain wrong or where my thinking could be improved.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[近70%的美國加密貨幣持有者在2021年開始投資]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s50xb1/almost_70_of_us_crypto_holders_started_investing/?score=333&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs50xb1%2Falmost_70_of_us_crypto_holders_started_investing%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs50xb1%2Falmost_70_of_us_crypto_holders_started_investing%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s50xb1/almost_70_of_us_crypto_holders_started_investing/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 15:37:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[事實覈查。彭博社公然對其付費讀者撒謊。蘋果股票在2021年的表現並不優於比特幣]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4mxs3/fact_check_bloomberg_blatantly_lied_to_its_paid/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4mxs3%2Ffact_check_bloomberg_blatantly_lied_to_its_paid%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4mxs3%2Ffact_check_bloomberg_blatantly_lied_to_its_paid%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4mxs3/fact_check_bloomberg_blatantly_lied_to_its_paid/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 15:37:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[🇳🇱 16.01.22 農民參加在阿姆斯特丹舉行的反對電暈暴政的示威活動! 👏👏
https://t.co/eKa9PaahLm]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1482713370080030721/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1482713370080030721/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 14:40:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[🇳🇱今天在阿姆斯特丹的#博物館廣場的人海中，反對醫療種族隔離！！🔥https://t.co/RVchh8NIXh。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1482713340010979330/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1482713340010979330/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 14:40:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[通貨膨脹的艱難之路]]></title><description><![CDATA[百事可樂公司的人來到我的公司，走到我們的自動售貨機前，告訴我。
"你可能想宣佈一下--瓶子不再是1.5美元了。要到
$1.75."

從字面上看，這讓我想起了聽到 "在我那個年代，蘇打水是0.5美分"。這
就發生在我面前。我感到被侵犯了...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4lt7r/inflation_the_hard_way/?score=309&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4lt7r%2Finflation_the_hard_way%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4lt7r%2Finflation_the_hard_way%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4lt7r/inflation_the_hard_way/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 14:40:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Pepsi guy came into my work, walked over to our vending machines and told me. “You might want to make an announcement- bottles are no longer $1.50. Going to $1.75.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Literally reminded me of hearing “Back in my day soda pop was .50 cents.” This happened right in front of my face. I feel violated and robbed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;BTC fixes this&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特幣的兔子洞]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 1.  聽到人們談論它一段時間，但卻拂袖而去
 2.  屢次聽到它的消息，感到很好奇
 3.  搜索 "什麼是比特幣"--什麼都不懂
 4.  投資少量資金，因爲爲什麼不呢？
 5.  投資於前50名中的其他硬幣，因爲名字和標誌很酷。
 6.  是的，價值上升了，...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4w2xn/the_bitcoin_rabbit_hole/?score=316&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4w2xn%2Fthe_bitcoin_rabbit_hole%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4w2xn%2Fthe_bitcoin_rabbit_hole%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4w2xn/the_bitcoin_rabbit_hole/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 14:40:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Hear people talk about it for some time, but brush it off&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Hear about it again and again, be intrigued&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Search &amp;amp;quot;What is Bitcoin&amp;amp;quot; - don&amp;amp;#39;t understand shit&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Invest small amount because why tf not&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Invest in other coins in top 50 because cool name and logo&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Yeah value go up, buy more&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Realize 99% off crypto projects will be worth nothing because of centralization&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Sell altcoins&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Begins to understand videos explaining Bitcoin&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Understands Bitcoin will increase more in price&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Why is this guy on YouTube telling me about economic history, I just want to learn more about Bitcoin&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Learns about history off money&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Learns about Bretton Woods-system, then the Nixon-shock&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Research wtf happened in 1971, naaah that can&amp;amp;#39;t be true&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;wait, dollars is not backed by gold&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Understands Fiat money, naaah that&amp;amp;#39;s fucked up&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Become very interested in economics&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Thinks I fully understand Bitcoin now and there no more to learn&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;okay there is much more to learn&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Studies game theory, network effects&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;million forever&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You realize you have only scratched the surface&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Looks into philosophy and how Bitcoin not just changes the monetary system, but changes the world&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Wait, Christianity is not about a big guy in the sky??&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;1 BTC = 1 BTC = 100,000,000 SATS&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Bitcoin standard will unite people&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Automation will overtake, people will be free to do what they love&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Work will be mostly out of charity&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Bitcoin can&amp;amp;#39;t be stopped&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Bitcoin = freedom&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;.. &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;to be continued&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我已經在Defi方面生活和呼吸了一年多，以下是我對各主要連鎖店的最佳低風險Defi戰略。]]></title><description><![CDATA[Defi，去中心化的金融，通常被稱爲是狂野的西部的
低碳貨幣。但是，在Defi旅行了一年多之後，我瞭解到，西部只有牛仔和僱傭兵纔是 "狂野 "的。
只有牛仔和僱傭兵纔是 "野生 "的--他們在這些地方被稱爲 "Degens"。
他們在這些地方被稱爲 "墮落者"。在這篇文章中，我將爲你提供一些方法，以使你能在西部地區的生活。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s552ks/ive_lived_and_breathed_defi_for_over_a_year_now/?score=366&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs552ks%2Five_lived_and_breathed_defi_for_over_a_year_now%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs552ks%2Five_lived_and_breathed_defi_for_over_a_year_now%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s552ks/ive_lived_and_breathed_defi_for_over_a_year_now/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 13:46:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Defi, &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;decentralized finance,&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; is often referred to as the &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Wild Wild West of Crypto&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;. But after journeying in Defi for over a year, I&amp;amp;#39;ve learned that the West is only &amp;amp;#39;wild&amp;amp;#39; for the cowboys and mercenaries—they are known as &amp;amp;#39;degens&amp;amp;#39; around these parts. For this post, I&amp;amp;#39;ll provide ways for you to prosper in the Wild West as a steady and humble farmer.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: Forgot to mention that this guide prioritizes security over profits. The rules of the low-risk strategies are to (1) hold &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;pristine assets&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; like BTC and ETH, (2) avoid impermanent loss and splitting assets as you would by directly being in a LP position, (3) use reputable dapps, (4) use simple strategies (no leverage, no auto-compounding, etc.). &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Ethereum - Very high gas fees&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Wallet - &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://metamask.io/&quot;&amp;gt;Metamask&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; or &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ledger.com/ledger-live&quot;&amp;gt;Ledger&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;   |   Dex - &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://defillama.com/protocol/uniswap&quot;&amp;gt;Uniswap&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; or &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://defillama.com/protocol/sushiswap&quot;&amp;gt;SushiSwap&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; are both good&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I wouldn&amp;amp;#39;t recommend Defi on Ethereum due to high fees and because the roadmap is to &amp;lt;del&amp;gt;stop using Ethereum for general purposes&amp;lt;/del&amp;gt; migrate to layer 2s; but, there are protocols that are only the Ethereum network right now. When using Ethereum, I recommend using as few dapps as possible to avoid gas fees.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;The simplest Ethereum Defi strategy is to deposit ETH into Tokemak.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; The expected yield is 8-12%. Using &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://defillama.com/protocol/tokemak&quot;&amp;gt;Tokemak&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, you&amp;amp;#39;ll be a single-token liquidity provider. This allows you to avoid impermanent loss (IL) and you can hold 100% of ETH instead of splitting your assets like a typical liquidity provider.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But the IL doesn&amp;amp;#39;t just disappear. There are other type of users that work as &amp;amp;quot;managers&amp;amp;quot; who play a role in deciding how the protocols makes profits. I won&amp;amp;#39;t dive deeper into this aspect since it&amp;amp;#39;s a different strategy but for those interested to learn more, here&amp;amp;#39;s an &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FMZ_fS1uZaU&quot;&amp;gt;explanation&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Downsides: Expect to spend heavily on fees (~$200) on bridging to Ethereum as well as approving and depositing ETH. And the same amount for the withdrawing process. If the fees are peanuts to you, feel free to use this strategy, Mr/Mrs. Whale. You&amp;amp;#39;ll be earning rewards via the protocol token, TOKE, as rewards, which may not be ideal given that TOKE does suffer from high price volatility and selling pressure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Polygon - Negligible fees (~$0.02)&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Wallet - &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://metamask.io/&quot;&amp;gt;Metamask&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; or &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ledger.com/ledger-live&quot;&amp;gt;Ledger&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;   |   Dex - &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://defillama.com/protocol/quickswap&quot;&amp;gt;QuickSwap&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://defillama.com/protocol/uniswap&quot;&amp;gt;Uniswap&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, or &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://defillama.com/protocol/sushiswap&quot;&amp;gt;SushiSwap&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Polygon really made its strides between April to July 2021 when they launched a $40M &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptobriefing.com/polygon-launches-40m-liquidity-mining-program-with-aave/&quot;&amp;gt;incentive program&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and since they&amp;amp;#39;ve been reliable and competitive. And with Polygon fees being so low, you’re pretty much free to do whatever.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;In terms of low-risk Defi investing, an Aave + Curve strategy is currently the golden standard.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Adding the rates for lending and providing liquidity and subtracting it from the costs of borrowing, the expected yield is 4-6%. This can be done by depositing into &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://defillama.com/protocol/aave&quot;&amp;gt;Aave&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, using the deposits as collateral to borrow a stablecoin, and using the borrowed stablecoins to provide liquidity in Curve.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a low-risk user, the ideal borrowing rate is 30% of your deposits (ie. deposit $1K, borrow $300). At this rate, you&amp;amp;#39;ll be liquidated if your deposits depreciate more than 45%. Given that it historically takes several days or cryptos like BTC or ETH to crash, giving you a long enough timeframe to manage your risks. You can further mitigate liquidation risks are to deposit stablecoins, which improves the stability of your portfolio, while depositing even more volatile assets like MATIC will increase risks. It&amp;amp;#39;s all about risk management.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Downsides: Borrowing and lending on Aave exposes you to liquidation risk and will require you to properly manage your assets. You will &amp;amp;quot;be your own bank&amp;amp;quot; and that isn&amp;amp;#39;t easy. Alas, this is one of the few ways to participate while holding assets like BTC and ETH and avoiding liquidity providing risks. You&amp;amp;#39;ll be earning rewards in wrapped MATIC and some rewards in CRV (a protocol token but has good fundamentals and has held its value historically).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Terra - Relatively high fees (~$1)&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Wallet - &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://station.terra.money/&quot;&amp;gt;Terrastation&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;   |   Dex - &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://defillama.com/protocol/terraswap&quot;&amp;gt;TerraSwap&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; or &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://defillama.com/protocol/astroport&quot;&amp;gt;AstroPort&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Terra is flag-shipped by the successes of Anchor Protocol and their stablecoin ecosystem that has a presence among most major defi networks thanks to the Cosmos network. But the option in Terra network itself are limited. I would only recommend using Terra if you want exposure to LUNA or if you&amp;amp;#39;re in need of a Defi savings account. But I would consider exposure to LUNA as having medium to high risks, which is beyond the scope of this post.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;For low-risk Defi participation, I can only recommend depositing UST in Anchor&amp;amp;#39;s Saving Protocol.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; The expected yield is 19% annual percentage yield. By using &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://defillama.com/protocol/anchor&quot;&amp;gt;Anchor&amp;amp;#39;s&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; savings protocol, you&amp;amp;#39;ll be reward from the protocol&amp;amp;#39;s revenue streams from (1) borrowing interest and (2) staking deposits. This revenue comes from another feature in Anchor that allows users to deposit LUNA or ETH and borrow UST, the native algorithmic stablecoin.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can further optimize your yield via strategies like using your deposit as collateral for other protocols, but again those are medium to high risk strategies that go beyond the scope.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Downsides: A ~19% savings account is an undoubtedly insane yield granted traditional banks can barely offer 1% for a similar product. But this isn&amp;amp;#39;t too far fetched given that Defi flips the model and instead of getting 20% of the revenue while banks get 80%, Defi users get 100%. The risks are explained thoroughly &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptorisks.substack.com/p/ust-december-2021&quot;&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. The ones that stand out are de-pegging, regulatory risk, and lowered yield as a result of &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptorisks.substack.com/p/on-abracadabra-degenbox-strategies&quot;&amp;gt;decreasing protocol revenue&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.  You&amp;amp;#39;ll be earning rewards in UST.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Avalanche -  Low fees ($0.3) but can high (&amp;amp;gt;$5) when congested&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Wallet - &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://metamask.io/&quot;&amp;gt;Metamask&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;   |   Dex - &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://defillama.com/protocol/trader-joe&quot;&amp;gt;TraderJoe&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; or &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://defillama.com/protocol/sushiswap&quot;&amp;gt;SushiSwap&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A lot of big Defi players such as Aave, Curve, and Abracadabra also built on Avalanche, which is why it was able to rapidly grow when it first launched. That and it&amp;amp;#39;s $180M &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/avalancheavax/avalanche-foundation-announces-180m-defi-incentive-program-d320fdfafff7&quot;&amp;gt;incentive program&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, which dwarfed Polygon&amp;amp;#39;s incentive program.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;With Avalanche, you could do the same Aave + Curve strategy and get a similar yield.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; But, unlike Polygon (&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://forum.abracadabra.money/t/aip-3-deploy-abracadabra-money-on-polygon-pos/864&quot;&amp;gt;at least not yet&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;), Avalanche has Abracadabra, which is a reputable dapp that&amp;amp;#39;s also built on Ethereum. So an &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;alternative low-risk strategy would be to use AAVE + Abracadabra.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; The expected yield is 4-6%. You&amp;amp;#39;ll be borrowing and lending on &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://defillama.com/protocol/aave&quot;&amp;gt;Aave&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and providing liquidity on &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://defillama.com/protocol/curve&quot;&amp;gt;Curve&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; or &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://defillama.com/protocol/abracadabra&quot;&amp;gt;Abracadabra&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Under the hood, you&amp;amp;#39;re using Curve to provide liquidity for stablecoins that includes its algorithmic stablecoin, Magic Internet Money (MIM). The revenue comes from a liquidity fee that traders pay to swap between these stablecoins pairs. Again, you don&amp;amp;#39;t need to know any more about the protocol but you can read more about it &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/abracadabra-money/abracadabra-spell-and-magic-internet-money-a563637ce92e&quot;&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Downsides: Again, you&amp;amp;#39;re borrowing and lending, which makes you vulnerable to liquidation risks if you&amp;amp;#39;re mismanaging your assets. By using Abracadabra, which works on top of Curve, you&amp;amp;#39;re increasing your exposure to the smart contracts of three protocols. In Aave, you&amp;amp;#39;ll be earning rewards in wrapped AVAX and, in Abracadabra, in the protocol token, SPELL (likewise to TOKE, protocol tokens are not as ideal to hold as network tokens).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;---&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ll end this post with these four networks that I believe present the best opportunities at a low-risk based on factors that include total value locked and history among others. This also isn&amp;amp;#39;t a list to rank Defi ecosystems, I think each have their own benefits, opportunities, and risks. I know there are other promising networks out there with equally good, if not better opportunities. I&amp;amp;#39;ll be making a follow-up posts on them. But for now, thanks to anyone who read up to this point!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我創建了一個應用程序，可以免費接收algorand網絡上的空投，而且無需註冊]]></title><description><![CDATA[在過去的幾個月裏，我一直在建立一個應用程序/網站，我計劃在那裏
向Algorand網絡中的ASA業主提供不同的工具。
在訪問量和 "客戶 "方面可以說是相當成功。

目前，網站上有幾個活躍的空投，數以千計的...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s51xy9/i_created_an_application_to_receive_airdrops_on/?score=332&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs51xy9%2Fi_created_an_application_to_receive_airdrops_on%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs51xy9%2Fi_created_an_application_to_receive_airdrops_on%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s51xy9/i_created_an_application_to_receive_airdrops_on/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 12:32:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For the past few months I have been building an application/website where I plan to offer different tools to ASA owners in the Algorand network, and I have been quite successful in terms of visits and &amp;amp;quot;customers&amp;amp;quot; so to speak.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Currently there are several active airdrops on the site, thousands of daily users and a community that grows day by day hand in hand with the growth of the code and the tools I offer that I am developing in my spare time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Why and how?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;While it started as a way to expand the algorand ecosystem and as a way to learn more about blockchain development, especially in regards to Algorand, I am increasingly excited about the project&amp;amp;#39;s growth, and I look forward to its future as long as I keep working as I do now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On the monetary side my only &amp;amp;quot;income&amp;amp;quot;, if I can call it that because between servers and the coins I buy to give away I&amp;amp;#39;m still in the red, are the Ads and a small fee paid by token creators to publish theirs on their platform. For users who enter the site to receive an airdrop, they don&amp;amp;#39;t need anything more than to leave the public address of their Algorand wallet, which they can create for free by downloading the corresponding application on their smartphones.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I welcome all of you to visit the site, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://algodrops.org&quot;&amp;gt;algodrops.org&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;\&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt;There are some limitations imposed by the Algorand network, not by me:) &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;You must have a minimum amount of Algorand in your wallet to receive an Airdrop&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt; &amp;lt;sup&amp;gt;You must opt-in to each asset before you can receive it for the first time.&amp;lt;/sup&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[22歲的印尼學生認爲把自拍當作NFT出售很 "有趣"，賺了100萬美元]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s52qx1/indonesian_student_22_who_thought_it_was_funny_to/?score=307&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs52qx1%2Findonesian_student_22_who_thought_it_was_funny_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs52qx1%2Findonesian_student_22_who_thought_it_was_funny_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s52qx1/indonesian_student_22_who_thought_it_was_funny_to/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 12:32:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[把這個發給你對比特幣感興趣的聯繫人，以便他們能更好地吞下橙色的藥丸。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s54g8x/send_this_to_your_contacts_interested_in_bitcoin/?score=395&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs54g8x%2Fsend_this_to_your_contacts_interested_in_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs54g8x%2Fsend_this_to_your_contacts_interested_in_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s54g8x/send_this_to_your_contacts_interested_in_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 11:34:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[16,844種加密貨幣。其中80%是純粹的垃圾]]></title><description><![CDATA[根據Coin Market cap的數據，世界市場上有16,844個加密貨幣。
儘管Coin Gecko顯示有12,463個。儘管如此，這仍然是一個巨大的數字。難怪我的一些
非加密貨幣的朋友認爲加密貨幣僅僅是一個便士股票市場。我們這些人在
的人知道一些項目有非常好的意圖，而且...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5232l/16844_crypto_currencies_80_of_them_are_pure/?score=350&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5232l%2F16844_crypto_currencies_80_of_them_are_pure%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs5232l%2F16844_crypto_currencies_80_of_them_are_pure%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s5232l/16844_crypto_currencies_80_of_them_are_pure/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 08:40:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;According to Coin Market cap there are 16,844 cryptos out on the world market although Coin Gecko shows 12,463. Still, that&amp;amp;#39;s a shitload. No wonder some of my non crypto friends think crypto is simply a penny stock market. Those of us in the space know some project have very good intentions and fail.  Some succeed. Some just hang out. But so many others are pure scam and we all know it. I guess that is the price of decentralization and I sometimes struggle with this. We don&amp;amp;#39;t believe in censorship so why would we be in the business of telling new projects they aren&amp;amp;#39;t allowed because we are already too many in the room.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sadly too many people will invest their life in dumb things like squid game tokens only to find no liquidity when trying to cash out. Others will simply be rug pulled. The worse part is the hit we as investors and believers of fundamentals take as it creates a bad reputation and gives crypto a terrible image. If politicians and regulators should have a beef with anything about crypto its these shady scam projects but how to determine a shady scam project until it is officially a scam. Many people in the crypto world still say Shib for example is a scam and that&amp;amp;#39;s their opinion. Many people not in crypto say Bitcoin is a scam. Many bitcoiners say ethereum is a scam and so on.  So where do we go from here? One critique politicians often use is crypto can&amp;amp;#39;t police itself when it comes to these scams and rug pulls so they need harsh and strict regulation to be enforced and penalized.  How can crypto police itself when project tribes can&amp;amp;#39;t stand each other and all they do is throw each other trash on twitter. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My hope is that in time as more and more people come in there are better educational tools for noobs to be aware of what is a fire hazard but I am not optimistic. People will do what they want to do in hopes of hitting a moon shot and some shady scammers know this so I imagine that number I typed in the title will likely reach 20,000 or 25,0000 by the time 2022 is over.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[從沙子到黑金。阿拉伯人明白了這個問題。沙特和阿聯酋會在2022年購買比特幣嗎？]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4la8m/from_sand_to_black_gold_arabs_understands_the/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4la8m%2Ffrom_sand_to_black_gold_arabs_understands_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4la8m%2Ffrom_sand_to_black_gold_arabs_understands_the%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4la8m/from_sand_to_black_gold_arabs_understands_the/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 08:40:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[勿忘我》和《大空頭》背後的電影人。我的加密貨幣電影將是關於貓糞的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一次採訪中
[https://www.nytimes.com/2022/01/13/opinion/tech-congress-subpoenas.html]，Kara
Swisher問Adam McKay："你認爲一部以加密貨幣爲中心的電影
會是什麼樣子？"，他的回答是這樣的。

> "這將是關於一種加密貨幣，而不是存在於
>...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4g4ay/filmmaker_behind_dont_look_up_and_the_big_short/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4g4ay%2Ffilmmaker_behind_dont_look_up_and_the_big_short%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4g4ay%2Ffilmmaker_behind_dont_look_up_and_the_big_short%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4g4ay/filmmaker_behind_dont_look_up_and_the_big_short/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 07:30:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In an &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2022/01/13/opinion/tech-congress-subpoenas.html&quot;&amp;gt;interview&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, Kara Swisher asked Adam McKay: “What do you imagine a cryptocurrency-centered movie would look like?”, and this was his answer:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“It would be about a cryptocurrency that, rather than existing on the blockchain, exists exclusively in the form of Siamese cat turds. Governments would go on to create giant litter boxes in airplane hangars where thousands of cats create turds 24/7 that are then shipped to the national bank vault. Counterfeit turds are created by black-and-white tuxedo cats but can be detected by —&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m going to stop this answer right now and apologize to you. I’m a bit tired. Ha-ha.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hehe, I’m giving it a a week before CATTURD becomes a meme coin 😂&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Edit&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;:Typos&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果這東西像牛奶一樣老化，那麼這傢伙已經變得多麼爛了？]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4wb2r/if_this_aged_like_milk_how_rotten_has_this_guy/?score=323&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4wb2r%2Fif_this_aged_like_milk_how_rotten_has_this_guy%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4wb2r%2Fif_this_aged_like_milk_how_rotten_has_this_guy%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4wb2r/if_this_aged_like_milk_how_rotten_has_this_guy/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 06:43:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[令人震驚--一個投資巨頭剛剛建議各國和中央銀行在價格低迷時購買比特幣]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4omsa/astonishingan_investment_giant_just_advised/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4omsa%2Fastonishingan_investment_giant_just_advised%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4omsa%2Fastonishingan_investment_giant_just_advised%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4omsa/astonishingan_investment_giant_just_advised/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 06:43:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[馬克斯-凱澤說，擠兌白銀 "在我看來不再是一個可行的遊戲"。"我認爲最好的運動就是購買比特幣"。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4vonj/max_keiser_says_silver_squeeze_is_no_longer_a/?score=353&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4vonj%2Fmax_keiser_says_silver_squeeze_is_no_longer_a%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4vonj%2Fmax_keiser_says_silver_squeeze_is_no_longer_a%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4vonj/max_keiser_says_silver_squeeze_is_no_longer_a/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 04:33:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto.com Coin (CRO)在創下歷史新高後下跌55%：每週最大的跌幅 - BeInCrypto]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4dz3n/cryptocom_coin_cro_decreases_by_55_after_alltime/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4dz3n%2Fcryptocom_coin_cro_decreases_by_55_after_alltime%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4dz3n%2Fcryptocom_coin_cro_decreases_by_55_after_alltime%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4dz3n/cryptocom_coin_cro_decreases_by_55_after_alltime/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 02:44:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞波公司通過與政府合作傳播能源恐懼症來資助反對比特幣的宣傳活動]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞波實驗室一直在資助 "研究"，與政府實體一起傳播
資助 "研究"，與政府實體一起傳播反對比特幣和挖礦的宣傳。

2021年，他們資助了一篇評論文章，聲稱紐約的消費者的能源價格已經增加了6美元。
因爲挖礦，紐約的消費者每月增加了6美元。

聲稱：挖礦推動了家庭...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4vtk9/ripple_is_funding_propaganda_against_bitcoin_by/?score=786&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4vtk9%2Fripple_is_funding_propaganda_against_bitcoin_by%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4vtk9%2Fripple_is_funding_propaganda_against_bitcoin_by%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4vtk9/ripple_is_funding_propaganda_against_bitcoin_by/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 00:53:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Ripple labs has been funding &amp;amp;quot;research&amp;amp;quot; along with government entities to spread propaganda against Bitcoin and mining. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In 2021, they funded a hit piece that claims energy prices for consumers in New York has increased by $6 per month because of mining. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/m0ta2tae4xb81.png?width=1318&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=8079d16b0fde7bc74ebd204d4362ff823da26d3f&quot;&amp;gt;Claim: Mining drives up household electricity bills&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Surely its not the soaring costs of natural gas that is driving up electricity prices, but mining? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/iprxvhfj5xb81.jpg?width=2610&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e4da2516b82eb585706d4d1af417320b5b82889e&quot;&amp;gt;Since June 2020, Natural gas prices have gone up by 350&amp;amp;#37; in the USA (Henry Hub natural gas futures rolling contracts)&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/v2gl6rmx3xb81.jpg?width=3094&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9dae03fee6dfbbfaf58df82519db809462d01254&quot;&amp;gt;Not just in USA, in UK, natural gas is at decadal highs. &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Surely, electricity prices that consumers pay have nothing whatsoever to do with inflation, or soaring gas prices that are in decadal highs.. but is due to bitcoin mining?!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crude oil WTI futures are currently at 84, for comparison it was around 56 in Nov 2019 (pre pandemic). The last time WTI was above 80 was all the way back in 2014. Increasing crude oil natural gas prices, along with inflation that is at multi-decade high is not the reason for increase in household electricity, but its bitcoin mining that is responsible.. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/a4z5aqnyaxb81.jpg?width=1944&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=6656489541bece07a0e9b83837d42345157f987c&quot;&amp;gt;Thats according to this study funded by Ripple in collusion with the Department of Treasury. &amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;... The same Department of Treasury headed by another well known Bitcoin hater Janet Yellen, who earned $7m as &amp;amp;quot;speaking fee&amp;amp;quot; from the same banks she is supposed to regulate but has tried to stifle Bitcoin and crypto at every opportunity. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Research with &amp;amp;quot;financial support&amp;amp;quot; is nothing but propaganda, especially when it&amp;amp;#39;s funded by a competitor to bitcoin that lobbies with the government. Ripple continues to be a centralised premine scam created to enrich its founders. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Ripple has also cozied up with the likes of WEF, the very organisations Bitcoin was created as a fuck you to. &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.weforum.org/organizations/ripple&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.weforum.org/organizations/ripple&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As its price and narrative around the shitcoin has stagnated, Ripple is resorting to dirty political tricks to get a leg up. As usual, they will fail. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The narrative that bitcoin mining companies cause increase in electricity bills in NY is rubbish, as the largest BTC mining companies in New York produce their own energy. Infact the last one to start mining in NY is a hydro electric plant that was unused for years, before they started mining Bitcoin last year. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.timesunion.com/news/article/Mechanicville-hydro-plant-gets-new-life-16299115.php&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.timesunion.com/news/article/Mechanicville-hydro-plant-gets-new-life-16299115.php&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The other large mining company Greenidge Generation also produces its own energy.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: Buttcoin losers in comments say &amp;amp;quot;reee bitcoin move to POS or govt will ban it&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Yeah not too bright, the whole point of Bitcoin is that it cant be banned unlike the proof of stake shitcoins you support that can be created out of thin air at the press of a button and shut down at the press of a button.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Another one who is literally a war monger calling for Ukraine invasion but pretends to care about global e-waste. Lmao. Bitcoin haters are really a funny bunch&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼我們需要去中心化：我的YouTube賬戶無緣無故地被永久取消了]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一名加密貨幣YouTuber，也是一名內容作家，但在你開始向我投擲石塊並稱我爲騙子之前
之前，我教人們如何建立和測試加密貨幣
交易算法，作爲自動化交易策略的一種手段，或者僅僅是
在一個安全、測試的環境中嘗試算法交易...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4ulz9/why_we_need_decentralisation_my_youtube_account/?score=397&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4ulz9%2Fwhy_we_need_decentralisation_my_youtube_account%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4ulz9%2Fwhy_we_need_decentralisation_my_youtube_account%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4ulz9/why_we_need_decentralisation_my_youtube_account/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 00:53:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m a crypto YouTuber, and content writer, but before you start throwing rocks at me and call me a shill, I teach people how to build and test cryptocurrency trading algorithms as a means of automating their trading strategies, or simply to experiment with algo trading in a safe, testing environment.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some of you may have seen my previous posts, where I open source entire projects and share them with the community if I feel like they could add value to you guys. I like doing it and it makes feel good that you guys appreciate the content so much.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Because everything that I build is open source and available for everyone, the only way that I&amp;amp;#39;ve been able to monetise my passion is by becoming a YouTube partner, and monetising my videos.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I don&amp;amp;#39;t make a huge amount, but enough to keep me hopeful that one day, it will grow and actually make a difference.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here&amp;amp;#39;s a video I just made explaining the whole thing in more detail. I&amp;amp;#39;m also using that video to raise awareness against the corrupted mess that is YouTube so if you feel like helping, feel free to show this video to other people who might not understand just how destructive these corporations are for the freedom of our Internet: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/VRJXvJnUWV8&quot;&amp;gt;https://youtu.be/VRJXvJnUWV8&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ve recently received an e-mail from Google telling me that my Adsense account has been cancelled. For those that don&amp;amp;#39;t know, without an adsense account, you can&amp;amp;#39;t get paid by YouTube.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They haven&amp;amp;#39;t sent a warning, started in investigation, or asked me anything prior to that.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is literally all the information that they have given me:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/sba6q2jv3xb81.png?width=629&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=882822e4b75bd9d9ec128a6bb63f393a91c916ce&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/sba6q2jv3xb81.png?width=629&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=882822e4b75bd9d9ec128a6bb63f393a91c916ce&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I have appealed this decision, and got back a dry response, saying that my adsense account will not be re-instated.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know I&amp;amp;#39;m not the first, and sadly won&amp;amp;#39;t be the last crypto YouTuber to be cancelled by google without any prior explanation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ve spent hours reading their terms and conditions, and it doesn&amp;amp;#39;t seem that Google was ever in the right with this, making this a breach of contract.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I was always for the idea of a decentralised internet and social media, but I never realised before how much we need it, and how valuable freedom and justice truly are as given by the blockchain and decentralisation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I hope that my experience has given you the extra fuel you needed to want to search for alternative decentralised solutions in favour of the established tech giants who don&amp;amp;#39;t care about anything but their own obscene profits.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;EDIT:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;For those wanting to see proof of demonetisation and that there is no invalid traffic coming into my youtube channel:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/gt461bl0bxb81.png?width=398&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=f749caec3e9c4ecf7e61124f82f7887c714d6c8e&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/gt461bl0bxb81.png?width=398&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=f749caec3e9c4ecf7e61124f82f7887c714d6c8e&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And here are the analytics for the period that my monetisation started, showing no artificial or fraudulent traffic:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/qg4owscgbxb81.png?width=909&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=bc86426b9765ae1b200de72fbb75a8f2af49a7af&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/qg4owscgbxb81.png?width=909&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=bc86426b9765ae1b200de72fbb75a8f2af49a7af&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And here are more analytics explaining this traffic:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ojvf749mbxb81.png?width=1125&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=ad79ef279207be857b1ff22081f1f10f3e19c967&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/ojvf749mbxb81.png?width=1125&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=ad79ef279207be857b1ff22081f1f10f3e19c967&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[停止對加密貨幣採用的把關]]></title><description><![CDATA[諷刺特斯拉接受dogecoin購買某些物品的帖子鹹魚翻身，獲得了很高的投票率。
物品--世界上市值第六大的公司，而且無疑是最引人注目的公司之一。
世界上市值第六大的公司之一，無疑是世界上最引人注目的公司之一，接受用加密貨幣購買物品。
用加密貨幣購買物品--以加密貨幣而不是法幣定價 ...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4r422/stop_gatekeeping_crypto_adoption/?score=403&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4r422%2Fstop_gatekeeping_crypto_adoption%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4r422%2Fstop_gatekeeping_crypto_adoption%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4r422/stop_gatekeeping_crypto_adoption/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 22:38:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The salty, highly upvoted post mocking dogecoin being accepted at Tesla for some items - the sixth largest company in the world in market cap, and undoubtedly one of the most visible companies in the world, accepting the purchase of items with cryptocurrency - priced in cryptocurrency and not fiat - is absolutely disgraceful. It shows what this sub is - not an advocate for cryptocurrency, but a thinly veiled place to be tribal and act salty when other people’s bags do well.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That’s pathetic.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is a win for cryptocurrency in general. I’ve been around this space since 2013. Back then, Bitcoiners were screaming for companies to accept cryptocurrency and price things in cryptocurrency. Then when it happens 8 years later, the primary attitude about it is salt just because the cryptocurrency of choice isn’t in the bag of certain people in the sub.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Grow up, take a step back, and recognize this as a win for cryptocurrency. We are in this together.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If it was your cryptocurrency of preference being accepted, you’d magically consider it a good thing. That’s the truth.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Note: My bad, this is a remade post - the original was closed as I shared it on my Twitter, which I have found is against this subreddit’s rules.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我可以告訴很多人已經對加密貨幣空間失去了希望，這沒有關係]]></title><description><![CDATA[在過去的18個月裏，我一直被關在裏面，這個社區幫助了我
了很多。這不是關於月亮的耕作，而是關於參與、學習、寫作。
和社區。

但我可以告訴人們已經失去了希望，參與度下降，情緒消極。
積極的前景是低的，這沒關係，...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4e68d/i_can_tell_a_lot_of_people_have_lost_hope_towards/?score=310&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4e68d%2Fi_can_tell_a_lot_of_people_have_lost_hope_towards%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4e68d%2Fi_can_tell_a_lot_of_people_have_lost_hope_towards%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4e68d/i_can_tell_a_lot_of_people_have_lost_hope_towards/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 20:40:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve been locked inside for the past 18months and this community has helped me so much. It’s not about moon farming, it’s about engagement, learning, writing, and community.        &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But I can tell people have lost hope, engagement is down, sentiment is negative, positive outlooks are low, and that’s okay, I still believe in the projects I’m holding, the community here is still vast, and for that want to thank everyone here for being on my list of anti-depressant activities.         &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As the fear and greed index fluctuates in times of uncertainty, I can always trust my fellow cryptonauts to support me through it all!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[0.1]]></title><description><![CDATA[剛剛達到0.1 BTC。這是個小成就，但還是個成就。

我正在使用Coinbase Pro。

HODL

我這樣做對嗎？]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4m4kc/01/?score=441&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4m4kc%2F01%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4m4kc%2F01%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4m4kc/01/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 18:45:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just hit 0.1 BTC.  It is a small achievement, but an achievement nonetheless.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I am using Coinbase Pro.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;HODL&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Am I doing this right?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[還有誰無視FUD，覺得2022年真的看漲加密貨幣？]]></title><description><![CDATA[標題涵蓋了一句話，我已經在加密貨幣領域工作了幾年，我在今年一月聽到了同樣的藉口。
今年1月，我聽到了同樣的藉口，每次市場下跌/修正/崩潰時都會重複這些藉口。
市場下跌/修正/崩潰的時候都會聽到同樣的藉口。

"這一次，它結束了"

"專家們說，股市隨時會崩潰"

"BTC是...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4kuct/who_else_is_ignoring_the_fud_and_feeling_really/?score=322&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4kuct%2Fwho_else_is_ignoring_the_fud_and_feeling_really%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4kuct%2Fwho_else_is_ignoring_the_fud_and_feeling_really%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4kuct/who_else_is_ignoring_the_fud_and_feeling_really/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 18:45:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Title covers it in a sentence, I&amp;amp;#39;ve been in crypto for a few years and I&amp;amp;#39;m hearing the same tired excuses this January that are repeated every time the market dips/corrects/crashes.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;This time it&amp;amp;#39;s over&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;The experts are saying that the stock markets are going to crash any day now&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;BTC was funded by printed money is the only reason it pumped, it will never pump again&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Blah, blah blah. Every time these lines of reason are rolled out and every time crypto pumps back up again. You wouldn&amp;amp;#39;t get this in the regular stock market, people don&amp;amp;#39;t see a recession and be all like &amp;amp;quot;well that&amp;amp;#39;s it for stocks, it&amp;amp;#39;s been all pump for 100 years but it&amp;amp;#39;s over forever now&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Well I&amp;amp;#39;ve read it all before and I don&amp;amp;#39;t see anything to worry me. The markets already down almost 50% from ATH and has been stable for 9 days and counting meaning huge gains when we set a new ATH and despite the painting the FUD want&amp;amp;#39;s to share I see that ATH hitting in this year with no issue.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[里約熱內盧將分配1%的國庫資金給比特幣]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4guu0/rio_de_janeiro_will_allocate_1_of_treasury_to/?score=411&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4guu0%2Frio_de_janeiro_will_allocate_1_of_treasury_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4guu0%2Frio_de_janeiro_will_allocate_1_of_treasury_to%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4guu0/rio_de_janeiro_will_allocate_1_of_treasury_to/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 16:52:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[昨天看了《大空頭》，對實際發生的事情感到震驚。我完全理解爲什麼要創建加密貨幣，因爲系統出現了大混亂。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你沒有看過這部電影，我肯定會推薦你去看! 這段文字可能
含有一些破壞性的內容。

我一直聽說過電影《大空頭》，但以前從未看過它。I
我對所發生的事情感到震驚，以及人們、銀行、對沖基金等對提供貸款或者
基金等對提供貸款或投資於...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4hj2z/watched_the_big_short_yesterday_and_was_shocked/?score=337&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4hj2z%2Fwatched_the_big_short_yesterday_and_was_shocked%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4hj2z%2Fwatched_the_big_short_yesterday_and_was_shocked%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4hj2z/watched_the_big_short_yesterday_and_was_shocked/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 16:52:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you&amp;amp;#39;ve never seen the movie I definitely recommend it! This text might contain some spoilers.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ve always heard of the movie &amp;amp;#39;the big short&amp;amp;#39; but never watched it before. I was shocked at what went down and how totally ignorant people, banks, hedge funds etc were to giving loans or investing in loans without having any liquidity behind it. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For me the most mind blowing fact is that only 1 guy went to jail, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;1 GUY!&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Like always the average Joe ended up paying for all the shit that banks started being so greedy. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Although cryptocurrency is far from perfect it&amp;amp;#39;s a very different approach being (mostly) decentralised and trying to even the playing field for both the rich and the poor. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Have you seen the movie? What do you think of the events that happened? Curious!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[還記得Nano嗎，這個子的（以前？）最喜歡的硬幣？今天，它自2017年以來首次離開前200名]]></title><description><![CDATA[還記得納米嗎？那個真正從2017年11月的0.15美元飆升到兩個月後的33美元的硬幣？
到兩個月後的33美元？它甚至還在前20名中呆過一段時間。嗯，我想
這裏的許多人當時一定是在接近ATH的地方買的，因爲他們總是
真心希望它能再次走到那裏，並談到了他們的...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4iozd/remember_nano_this_subs_former_favorite_coin_it/?score=411&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4iozd%2Fremember_nano_this_subs_former_favorite_coin_it%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4iozd%2Fremember_nano_this_subs_former_favorite_coin_it%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4iozd/remember_nano_this_subs_former_favorite_coin_it/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 15:32:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Remember Nano? That coin that really shot up from, like, $0.15 in November 2017 to $33 two months later? It even was in the top 20 for a bit. Well, I suppose many people on here must have bought close to ATH back then, because they always REALLY wanted it to go there again and talked about their love for it a lot&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Unfortunately it never did. It was hit HARD by the bear market of 2018ff., even went below $0.4. While it did quite well in the bullrun of 2021, it was one of those coins that stayed way below their 2017-2018 ATHs, it got close to $15. Other than most other formerly huge coins that didn&amp;amp;#39;t reach a new ATH this bull run - stuff like XRP, BCH, EOS, NEO, DASH... - which don&amp;amp;#39;t get a lot of love on here, Nano stayed a sub favorite, I don&amp;amp;#39;t think any other coin outside the top 100 (except Moons) is mentioned this often.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Speaking of the top 100: you can see how much this sub loves Nano, if you read &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/og5u6m/its_official_nano_is_no_longer_among_the_top_100/&quot;&amp;gt;this post&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; from last July, when it left the top 100 - OP was at a &amp;amp;quot;loss for words&amp;amp;quot;, how could a coin that was &amp;amp;quot;perfect: Instant. Feeless. Green&amp;amp;quot; not be much higher? Many people agreed, the post has over 5k upvotes. I would argue the post was a bit dramatic - Nano hat only re-entered the top 100 3 months earlier after spending a few weeks below that - but you see how much love there is for the coin.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Today, it left the top 200 for the first time since its big explosion in late 2017, as I am writing this it&amp;amp;#39;s 202 on Coingecko, -91% since ATH, the downtrend has been pretty consistent the past few months.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What do you think about Nano? Do you still believe in it, do you think it will break its ATH ever again? Do you think it&amp;amp;#39;s a dead coin that will just continue to go down? Other coins have been declared dead for less but hey, it&amp;amp;#39;s crypto, anything can happen&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是唯一一個討厭用 "聰 "作爲比特幣單位的人嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道 "Satoshi "是向比特幣的創造者致敬（儘管這可能不是他們的名字）。
可能不是他們的名字），但我覺得它並不合適。
"比特幣 "是一個美麗的，合乎邏輯的，巧妙的名字，它可以在口中滾動
正如我所期望的那樣，它是由發明和命名它的天才創造的...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4beq9/am_i_the_only_one_who_hates_using_satoshi_as_the/?score=313&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4beq9%2Fam_i_the_only_one_who_hates_using_satoshi_as_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs4beq9%2Fam_i_the_only_one_who_hates_using_satoshi_as_the%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s4beq9/am_i_the_only_one_who_hates_using_satoshi_as_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 15:32:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;like, i get that “satoshi” is homage to bitcoin’s creator (even though that probably isn’t their name), but it just doesn’t feel like it fits well. “bitcoin” is such a beautiful, logical, and ingenious name thats rolls of the tongue (as i would expect from the genius that invented and named it) but “satoshi” just isn’t and doesn’t—especially when pronouncing it “sats”. i always felt like “bits” made perfect sense: a bitcoin is a coin made up of bits, and 100 million bits make up a bitcoin—bits and coins, digits and money, together in perfect harmony. it sounds like something straight out of a videogame too: “that coffee will be 10,000 bits.” versus “that coffee will be 10,000 sats.” and if you divide further, you get millibits and mbits, which is still easy to say and still sounds cool, versus millisatoshi and msats.  i saw that apparently “bits” was proposed for a unit of 100 sats, but that’s just unnecessarily complicated; in america we use dollar whether its $1 or $100 or $1 billion and it works just fine. im sure it’s a losing battle but the word “satoshi” just sucks aesthetically and linguistically and i hate it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ticketmaster公司注意了。NFT票務即將顛覆票務行業。一個全面的名單，其中包括那些建議使用NFT票務的人。從馬克-庫班到維塔利克]]></title><description><![CDATA[NFT門票的好處包括。



 * 防止詐騙和假票。區塊鏈提供了一個單一的真相來源
   區塊鏈爲組織者和持票人提供了單一的事實來源。NFT的轉讓從最初的銷售到任何後續的轉售都會在區塊鏈上被永久記錄下來。
   區塊鏈爲組織者和持票人提供了一個單一的真相來源，從最初的銷售到隨後的轉售，都在區塊鏈上有不可更改的記錄。
   區塊鏈，因此所有各方都可以在區塊鏈上進行交易...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4hk9c/ticketmaster_watch_out_nft_tickets_are_about_to/?score=378&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4hk9c%2Fticketmaster_watch_out_nft_tickets_are_about_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4hk9c%2Fticketmaster_watch_out_nft_tickets_are_about_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4hk9c/ticketmaster_watch_out_nft_tickets_are_about_to/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 12:56:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Benefits of NFT tickets include:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Preventing      scams and fake tickets&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: The blockchain provides a single source of truth for both organisers      and ticket holders. The transfer of NFTs from initial sale to any      subsequent resale is recorded immutably on the blockchain, so all parties      involved can easily verify the authenticity of the ticket. Even cooler, in      cases where resale of tickets is strictly forbidden, NFTs can be      programmed as non-transferrable, so they physically cannot be moved to      another buyer.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Perpetual      revenue:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; As      programmable digital assets NFTs can have built-in rules for resales,      merchandise, content and royalty splits. This means that the organiser can      determine profit sharing percentages for any future resales or downstream      creative content on secondary markets, and reliably receive these funds      knowing they are unalterable within the NFT’s coding.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;New      revenue opportunities:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; NFTs put tickets into the realm of programmable money, opening      up unlimited potential for new revenue opportunities. For example resale      of NFT tickets as &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;collectables,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; using NFT tickets as a gateway for giving      food and drink deals, even rewarding super fans who have collected a      certain number of event tickets.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Over the past year the NFT tickets have gained more attention in the crypto space. I have compiled extensive list of developers, investors, financial instintutions, ticketing companies and NBA owners that have advocated the benefits of NFT ticketing&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Mark Cuban – Entrepreneur, shark and owner of the Dallas Mavericks&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/k2zoj07hvtb81.png?width=632&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=65a0e2c83821f1b3bff121891cf67aa030b1bcf2&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/k2zoj07hvtb81.png?width=632&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=65a0e2c83821f1b3bff121891cf67aa030b1bcf2&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Gary Vaynerchuk -   CEO of&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Vaynermedia&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;, Creator of veefriends&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/59781hd3ttb81.png?width=512&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=08406f2bc45d558d4216ff0c05e71f5678bd3b50&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/59781hd3ttb81.png?width=512&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=08406f2bc45d558d4216ff0c05e71f5678bd3b50&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Jack Groetzinger – CEO Seatgeek&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/m9lkfhk8ttb81.png?width=359&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e12323191a507d1f7ad0836fe9b9aba0b7e86353&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/m9lkfhk8ttb81.png?width=359&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e12323191a507d1f7ad0836fe9b9aba0b7e86353&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Ted Leonsis – owner of  NBA&amp;amp;#39;s Wizards, the NHL&amp;amp;#39;s Capitals, the WNBA&amp;amp;#39;s Washington Mystics&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/14k6idkjttb81.png?width=944&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=b04d6ab877077c18f85100b75d277cf4e6faab0e&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/14k6idkjttb81.png?width=944&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=b04d6ab877077c18f85100b75d277cf4e6faab0e&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Barry Ritholtz – co-founder of Ritholtz wealth mangement – 2 billions usd under management&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/74jxll3mutb81.png?width=455&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=fc4886553e652a7c5fb9a3755c822346f823df25&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/74jxll3mutb81.png?width=455&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=fc4886553e652a7c5fb9a3755c822346f823df25&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Coinmarketcap&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/fy7m0emsutb81.png?width=474&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=c2d550c78c90425602937f60d5dba9c42c62b4e0&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/fy7m0emsutb81.png?width=474&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=c2d550c78c90425602937f60d5dba9c42c62b4e0&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Bankless&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/vnt6j50zutb81.png?width=368&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d776fa5502b8b6d16f34ee232e1f7e23d19edec8&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/vnt6j50zutb81.png?width=368&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d776fa5502b8b6d16f34ee232e1f7e23d19edec8&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Joe Rogan Experience&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/kqll0w03vtb81.png?width=389&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=0667fe950610653de77b1a7169d978608675139b&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/kqll0w03vtb81.png?width=389&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=0667fe950610653de77b1a7169d978608675139b&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Grayscale - Worlds largest crypto asset manager&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/w85b3prcvtb81.png?width=945&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d1e2bf71ba91c0ea3b5c3bcd98fc01da82c40373&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/w85b3prcvtb81.png?width=945&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d1e2bf71ba91c0ea3b5c3bcd98fc01da82c40373&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Vitalik Buterin - co-founder Ethereum&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/0lv82fosstb81.png?width=345&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e7e2f03ab0d0edd960a1fbed027624b503dec373&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/0lv82fosstb81.png?width=345&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e7e2f03ab0d0edd960a1fbed027624b503dec373&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密貨幣的初學者指南]]></title><description><![CDATA[什麼是區塊鏈？

它是一個 "不可變的賬本"。想想看，它就像一本住在天上的書。
每當有什麼變化時，它就會用神奇的墨水寫下來，當墨水乾了之後。
永遠不會改變。而這些書有成千上萬的副本，都是在同一時間被更新。
在同一時間更新。如果有一天...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s41z1x/a_beginners_guide_to_cryptocurrency/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs41z1x%2Fa_beginners_guide_to_cryptocurrency%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs41z1x%2Fa_beginners_guide_to_cryptocurrency%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s41z1x/a_beginners_guide_to_cryptocurrency/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 08:35:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What is a blockchain?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is an “immutable ledger.” Think about it like a book that lives in the sky. Every time something changes, its written down with magic ink, that when dries, never changes. And there are thousands of copies of these books, all getting updated at the same time. If one is ever messed with, the other books would wipe out the problem and replace it with the correct entry.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(Tedtalk – Blockchain Massively simplified)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mbcg.io/vision?pgid=kn921drf-2058f817-4ebc-4c29-8430-a667933ff044&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.mbcg.io/vision?pgid=kn921drf-2058f817-4ebc-4c29-8430-a667933ff044&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What is proof of Work?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;First generation crypto currency worked of the concept of Poof of work. There, it is a race to solve a complicated math puzzle, and perform the block write operation. And as a reward get coin. “Mining.” Mining is slow. Bitcoin can only do 7 transactions a minute.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Of the thousands and thousands of machines out there racing to win the next block, only 1 at a time wins. That means the others have literally wasted their energy via compute CPU and GPU cycles. Bitcoin used more energy than Argentina last year.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
But its not all bad. POW is still the oldest and most battle tested consensus algorithm, and many ague more secure because of it. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/p/proof-work.asp&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/p/proof-work.asp&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-56012952&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-56012952&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What is proof of Stake?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Proof of Stake works on different types of newly developed “Consensus” algorithms. Ouroboros protocol, created by IHOK and Cardano, along with a team of PHDs and mathematicians, is the first of its kind. They created a secure “lottery” consensus mechanism to “elect” the next “slot leader” to write the block. Here each Stake pool can get a chance to be elected by winning the lottery. Each Ada coin represents 1 lottery ticket. When you delegate to the pool, you give that pool your ticket, not your coin. If the pool wins, you get the reward along with everyone in the pool, and the operator. Because there is no more complicated math puzzle, and no more computers racing to solve the puzzle, its much much faster, and much much cheaper. Cardano nodes can be run on Raspberry Pi.. A lot of nodes out there run on Solar energy. It’s so good, Ethereum, who is proof of work currently, is moving to this model as part of their ETH 2.0 migration. Hopefully this summer with the &amp;amp;quot;merge.&amp;amp;quot; In efforts to reduce gas fees and energy concerns. Pokodot created its own Consensus algorithm. Called Grandpa. Tezos has its Emmy+, and the list goes on. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Each other their own way of doing things. But “gen 3” is not Proof of work.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What you should remember is that for both POW, POS, and others, they are all a means of incentivizing the actual people that run the computers hosting the blockchain code. Without them, there is no “decentralized network of immutable ledgers.” Which is because that’s just fancy talk for machines running our code to support the blockchain. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/p/proof-stake-pos.asp&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/p/proof-stake-pos.asp&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cardano.org/ouroboros/&quot;&amp;gt;https://cardano.org/ouroboros/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://wiki.polkadot.network/docs/en/learn-consensus&quot;&amp;gt;https://wiki.polkadot.network/docs/en/learn-consensus&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://ethereum.org/en/developers/docs/consensus-mechanisms/pos/&quot;&amp;gt;https://ethereum.org/en/developers/docs/consensus-mechanisms/pos/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://wiki.tezosagora.org/learn/baking/proofofstake/consensus&quot;&amp;gt;https://wiki.tezosagora.org/learn/baking/proofofstake/consensus&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What is Market Cap and coin supply and why should we care?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Market Capitalization is equal to Price of Coin times Supply of Coin. That is, it. But very important.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;BITCOIN has a fixed supply. It is not all mined yet. Not until 2140. But it does have a finite amount, 21 Million.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here is why you can see a 65K or even 100K bitcoin, but you’ll probably never see a 100 dollar DOGE, or even a 30 Dollar Ada (not soon anyway)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Currently there are  18,929,200 BTC out there at a cost of 43,087.16.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That means, the market cap is 43,087.16 x 18,929,200  = 815,605,469,072 (815B)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cardano, has a fixed coin supply as well. But it is 45 Billion. There are currently 33,526,814,681. So you see the max is 2500x more. Likewise, with 130B DOGE vs 18M BTC - it’s ~6700X more. DogeCoin also makes 10,000 new coins a minute.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At a price is 1.26 that means the market cap for Cardano is 1.26 X 33,526,814,681 = 42,243,786,498.06 (42B)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You’ll need 136B market cap to reach a 1-dollar DOGE in the next year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;132,670,764,300 + ((10,000*60*24*351) = 137,725,164,300 (Supply of DOGE in 1 year from now)&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
137,725,164,300 * 1 = 137,725,164,300&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You&amp;amp;#39;ll need an almost 1 Trillion Market Cap for Cardano to hit 3032,127,627,594 * 30 = 963,828,827,820&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To give you some reference. Here is the Market cap of some big names.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Visa – 499B&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Adobe – 250B&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Amazon – 1.7T&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It’s very confusing because every coin has their own supply. Their own way of creating coins and at what cadence. Some even “burn” coins. So, know what yours does and how it works.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bitpanda.com/academy/en/lessons/what-is-market-capitalisation-market-cap-and-why-does-it-matter/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.bitpanda.com/academy/en/lessons/what-is-market-capitalisation-market-cap-and-why-does-it-matter/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coinmarketcap.com/&quot;&amp;gt;https://coinmarketcap.com/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/tech/cryptocurrency-burning-can-it-manage-inflation/#:%7E:text=Coin%20burning%20is%20the%20process,according%20to%20the%20Motley%20Fool&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.investopedia.com/tech/cryptocurrency-burning-can-it-manage-inflation/#:~:text=Coin%20burning%20is%20the%20process,according%20to%20the%20Motley%20Fool&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://companiesmarketcap.com/visa/marketcap/&quot;&amp;gt;https://companiesmarketcap.com/visa/marketcap/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://companiesmarketcap.com/adobe/marketcap/&quot;&amp;gt;https://companiesmarketcap.com/adobe/marketcap/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://companiesmarketcap.com/amazon/marketcap/&quot;&amp;gt;https://companiesmarketcap.com/amazon/marketcap/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;How can I “get in early?”&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;First. We are all early. You might not have gotten in on the first floor, but we’re only halfway up the stairs to the second flight.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Global wealth is estimated at 1 quadrillion. All the Market Cap in crypto is at 2.05 Trillion. That’s only 0.21% of the world’s wealth.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When looking for “what could be the next big thing” find something with a low market cap, regardless of coin price, that has a strong chance of doing well because of team and tech, the two Ts.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also ask yourself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What are these coins use cases?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Who is their target audience for adoption?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Who is funding them?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Who is their team building it? What is their history?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do they have a good plan?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://river.com/learn/how-much-worlds-money-in-bitcoin/#:%7E:text=Global%20wealth%20is%20estimated%20at,represents%200.09%25%20of%20global%20wealth&quot;&amp;gt;https://river.com/learn/how-much-worlds-money-in-bitcoin/#:~:text=Global%20wealth%20is%20estimated%20at,represents%200.09%25%20of%20global%20wealth&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What are your goals?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto is really split into 4 worlds.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Day traders, H.O.D.L.’ers, Whales, and weak hands.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Day traders realize that this market is very volatile, now, and historically. Good ones, can capitalize on quick gains by buying low and selling high, waiting for a dip, then buying back in, and selling high again, cyclically.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then there are those that “Hold On for Dear Life.” These people tend to find something they really are passionate about, and never sell. They keep buying. If they see their coin dips, below at what they bought it at, and have some extra funds, they buy more, to &amp;amp;quot;Average Down.&amp;amp;quot; Or Dollar cost average (DCA) by buying a set amount on a regular cadence. They only “take profit” buy selling a small portion when price is really high.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Whales, are investors that come in with millions and billions of dollars. They often “test” the market buy either buying or dumping millions and billions in hopes to manipulate the market to their advantage. If you’re reading this, you’re probably not in this category, but you should know they exist and effect this marketplace.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then there are “weak hands.” Do not pick this one. These people buy high and sell low. They only invest based on emotion, and nothing else. When things start going bad, they panic, and sell at a loss. Its much better to let your coin go to .000000001 cents, and just hold on to it in the hopes of a rally years later, then it is to ever sell at a loss. Never do this. Never.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Each has its own risks and rewards.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Day trading can rack up dollars quick, but you can lose them just as quick. And there are tax implicates with trades. Some unknown, and constantly changing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;HODL, might take years, but if you do, the chance of your Return on Invest improves significantly in crypto.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Pick what works best for you but have a plan.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptocurrencyfacts.com/hodling-vs-trading-for-new-cryptocurrency-investors/&quot;&amp;gt;https://cryptocurrencyfacts.com/hodling-vs-trading-for-new-cryptocurrency-investors/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What are things to look out for?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Do your own research&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. There are now more then 4K types of crypto currencies. You can create your own in about 30 minutes with the right free tools.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The mortality rate of new coins is super high this year. Lots of people trying to do Pump and Dumps.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There is nothing in life that goes up for no reason, if it does, it’s a Ponzi scheme.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://lifehacker.com/how-to-create-your-own-cryptocurrency-1825337462&quot;&amp;gt;https://lifehacker.com/how-to-create-your-own-cryptocurrency-1825337462&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.financialexpress.com/market/rip-cryptocurrencies-number-of-dead-coins-up-35-over-last-year-tally-nears-2000-mark/2226169/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.financialexpress.com/market/rip-cryptocurrencies-number-of-dead-coins-up-35-over-last-year-tally-nears-2000-mark/2226169/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://bravenewcoin.com/insights/how-to-identify-a-crypto-pump-and-dump-scheme&quot;&amp;gt;https://bravenewcoin.com/insights/how-to-identify-a-crypto-pump-and-dump-scheme&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What is the difference between storing on an exchange or in a wallet?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A lot.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;First, you must remember what the dream of crypto is really offering.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Its offering a way for us to break away from banks. Forever.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Centralized banks that can print money, is a problem. Blockchain solves this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But not if the new bank ends up being Binace or Coinbase. In fact, keeping your coin in exchanges puts us all at risk of market manipulation by them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When a certain 1 person or group owns too many nodes, they can make choices that would benefit them. The attack vector is called a 51% attack or sybil attack.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Today however, you need exchanges to on ramp and off ramp FIAT. FIAT money is government-issued currency that is not backed by a physical commodity, such as gold or silver.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But it will not be like that forever. Chains like ADA and DOT will be interoperable with legacy banks and will eventually cut out exchanges.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Personally, I despise BNB coin and binace. They already take high fees, and now they want the control and the rewards too. Coinbase isn’t much better. Again though, a necessary evil, for now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But more important than the “dream” is that they can be hacked.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They are a website. Not a blockchain. They hold the keys to your wallet, and let you use them with a weak password and no mfa if you like. Its literally like storing your money in a bank. So know your bank. Good thing, like a bank, SOME, are federally insured up to a certain amount. But some are not, and people have lost millions and billions in the past this way.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Lastly, there is the notification of “passive income” and “interest.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With POS systems, delegators are incentivized to “stake” their coin by earning interest.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With POW systems, like bitcoin, you’d have to stand up your own machine, configure it, and let it use your energy in your house. With withs like Cardano Ada, and ETH 2.0, you can now pull your coin off the exchange, put it in a wallet, delegate to a pool, and earn interest. All while maintaining full control of your coins.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://academy.binance.com/en/articles/sybil-attacks-explained&quot;&amp;gt;https://academy.binance.com/en/articles/sybil-attacks-explained&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/f/fiatmoney.asp&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/f/fiatmoney.asp&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/hack-binance-cryptocurrency-exchange/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.wired.com/story/hack-binance-cryptocurrency-exchange/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://help.coinbase.com/en/coinbase/other-topics/legal-policies/how-is-coinbase-insured&quot;&amp;gt;https://help.coinbase.com/en/coinbase/other-topics/legal-policies/how-is-coinbase-insured&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1jiWH6Up0pPNRssCkMFw4drLRQjKVGsQtGAArITgqABE/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&amp;gt;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1jiWH6Up0pPNRssCkMFw4drLRQjKVGsQtGAArITgqABE/edit?usp=sharing&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What are Smart Contracts? (This one will blow your mind if you are a developer)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;First let us start with what most people say.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“Smart contracts are self-executing contracts with the terms of the agreement between buyer and seller being directly written into lines of code.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Which is true for sure. It helps build trust and removes the cumbersome third party “trusted agent” like a bank.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But what smart contracts really are is “ANY Code” that can be written to a blockchain and NEVER be changed, forever.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;ANY CODE. You can write your own coins and put them into the block. It happens a lot.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Games, sure, put in the chain. Check out CryptoKitties.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the future ALL business will be blockchain businesses. Every transaction, every process in the building and distribution, will be written to a magic book that can’t be messed with.. Ever..&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/s/smart-contracts.asp&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/s/smart-contracts.asp&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dappuniversity.com/articles/code-your-own-cryptocurrency-on-ethereum&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.dappuniversity.com/articles/code-your-own-cryptocurrency-on-ethereum&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cryptokitties.co/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.cryptokitties.co/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What are NFTs?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;NonFungible Tokens is metadata attached to an asset. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The metadata is things like who created it, and when. Along with the most important piece the link to the asset. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The asset is what most people think of when they talk about NFTs.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Its a digital file. Like a jpg or a mov file.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
But its not stored in the blockchain like most assume.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Instead they are stored, most often, in IPFS storage.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
IPFS is very cool, but its not blockchain, and thus not &amp;amp;quot;immutable.&amp;amp;quot; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So what’s the big deal? I can upload a gif to the internet today.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The big deal is twofold.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;First, you are not uploading anything to the “internet.” That whole thing we call the internet is flawed. Tracked, centralized, monitored, and gated.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What you are doing is creating an EARLY entry, in a book that will never change for the rest of time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let us sit and think about that for a second.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;De Beers is going to have to get new slogan. “A &amp;lt;del&amp;gt;diamond&amp;lt;/del&amp;gt; NFT is forever”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Right now, it is some awful GIF of a dogecoin. But it is not what it is. It is what it represents.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is the next chapter in Art history. What is created will last longer than the Mona Lisa. Someday you will have blockchain archaeologist that comb though chains.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Plus, taking away the cool factor, they create a place that you can now prove you did it first.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Artist could upload lyrics as an NFT, and later sell them, without the fear their art might be stolen before a contract is in place. People could attach their house deed to a chain, and ever again dispute who owns the land after a conflict.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Besides gaming, NFTs are frequently used to sell a wide range of virtual collectibles, including NBA virtual trading cards, music, digital images, video clips and even virtual real estate in &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://decentraland.org/&quot;&amp;gt;Decentraland&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, a virtual world.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That of course is the rosier outlook on NFTs.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Unfortunately, in practice there are many gaps today.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The first I already mentioned. The asset is not stored in the blockchain.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
What that means is that the IPFS provider could &amp;amp;quot;unpin&amp;amp;quot; your asset, and if its not saved anywhere else, you&amp;amp;#39;ll end up with an NFT that has metadata that points to a url that has nothing there.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The second problem, is that there are thousands of blockchains. People can take your asset, because its publicly pined, and then go create an NFT on another blockchain, and then claim theirs is in fact the original. You&amp;amp;#39;d have to check every chain that supports NFTs to ensure it was in fact the first first.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Or people have taken hard artwork, like paintings, and then minted and sold them as NFTs. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/22310188/nft-explainer-what-is-blockchain-crypto-art-faq&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.theverge.com/22310188/nft-explainer-what-is-blockchain-crypto-art-faq&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://theconversation.com/how-nonfungible-tokens-work-and-where-they-get-their-value-a-cryptocurrency-expert-explains-nfts-157489#:%7E:text=Besides%20gaming%2C%20NFTs%20are%20frequently,in%20Decentraland%2C%20a%20virtual%20world&quot;&amp;gt;https://theconversation.com/how-nonfungible-tokens-work-and-where-they-get-their-value-a-cryptocurrency-expert-explains-nfts-157489#:~:text=Besides%20gaming%2C%20NFTs%20are%20frequently,in%20Decentraland%2C%20a%20virtual%20world&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://hyperallergic.com/702309/artists-say-plagiarized-nfts-are-plaguing-their-community/&quot;&amp;gt;https://hyperallergic.com/702309/artists-say-plagiarized-nfts-are-plaguing-their-community/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Terminology?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;HODL = Hold On for Dear Life&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Hopium  =  Represents the belief that the situation will someday improve.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
FOMO = Fear of Missing Out&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
FUD = Fear, Uncertainty, and Doubt&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Bear/Bearish =  &amp;amp;quot;Bears&amp;amp;quot; believe that an asset, for example a digital currency, will decline in value.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Bull/Bullish =  If a trader believes that an asset will rise in value, he or she is a &amp;amp;quot;bull.&amp;amp;quot; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://fintechmagazine.com/financial-services-finserv/140-blockchain-and-crypto-words-ultimate-z-glossary&quot;&amp;gt;https://fintechmagazine.com/financial-services-finserv/140-blockchain-and-crypto-words-ultimate-z-glossary&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Who the hell are you?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Who me? &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;I’m not a finical advisor&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. I work for a major software company as my full-time job, and manage Microsoft Active Directory and Azure AD. 😊I do however love the idea of blockchain, and what it can bring to the world. I also am a cofounder of Mirai Blockchain Group. A small team of industry professionals that have come together to support reputable chains and provide education to those looking to gain knowledge. We mange Stake Pools, for Cardano, and possible other chains in the future, like ETH. Delegate to our pool today and we can grow together! &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;MBCG&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Pool&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Find us on the web: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://mbcg.io/&quot;&amp;gt;https://mbcg.io&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Follow on Reddit for other great content! And follow on Linkedin: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/company/mirai-blockchain-group&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.linkedin.com/company/mirai-blockchain-group&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你讓索拉納負責倒下，卻假裝和諧號什麼都沒發生，你就是一個絕望的僞君子。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不持有任何SOL或ONE，我也不打算這樣做（至少不是很快），但我
但我知道，這個組織的大多數人都害怕索拉納，害怕到他們一直在散佈謠言。
以至於他們一直試圖散佈虛假信息，好像這部分人真的有任何影響力一樣。
你真的認爲5k的支持率會有字面意義上的......]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4adpl/if_you_hold_solana_accountable_for_going_down_but/?score=326&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4adpl%2Fif_you_hold_solana_accountable_for_going_down_but%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4adpl%2Fif_you_hold_solana_accountable_for_going_down_but%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4adpl/if_you_hold_solana_accountable_for_going_down_but/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 08:35:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I don’t hold any SOL or ONE and I don’t plan to do it (at least not soon) but I know that the majority of this sub is scared of Solana, so scared that they’re trying to spread FUD all the time, as if this sub actually has any influence on the market (you really think 5k upvotes will have literally any effect on the market?)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If one posts “LUL Solana is so garbage Ethereum never went down” for when Solana went down, but then post “it’s no big deal stuff happens” for when Harmony went down, that’s just desperate hypocritical behavior. Either hold them both accountable for the same problem, or don’t hold either accountable. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It’s easy to pass on circle-jerking sub and shilling random coins on this sub, but this one is just too sad and disgusting to look over imo.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[國會將就比特幣的能源使用舉行聽證會....oh boy....，這將帶來什麼樣的妖魔化、蠱惑人心和錯誤信息？？]]></title><description><![CDATA[國會宣佈就比特幣的能源使用舉行聽證會 - CryptoShameless
[https://cryptoshameless.com/2022/01/congress-announces-hearing-on-bitcoins-energy-use/]

所以聽證會從下週四，1月20日開始。誰會成爲國會山下的一個完全
在這些聽證會上，誰會成爲國會山的傻瓜？有多少...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s43xq7/congress_to_have_hearing_on_bitcoins_energy_useoh/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs43xq7%2Fcongress_to_have_hearing_on_bitcoins_energy_useoh%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs43xq7%2Fcongress_to_have_hearing_on_bitcoins_energy_useoh%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s43xq7/congress_to_have_hearing_on_bitcoins_energy_useoh/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 05:38:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptoshameless.com/2022/01/congress-announces-hearing-on-bitcoins-energy-use/&quot;&amp;gt;Congress Announces Hearing on Bitcoin’s Energy Use - CryptoShameless&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So the hearing starts next Thursday, Jan 20th.  Who&amp;amp;#39;s going to be the complete fool up there on capitol hill during these hearings?  How much just total idiocy will Maxine Waters show?  How about Brad Sherman?  Pick your favorite idiotic politician!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉不會接受DOGE....，這是現實，假裝能夠在特斯拉商店購買一些玩具或皮帶扣（835 DOGE）與實際採用是一回事，充其量是虛僞的。真正的採用=能夠使用DOGE購買S型車或網絡卡車。]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，像往常一樣，DOGE的月亮男孩對彌賽亞-伊隆發佈他的一個
毫無意義的推文......宣佈Telsa實際上不接受
DOGE作爲任何特斯拉車輛的付款。

以下是特斯拉將接受DOGE的內容。

> 特斯拉公司（TSLA.O）將接受基於備忘錄的...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4871s/tesla_will_not_be_accepting_doge_thats_the/?score=486&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4871s%2Ftesla_will_not_be_accepting_doge_thats_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4871s%2Ftesla_will_not_be_accepting_doge_thats_the%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4871s/tesla_will_not_be_accepting_doge_thats_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 04:52:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So as usual the DOGE moon boys are ecstatic that Messiah Elon posted one of his pointless tweets... to announce that Telsa would effectively NOT be accepting DOGE as payment for any Tesla vehicles.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here&amp;amp;#39;s what Tesla &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;will&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; be accepting DOGE for:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Tesla Inc (TSLA.O) will accept meme-based cryptocurrency dogecoin as payment for its &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;merchandise&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; such as the &amp;amp;quot;Giga Texas&amp;amp;quot; belt buckle and mini models of electric vehicles, Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk said in a tweet on Friday.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In other words, you can buy a few Tesla toys and a belt buckle like this one (835 DOGE):&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://shop.tesla.com/product/giga-texas-belt-buckle?sku=1758879-00-A&quot;&amp;gt;https://shop.tesla.com/product/giga-texas-belt-buckle?sku=1758879-00-A&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;DOGE had a predictable and modest 20% gain following the non news &amp;amp;#39;news&amp;amp;#39;, which probably enabled Elon to lighten his bags yet again.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/technology/tesla-merchandise-buyable-using-dogecoin-musk-says-tweet-2022-01-14/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.reuters.com/technology/tesla-merchandise-buyable-using-dogecoin-musk-says-tweet-2022-01-14/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To see that this really is becoming a joke, the EXACT SAME news was reported on the EXACT SAME DAY last month (14th December):
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/musk-says-tesla-will-accept-dogecoin-merchandise-2021-12-14/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/musk-says-tesla-will-accept-dogecoin-merchandise-2021-12-14/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[維基百科編輯投票決定不將NFT列爲藝術，引發了加密貨幣社區的憤怒]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s44fhb/wikipedia_editors_have_voted_not_to_classify_nfts/?score=356&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs44fhb%2Fwikipedia_editors_have_voted_not_to_classify_nfts%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs44fhb%2Fwikipedia_editors_have_voted_not_to_classify_nfts%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s44fhb/wikipedia_editors_have_voted_not_to_classify_nfts/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 04:52:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特幣可能在今年年底前成爲湯加的法定貨幣]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3nwqc/bitcoin_could_become_legal_tender_in_tonga_by_the/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3nwqc%2Fbitcoin_could_become_legal_tender_in_tonga_by_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3nwqc%2Fbitcoin_could_become_legal_tender_in_tonga_by_the%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3nwqc/bitcoin_could_become_legal_tender_in_tonga_by_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 02:31:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你會選擇每年有保障的5萬美元的工資，直到死亡，還是現在就選擇100萬美元的加密貨幣。]]></title><description><![CDATA[假設你救了這個老人的命，他變成了有錢人，但他也喜歡和人玩，所以作爲禮物，他給了你一個禮物。
他也喜歡和人玩，所以作爲禮物，他給你提供了每年5萬美元的工資，直到你死爲止，但條件是你不能將其投資。
50,000美元，直到你死，條件是你不能投資任何東西，或
100萬美元在任何你想要的加密貨幣中，不能...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4268h/would_you_take_a_guaranteed_50000_a_year_salary/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4268h%2Fwould_you_take_a_guaranteed_50000_a_year_salary%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4268h%2Fwould_you_take_a_guaranteed_50000_a_year_salary%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4268h/would_you_take_a_guaranteed_50000_a_year_salary/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 02:31:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So let&amp;amp;#39;s say you saved this old man&amp;amp;#39;s life and he turned out to be rich but he also likes to play with people so as a gift he offers you a yearly salary of $50,000 until you die with the condition that you cannot invest any of it, or $1,000,000 in any crypto currency you want that cannot be withdrawn for a minimum of five years.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;$50,000 would have to be spent fully every year.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;$1,000,000 in crypto could not be moved for five years.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Of you choose the one million in crypto, which one would you choose?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我開了一家出租私人飛機的公司，接受BTC 🙌。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我靠着從軍隊退休後的一點收入，已經環遊世界5年了。
從軍隊退休後，我在南美遇到了一個了不起的女人。

我們剛剛開了一傢俬人包機公司（她已經在這個領域工作了6年）。
6年了）。而且我們很自豪地接受BTC。

我曾經看到，在...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s3xhfl/i_opened_a_company_that_rents_private_planes_and/?score=338&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs3xhfl%2Fi_opened_a_company_that_rents_private_planes_and%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs3xhfl%2Fi_opened_a_company_that_rents_private_planes_and%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s3xhfl/i_opened_a_company_that_rents_private_planes_and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 01:46:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I have been traveling the world for 5 years on a small income from my medical retirement from the military and met an amazing woman in South America. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We just opened a private charter jet company (she has been working in this space for 6 years). And we proudly accept BTC. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I once saw the power in using crypto when I paid for part of my stay at a hotel in Colombia where my payment hit their account in minutes. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The banking system is too slow. And they have too much power over our money. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I will be having meetings with other brokers and charter jet providers about accepting Bitcoin too. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto is the revolution this world needs and I love to be a part of this movement in a small way.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Loopring - 深入探討]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，夥計們，我是Spragg，我在YouTube（SpraggTalksMoney）上對各種不同的硬幣/代幣進行了深入的研究。
我想既然我已經爲我的視頻寫好了腳本，那麼我也會在這裏發佈摘要。
我想既然我已經爲我的視頻寫了腳本，我也會在這裏發佈摘要。

如果有人對未總結的完整版本感興趣，鏈接是...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3zv3b/loopring_a_deep_dive/?score=320&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3zv3b%2Floopring_a_deep_dive%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3zv3b%2Floopring_a_deep_dive%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3zv3b/loopring_a_deep_dive/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 00:32:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hey guys, Im Spragg, I do deep dives into various different coins/tokens on youtube (SpraggTalksMoney), I thought since I’ve already written the scripts for my video anyway I’d post the summary on here too.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If anyone’s interested in the full un-summarized version the link is here: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/j5cEdmAeICU&quot;&amp;gt;https://youtu.be/j5cEdmAeICU&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Preface&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the top 40 tokens ranked by market cap only 6 aren’t on Ethereum, with those being on the Binance smart chain, but this makes sense, if you were opening a shop in real life, you’d want to do it where the people are, and not in the middle of the countryside. Ethereum, while long maintaining it’s position as the largest smart contract chain does have its problems, those being gas fees and congestion.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This means that while anything built on Ethereum gets the benefits of decentralisation and security, it inherits those problems too.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;DEXs are in my opinion though are some of the most important aspects to the free trade of crypto, allowing for swapping between any on chain, or wrapped asset, but if you wanted to perform a trade on uniswap now you’d be paying well over $150 in fees.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And this is where loopring comes in, aiming to not only solve these existing problems and provide a completely new take on how DEX’s should function.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Foundation&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Like a lot of the current markets most promising protocols, Loopring, created by Daniel Wang an ex google software engineer, first appeared in the form of an ICO in the 2017 bull run raising 45 million. Unfortunately, Daniel and his team are based in Shanghai, and as we all know China loves to flip flop on their crypto regulation, coming out with new laws outlawing ICO’s forcing the Loopring Foundation to refund most of the funds earnt. However, from the ICO there was 20k Ethereum not refunded, which at the time was worth around 7.5 million, and with this they forged on with the creation of the Loopring protocol.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Unlike a lot of projects in the crypto space that start their marketing extremely early to try and hook investors sometimes before the product even has a working first version, Looping’s focus was on creating the product and then letting it sell itself. Arguably had the market not become so crowded with people almost acting like salesmen trying to shove any half-baked crypto project down people’s throats this strategy probably would’ve worked.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This isn’t to say that the company isn’t starting to move towards providing a greater feature set such as Ethereum virtual machine compatibility but given how tight lipped they’ve been on the topic shows that they don’t want this to dominate the narrative of what the platform actually currently does.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Loopring Protocol&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Loopring aims to give anyone the tools to build their own DEX but without needing to go through any of the problems in actually starting a DEX, Loopring is to decentralised exchanges what the Tendermint SDK is to Proof of stake. Its certainly not the only way to do it, but it cuts out a large portion of the groundwork required.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At the core of Loopring is a Zero Knowledge Proof rollup layer built on top of the Ethereum base chain, since not many people know what this actually is or entails, I thought Id briefly explain it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Zero Knowledge proof is not unique to crypto, it in fact pre-dates it by over 25 years, and is a cryptographic protocol that allows a party to prove that a statement is true to a recipient party, what makes it significant though is that the recipient party doesn’t need to be privy to any potentially secret information that goes into proving the statement.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Think of it like a magic trick, if a magician said he could predict the suit and number of a card we will draw from a deck of cards, and then proceeds to do it and get it right, we can assume that it wasn’t just sheer luck, and that he can in fact do what he says he can, but we as the second party have no idea how the trick was done.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So when we apply this to crypto we get the ability to prove to the base chain that something happening on a side chain or layer 2 is verifiably true, which as we all know is extremely important in a trustless environment like a blockchain.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So now we move onto the rollup part, on the base chain, in this case Ethereum, a transaction is a single monetary transfer from a to b, this means that to process 100 transfers, you need 100 transactions.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A much more efficient way of doing this would be to process 100 transfers and put them all through at once under a single transaction. The problem with doing this however is the blockchain can only verify the transaction and not data within the event log of the transaction and so in this case it would assume the 100 transactions are all invalid and reject them unless it could be proven otherwise.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, to combine this all together, a zkRollup works by performing transactions off chain, and then submitting them back to the main chain as a single transaction with the proof required to confirm that what happened off chain still conforms to the base chain’s rules, and that they’re all valid transactions so that the base chain can process them accordingly as though it had done the work itself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This technology is what Loopring uses along with Relayers to allow anyone to create a DEX and keep gas fees low.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At the core of everything is the loopring relayer. The relayer is in charge of virtually everything in the ecosystem, from generating the proofs, building blocks, matching orderbooks and more.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The loopring protocol will work with any relayer, however there is currently a single canonical relayer being used which is run by the Loopring foundation, now I do have some concerns about this which I will, as usual, cover at the end, but all you need to know is that the Loopring protocol is entirely non-custodial.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Token Supply and Distribution&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There’s currently 1.2 billion LRC in circulation, which is 100 million less than the max supply of 1.3 billion which is due to the fact that a portion of the supply has been burnt.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Any operation the loopring protocol will incur a fee, same as performing any action on the blockchain, in the case of Loopring this is just 0.3% of the transaction value, where 0.2% is returned to the liquidity providers as incentive and 0.1% goes to the loopring DAO.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The use of the LRC value held by the Loopring DAO is voted on, with the options for its use being grants to incentivize partnerships, impermanent loss protection, liquidity incentives on top of the 0.2% fee, and then finally burning LRC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Concerns&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Firstly, despite the protocol being Relayer agnostic, that is to say that anyone can build a relayer and start to perform network actions, the only current Relayer operated by the Loopring foundation. This unfortunately does mean that there’s a centralised aspect to the network as it currently stands.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now, hopefully I’ve done a good enough job of explaining why this isn’t an immediate red flag for the platform, given that the entire point is to be non-custodial and have layers on layers of protocol specifics to ensure that control is always entirely in the user’s hands, I just personally don’t like the fact that the security of an investment into LRC would depend on the Loopring foundation upkeeping that relayer.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And my second concern is to do with marketting.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As it stands currently loopring has $450m locked within the contract, which for a project sitting at 2.1 billion market cap is lower than I would’ve expected. Take Curve for example, which is sitting only 100 million dollars higher in market cap but has over 20 billion dollars locked by it’s contract on Ethereum alone.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This on its own might not be cause for concern but the DEX created by the Loopring foundation was born out of being unable to secure partners to build their own DEX’s and show off the platform. This to me shows that for the platform to survive, more of an emphasis needs to be placed on getting the protocol out into the wider DeFi audience and not just within the retail space where it currently seems to be sitting.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對市場來說是個好消息。USDC在以太坊上的供應量首次超過了競爭對手USDT的供應量]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3y8av/good_news_for_the_market_usdcs_supply_on_ethereum/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3y8av%2Fgood_news_for_the_market_usdcs_supply_on_ethereum%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3y8av%2Fgood_news_for_the_market_usdcs_supply_on_ethereum%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3y8av/good_news_for_the_market_usdcs_supply_on_ethereum/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 23:40:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>