<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[加密貨幣國外熱門討論]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 04:26:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[在下一次比特幣減半之前，需要轉發的大事件清單。你現在必須積累。]]></title><description><![CDATA[ *由美國共和黨的辛西婭-盧米斯和民主黨的克里斯汀-吉林布蘭德提出的兩黨加密法案
   共和黨的辛西婭-盧米斯和民主黨的克里斯汀-吉林布蘭德（這個人在2008年左右投票反對救助華爾街和銀行）提出的兩黨加密法案。
   街和銀行的人，大約在2008年）。該法案應該在本月出臺，但可能
   但可能要到明年第118屆國會開始時纔會得到投票。我的...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v5hrsf/list_of_big_things_to_forward_to_before_the_next/?score=374&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv5hrsf%2Flist_of_big_things_to_forward_to_before_the_next%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv5hrsf%2Flist_of_big_things_to_forward_to_before_the_next%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v5hrsf/list_of_big_things_to_forward_to_before_the_next/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 03:10:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Bi-partisan crypto bill&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; by the GOP&amp;amp;#39;s Cynthia Lummis and the Democrat&amp;amp;#39;s Kristen Gillinbrand (this is a person who voted against bailing out Wall Street &amp;amp;amp; banks circa 2008). The bill should be out this month, but probably won&amp;amp;#39;t get a vote until the 118th Congress begins next year. My belief is that after regulatory clarity, bitcoin will absorb TradFi and trust rapidly. Governments won&amp;amp;#39;t be able to control programmable money like this and it will run wild. Anything unfavorable in any bills will get programmed around and that&amp;amp;#39;ll be a wrap&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Taproot Support.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Praise the lord, because we already have 75%+ nodes supporting it, and Taproot addresses, signatures, and scripting are necessary to unleash the security and innovation we need to begin onboarding institutions, governments, and individuals en masse&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TARO&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; (taproot asset representation overlay). This means stablecoins, products, services, NFT collectibles, tokenized securities, and anything else that you can assign value. It&amp;amp;#39;s difficult to stress the absurd liquidity and power this can bring the Bitcoin Network. All of this stuff will ultimately get settled in bitcoin. Why? Because bitcoin is a payment network that only bitcoin travels on. Meaning anything built on or traveling above bitcoin&amp;amp;#39;s base layer gets settled in BTC. This is how we &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;bitcoinize the dollar&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; flipping the dynamic we&amp;amp;#39;re so accustomed to on exchanges, where bitcoin is settled in US dollars. This will fire a major shot across the bow spurning a circular economy war. TARO is also cool because the upgrade to wallets is so minimal. Of course none of this is good news for centralized exchanges&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;The Merge&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. This will set that protocol rapidly on its path towards centralization and self-immolation. Liquid staking derivative platforms will within 1 year acquire the network effects and stakes necessary to capture over 50% of the network and control it forever unless hard-forked, creating several problems itself because of L2, bridges, and sidechains obviously. If it&amp;amp;#39;s not a single platform acquiring the network, it will be two of them colluding. The decentralized autonomous organizations that run these platforms are made of TradFi and erstwhile hegemons. Expect them to utilize carry trades (low interest cash borrowing), use it to buy the crypto, stake it, and use their staking derivatives to short the crypto, creating near delta-neutral positioning. Remember, if you&amp;amp;#39;re not staking, you&amp;amp;#39;re being diluted by whatever the staking APY is. I suspect this inflation will match the USD&amp;amp;#39;s traditionally (4% or so). Just another reason why fixed monetary policy (bitcoin) and PoW are important&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;SEC regulation&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: this means securities designations for much of the space which will damage centralized exchanges as much as VC&amp;amp;#39;s and (expletive)coins themselves. This is the s-curve adoption shakeout we bitcoiners have been warning about. It will help end the above system we talked about even faster&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Full-blown LiFi&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; (Lightning Finance). If I can send you bitcoin and you get stablecoins on the other end; or you send someone stablecoins and they get milk, then you can see how most people using the Bitcoin Network won&amp;amp;#39;t know they&amp;amp;#39;re using the network. They won&amp;amp;#39;t see or understand what&amp;amp;#39;s happening in the background anymore than they do Visa when buying a concert ticket, or HTTP when clicking through a website. You don&amp;amp;#39;t have to price things at the store in sats people. It doesn&amp;amp;#39;t matter what they&amp;amp;#39;re priced in. I can see several payment processors bypassing traditional discrete payment networks (like Visa or PayPal) and leveraging the LN. I expect banks, the traditional payment networks themselves, and even governments to use it. One major chartered bank is already in talks to issue fiat (not stablecoins, but digital fiat) on the LN. It&amp;amp;#39;s pretty cool to know the LN will connect everybody in the world, and to get started all that&amp;amp;#39;s needed is downloading a free wallet&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Hyperinflation.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; It&amp;amp;#39;s unavoidable. We&amp;amp;#39;re at the end of the debt cycle. The USD is trapped. You can&amp;amp;#39;t raise interest rates enough because the debt is too high (over $30T) making the interest paid too high. Foreign demand for Treasuries peaked years ago. Supply chains are broken, many for the rest of this decade. Energy inputs can&amp;amp;#39;t be reigned in, not just because of sanctions which cause an immediate impact, but because even when those are gone, the chronic underinvestment in exploration/extraction will take years to fix with proper investment (even if we made a sweetheart deal with Venezuela). And lastly, inflation is high everywhere you look. This is what Robert Triffin predicted back in the 1960s for an inflationary world reserve currency--an eventual doom vortex when the currency got trapped between low rates, inflation, debt, and falling foreign demand. Several countries have currencies which are more volatile than BTC is (Turkey, Iran, Argentina, Cuba, much of Africa, etcetera). Is Japan next? What I know is it&amp;amp;#39;s climbing the ladder, and when BTC is more stable than major currency pairs are, with longterm bias to the upside, we&amp;amp;#39;ll see a credit market rapidly develop around bitcoin collateral globally. Point is, the capital flight release valve in a hyper event is pretty obvious: Bitcoin. The USD isn&amp;amp;#39;t going away just yet, but stopping inflation doesn&amp;amp;#39;t mean prices go down, it simply means prices stop going up. Thankfully BTC will be there to do whatever you need it to do: issue new assets, collateralize, lend, borrow, save, send, or spend. The new global reserve asset&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Seriously though, this shit is going to disappear into the internet stack. And the sooner we&amp;amp;#39;re the internet of money, the sooner the price becomes apparent:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;∞/21M&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Conclusion: HODL. BUY. REPEAT.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[新西蘭最大的報紙刊登 "爲什麼比特幣是人類的升級版"]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v5itrv/why_bitcoin_is_an_upgrade_for_humanity_in_new/?score=382&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv5itrv%2Fwhy_bitcoin_is_an_upgrade_for_humanity_in_new%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv5itrv%2Fwhy_bitcoin_is_an_upgrade_for_humanity_in_new%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v5itrv/why_bitcoin_is_an_upgrade_for_humanity_in_new/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 03:10:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我們剛剛打破了連續9周的紅燭記錄]]></title><description><![CDATA[祝賀那些在這個非常痛苦的時刻仍在堅持的人！我們得到了一個很好的結果。Well we got
沒有太多的選擇，反正¯\_(ツ)_/¯

在東南亞的大部分地區，今天已經是星期一了，每週的蠟燭已經
已經是綠色的了，我懷疑在其他時區的本週剩餘時間裏，它還會拋出。
時區的剩餘時間，我懷疑它是否會下跌（我不是想...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v5lrll/we_just_broke_the_9_consecutive_week_of_red/?score=736&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv5lrll%2Fwe_just_broke_the_9_consecutive_week_of_red%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv5lrll%2Fwe_just_broke_the_9_consecutive_week_of_red%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v5lrll/we_just_broke_the_9_consecutive_week_of_red/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 01:29:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Congrats to those who is still sticking in this very bitter time! Well we got not much choice anyway ¯\_(ツ)_/¯&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s already Monday here in most part of South East Asia, weekly candle is already green I doubt it will dump with the remaining time of the week in other timezones (I&amp;amp;#39;m not trying to jinx it!)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As you guys know the worse consecutive red weekly candles happened from August to September of 2014. I&amp;amp;#39;ve skimmed through the weekly chart and there are a lot of 4 consecutive red candles btw.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/i03nxrhr2v391.png?width=853&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=6453af956a3920345f24a6f836a94215f8ceec1c&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/i03nxrhr2v391.png?width=853&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=6453af956a3920345f24a6f836a94215f8ceec1c&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We&amp;amp;#39;ve been through another shitty situation it seems.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But we&amp;amp;#39;re not done yet! We&amp;amp;#39;re still in a bear market, yes we&amp;amp;#39;re in a bear market stop the denial.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;If you really wanna make money, be patient and stick around!&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[~66%的比特幣已經一年多沒有動過了（歷史最高點）。這是看漲的，它表明持有者從未有更多的信念。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v5e0lw/66_of_bitcoin_hasnt_moved_in_over_a_year_alltime/?score=350&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv5e0lw%2F66_of_bitcoin_hasnt_moved_in_over_a_year_alltime%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv5e0lw%2F66_of_bitcoin_hasnt_moved_in_over_a_year_alltime%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v5e0lw/66_of_bitcoin_hasnt_moved_in_over_a_year_alltime/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 23:32:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Do Kwon &amp; Bernie Madoff讓 "投資者 "損失了600億美元。]]></title><description><![CDATA[2009年，[TLDR]麥道夫在他的龐氏騙局中讓投資者損失了600億美金。
龐氏騙局在經濟大衰退期間慢慢解體，當投資者開始
想提取資金，他不能夠跟上提取請求，因爲
他現在缺乏資金。他最終告訴了他的兒子們。他們...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v53ulp/both_do_kwon_bernie_madoff_lost_investors_60/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv53ulp%2Fboth_do_kwon_bernie_madoff_lost_investors_60%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv53ulp%2Fboth_do_kwon_bernie_madoff_lost_investors_60%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v53ulp/both_do_kwon_bernie_madoff_lost_investors_60/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 22:33:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In 2009 ,[TLDR]  Bernie Madoff lost investors 60billion usd in his ponzi scheme. The ponzi slowly unravelled during the Great Recession when investors started to want to withdraw funds, he wasnt able to keep up with the withdraw requests as he was now lacking funds. He eventually told his sons. They then reported it to the feds. He was then sentenced to 150 years in prison. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Whereas, in 2022, Do Kwon lost investors around 60billion (Luna and UST combined market value). And instead of answering questions/investigations or serving time. He created Luna 2.0 &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It baffles me how he has the guts/audacity to launch Lunacy two point zero. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For old luna bag holders / new comers thinking on “investing” on lunacy 2.0, I will leave you with a quote to think about.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“Fool me once , shame on you. 
                          Fool me twice, shame on me”  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now I wonder if Do will ever see jail time? As south korean authorities are conducting investigations with regards to the collapse of both ust and luna. Plus allegations that Terraform Labs is being used to move/launder money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://archives.fbi.gov/archives/newyork/press-releases/2009/nyfo062909.htm&quot;&amp;gt;Madoff 150 yr sentence fbi archives link&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptoslate.com/terraform-labs-caught-moving-4-8m-through-shell-company/?amp=1&quot;&amp;gt;Terraform Labs moving money through shell company article&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;IMO, Luna 2.0 is a spit on the face to the unlucky ones who got duped by the “stablecoin” and a somewhat “conservative” 20% apy combo. The 20% is what I call “Good , but not that good to NOT be true” the perfect bait&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[新的突破性的Astronomia Solar Bitcoin裝在44毫米的黑色DLC鈦合金錶殼裏，是對加密貨幣世界的象徵性和鐘錶方面的致敬。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v4yxn6/housed_in_a_44_mm_black_dlc_titanium_case_the_new/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv4yxn6%2Fhoused_in_a_44_mm_black_dlc_titanium_case_the_new%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv4yxn6%2Fhoused_in_a_44_mm_black_dlc_titanium_case_the_new%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v4yxn6/housed_in_a_44_mm_black_dlc_titanium_case_the_new/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 18:34:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[寄錢]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v57sbp/sending_money/?score=335&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv57sbp%2Fsending_money%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv57sbp%2Fsending_money%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v57sbp/sending_money/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 16:43:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[所有的炒作投資者似乎都消失了，現在只有我們這些真正的持有人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在過去的幾個月裏，在加密貨幣的過山車上出現了幾次非常艱難的震盪。
過山車。但這一切都如市場所願，幾乎所有的炒作
投資者似乎都走了。只有對技術或價格行爲有信心的真正投資者
價格行爲或其他什麼的真正的投資者纔會留下來。

如此急劇的下跌...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4yqup/all_the_hype_investors_seem_to_be_gone_its_now/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4yqup%2Fall_the_hype_investors_seem_to_be_gone_its_now%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4yqup%2Fall_the_hype_investors_seem_to_be_gone_its_now%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4yqup/all_the_hype_investors_seem_to_be_gone_its_now/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 13:40:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The past months have been showing several very hard shake offs on the Crypto rollercoaster. But it&amp;amp;#39;s all playing out like the market wanted, nearly all hype investors seem to be gone. Only real investors with conviction in the tech or price action or whatever are remaining.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Such drastic declines in New investors who just hold for a few months are very good because the market is now getting settled up for the next leg upwards and is making space for those hype investors to once again return and buy at the ATH.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Currently only we are remaining here and if you made it this far you can definitely call yourself a long-term investor and also a Crypto Citizen. It definitely was not easy to come this far and you should not give up after coming this far too.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美國立法者提出法案，要求國會議員披露加密貨幣持有情況。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v58se6/us_lawmakers_introduce_bill_to_require_members_of/?score=421&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv58se6%2Fus_lawmakers_introduce_bill_to_require_members_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv58se6%2Fus_lawmakers_introduce_bill_to_require_members_of%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v58se6/us_lawmakers_introduce_bill_to_require_members_of/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 13:40:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我花了一週時間根據人工智能的信號進行交易，所以你不必如此。下面是結果。]]></title><description><![CDATA[人工智能正在接管許多工作，從收銀員開始一直到醫生。I
我想通過運行一個小的（也許是一個昂貴的）實驗，看看人工智能是否能取代交易員。
昂貴的）實驗，看看人工智能能否取代交易員。

規則很簡單。在接下來的一週裏，我將根據一個人工智能做多/做空比特幣
twitter機器人[https://twitter.com/predictBTC]的...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4ux6l/i_spent_a_week_trading_based_on_an_ais_signals_so/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4ux6l%2Fi_spent_a_week_trading_based_on_an_ais_signals_so%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4ux6l%2Fi_spent_a_week_trading_based_on_an_ais_signals_so%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4ux6l/i_spent_a_week_trading_based_on_an_ais_signals_so/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 12:57:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;AI is taking over many jobs, starting from cashiers all the way to doctors. I wanted to see if AI could replace traders by running a small (and maybe a costly) experiment.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Rules are simple. For the next week, I’ll long/short Bitcoin based on an &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/predictBTC&quot;&amp;gt;AI twitter bot&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#39;s forecasts. Every position will be opened at 00:00 UTC and closed at 23:59 UTC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Our start balance is $1000. And we won’t use leverage in our trades.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Day 1/7: Great start?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/u0cbdnzg1n391.png?width=537&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=dd02d5ade8d842836c3e8849d98f1dc0a4b2fbf9&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/u0cbdnzg1n391.png?width=537&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=dd02d5ade8d842836c3e8849d98f1dc0a4b2fbf9&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/klmq40rr1n391.png?width=664&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e2a6715f19fd7f0301bfffe75decbff1d0643ae2&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/klmq40rr1n391.png?width=664&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e2a6715f19fd7f0301bfffe75decbff1d0643ae2&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The bot&amp;amp;#39;s forecast was barely bearish. We opened a short position at $29.5K (when the forecast was tweeted) and closed it at $29K (at the end of the day). We ended up with a profit of $17. This brings our final balance to $1017. Probably luck. We will see by the end of this experiment.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Day 2/7: Sometime it happens&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/30lwoo8n2n391.png?width=542&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=93946c2f5e9a027da1144dcb3c3be2a63ac6874a&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/30lwoo8n2n391.png?width=542&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=93946c2f5e9a027da1144dcb3c3be2a63ac6874a&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This time I couldn&amp;amp;#39;t really tell if the bot was bullish or bearish, so I didn&amp;amp;#39;t open any positions that day.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Day 3/7: Two wins in a row?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/5xo4bk0a3n391.png?width=536&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=4e187438ffd3548059e3ae1151b714822a98ecec&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/5xo4bk0a3n391.png?width=536&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=4e187438ffd3548059e3ae1151b714822a98ecec&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/xe5huq6b3n391.png?width=644&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=03ea13b5a5f7685d583ea8fa07a312913300c149&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/xe5huq6b3n391.png?width=644&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=03ea13b5a5f7685d583ea8fa07a312913300c149&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here, the forecast was clearly bullish. Time to long. We opened a long position at $28.6K (when the forecast was tweeted) and closed it at $29K (at the end of the day). We ended up with a profit of $14. This brings our final balance to $1031. Two wins in a row baby!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Day 4/7: THREE wins in a row?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/galtlt9w3n391.png?width=536&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=1bda49e023e869f0099f102ede3288241d6c08b2&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/galtlt9w3n391.png?width=536&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=1bda49e023e869f0099f102ede3288241d6c08b2&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/k20ww8gx3n391.png?width=660&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e070877ad3a2d91043e0923f900674eef55f6f70&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/k20ww8gx3n391.png?width=660&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e070877ad3a2d91043e0923f900674eef55f6f70&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is our luckiest day yet (I really hope this continues). We longed at $29K and closed the position at $30.3K, ending up with a profit of $46. This brings our final balance to $1077.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Day 5/7: I knew it&amp;amp;#39;d happen&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/vo927hr55n391.png?width=533&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=86edac09d9330d4d0e687bba7da8b506371cb5ec&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/vo927hr55n391.png?width=533&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=86edac09d9330d4d0e687bba7da8b506371cb5ec&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/c1syxmx65n391.png?width=682&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=06ae1a81129a4401adc2a9a852998ebb296dfb56&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/c1syxmx65n391.png?width=682&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=06ae1a81129a4401adc2a9a852998ebb296dfb56&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here, the bot seemed neutral and bearish at the same time, so short it is. We opened a short position at $29.5K and closed it at $31.8K (at the end of the day). We ended up with a loss of $84. We&amp;amp;#39;ve successfully wiped all of our previous profits, bringing our final balance to $993. Yay!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Day 6:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/z7jquj3a6n391.png?width=537&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=7fd0c60c3bd889b2e03c21a9c7a5aa5c271e7f7c&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/z7jquj3a6n391.png?width=537&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=7fd0c60c3bd889b2e03c21a9c7a5aa5c271e7f7c&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here, the bot seemed neutral, and its confidence was slightly high, so we didn&amp;amp;#39;t end up opening any positions that day.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Day 7/7: Comeback or Horrible Fail?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/oc5tysfj7n391.png?width=543&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=0627a3744df61afd0633595193f01418106edaca&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/oc5tysfj7n391.png?width=543&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=0627a3744df61afd0633595193f01418106edaca&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/nnn66avk7n391.png?width=667&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e06653510c139ff7d5f5a65f5a51c8e21d37ae32&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/nnn66avk7n391.png?width=667&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e06653510c139ff7d5f5a65f5a51c8e21d37ae32&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Ah yes. Nothing goes up forever. The bot here was barely bullish, so I ended up longing. Big mistake. We longed at $31.8K (when the forecast was tweeted) and closed it at $29.7K (at the end of the day). We ended up with a loss of $66.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Summary&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;We won three trades and lost two. Our win rate seems to be 60%.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;We won a total of $77 and lost $150. Finishing up with a total loss of $73.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Of course, five trades aren’t enough to evaluate any trading strategy. The bot seemed to do well initially, but then the market started crashing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This small experiment shows that the crypto market is genuinely unpredictable. Not even by a shitty AI Twitter bot that made me lose $73, which probably flips a coin to generate random predictions.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[雜草&amp; 比特幣：爸爸和兒子被抓到從星巴克經營1300萬美元的帝國]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v50dad/weed_bitcoin_dad_and_son_caught_running_13m/?score=316&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv50dad%2Fweed_bitcoin_dad_and_son_caught_running_13m%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv50dad%2Fweed_bitcoin_dad_and_son_caught_running_13m%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v50dad/weed_bitcoin_dad_and_son_caught_running_13m/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 12:57:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我在加密貨幣領域的時間越長，就越傾向於以太坊極簡主義。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在4天后，Ropsten測試合併將發生，將Ropsten測試網
從POW變成Proof of stake。6月30日，難度炸彈將被引爆。
逐漸增加礦工開採區塊的難度。相關數據可以在
在這裏找到。

Http://wenmerge.com

而在一個尚未確定的...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v54kg9/the_longer_im_in_crypto_the_more_i_lean_toward/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv54kg9%2Fthe_longer_im_in_crypto_the_more_i_lean_toward%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv54kg9%2Fthe_longer_im_in_crypto_the_more_i_lean_toward%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v54kg9/the_longer_im_in_crypto_the_more_i_lean_toward/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 10:43:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In 4 days time the Ropsten test merge will happen, turning the Ropsten testnet from POW to Proof of stake.  On the 30th june, the difficulty bomb will go off, gradually increasing the difficulty for miners to mine blocks.  The data can be found here: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;Http://wenmerge.com&quot;&amp;gt;Http://wenmerge.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And in an as yet unspecified date in august, the real main net merge will happen.  So why am I so bullish about the merge?  Its largely Eth moving instantly from 3.3% inflation to -0.7% inflation. But it&amp;amp;#39;s also these. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;99% reduction in energy cost per Tx. &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;90% issuance reduction.  12500 eth a day to 1250. &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Miner sell pressure drops from 14,000 eth a day to 0. &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;More eth locked in the staking contract for 6 months after the merge . &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Deflationary asset.  More eth burned than produced if gwei &amp;amp;gt;20gwei.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Number 3 is I think the most important. While it wont drop to exactly 0 on the first night, removing $30 million of sell pressure per day will have a massive effect.  The market would need to refind this pressure just to stop the price going up. (Its guaranteed profit). It wont find this sell pressure.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There won&amp;amp;#39;t be a &amp;amp;#39;massive selloff&amp;amp;#39; on merge night.  All eth remains locked into the contract until the next update.  After that, there is a queued release. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I believe that both Bitcoin and Ethereum are stores of value,  but Ethereum is currently also the worlds largest and most secure crypto network.  It is the foundation of web3.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a final note, it took 19 months to get 12.6 million into the deposit contract.   In the last 2 months alone,  2.6 million of that amount was deposited.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As a final final note, I&amp;amp;#39;d like to thank Do Kwon for causing the luna crash and allowing us to buy Eth this cheap, this close to the merge.  And also removing luna from the market and allowing Ethereum more room to grow in MC.  You&amp;amp;#39;re a bastard, make no mistake; but you&amp;amp;#39;re a magnificent one.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我記得幾年前看到這個，我認爲這是一個騙局，它至今仍困擾着我。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v54db9/i_remember_seeing_this_years_ago_and_i_thought_it/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv54db9%2Fi_remember_seeing_this_years_ago_and_i_thought_it%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv54db9%2Fi_remember_seeing_this_years_ago_and_i_thought_it%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v54db9/i_remember_seeing_this_years_ago_and_i_thought_it/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 08:36:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bored Ape Yacht Club和Otherside Metaverse Discord服務器再一次被黑。據報道，價值 "數百萬 "的NFTs被盜。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這發生在他們的社區經理的迪斯科賬戶被入侵，並且
黑客通過他的賬戶發佈了一個釣魚鏈接，盜取了近175個ETH。



社區經理...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4s6kh/once_again_bored_ape_yacht_club_and_otherside/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4s6kh%2Fonce_again_bored_ape_yacht_club_and_otherside%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4s6kh%2Fonce_again_bored_ape_yacht_club_and_otherside%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4s6kh/once_again_bored_ape_yacht_club_and_otherside/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 03:43:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This happened when their community manager&amp;amp;#39;s discord account got compromised and hackers posted a phishing link through his account and stole almost 175 ETH.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/cqejnoiqpm391.jpg?width=1053&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=53777db15851bf31a80403ed3661d896a6e04810&quot;&amp;gt;Community Manager account&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Apparently this is the second time their discord got compromised. People got &amp;amp;quot;Millions&amp;amp;quot; worth of NFTs but still hunt for the these giveaways.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/4z7gn8nxpm391.png?width=819&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=2073781a1cfe04423c69231ae96f069e98698e77&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/4z7gn8nxpm391.png?width=819&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=2073781a1cfe04423c69231ae96f069e98698e77&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Last time it got hacked in April 2022.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source of first attack: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2022/04/01/bayc-says-discord-briefly-compromised-tells-users-to-avoid-discord-for-minting-ape-nfts/#:%7E:text=The%20official%20channel%20of%20the,in%20a%20tweet%20on%20Friday&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.coindesk.com/tech/2022/04/01/bayc-says-discord-briefly-compromised-tells-users-to-avoid-discord-for-minting-ape-nfts/#:~:text=The%20official%20channel%20of%20the,in%20a%20tweet%20on%20Friday&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Second: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/NFTherder/status/1533037408144572417&quot;&amp;gt;https://twitter.com/NFTherder/status/1533037408144572417&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dogecoin創始人抨擊Binance智能鏈上的每個代幣都是 "垃圾"]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4uym8/dogecoin_founder_slams_every_token_on_the_binance/?score=368&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4uym8%2Fdogecoin_founder_slams_every_token_on_the_binance%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4uym8%2Fdogecoin_founder_slams_every_token_on_the_binance%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4uym8/dogecoin_founder_slams_every_token_on_the_binance/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 03:09:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我在加密貨幣領域的時間越長，我就越傾向於比特幣最大化主義]]></title><description><![CDATA[只做了兩年的加密貨幣。起初，我投資於各種硬幣，隨着我花更多時間研究和學習，慢慢地開始縮小範圍。
慢慢地，隨着我花更多時間研究和學習，開始縮小範圍。
但是，我一直在回想，而且我的信念也在不斷增強。
的，是BTC。它不斷地經受着風暴的洗禮，並在不斷地發展。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4vxwo/the_longer_im_in_crypto_the_more_i_lean_toward/?score=370&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4vxwo%2Fthe_longer_im_in_crypto_the_more_i_lean_toward%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4vxwo%2Fthe_longer_im_in_crypto_the_more_i_lean_toward%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4vxwo/the_longer_im_in_crypto_the_more_i_lean_toward/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 03:09:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Only been in crypto for two years. At first I invested in all sorts of coins and slowly, as I spent more time researching and learning, began to narrow it down. But the one I keep coming back to, and the one in which my conviction continues to strengthen, is BTC. It keeps weathering storms and coming back, and it&amp;amp;#39;s the most truly decentralized coin I know. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;All the recent stuff with LUNA has also swayed me toward BTC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I don&amp;amp;#39;t think I will ever be a pure 100% BTC maxi. I invest in BTC, ETH, and the Cosmos ecosystem, but the percentage of BTC in my portfolio continues to grow (about 75% now), and it&amp;amp;#39;s the one I feel most secure investing in.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know I may lose out on some coins that go to the moon far more quickly, but I&amp;amp;#39;ll also miss out on the many more coins that promise the moon yet hardly make it off the launching pad.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這一年是2050年。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v4wyuv/the_year_is_2050/?score=474&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv4wyuv%2Fthe_year_is_2050%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv4wyuv%2Fthe_year_is_2050%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v4wyuv/the_year_is_2050/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 01:57:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以太坊從第2層網絡賺到了比以往更多的錢]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4m6uv/ethereum_is_making_more_money_than_ever_from/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4m6uv%2Fethereum_is_making_more_money_than_ever_from%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4m6uv%2Fethereum_is_making_more_money_than_ever_from%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4m6uv/ethereum_is_making_more_money_than_ever_from/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 23:39:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對於我的鐵桿堆積者和HODLers來說]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v4svkb/for_my_hardcore_sat_stackers_and_hodlers/?score=330&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv4svkb%2Ffor_my_hardcore_sat_stackers_and_hodlers%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv4svkb%2Ffor_my_hardcore_sat_stackers_and_hodlers%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v4svkb/for_my_hardcore_sat_stackers_and_hodlers/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 23:39:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nocoiner世界是可悲的。比特幣是一種能量的浪費。我們將堅持使用一個由暴力支持的腐敗系統，在這個系統中，整個經濟都依賴於一個有政治學位的前律師的意見。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v4up7o/nocoiner_world_is_sad_bitcoin_is_a_waste_of/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv4up7o%2Fnocoiner_world_is_sad_bitcoin_is_a_waste_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv4up7o%2Fnocoiner_world_is_sad_bitcoin_is_a_waste_of%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v4up7o/nocoiner_world_is_sad_bitcoin_is_a_waste_of/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 22:31:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我賣掉了所有能賣的東西，爲我女兒的未來買了比特幣。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v4qr1x/i_sold_everything_i_could_and_bought_bitcoin_for/?score=431&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv4qr1x%2Fi_sold_everything_i_could_and_bought_bitcoin_for%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv4qr1x%2Fi_sold_everything_i_could_and_bought_bitcoin_for%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v4qr1x/i_sold_everything_i_could_and_bought_bitcoin_for/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 18:43:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在2017年的崩潰之後，BTC和ETH花了大約1年的時間來尋找底部。]]></title><description><![CDATA[2017年崩盤後，BTC和ETH大概花了1年時間才找到底部。那些所謂的專家們
所謂的專家告訴你，這可能是底部，然後把它與
粒鹽。

> 如果我們與2017年BTC和ETH的跌幅一致，分別爲85%和95%。
> 那麼我們就會看到1萬美元的BTC水平...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4nw6o/after_2017_crashit_took_roughly_1_year_to_find/?score=441&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4nw6o%2Fafter_2017_crashit_took_roughly_1_year_to_find%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4nw6o%2Fafter_2017_crashit_took_roughly_1_year_to_find%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4nw6o/after_2017_crashit_took_roughly_1_year_to_find/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 16:40:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After 2017 crash,it roughly took 1 year to find the bottom for BTC and ETH. The so called experts telling you this could be the bottom then take that with the grain of salt. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If we match the 2017 drawdowns for BTC and ETH, it&amp;amp;#39;s 85% and 95% respectively, then we are looking at levels of $10k BTC and $250 for ETH. 
It might seem highly unlikely, but the market is surely reflecting some fear of this happening.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto exchanges halting new hirings,even cutting the current staff, miners selling their stacks to cover up for the expenses could be the some of the signs you are looking for. 
Even the rest of the financial markets are not doing good, fearing a recession might be coming. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Overall, the picture of market is still negative.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[傑克-保羅促進了另一個NFT地毯的發展；創始人以630萬美元脫身]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4hzjm/jake_paul_promotes_yet_another_nft_rug_pull/?score=422&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4hzjm%2Fjake_paul_promotes_yet_another_nft_rug_pull%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4hzjm%2Fjake_paul_promotes_yet_another_nft_rug_pull%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4hzjm/jake_paul_promotes_yet_another_nft_rug_pull/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 16:40:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[只是另一個小紅年。如果你在這裏長期工作，應該不會有什麼問題。瓦格米]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v472sb/just_another_small_red_year_shouldnt_matter_if/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv472sb%2Fjust_another_small_red_year_shouldnt_matter_if%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv472sb%2Fjust_another_small_red_year_shouldnt_matter_if%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v472sb/just_another_small_red_year_shouldnt_matter_if/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 16:40:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[人們總是會找到藉口來保持現狀 🎯]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v4l7ld/people_will_always_find_excuses_to_keep_the/?score=662&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv4l7ld%2Fpeople_will_always_find_excuses_to_keep_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv4l7ld%2Fpeople_will_always_find_excuses_to_keep_the%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v4l7ld/people_will_always_find_excuses_to_keep_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 12:48:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特幣 人們是愚蠢的 😂]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v44ofa/bitcoin_people_are_stupid/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv44ofa%2Fbitcoin_people_are_stupid%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv44ofa%2Fbitcoin_people_are_stupid%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v44ofa/bitcoin_people_are_stupid/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 09:31:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這個地方已經直接死亡，這對你我都有好處。]]></title><description><![CDATA[你想知道什麼讓我興奮嗎？機會，你可以說它是病態的，但
每個人都會因爲不同的事情而興奮。對我來說，有趣的是，一些大公司如何支撐起市場，而它卻沒有。
撐起了市場，這一點沒有比現在更明顯。

只要看看這個子，一個月前，即使是在那個大規模的衰退期，我們也...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4e3d1/this_place_has_straight_up_died_which_is_good_for/?score=700&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4e3d1%2Fthis_place_has_straight_up_died_which_is_good_for%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv4e3d1%2Fthis_place_has_straight_up_died_which_is_good_for%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v4e3d1/this_place_has_straight_up_died_which_is_good_for/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 04:35:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You wanna know what makes me excited? Opportunity, you can call it morbid but everyone is excited by different things. It&amp;amp;#39;s interesting to me how a few big players prop up the market and it&amp;amp;#39;s no more apparent than now. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just look at this sub, a month ago even during that massive downturn we still had some discussions. The new posts page is a straight up cemetery, beyond a couple news articles that gets posted there&amp;amp;#39;s nothing. Outside this sub most people hate crypto, actively talking it down completely if you even mention it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is the start of winter, the crypto winter that is. This is the time that will test those that truly believe and are staying and averaging in until the next bull market. If you can manage to hold on, and it won&amp;amp;#39;t be easy you may just have what it takes to quit a regular job and live financially free. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;None of that &amp;amp;#39; financial freedom &amp;amp;#39; stuff is of course guaranteed, but the people that have made it in this market are the ones that planned and stayed. If you can ignore your emotions, you can secure financial promotions!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[新法案將迫使國會披露加密貨幣持有情況 - Crypto Briefing]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v485px/new_bill_would_force_congress_to_disclose_crypto/?score=307&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv485px%2Fnew_bill_would_force_congress_to_disclose_crypto%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv485px%2Fnew_bill_would_force_congress_to_disclose_crypto%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v485px/new_bill_would_force_congress_to_disclose_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 03:32:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你的計劃是HODL，請確保你知道這意味着什麼。]]></title><description><![CDATA[TL;DR：堅持你的計劃並充分意識到它的意義是非常重要的。
意義。

最重要的部分是要始終有一個計劃。很多人都遵循
HODL策略和 "我永遠不會賣掉它，它會再漲回來 "的心態。這是有道理的。
它是有道理的，是一個很好的策略，但請注意什麼是......]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3ypxp/if_your_plan_is_to_hodl_please_make_sure_you_are/?score=324&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3ypxp%2Fif_your_plan_is_to_hodl_please_make_sure_you_are%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3ypxp%2Fif_your_plan_is_to_hodl_please_make_sure_you_are%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3ypxp/if_your_plan_is_to_hodl_please_make_sure_you_are/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 02:52:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TL;DR: it’s very important to stick to your plan and be fully aware what it means.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The most important part is to always have a plan. A lot of people follow the HODL strat and “I’m never gonna sell it’ll go back up again” mentality. It makes sense, it’s a good strategy but please be aware of what can happen.
Let me give you an example.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;The 2017 Incident&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Imagine you bought around the ATH in 2017. 10-16.000$ back then. After 2017 a bear market hit. And it was a brutal one for the mentality of a lot of investors. -80% investment &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;on BITCOIN&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; not just alts. And this wasn’t happening in a couple months it happened over years.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Fast foreword it’s 2019 and BTC is currently at 9k again. You hope for a new ATH to cut your losses or at least break even and what happens? It goes back down again. It’s 2020 and BTC is still at 9000$. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;It’s been nearly 3 years now&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; since you bought BTC and your portfolio was always in a loss. And now Covid happens. BTC falls towards 5000$. All that with the years of mentality “Will it ever hit 10-16k again?”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you managed to even hold through that time after 4 years you finally get rewarded. The next big bullrun hits and it was the biggest that ever happen. In a matter of weeks BTC doubles. After that it doubles every couple weeks. New all time highs every week reaching up to 60k+&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you managed to HODL through those years congratulations you just 6-8x your initial investment. I’ve been through this time and I can promise you the majority of people with that HODL mentality gave up and sold eventually. It’s rough and not as easy as a lot of people think.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[USDD和TRX擁有與殺死UST和Terra完全相同的鑄幣和燃燒機制。下面是做空的方法。]]></title><description><![CDATA[重要編輯：剛纔有人提到似乎沒有鑄幣的合同
TRX。我仔細檢查了白皮書，看起來完整的鑄幣和燒燬機制不會出現。
燃燒機制要到11月纔會實施。在USDT可以被燒燬以換取
新鑄造的TRX之前，失敗的鑄幣和燒燬的可能性爲零。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3uxj0/usdd_and_trx_has_the_exact_same_mint_and_burn/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3uxj0%2Fusdd_and_trx_has_the_exact_same_mint_and_burn%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3uxj0%2Fusdd_and_trx_has_the_exact_same_mint_and_burn%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3uxj0/usdd_and_trx_has_the_exact_same_mint_and_burn/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 02:52:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Important Edit:&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Someone just mentioned there seems to be no contract for minting TRX right now. I double checked the white paper and looks like the full mint and burn mechanism wont be implemented until November. Until USDD can be burned for newly minted TRX there is 0 chance of a failed mint and burn scenario similar to Terra / UST&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just pulled up the white paper for USDD. Seems that the &amp;amp;quot;stability&amp;amp;quot; mechanism for USDD is the exact same as UST.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here&amp;amp;#39;s the white paper so you can read for yourself &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://usdd.io/USDD-en.pdf&quot;&amp;gt;https://usdd.io/USDD-en.pdf&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Page 3 and 4 show very plainly what the mint and burn mechanism is. You don&amp;amp;#39;t have to know much about any of this to understand it. Simply 1 USDD can be burned for $1 equivalent of TRX minted. $1 worth of TRX can be burned for 1 USDD minted.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Looks like right now USDD borrow rates on &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://justlend.org&quot;&amp;gt;justlend.org&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; are 5%&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So if you want to short USDD with leverage here&amp;amp;#39;s how to do it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Deposit collateral on &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://justlend.org&quot;&amp;gt;justlend.org&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; - Eth, BTC, USDC take your pick&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Borrow USDD&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Immediately sell USDD for more collateral&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Deposit collateral&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Repeat steps 2 and 3 depending on how much leverage you want exposure too&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The loan to value ratio on justlend will determine how many times you can repeat this process. Each time you repeat steps 2 and 3 you increase your leverage. So at 10x leverage every 1% move in either direction is a 10% gain or loss. You&amp;amp;#39;ll want to figure out what the liquidation threshold is so you don&amp;amp;#39;t lose your collateral.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some of the more obvious risks in this trade are the APY you pay on borrowed USDD, not managing your collateral and getting liquidated, and also maybe a not so obvious one is since justlend runs on tron, its worthwihile to think about if USDD and TRX fail will Tron shutdown? In the event of a network shutdown you wont be able to repay your USDD and release your collateral.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s also a much easier way to short Tron and USDD in the event of a failure of the mint and burn mechanism. Just set an alert (or program a script if your savvy enough) and short TRX on a centralized exchange like Kucoin if USDD depegs to $0.97 then short TRX with leverage in your margin account. I&amp;amp;#39;m sure you can find TRX perpetuals on other exchanges too if you want to increase your leverage. Then if USDD repegs you close the trade. Rinse and repeat every time USDD depegs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[薩爾瓦多已經在經歷IMF所擔心的經濟毀滅]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v43xv8/el_salvador_is_already_experiencing_the_economic/?score=416&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv43xv8%2Fel_salvador_is_already_experiencing_the_economic%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv43xv8%2Fel_salvador_is_already_experiencing_the_economic%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v43xv8/el_salvador_is_already_experiencing_the_economic/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:02:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你應該定期閱讀反加密貨幣的文章和論點，即使你完全不同意他們的觀點。]]></title><description><![CDATA[不幸的是，在一個回聲室中，很容易陷入騙局或被騙。
只是非常糟糕的投資。即使你認爲加密貨幣是未來，即使你
即使你認爲那些反對它的人是什麼都不懂的新人類，而且永遠不會被人喜歡。
永遠不會被人喜愛，它可能仍然是一個好主意，搜索...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v41kz3/you_should_regularly_read_anticrypto_pieces_and/?score=620&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv41kz3%2Fyou_should_regularly_read_anticrypto_pieces_and%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv41kz3%2Fyou_should_regularly_read_anticrypto_pieces_and%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v41kz3/you_should_regularly_read_anticrypto_pieces_and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:02:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Unfortunately being in an echo chamber makes it very easy to fall into scams or just really bad investments. Even if you think crypto is the future, even if you think those against it are neanderthals who don&amp;amp;#39;t understand anything and will never be loved, it&amp;amp;#39;s probably still a good idea to search out the best arguments against what you&amp;amp;#39;re investing in.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The biggest falls are the ones we don&amp;amp;#39;t see coming. Whether it&amp;amp;#39;s specific coins or crypto as a whole, you can&amp;amp;#39;t see the storm coming if you&amp;amp;#39;re adamant on looking the other way.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Truth is only reached by looking at things from opposing points of view. If you&amp;amp;#39;re only looking with one eye, that&amp;amp;#39;s not a three-dimensional view, it&amp;amp;#39;s a biased one.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我在Loopring L2上鑄造了一個完全可玩的遊戲]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3z111/i_minted_a_fully_playable_game_on_loopring_l2/?score=345&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3z111%2Fi_minted_a_fully_playable_game_on_loopring_l2%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3z111%2Fi_minted_a_fully_playable_game_on_loopring_l2%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3z111/i_minted_a_fully_playable_game_on_loopring_l2/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 19:33:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[國際貨幣基金組織和世界銀行現在正在威脅中非共和國，但總統解釋了爲什麼比特幣是他的國家的唯一選擇。"一個不可逾越的官僚機構使我們被困在不給我們成功機會的系統中。比特幣開闢了一條通往光明未來的新道路"。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v41iwq/imf_and_world_bank_are_now_threatening_central/?score=374&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv41iwq%2Fimf_and_world_bank_are_now_threatening_central%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv41iwq%2Fimf_and_world_bank_are_now_threatening_central%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v41iwq/imf_and_world_bank_are_now_threatening_central/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 18:45:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有人改變了神奇寶貝的顏色，並以Animoon的名義在Opensea上出售，賺了630萬美元。這本來是一個P2E遊戲，但5個月後，他們什麼都沒有交付，反而刪除了他們的Twitter賬戶。這款遊戲還得到了傑克-保羅的支持。]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，傑克-保羅的宣傳應該是最大的紅旗，但人們仍然
但人們還是選擇了它。第二個紅旗是如此明顯，他們說前15張卡是
傳說中擁有這些卡的人將終身每月獲得2500美元。

紅...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3zbp1/someone_changed_the_colors_of_pok%C3%A9mon_and_made_63/?score=343&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3zbp1%2Fsomeone_changed_the_colors_of_pok%C3%A9mon_and_made_63%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3zbp1%2Fsomeone_changed_the_colors_of_pok%C3%A9mon_and_made_63%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3zbp1/someone_changed_the_colors_of_pokémon_and_made_63/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 17:33:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Well Jake Paul promoting should have been the biggest red flag but people still went for it. The second red flag was so obvious they said first 15 cards are legendary whoever owns them will get &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$2500 every month for life.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/5qq3k7txoe391.jpg?width=1284&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=79b65b97f77bf0e1ca6a03d929d8b5f514fe4c02&quot;&amp;gt;Red flag.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Well they also claimed they will giveaway Jordan shoes. You can guess nobody got them even after 5 months.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/t01jaib4pe391.jpg?width=1204&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=f917a70b901748c3459e85114d0d744eafd56b14&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/t01jaib4pe391.jpg?width=1204&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=f917a70b901748c3459e85114d0d744eafd56b14&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Breeding will generate ETH &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;DAILY&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; LMFAO.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/p77mhznape391.jpg?width=1284&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e65a0f9c73e78d1bb5b6a805d9991ab35e9b5807&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/p77mhznape391.jpg?width=1284&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e65a0f9c73e78d1bb5b6a805d9991ab35e9b5807&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/iqknmi0gpe391.jpg?width=1284&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=6dfd389f55817019dd8198726cca4bda0e368be1&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/iqknmi0gpe391.jpg?width=1284&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=6dfd389f55817019dd8198726cca4bda0e368be1&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I think this might be the reason most people fell for this scam. They claimed they have signed NDA with Pokémon.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/as2lsx7ope391.jpg?width=709&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=8564adf1df421487abee404e53f849db8fc211d4&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/as2lsx7ope391.jpg?width=709&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=8564adf1df421487abee404e53f849db8fc211d4&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;$6.3 Million they made from this project already have been transferred to different exchanges.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.breadcrumbs.app/reports/1934&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.breadcrumbs.app/reports/1934&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There might be another rug pull coming from them under different name since they claimed to be working with  Bandai Namco (Digimon)  now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/tuy89i07qe391.jpg?width=1154&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=1236faf7077183b1ff2a576e012331370a35ad16&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/tuy89i07qe391.jpg?width=1154&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=1236faf7077183b1ff2a576e012331370a35ad16&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Twitter account for Animoon has been gone along with their Website. General chat has also been removed from their Discord.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1532390797479403521&quot;&amp;gt;https://twitter.com/zachxbt/status/1532390797479403521&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我有一個房子，我想要一個比特幣]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v3y61y/i_have_a_house_i_want_a_bitcoin/?score=719&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv3y61y%2Fi_have_a_house_i_want_a_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv3y61y%2Fi_have_a_house_i_want_a_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v3y61y/i_have_a_house_i_want_a_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 15:42:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特幣公司拒絕發表評論。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v3ssxm/bitcoin_declined_to_comment/?score=314&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv3ssxm%2Fbitcoin_declined_to_comment%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv3ssxm%2Fbitcoin_declined_to_comment%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v3ssxm/bitcoin_declined_to_comment/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 13:39:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[彭博社稱日本通過穩定幣法案確保按面值贖回]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3uumc/japan_passes_stablecoin_bill_ensuring_redemption/?score=315&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3uumc%2Fjapan_passes_stablecoin_bill_ensuring_redemption%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3uumc%2Fjapan_passes_stablecoin_bill_ensuring_redemption%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3uumc/japan_passes_stablecoin_bill_ensuring_redemption/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 13:39:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[大多數加密貨幣投資者不知道的事實：它實際上不是零和]]></title><description><![CDATA[幾天前，一個帖子
[https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v2c9h5/a_fact_ignored_by_most_crypto_investors_profits/?utm_source=share&utm_medium=web2x&context=3]
幾天前，一個帖子[]很受歡迎，其中包含了相當多的 "扶手式紅客的專業知識"，講述了什麼是
正在發生的 "加密貨幣"，使用了一個非常...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3qbct/fact_not_known_by_most_crypto_investors_its_not/?score=320&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3qbct%2Ffact_not_known_by_most_crypto_investors_its_not%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3qbct%2Ffact_not_known_by_most_crypto_investors_its_not%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3qbct/fact_not_known_by_most_crypto_investors_its_not/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 13:07:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A couple of days ago, a &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v2c9h5/a_fact_ignored_by_most_crypto_investors_profits/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;amp;amp;context=3&quot;&amp;gt;post&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; got popular that contained a fair bit of &amp;amp;quot;armchair redditor expertise&amp;amp;quot; on what &amp;amp;quot;is happening&amp;amp;quot; in crypto using a very simple diagram.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Many crypto critics charge that the whole space is an elaborate ponzi scheme, and a zero sum greater fools game. This is due to the fact that they narrowly define &amp;amp;quot;utility&amp;amp;quot;. The truth is, as soon as there is a secondary liquid market for a cryptocurrency or blockchain and its native asset, it becomes a utility in the real world because it offers the transmission and manipulation of real world value. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here is the revised diagram, and my point in summary:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/3b3y9dtrnb391.png?width=2252&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=1b3f31899487a26f35ce3ffc7e547ac57e2b6630&quot;&amp;gt;Blockchains are not zero sum&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You will see that in addition to investors cashing out, the security fee is the other leak of accrued value in a blockchain. I posted earlier an &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v0j27u/a_coherent_investment_thesis_looking_forward_to/&quot;&amp;gt;investment thesis&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; where I mentioned how to fundamentally value crypto, or at least the rough framework I use. It is important to realize &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;that most blockchains pay more in security costs than the transaction fees they receive from use&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. This means they ARE essentially zero sum most of the time. Only a few are not, and that is essentially Ethereum and its roll ups, though other modular PoS chains can eventually achieve the steady state of paying for security outright without diluting holders.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這些天的生活費用翻了一番]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v3rodr/life_costs_double_these_days/?score=429&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv3rodr%2Flife_costs_double_these_days%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv3rodr%2Flife_costs_double_these_days%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v3rodr/life_costs_double_these_days/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 13:07:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SOL再次受到攻擊! 既然存在100%正常運行時間的加密貨幣，爲什麼還要投資於SOL？]]></title><description><![CDATA[衆所周知，SOL網絡經常出現故障，被黑客攻擊，無法使用等，但人們仍然繼續投資於它。
黑客攻擊，不工作等，但人們仍然繼續投資於它。然而
最近，它又一次受到了攻擊。如果傳統的銀行業務是如此脆弱
政府就會把它拖到炭火上，看着它燃燒。

然而...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3vcls/sol_attacked_yet_again_why_invest_in_sol_when/?score=421&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3vcls%2Fsol_attacked_yet_again_why_invest_in_sol_when%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3vcls%2Fsol_attacked_yet_again_why_invest_in_sol_when%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3vcls/sol_attacked_yet_again_why_invest_in_sol_when/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 13:07:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s common knowledge here that the SOL network goes down frequently, gets hacked, doesn&amp;amp;#39;t work etc yet people still continue to invest in it. And yet again it was attacked YET AGAIN recently! If traditional banking was this flakey the government would haul it over the coals and watch it burn.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Yet people still invest in this centralized chain.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Litecoin for example (and I am sure there are many other examples that people can name) has had 100 percent uptime with literally no hacks or exploits, yet people instantly dismiss.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It brings me to the conclusion that we don&amp;amp;#39;t really care about fundamentals in the crypto space, only juicy profits. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So it brings me back to the original point of this post, why an earth are people investing in SOL when it is the least secure and reliable chain in crypto?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[是時候對比特幣的供應/需求動態進行一次新的分析了。看看這第一張圖表，我們將深入瞭解。🧵 https://t.co/3Eji34BLZH]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1532667281892954112/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1532667281892954112/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 11:45:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Epic Games執行官表示，人們對metaverse "失去興趣"。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3gohi/people_lost_interest_in_metaverse_says_epic_games/?score=310&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3gohi%2Fpeople_lost_interest_in_metaverse_says_epic_games%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3gohi%2Fpeople_lost_interest_in_metaverse_says_epic_games%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3gohi/people_lost_interest_in_metaverse_says_epic_games/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 08:47:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[至少持有1枚比特幣的地址達到歷史最高點848,082個]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://preview.redd.it/dpl70ao5j8391.png?width=700&format=png&auto=webp&s=e65a99aeeb9c02b3142694aafa966a5e5e03480b

至少持有一個比特幣的地址數量已達到歷史新高，爲84個。
848,082的歷史新高。似乎鯨魚正在購買比特幣的跌勢，你是
目前做多還是做空$BTC？]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v3cv9i/addresses_holding_at_least_1_bitcoin_hits_alltime/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv3cv9i%2Faddresses_holding_at_least_1_bitcoin_hits_alltime%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv3cv9i%2Faddresses_holding_at_least_1_bitcoin_hits_alltime%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v3cv9i/addresses_holding_at_least_1_bitcoin_hits_alltime/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 04:43:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/dpl70ao5j8391.png?width=700&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e65a99aeeb9c02b3142694aafa966a5e5e03480b&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/dpl70ao5j8391.png?width=700&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e65a99aeeb9c02b3142694aafa966a5e5e03480b&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The number of addresses holding at least one Bitcoin has reached a new all-time high of 848,082. It seems whales are buying the dip in bitcoin, are you currently long or short $BTC?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Algorand在過去7天內結算了850萬筆交易，平均每天120萬筆。自2019年以來，它每4.4秒產生一個區塊，沒有中斷過，交易成本爲0.0005美元。國際足聯、環球音樂集團和尼日利亞都在建設Algorand。成爲Algonaut的一員是件好事。]]></title><description><![CDATA[來源：https://metrics.algorand.org/

關於ALGO技術的其他很酷的東西。

Algorand擁有驚人的開發者資源和文檔。

你可以用這些語言中的任何一種在Algorand上編程dApps。

Python, PyTEAL, Java, JavaScript, Go, Reach

來源：...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3il6w/algorand_has_settled_85_million_transactions_in/?score=447&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3il6w%2Falgorand_has_settled_85_million_transactions_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3il6w%2Falgorand_has_settled_85_million_transactions_in%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3il6w/algorand_has_settled_85_million_transactions_in/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 02:21:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://metrics.algorand.org/&quot;&amp;gt;https://metrics.algorand.org/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Other cool stuff about ALGO Tech:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Algorand has amazing developer resources and documentation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can program dApps on Algorand in any of these languages:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Python, PyTEAL, Java, JavaScript, Go, Reach&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.algorand.org/docs/&quot;&amp;gt;https://developer.algorand.org/docs/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Additionally, Algorand is launching elegant and innovative &amp;amp;quot;state proofs&amp;amp;quot; that will allow for trustless interoperability between blockchains. Most don&amp;amp;#39;t realize how HUGE these state proofs are:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Big Picture  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Algorand State Proofs fortify cross-chain applications with Post-Quantum security. By using advanced cryptography, ASPs can withstand attacks by powerful quantum computers that try to alter the reported state of the blockchain, providing a robust, portable source of truth about on-chain data.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;From trustless bridges that move assets across blockchains to decentralized oracles that export valuable on-chain data, people will be able to leverage Algorand’s fast, cheap, and reliable protocol in new ecosystems without trust in an intermediary–they only need to trust the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.algorand.com/technology/security&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;security&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; of the underlying blockchain itself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.algorand.com/resources/algorand-announcements/powering-blockchain-interoperability-and-post-quantum-security&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.algorand.com/resources/algorand-announcements/powering-blockchain-interoperability-and-post-quantum-security&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Other big announcements:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Nigeria(200m Population) just announced a technical partnership with Algorand:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nigeria-launch-major-crypto-initiative-233000248.html&quot;&amp;gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/nigeria-launch-major-crypto-initiative-233000248.html&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Universal Music Group, the largest music corporation in the world is building a music NFT marketplace via Limewire on Algorand:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://decrypt.co/100704/universal-music-group-nfts-limewire-algorand-marketplace&quot;&amp;gt;https://decrypt.co/100704/universal-music-group-nfts-limewire-algorand-marketplace&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;FIFA, the largest sports organization in the world(Billions of fans) announced a technical partnership with Algorand:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fifa.com/en/about-fifa/president/media-releases/fifa-announces-partnership-with-blockchain-innovator-algorand&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.fifa.com/en/about-fifa/president/media-releases/fifa-announces-partnership-with-blockchain-innovator-algorand&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To me Algorand is the most reliable way to transact value with others. Cheap, Global, Instant, Secure. Large corporations and countries are realizing this and jumping on board.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the 2 years I&amp;amp;#39;ve been using it, it has never once been delayed or down. Every time I press send, the transaction is complete in 4.4 seconds almost like magic.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[友好提醒：FTX和SBF不是我們的朋友，他們會割斷用戶的喉嚨來賺錢。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3gipr/friendly_reminder_that_ftx_and_sbf_are_not_our/?score=316&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3gipr%2Ffriendly_reminder_that_ftx_and_sbf_are_not_our%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv3gipr%2Ffriendly_reminder_that_ftx_and_sbf_are_not_our%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v3gipr/friendly_reminder_that_ftx_and_sbf_are_not_our/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 02:21:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GameStop報告第一季度數字資產銷售收入爲7690萬美元]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v2zsxw/gamestop_reports_769m_in_proceeds_from_sales_of/?score=314&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv2zsxw%2Fgamestop_reports_769m_in_proceeds_from_sales_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fv2zsxw%2Fgamestop_reports_769m_in_proceeds_from_sales_of%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/v2zsxw/gamestop_reports_769m_in_proceeds_from_sales_of/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 02:21:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這傢伙認爲他在2010年錯過了公交車。猜猜看，我們在2022年還早着呢!]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v3iysk/this_guy_thought_he_missed_the_buss_in_2010_guess/?score=355&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv3iysk%2Fthis_guy_thought_he_missed_the_buss_in_2010_guess%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv3iysk%2Fthis_guy_thought_he_missed_the_buss_in_2010_guess%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v3iysk/this_guy_thought_he_missed_the_buss_in_2010_guess/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 02:21:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[新印製的新1美元紙幣，由FED發行]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v3gey3/freshly_printed_new_1_note_by_fed/?score=553&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv3gey3%2Ffreshly_printed_new_1_note_by_fed%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv3gey3%2Ffreshly_printed_new_1_note_by_fed%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v3gey3/freshly_printed_new_1_note_by_fed/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 23:44:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特幣是我唯一的希望，有一天我能夠從我們生活的這個腐敗骯髒的法幣世界中獲得一些財務自由。也許我把所有的雞蛋都放在一個籃子裏，但我已經沒有什麼可相信的了。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v3971l/bitcoin_is_my_only_hope_that_one_day_ill_be_able/?score=321&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv3971l%2Fbitcoin_is_my_only_hope_that_one_day_ill_be_able%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fv3971l%2Fbitcoin_is_my_only_hope_that_one_day_ill_be_able%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/v3971l/bitcoin_is_my_only_hope_that_one_day_ill_be_able/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 18:52:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>