<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£åœ‹å¤–ç†±é–€è¨Žè«–]]></title><description><![CDATA[ç”¨ä¸­æ–‡æµè§ˆå…³äºŽåŠ å¯†è´§å¸çš„å›½å¤–çƒ­é—¨è®¨è®º]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 07:27:20 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[ç ”ç©¶è¡¨æ˜Žï¼Œç¾Žåœ‹äººæ›´å–œæ­¡åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£è€Œä¸æ˜¯å‚³çµ±çš„å„²è“„è³¬æˆ¶]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sobj4s/americans_prefer_crypto_over_a_traditional/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsobj4s%2Famericans_prefer_crypto_over_a_traditional%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsobj4s%2Famericans_prefer_crypto_over_a_traditional%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sobj4s/americans_prefer_crypto_over_a_traditional/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 06:35:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[åœ¨åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£å’Œç©©å®šå¹£ä¸Šè³ºå–åˆ©æ¯ï¼šå¾žåˆç´šåˆ°é«˜ç´šæŒ‡å—ï¼ŒDeFiï¼ŒLPï¼Œè³­æ³¨ï¼Œå€Ÿè²¸]]></title><description><![CDATA[åœ¨åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£ä¸Šç”¢ç”Ÿæ”¶ç›Šæ˜¯ä¸€ä»¶ç¹æ¦®çš„äº‹æƒ…ã€‚æœ‰å¾ˆå¤šæ–¹æ³•å¯ä»¥æé«˜ä½ çš„
æ”¶ç›Šï¼Œé€™åŒ…æ‹¬å€Ÿè²¸ã€æŠ¼æ³¨ã€æä¾›æµå‹•æ€§ç­‰ã€‚ä½ å¯ä»¥é€šéŽ
ç”¨CeFiå’ŒDeFiã€‚é€™æ˜¯ä¸€å€‹æœ€æ–°çš„å˜—è©¦ï¼Œçˆ²åˆå­¸è€…æä¾›æŒ‡å—ã€‚
ä½†å³ä½¿æ˜¯æœ‰ç¶“é©—çš„ç”¨æˆ¶ä¹Ÿæœƒç™¼ç¾ä¸€äº›æœ‰ç”¨çš„æ±è¥¿......]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soiu05/earn_interest_on_crypto_and_stablecoins_begginer/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoiu05%2Fearn_interest_on_crypto_and_stablecoins_begginer%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoiu05%2Fearn_interest_on_crypto_and_stablecoins_begginer%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soiu05/earn_interest_on_crypto_and_stablecoins_begginer/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 06:35:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Generating yield on crypto is a booming thing. There are many ways to boost your gains, this includes lending, staking, liquidity providing, etc. You can do this with CeFi and DeFi. This is an updated attempt to provide guide for begginers, but even experieneced user might find some useful tips.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;First let get some terms right:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Staking&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - refers to generating income by block generation on Proof of Stake (PoS) blockchains. The term is heavily misused everywhere, so nowadays it can mean anything from staking to liquidity providing&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Lending&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - you lend your crypto and get interest. Counterparty does anything it want with it and hopefully pays back some day.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Liquidity providing (LP)&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - you provide two (sometimes even more) cryptocurrencies to a DEX (decentralized exchange), so people can trade. You get your share of trading fees.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;CeFi&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - centralized companies, you can lend them your coins, they pay you interest.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;DeFi&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; - decentralized (well, at least in theory) applications like DEXes, lending apps etc&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Risks&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are obviously risks that come with all this, so beware. CeFi can get hacked, can scam you, can bankrupt. DeFi can get hacked, can scam you and its happening a lot. With staking you can get slashed (happens rarely), but if you delegate your funds to a validator, he can misbehave (depends on specific chain what he can or cant do). When doing LP, you face impermanent loss, in addition to all the DeFi risks.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;How to get yield&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now lets get to generating some money, starting from the simplest options.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;CeFi&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Probably easiest thing to do is to lend your coins to a big CeFi lender, like Celsius. They have been around for a while, have $20B in assets under management and among CeFi its as safe as it gets. But their rates are somewhat lower than what competitors can pay you. Rates for different coins are a lot different and every CeFi lender has different rates for the coin, so you can optimize by using several CeFi. When deciding between platforms these are important things to consider: rates, security, jurisdiction, withdrawal fees, how customer support works. Also not every lender will be available in your country.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Where to find best rates:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coinlenders.net/&quot;&amp;gt;https://coinlenders.net&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; - this a is site i put together myself, you can search for rates among several CeFi and DeFi lending platforms. Just select a coin and see what your options are.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Note that most of the CeFi platforms have tiered system, meaning you can get best rate on limited amount - if that affects you, consider splitting funds between multiple platforms to get best value. It also helps with diversification.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
StakingIf you have Proof of Stake coins, than very likely staking will be safest option with great return. Many CeFi providers will just stake the coin for you and take their cut for doing this, so consider doing it yourself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Typical yield for stablecoins is 10-12%, 5-6% on bitcoin and ether.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There are services that promise a way bigger yield than this, but i don&amp;amp;#39;t find them trustworthy enough for sharing. But just in case you want to gamble, know that if you look, you can find yields like 15-30% on btc - but dont be suprised if you end up with nothing...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;DeFi&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Moving to DeFi. First of all try to eliminate unnecessary risks by obtaining HW wallet. Ledger or Trezor. Chose wisely according to the chains you wanna use, not all chains are supported. If possible, go for the Nano X or Model T, as these support all the modern stuff. Learn to use Metamask with you HW wallet, it will work well for all the EVM chains.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;DeFi lending&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just like CeFi, you can just lend you coin with some lending protocol like AAVE, Compound etc. Most of the DeFi protocols issue its own token, and sometimes they will give some as incentives to lenders, borrowers or liquidity providers. This is additional yield, sometimes these rewards are locked for some time, so there is a risk of the incentive token losing lot of value before you can sell. Interest rates are usually adjusted to current market situation and change a lot, so you need to monitor it.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Where to find good rates?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coinlenders.net/defi-lending&quot;&amp;gt;https://coinlenders.net/defi-lending&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coindix.com/?kind=single&quot;&amp;gt;https://coindix.com/?kind=single&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;DeFi - liquidity providing&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Liquidity providing is another great way to generate yield. You provide some liquidity to a DEX, in return you get fees and sometimes also incentive tokens. Usually you need to provide two assets in 50:50 ratio, which makes it more complicated. Understand, that by providing liquidity you are basically putting you assets for sale and you no longer have direct exposure to their price, so if the price in the pair changes, you will find that you own different amount of tokens and always, you will own more of the worse one.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
This is called impermanent loss, but there is nothing really impermanent about it, its quite normal loss. To avoid impermanent loss you can chose a pool with currencies of equal or correlated value, like USDC-USDT. Also note that due to the impermanent loss, if one token loses 100% of value, you lose everything in the pool not just half - because you will be left with with 100% of the worthless one, due to arbitrage. Sometimes with the LP pools you will see ridiculous APYs like 1000000%, that does not mean you are getting rich. The reason for these crazy APYs is usually one of these:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;its a new platform and it will go down quickly as more liquidity is added&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;You need to but hyperinflating token which will lose a lot of value over time, negating the gains&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Its very unsecure/untrustworthy platform with high risk of getting robbed&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Where to find the best pools? Here are some resources to help:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coindix.com/&quot;&amp;gt;https://coindix.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://kingdata.com/&quot;&amp;gt;https://kingdata.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://app.apy.vision/liquidity-pools&quot;&amp;gt;https://app.apy.vision/liquidity-pools&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;How to handle incentive tokens/rewards&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
You usually will want to sell it and add to your lending/LP positions to get compounding effects. These incentive tokens are normally very inflationary and are losing value quickly, especially when the protocol is new. Claiming the rewards and swapping it on DEX are transactions which can cost you tx fees, so if this is on expensive chain like Ethereum, this is only profitable for whales basically. Solution is to use automatic compounders, like Autofarm, more on this later. When the reward is locked for some time, it may go down a lot during this period, and your yield will be smaller than expected. Be sure to include this in your risk assessment.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Advanced strategies&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When you get familiar with DeFi, you might want to try some advanced stuff, combining multiple protocols together to boost your yields even further. These come with more risk and usually involve some kind of leverage, so be careful. There are plenty of options, lets check some usual or popular options.Some of these strategies:  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Recursive lending&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is when you lend your asset to a DeFi protocol and borrow it right back, then supply it into the same protocol. You can do the loop several time until limit is reached, the limit is a function of collateral factor. So lets say you deposit $1k and collateral factor is 80%, you can max you position to 1/(1-CF), so to $5k deposit and $4k borrow position. There will be a lot of transactions doing this, so you need cheap chain or big deposit to be worthy. This strategy is profitable if deposit interest is bigger than borrow interest, which is possible when incentive token rewards are high. But you will need to do constant compounding to avoid liquidation (without it your debt grows). You need to monitor the incentive token price and the APYs, so you can recognize when its no longer profitable.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tranquil.finance/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.tranquil.finance/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; is one place this is possible at this moment&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Lend and borrow, then put into LP&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some protocols do not allow recursive lending, you can maybe circumvent this with multiple accounts, or you can do something else, like deposit USDT, borrow USDC, sell half of the USDC for USDT and put it in LP pool. Again, you need high incentive token rewards to make it profitable.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Automated compounding&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As compounding on some platforms is costly due to blockchain fees, solution is to use automated compounder, like Autofarm, which does all the work for you in optimal way. You add some risk by doing this, if the auto compounding protocol gets compromised, you also lose your deposit.Examples:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Autofarm: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://autofarm.network/&quot;&amp;gt;https://autofarm.network/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Beefy: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://beefy.finance/&quot;&amp;gt;https://beefy.finance/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Leveraged yield farming&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Basically you provide liquidity, while borrowing additional money to get more yield. You pay interest to lenders, but you earn more of the incentive tokens and fees. You put your money as collateral. Examples: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Alpaca: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://app.alpacafinance.org/farm&quot;&amp;gt;https://app.alpacafinance.org/farm&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Tulip: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://tulip.garden/leverage&quot;&amp;gt;https://tulip.garden/leverage&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Anchor+Mirror&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anchor protocol is one of the most favorite places to earn interest on stablecoins, with stable 19.5% its a no brainer. But you can get more when combining with Mirror protocol. This is covered in depth in many articles, so i am not going to repeat it: just google Anchor Mirror delta neutral strategy.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anchorprotocol.com/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.anchorprotocol.com/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://mirrorprotocol.app&quot;&amp;gt;https://mirrorprotocol.app&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Anchor+MIM leverage&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Another thing people have been doing is basically leveraging your position. You borrow MIM against your aUST tokens (representing your deposit), sell MIM for UST, deposit again. I have never done this though, &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.anchorprotocol.com/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.anchorprotocol.com/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Nexus&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Next generation of these combined strategies is automated. Nexus Protocol is a great example: you deposit LUNA or ETH(PoS version) to nexus, it uses it as collateral in Anchor to borrow UST, deposits the UST to Anchor for additional yield, it monitors and maintains your LTV to ensure you are not liquidated, sell you profits for LUNA/ETH and it results in safer and higher yield. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Check it out: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://nexusprotocol.app/&quot;&amp;gt;https://nexusprotocol.app/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Moving funds between chains&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you are going the DeFi way, you may need to move funds between chains a lot. Especially valid for stablecoins and WBTC. Some tips to do this effectively:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Register on exchanges which support withdrawals and depostits to multiple chains: Binance, Bitfinex, Crypto. com - you can deposit with one chain, withdraw with other, usually paying some withdrawal fees&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;For swapping one stablecoin for another, use Binance rather than DEX, as fees are way lower. (if low cost is a priority, understandably for some of you priorites might be different, or you dont have binance available etc.)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Learn how to use multichain router: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://app.multichain.org/#/router&quot;&amp;gt;https://app.multichain.org/#/router&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for cheap cross chain transfers&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;For larger amounts, avoid services which charge percentual fees&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Swapping to one crypto and than back for cross chain transafers is sometimes possible, but usually not very cheap and might trigger taxable event. Sometimes it might be only option though.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ethereum bridges are usually the most expensive way to do this, unless you are handling very large amounts&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Some additional tips:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;If you just starting with few hundreds dollars, don&amp;amp;#39;t bother with DeFi. You will get crushed by blockchain fees. Use some CeFi lender with free withdrawals to accumulate, when you have more, you can start with DeFi. Also these CeFis will often give you nice sign-up bonuses, which will probably be worth a lot more than the interest, so be sure to get it. You can even jump between several CeFis to collect more of it. If still want to do DeFi, use a cheap chain. Harmony and Solana come to mind. Avoid Ethereum.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Don&amp;amp;#39;t get attached to a specific chain, good opportunities appear on different chains every time, it does not make sense to limit yourself to one favorite. Of course, if you are hodling SOL token, you will probably find best opportunities on Solana network, but with universal assets like stablecoins or BTC, it can be anywhere.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Always monitor your gains. If something doesn&amp;amp;#39;t add up, investigate and be prepared to move your funds.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Depending on your jurisdiction, you might have to pay taxes on your lending/staking/LP gains. &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My favorite CeFi products:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Hodlnaut.com&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Ledn.io&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Celsius&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;FTX&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Less known, but very promising: Vauld&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My favorite DeFi products:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Anchor Protocol - note that Anchor Yield reserve is bleeding rapidly, its possible that yield will go down. &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Tranquil.finance on Harmony (+Mimas clone from the same team on Cronos)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;TraderJoe on Avalanche&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Sovryn on RSK&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Note: this is an updated post from January, update includes: some more strategies a tips, more specific examples. Added cross-chain transfers tips.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[å¯¦éš›ä¸Šæˆ‘åœ¨æƒ³ï¼Œä¹Ÿè¨±Facebook/Metaæœƒé€™æ¨£åšã€‚å‚‘å…‹ï¼š"æˆ‘å‘Šè¨´è¿ªå§†ä»–å€‘åšéŒ¯äº†ã€‚ä½ å€‘æ‡‰è©²ä½¿ç”¨é–ƒé›»ã€‚"]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/som20p/i_actually_was_thinking_that_maybe_facebook_meta/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsom20p%2Fi_actually_was_thinking_that_maybe_facebook_meta%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsom20p%2Fi_actually_was_thinking_that_maybe_facebook_meta%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/som20p/i_actually_was_thinking_that_maybe_facebook_meta/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 06:35:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1997å¹´çš„äº’è¯ç¶²ç”¨æˆ¶ï¼š1.3å„„ã€‚ä»Šå¤©çš„BTCç”¨æˆ¶ã€‚130M]]></title><description><![CDATA[1997å¹´çš„äº’è¯ç¶²ç”¨æˆ¶ï¼š1.3å„„ã€‚

ä»Šå¤©çš„BTCç”¨æˆ¶ã€‚130M

1997å¹´äº’è¯ç¶²æœ‰14å¹´çš„æ­·å²ï¼Œè€ŒBTCä»Šå¹´æœ‰13å¹´ï¼ˆ?ï¼‰çš„æ­·å²ã€‚

çœ‹èµ·ä¾†æˆ‘å€‘çš„å¢žé•·é€Ÿåº¦æ¯”äº’è¯ç¶²ç•¶å¹´çš„å¢žé•·é€Ÿåº¦å¿«ï¼Œä½†æˆ‘çŸ¥é“é€™ä¸æ˜¯æ‰€æœ‰çš„é»‘è‰²å’Œç™½è‰²ï¼Œé‚„æœ‰å¾ˆå¤šå› ç´ åœ¨èµ·ä½œç”¨ã€‚
ä¸¦éžéƒ½æ˜¯é»‘ç™½åˆ†æ˜Žçš„ï¼Œé€™è£é‚„æœ‰å¾ˆå¤šå› ç´ åœ¨èµ·ä½œç”¨ã€‚
æŠ€è¡“...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soljnd/internet_users_in_1997_130m_btc_users_today_130m/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoljnd%2Finternet_users_in_1997_130m_btc_users_today_130m%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoljnd%2Finternet_users_in_1997_130m_btc_users_today_130m%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soljnd/internet_users_in_1997_130m_btc_users_today_130m/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 03:39:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Internet users in 1997: 130M. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;BTC users today: 130M&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Internet was 14 years old in 1997 while BTC is 13 (?) years old this year. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Looks like we&amp;amp;#39;re growing faster than internet did way back when but I know it&amp;amp;#39;s not all so black and white and there&amp;amp;#39;s many more factors at play here: technological literacy, avaliability of said technology, nearly 2 billion people more on the planet today compared to 1997 etc ...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just felt like sharing this here and maybe starting a discussion since somebody mentioned the numbers Bitcoin sub.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ä»Šå¤©å¹¾ä¹Žå¾žä¸€å€‹é¨™å­é‚£è£å¾—åˆ°äº†10å„„æ³°éŠ–ã€‚å°±å·®é‚£éº¼ä¸€é»žé»žã€‚]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sonz2c/almost_got_1btc_out_of_a_scammer_today_so_close/?score=367&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsonz2c%2Falmost_got_1btc_out_of_a_scammer_today_so_close%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsonz2c%2Falmost_got_1btc_out_of_a_scammer_today_so_close%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sonz2c/almost_got_1btc_out_of_a_scammer_today_so_close/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 02:42:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[æ˜¯å¦é‚„æœ‰å…¶ä»–å³å°‡æŽ¨å‡ºçš„ "çŽ©è³º "éŠæˆ²ï¼Œä½ èªçˆ²æœƒæœ‰åƒ¹å€¼ï¼Ÿ]]></title><description><![CDATA[æˆ‘æƒ³ç›¡æ—©æŠ•è³‡æ–¼P2EéŠæˆ²ï¼Œé€™æ¨£æˆ‘å°±èƒ½å¿«é€Ÿç²å¾—æŠ•è³‡å›žå ±ã€‚
è€Œä¸”ï¼Œåœ¨åƒ¹æ ¼ä¸é«˜çš„æ™‚å€™ã€‚(æˆ‘ä¸æœƒæŠŠå®ƒä½œçˆ²æˆ‘çš„ä¸»è¦æ”¶å…¥ä¾†æºã€‚
ç¸½ä¹‹ï¼Œä»¥ä¸‹æ˜¯æˆ‘ç™¼ç¾çš„ä¸€äº›éŠæˆ²ã€‚
ç™¼ç¾çš„ä¸€äº›éŠæˆ²ã€‚
1. å…ƒæ°£å¤§å‚·
æˆ‘èªçˆ²æˆ‘æ²’æœ‰é‚£éº¼æ—©æŽ¥è§¸é€™å€‹....ã€‚]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soc2jj/are_there_any_other_upcoming_play_to_earn_games/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoc2jj%2Fare_there_any_other_upcoming_play_to_earn_games%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoc2jj%2Fare_there_any_other_upcoming_play_to_earn_games%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soc2jj/are_there_any_other_upcoming_play_to_earn_games/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 02:42:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I want to invest in P2E games as early as possible so I can have my ROI fast, and also, while the prices arenâ€™t high. (Iâ€™m not gonna use it as my main source of income so donâ€™t come at me) Anyways, Here are some of the games that I have found.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;1. Metawars&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
I don&amp;amp;#39;t think I&amp;amp;#39;m that early with this one. I was hoping for phase one, but I think this will be enough. I&amp;amp;#39;m hoping the graphics aren&amp;amp;#39;t too bad considering we will be exploring planets and battling other players. (Itâ€™s kinda like star atlas? lol) Iâ€™m wondering how much the planets will cost alsoooooo, itâ€™s a multiplayer game which is kinda intriguing but still kinda skeptic about this.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;2. Wrejects&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Iâ€™m looking forward to this one too. Wrestling and aliens are the perfect combination for me. Still thinking if the graphics when wrestling will be good. Iâ€™m really realllyyy looking forward to the gameplay but Itâ€™s still on Q1 so thereâ€™s nothing much info out there. Every fighter, like in other PVP games, has their own backstory and unique special move. Also, unlike in Metawars, the team is doxxed.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;3. My Neighbor Alice&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Not early enough with this one too but this is a pretty wholesome game. Itâ€™s an open world game kinda like animal crossing? I wasnâ€™t able to join the pre-alpha access but seeing the gameplay was enough for me. I can see myself spending hours playing this, just like I did with AC also, Itâ€™s on steam which is a plus for me.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Any thoughts about the games that I mentioned?&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Ps. still new to this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ä½©æ´›è¥¿æ”¾æ£„åå°ï¼Œåœ‹æœƒç€æ‰‹ç¦æ­¢è­°å“¡äº¤æ˜“è‚¡ç¥¨]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sorx7h/congress_moves_to_ban_members_from_trading_stocks/?score=522&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsorx7h%2Fcongress_moves_to_ban_members_from_trading_stocks%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsorx7h%2Fcongress_moves_to_ban_members_from_trading_stocks%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sorx7h/congress_moves_to_ban_members_from_trading_stocks/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 02:42:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[æˆ‘æŠŠ0.003 BTCçš„é‘°åŒ™æ”¾åœ¨ä¿éšªåº«è£100å¹´ã€‚]]></title><description><![CDATA[å¥½å§ï¼Œä¸å®Œå…¨æ˜¯æˆ‘æŠŠå®ƒæ”¾åœ¨é‚£è£ï¼Œæˆ‘å±…ä½çš„åŸŽå¸‚æª”æ¡ˆé¤¨å°‡å­˜å„²
ä¿¡ä»¶100å¹´ã€‚ä»–å€‘å°‡åœ¨2122å¹´æ‰“é–‹å®ƒå€‘ã€‚æˆ‘å¯«äº†ä¸€å°ä¿¡ï¼Œä¹Ÿ
æŠŠåƒ¹å€¼100ç¾Žå…ƒçš„ç§é‘°æ”¾åœ¨BTCä¸­ã€‚ä½ èªçˆ²æœ‰å¤šå¤§çš„æ©Ÿæœƒ
ç¶²çµ¡é‚„èƒ½ç¹¼çºŒé‹è¡Œå—Žï¼Ÿä»€éº¼æœƒæ˜¯å€å¡Šéˆï¼Ÿ]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/soknl2/i_put_keys_to_0003_btc_in_a_vault_for_100_years/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsoknl2%2Fi_put_keys_to_0003_btc_in_a_vault_for_100_years%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsoknl2%2Fi_put_keys_to_0003_btc_in_a_vault_for_100_years%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/soknl2/i_put_keys_to_0003_btc_in_a_vault_for_100_years/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 01:36:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Well not exactly I put it there, the city archive where I live will store letters for 100 years. They will open them in 2122. I wrote a letter and also put the private keys for 100 $ worth in BTC. What do you think are the chances the network will be still up and running? What would be the block reward by then if so? What would you put in an envelope for 100 years?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[å¾ˆå¿«ï¼Œç”±æ–¼å€å¡Šéˆçš„å­˜åœ¨ï¼ŒäºŒæ‰‹è»Šå•†å°‡ç„¡æ³•æ‰­æ›²æ±½è»Šè£ç¨‹æ•¸ã€‚é˜¿çˆ¾æ³•-ç¾…å¯†æ­æŽ¨å‡ºä¸€æ¬¾æ–°çš„SUVï¼Œåˆ©ç”¨NFTå’Œå€å¡Šéˆè¿½è¹¤æ±½è»Šçš„ç”Ÿå‘½é€±æœŸ]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sohm0r/soon_used_car_dealers_will_not_be_able_to_twist/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsohm0r%2Fsoon_used_car_dealers_will_not_be_able_to_twist%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsohm0r%2Fsoon_used_car_dealers_will_not_be_able_to_twist%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sohm0r/soon_used_car_dealers_will_not_be_able_to_twist/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 01:36:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[åå¹´å‰ï¼Œæˆ‘æ›¾é è¨€Redditå°‡æŠŠå…¶å› æžœå ±æ‡‰ç³»çµ±è®ŠæˆåŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£ã€‚é€™æ˜¯æˆ‘ä¸‹ä¸€å€‹åå¹´çš„é æ¸¬ã€‚]]></title><description><![CDATA[å€å¡ŠéˆæŠ€è¡“æ­£è™•æ–¼æ§‹å»ºä¸€å€‹ç„¡ä¿¡ä»»çš„å…¨çƒæŠ•ç¥¨æ©Ÿçš„æ—©æœŸéšŽæ®µã€‚
çš„æ©Ÿå™¨ï¼Œäººé¡žå°‡ç”¨å®ƒä¾†å¿«é€Ÿé”æˆå°ç•¶å‰äº‹ä»¶çš„å¤§è¡†å…±è­˜ã€‚
äº‹ä»¶é”æˆå…±è­˜ã€‚VRé ­ç›”æˆ–ARçœ¼é¡ä¸­çš„ç”Ÿç‰©çµ±è¨ˆå­¸å’Œéºªéƒ¨è­˜åˆ¥å°‡è¢«ç”¨ä¾†é©—è­‰ç”¨æˆ¶çš„ç‰¹å®šéŒ¢åŒ…åœ°å€ã€‚
ç”¨ä¾†é©—è­‰ç”¨æˆ¶çš„ç‰¹å®šéŒ¢åŒ…åœ°å€ï¼Œ...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sohd28/ten_years_ago_i_predicted_that_reddit_would_turn/?score=339&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsohd28%2Ften_years_ago_i_predicted_that_reddit_would_turn%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsohd28%2Ften_years_ago_i_predicted_that_reddit_would_turn%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sohd28/ten_years_ago_i_predicted_that_reddit_would_turn/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 21:38:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Blockchain tech is in the early stages of constructing a trustless global voting machine that humanity will use to quickly reach popular consensus on current events. Biometrics and facial recognition in VR headsets or AR glasses will be used to authenticate users to a specific wallet address, guaranteeing that no user votes twice. This will lead to an informal global democracy. Ignoring or acting against the will of global consensus will be considered political taboo in many countries. Over time, this voting mechanism will fundamentally transform the way in which humanity governs itself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thank you for reading my silly prediction. Obligatory, this is not financial advice but entertainment only. Proof of my last prediction is noted in the subreddit&amp;amp;#39;s wiki under the crypto history section.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ç¾Žåœ‹æ”¿åºœç¾åœ¨æŒæœ‰40å„„ç¾Žå…ƒçš„æ¯”ç‰¹å¹£ï¼Œæ˜¯ç‰¹æ–¯æ‹‰å †ç©çš„å…©å€]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sogujw/us_government_now_holds_4_billion_in_bitcoin/?score=343&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsogujw%2Fus_government_now_holds_4_billion_in_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsogujw%2Fus_government_now_holds_4_billion_in_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sogujw/us_government_now_holds_4_billion_in_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 21:38:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ç¾é‡‘æ˜¯åžƒåœ¾]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sojhsr/cash_is_trash/?score=390&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsojhsr%2Fcash_is_trash%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsojhsr%2Fcash_is_trash%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sojhsr/cash_is_trash/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 20:39:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[æ¢…æ‹‰å°¼å©­-ç‰¹æœ—æ™®çš„NFTä»¥17è¬ç¾Žå…ƒè³£çµ¦äº†....herselfã€‚]]></title><description><![CDATA[é‘„é€ NFTçš„åœ°å€ï¼ˆåˆç¨±1è™Ÿåœ°å€ï¼‰å°‡473,657.64ç¾Žå…ƒç™¼é€åˆ°ä¸€ç®‡ä¸­ä»‹åœ°å€ï¼ˆ2è™Ÿï¼‰ã€‚
ä¸­ä»‹åœ°å€(#2)ã€‚ä¸­ä»‹åœ°å€å°‡å…¶ä¸­ä¸€äº›USDCæ›æˆäº†
1,816.08 SOLã€‚ç„¶å¾Œï¼Œ2è™Ÿåœ°å€å‘ç¬¬ä¸‰å€‹åœ°å€ç™¼é€äº†1800å€‹SOLã€‚

ç¬¬ä¸‰å€‹åœ°å€å‡ºåƒ¹ï¼Œä»¥1800 SOLè´å¾—äº†NFTã€‚é€™1800SOL...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sohojt/melania_trumps_nft_was_sold_for_170000_toherself/?score=470&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsohojt%2Fmelania_trumps_nft_was_sold_for_170000_toherself%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsohojt%2Fmelania_trumps_nft_was_sold_for_170000_toherself%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sohojt/melania_trumps_nft_was_sold_for_170000_toherself/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 20:39:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The address (aka address #1) that minted the NFT sent 473,657.64 USDC to an intermediary address (#2). The intermediary address swaps some of that USDC for 1,816.08 SOL. Then Address #2 sends 1800 SOL to a 3rd address.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The third address makes a bid and wins the NFT for 1800 SOL. That 1800 SOL goes to address #1 (the one that minted the NFT). Then address #1 sends the 1800 to the intermediary Address #2. The intermediary address swaps the 1800 SOL to USDC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Blockchains, amirite?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Credit to user @zachxbt on twitter did the digging here.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here it is on the solana explorer: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://explorer.solana.com/address/JB21HTccXiiyZUYpdWxoy1nSu6zbMBVKBQz1if85d7ud&quot;&amp;gt;https://explorer.solana.com/address/JB21HTccXiiyZUYpdWxoy1nSu6zbMBVKBQz1if85d7ud&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here is an article on it: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7vpx8/analyzing-the-very-bizarre-sale-of-melania-trumps-dollar170000-nft&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.vice.com/en/article/m7vpx8/analyzing-the-very-bizarre-sale-of-melania-trumps-dollar170000-nft&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[äººå€‘èªªæŠ•è³‡åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£çš„é¢¨éšªå¤ªå¤§ï¼Œç„¶è€Œçµå©šå»è¢«ç¤¾æœƒç¾ŽåŒ–å’ŒæŽ¥å—ã€‚çˆ²ä»€éº¼å‘¢ï¼Ÿå©šå§»æ˜¯é¢¨éšªæ›´å¤§çš„æŠ•è³‡ã€‚]]></title><description><![CDATA[åœ¨ç¾Žåœ‹ï¼Œä¸€å ´å©šç¦®çš„å¹³å‡è²»ç”¨å¤§ç´„æ˜¯20,000ç¾Žå…ƒã€‚é€™é‚„åªæ˜¯
çš„å©šç¦®ã€‚éš¨ç€é›¢å©šçŽ‡çš„ç©©æ­¥ä¸Šå‡ï¼Œå©šå§»æ˜¯
ä¸€å€‹äººåœ¨ä»–/å¥¹çš„ä¸€ç”Ÿä¸­å¯èƒ½åšå‡ºçš„æœ€æœ‰é¢¨éšªã€æœ€ä¸åˆ©çš„æŠ•è³‡ã€‚

é‚£éº¼ï¼Œå‡è¨­ä½ å’Œä½ çš„å¦ä¸€åŠæ±ºå®šé›¢å©š....ã€‚]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sojzqo/people_say_investing_in_crypto_is_too_risky_yet/?score=344&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsojzqo%2Fpeople_say_investing_in_crypto_is_too_risky_yet%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsojzqo%2Fpeople_say_investing_in_crypto_is_too_risky_yet%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sojzqo/people_say_investing_in_crypto_is_too_risky_yet/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 20:39:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The average cost of a wedding is roughly $20,000 here in the USA. Thatâ€™s just for the wedding. With the divorce rate steadily increasing, a marriage is the most risky, unfavorable investment one could make in his/her entire life. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then, letâ€™s say you and your significant other decides to divorce. Attorney fees, and divorce filings can well exceed $10k (If youâ€™re lucky) and thatâ€™s not even taking into account your significant other taking half of your shit + child support if you have children. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Society is programmed into thinking getting married and having children is happiness. Donâ€™t get me wrong, of course thereâ€™s happiness and love involved, but almost 65% of men and women find out the hard way there is A LOT of financial suffering involved too. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In conclusion, investing in Crypto is a risk, but so is living the blueprint model of happiness and success. Investing in crypto seems a lot safer than getting married to one person for the rest of your life. Iâ€™m just saying.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto.comå®£ä½ˆæˆçˆ²ä¸€ç´šæ–¹ç¨‹å¼Crypto.comé‚é˜¿å¯†å¤§çŽè³½çš„å®˜æ–¹å† ååˆä½œä¼™ä¼´]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soenkl/cryptocom_announced_as_official_title_partner_of/?score=395&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoenkl%2Fcryptocom_announced_as_official_title_partner_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsoenkl%2Fcryptocom_announced_as_official_title_partner_of%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/soenkl/cryptocom_announced_as_official_title_partner_of/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 18:47:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[çˆ†ç‚¸æ€§æ–°èžï¼šä¿„ç¾…æ–¯å°‡æŠŠ#æ¯”ç‰¹å¹£ä½œçˆ²ä¸€ç¨®è²¨å¹£å°å¾…! ðŸ˜±]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491437217608507393/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491437217608507393/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 16:36:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BBCå’ŒåŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£åª’é«”ã€‚"20æ­²çš„å¹´è¼•äººé€šéŽäº¤æ˜“åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£å°‡50ç¾Žå…ƒè®Šæˆäº†800è¬ç¾Žå…ƒï¼Œä»–è¨­ç«‹çš„ä»£å¹£å·²ç¶“çˆ²æ…ˆå–„æ©Ÿæ§‹å‹Ÿé›†äº†25è¬ç¾Žå…ƒçš„è³‡é‡‘ðŸ˜" ä»–å€‘æ²’æœ‰å ±é“çš„æ˜¯ï¼Œé‚£å€‹ä»£å¹£åœ¨10æœˆé—œé–‰äº†ï¼Œä¼¼ä¹Žæ˜¯ä¸€å€‹é¨™å±€ï¼Ÿ]]></title><description><![CDATA[ä»Šå¤©ï¼Œè‹±åœ‹å»£æ’­å…¬å¸(BBC)æœ‰ä¸€å€‹å¥åº·çš„æ•…äº‹ï¼Œä¸¦å¾—åˆ°ä¸€äº›åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£ "åª’é«” "çš„éŸ¿æ‡‰ã€‚
"åª’é«” "å ±é“äº†ä¸€å€‹å¹´è¼•çš„åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£ç™¾è¬å¯Œç¿ï¼Œåœ¨å¹¾å€‹æœˆå…§å°‡50ç¾Žå…ƒè®Šæˆäº†æ•¸ç™¾è¬ç¾Žå…ƒã€‚
å¹¾å€‹æœˆå…§äº¤æ˜“åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£ã€‚å¥½å§ï¼Œé€™è½èµ·ä¾†æœ‰é»žé›£ä»¥ç½®ä¿¡ï¼Œä½†é‚„æœ‰æ›´å¤šçš„
çš„æ•…äº‹ã€‚

ä»–å€‘å ±å‘Šèªªï¼Œä»–æ­£åœ¨å›žé¥‹çµ¦...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sobivz/bbc_and_crypto_media_20yearold_turned_50_into_8m/?score=315&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsobivz%2Fbbc_and_crypto_media_20yearold_turned_50_into_8m%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsobivz%2Fbbc_and_crypto_media_20yearold_turned_50_into_8m%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sobivz/bbc_and_crypto_media_20yearold_turned_50_into_8m/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 16:36:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There is a wholesome story going around by the BBC today, echoed by some crypto &amp;amp;quot;media&amp;amp;quot; about a young crypto millionaire that turned $50 into millions within months trading crypto. Okay, this sound somewhat unbelievable, but there&amp;amp;#39;s more to the story.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They report, he is giving back to the community and &amp;amp;quot;A cryptocurrency he set up to support charity has already seen more than Â£200,000 spent on causes, and he is looking to use further funds raised by his currency to realise his foodbank plans for his home town of Birmingham.&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The problem is: that token shut down in October, as a &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/jimwaterson/status/1491361991541538817&quot;&amp;gt;Twitter user&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; found out through a short search. If you look at their &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/Orfano/&quot;&amp;gt;subreddit&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; it&amp;amp;#39;s dead and people don&amp;amp;#39;t seem very happy - it seemingly was a scam.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What the fuck? I know crypto reporting in mainstream media is often bad, and crypto media is always awful, but how can such a big medium publish such a story without the most basic research?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Edit: seems like the BBC article was taken down! You can find an archived version &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sobivz/bbc_and_crypto_media_20yearold_turned_50_into_8m/hw7ofvc/&quot;&amp;gt;in my reply here&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; (I don&amp;amp;#39;t want to link it directly as my post couldn&amp;amp;#39;t be posted with the link originally)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[çˆ†ç‚¸ï¼šé¦–ç›¸é®‘é‡Œæ–¯-ç´„ç¿°éœå®£ä½ˆï¼Œæ”¿åºœå°‡æå‰ä¸€å€‹æœˆå–æ¶ˆè‹±æ ¼è˜­çš„æ‰€æœ‰Covidé™åˆ¶ï¼ŒåŒ…æ‹¬è‡ªæˆ‘éš”é›¢çš„æ³•å¾‹è¦æ±‚ã€‚

 https://t.co/xWwAM6JF6x]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491431981531680768/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491431981531680768/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 15:37:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Coinbaseç«Šå–äº†æˆ‘çš„Ethå­˜æ¬¾ï¼Œä¸¦ç„¡è¦–æˆ‘èˆ‡ä»–å€‘çš„é€šä¿¡ã€‚å¿«é€Ÿæœç´¢ä¸€ä¸‹ä»–å€‘çš„æ”¯æŒå­ï¼Œç™¼ç¾ä»–å€‘ç¶“å¸¸é€™æ¨£åšï¼Œè€Œä¸”é¡¯ç„¶ä»–å€‘æ˜¯åœ¨é€ƒé¿ã€‚]]></title><description><![CDATA[æˆ‘æŠŠETHå¾žä¸€å€‹æˆ‘ç”¨éŽå¾ˆå¤šæ¬¡çš„åœ°å€å­˜å…¥æˆ‘çš„CBåœ°å€ï¼Œæˆ‘å·²ç¶“ç”¨éŽå¾ˆå¤šæ¬¡äº†ã€‚
æˆ‘å·²ç¶“ä½¿ç”¨äº†å¾ˆå¤šæ¬¡ï¼Œæ²’æœ‰ä»»ä½•å•é¡Œã€‚å­˜æ¬¾æ˜¯åœ¨2021å¹´è–èª•ç¯€é‚£å¤©é€²è¡Œçš„ã€‚

æˆ‘æ”¶åˆ°äº†é€šå¸¸çš„CBé›»å­éƒµä»¶ï¼Œèªªä»–å€‘æ”¶åˆ°äº†æˆ‘çš„å­˜æ¬¾ï¼Œä¸¦ä¸”Txæ˜¯
åœ¨Etherscanä¸Šç¢ºèªã€‚

é€™äº›ç¡¬å¹£å¾žæœªè¢«æ”¾å…¥æˆ‘çš„æŠ•è³‡çµ„åˆã€‚

I...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sode68/coinbase_have_stolen_my_eth_deposit_and_ignored/?score=855&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsode68%2Fcoinbase_have_stolen_my_eth_deposit_and_ignored%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsode68%2Fcoinbase_have_stolen_my_eth_deposit_and_ignored%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sode68/coinbase_have_stolen_my_eth_deposit_and_ignored/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 15:37:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I deposited ETH, from an address I have used many times, to my CB address I have used many times without issues. Deposit made on Christmas day 2021.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I got the usual CB email saying they&amp;amp;#39;d received my deposit, and the tx is confirmed on etherscan.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The coins were never put into my portfolio.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I opened a support ticket, and got a vague non-answer by reply (we&amp;amp;#39;re looking into it). It was promptly closed without explanation. I have since opened another 3 tickets which have all been met with similar vague responses, and then the tickets are closed without explanation. My requests to make a complaint have been ignored. I posted on their subreddit 2 weeks ago and got another vague response, no DMs etc.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ve posted there again today but don&amp;amp;#39;t expect much.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My account is not suspended etc., I am still able to transact with existing funds and deposit fiat. I tested this yesterday.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The funny thing is I trade high volume and had I continued using CBP, I would have paid them multiples of the value of this deposit in fees over the next 12 months. Congrats, you played yourselves.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I was able to live with CBP constantly going down during periods of volatility (sus AF!) but this is crossing the line.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;I am purely posting to encourage others to stay away from coinbase and CBP.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; I am not the first person this has happened to. There are literally hundreds of posts like mine on their support sub where people have had funds vanish and the support team just ignores them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Aside from this their fee structure sucks anyway. People seem think CBP is the cheapest for fees but they&amp;amp;#39;re only the cheapest if you trade over $100k per month. I only used them because it was a quick cash onramp from my Revolut account. I&amp;amp;#39;ll be sticking with Binance and Kraken from here on out.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Be careful where you leave your funds.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: Lots of people doubting the legitimacy of my post which I guess is healthy skepticism. When I get home from work I will redact my personal details and edit in links to my (very one sided) correspondence with Coinbase.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ä¿„ç¾…æ–¯å°‡æ‰¿èªæ¯”ç‰¹å¹£çˆ²è²¨å¹£]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sob3c0/russia_to_recognize_bitcoin_as_currency/?score=554&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsob3c0%2Frussia_to_recognize_bitcoin_as_currency%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsob3c0%2Frussia_to_recognize_bitcoin_as_currency%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sob3c0/russia_to_recognize_bitcoin_as_currency/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 15:37:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[æ‹–è»Šå…¬å¸æ‹’çµ•æ‹–èµ°å µå¡žæ¸¥å¤ªè¯çš„å¤§å¡è»Š 
https://t.co/0uo4EI7XMX]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491400537606361088/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491400537606361088/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 14:37:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[æ³•å®˜å‘½ä»¤æ¸¥å¤ªè¯è­¦æ–¹å°‡æ²’æ”¶çš„ç‡ƒæ–™æ­¸é‚„çµ¦å¡è»Šå¸æ©Ÿã€‚]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491399794778341379/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491399794778341379/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 14:37:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ä¿„ç¾…æ–¯ä¸æœƒç¦æ­¢åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£ï¼Œè€Œæ˜¯å°å…¶é€²è¡Œç›£ç®¡ä¸¦å°‡å…¶ä½œçˆ²è²¨å¹£å°å¾…]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/so8ys0/russia_wont_ban_cryptocurrencies_will_regulate/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fso8ys0%2Frussia_wont_ban_cryptocurrencies_will_regulate%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fso8ys0%2Frussia_wont_ban_cryptocurrencies_will_regulate%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/so8ys0/russia_wont_ban_cryptocurrencies_will_regulate/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 14:31:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ä¿„ç¾…æ–¯æ”¿åºœå’Œä¿„ç¾…æ–¯éŠ€è¡Œå·²åŒæ„åƒç›£ç®¡è²¨å¹£ä¸€æ¨£ç›£ç®¡åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£ï¼Œè€Œä¸æ˜¯è³‡ç”¢]]></title><description><![CDATA[ä¿„ç¾…æ–¯éŠ€è¡Œå¸Œæœ›ä¿„ç¾…æ–¯æ”¿åºœå®£ä½ˆä½¿ç”¨
åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£åœ¨ä¿„ç¾…æ–¯æ˜¯éžæ³•çš„ï¼Œä½†ä¸æ˜¯ç¦æ­¢ä½¿ç”¨
ä½†ä¿„ç¾…æ–¯æ”¿åºœå’Œä¿„ç¾…æ–¯éŠ€è¡Œä¸¦æ²’æœ‰ç¦æ­¢ä½¿ç”¨åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£ï¼Œè€Œæ˜¯åŒæ„
åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£åœ¨ä¿„ç¾…æ–¯å°‡è¢«è¦–çˆ²è²¨å¹£çš„ä¸€ç¨®é¡žä¼¼ç‰©
å’Œ...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/so7ru7/the_russian_government_and_the_bank_of_russia/?score=374&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fso7ru7%2Fthe_russian_government_and_the_bank_of_russia%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fso7ru7%2Fthe_russian_government_and_the_bank_of_russia%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/so7ru7/the_russian_government_and_the_bank_of_russia/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 14:31:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Bank of Russia wanted the Russian government to declare the use of cryptocurrencies illegal in Russia, but instead of banning the use cryptocurrencies, the Russian government and the Bank of Russian have agreed that cryptocurrencies will be recognized as an analogue of currencies in Russia and they will be regulated as such.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;From this newspaper that is nationally distributed in Russia: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kommersant.ru/doc/5206307&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.kommersant.ru/doc/5206307&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The government and the Bank of Russia have agreed on a future regime for the circulation of cryptocurrencies in Russia: before February 18, they will prepare a draft law on the circulation of digital currencies in the Russian Federation, in which cryptocurrencies are recognized as an analogue of currencies, and not digital financial assets (DFA). Their circulation in the legal sector will be possible only with full identification, through the banking system or licensed intermediaries. Operations equivalent to more than 600 thousand rubles must be declared, transactions outside the legal sector for such amounts will become a criminal offense and an aggravating circumstance under the Criminal Code, fines will be introduced for the illegal acceptance of cryptocurrencies as a means of payment. Mining and related issues of DFA are not affected by the concept within which the project is being prepared.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The government, after meetings with Deputy Prime Minister, Chief of Staff of the White House Dmitry Grigorenko, published the approved &amp;amp;quot;Concept for regulating the mechanisms for organizing the circulation of digital currencies.&amp;amp;quot; Recall that the White House has been discussing the new status of cryptocurrencies and digital currencies in the Russian Federation since the summer of 2021, in January 2021 a road map was created on this issue, the Bank of Russia made a consultative report proposing to ban the circulation of cryptocurrencies in the Russian Federation, the Ministry of Finance - with its own development on this topic. The final concept is mainly based on the positions of the Ministry of Finance.Until February 18, the ministry and the Bank of Russia must formulate either a separate bill or amendments to the law on the CFA and other laws for its implementation.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The details of the &amp;amp;quot;transition period&amp;amp;quot;, as well as mining, are not discussed by the concept. Meanwhile, they are quite important: the regulation of turnover will require quick decisions from cryptocurrency owners - whether they should move into the emerging legal market segment, get rid of such assets, or stay in the illegal sector. The main difference between the concept, which, in fact, implements the Central Bank&amp;amp;#39;s strong distrust of cryptocurrency, is the proposal to develop amendments to the Criminal Code and the Code of Criminal Procedure, according to which evasion of declaring transactions with cryptocurrency will become a criminal offense, and its use will become an aggravating circumstance in other offenses.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The possession of cryptocurrency in the jurisdiction of the Russian Federation and transactions with it (as well as with the dollar) are not prohibited - but only through the &amp;amp;quot;organizer of the digital currency exchange system&amp;amp;quot; (a bank with a universal license) or a p2p exchanger legalized in the Russian Federation. The mode of operation of the legal segment involves the full identification of the client according to banking rules, work taking into account AML / CFT requirements, all information about transactions through the Transparent Blockchain system of Rosfinmonitoring will be available for state control in the same way as transactions with non-cash rubles or foreign currency on bank accounts. The mode of control over transactions with the cryptocurrency of natural persons, however, is described by the concept as not too different from the mode of control over cash transactions with any currency. Most likely, the main argument â€œforâ€ was that in the USA, the EU and Japan they are inclined to the same or to strict bans, as in China, which was also proposed by the Bank of Russia.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So far, the most intriguing is the organization of the legalization of the existing undeclared cryptocurrency, which is not described in the concept. Market participants have no doubts that the possibilities of working with &amp;amp;quot;legal crypto&amp;amp;quot; in the implementation of the concept are adequate. The same part of the owners who prefer to remain in the sector illegal for the jurisdiction of the Russian Federation depends on the future taxation of operations with cryptocurrencies (from the meaning of the concept it follows that it should not differ from the principles of holding foreign currency) and on the rules of legalization. The Ministry of Finance&amp;amp;#39;s estimate of the total amount of crypto assets in the Russian Federation has not changed - it is 12 million crypto wallets with assets worth 2 trillion rubles. It is decidedly unknown whether this figure takes into account the cryptocurrency used in the criminal sector, obviously.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[æœ€æœ‰è¶£çš„æ™‚é–“ç·šæ˜¯ä¿„ç¾…æ–¯åœ¨ç¾Žåœ‹ä¹‹å‰å°±æœ‰ä¸€å€‹ç¾è²¨#æ¯”ç‰¹å¹£ETFï¼Œè€Œæ–¯è«¾ç™»ä¸€ç›´åœ¨æŠ¨æ“Šç¾Žåœ‹ï¼Œèªçˆ²å®ƒä»ç„¶æ˜¯å…¨çƒè‡ªç”±çš„é ˜å°Žè€…ã€‚]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491374635161878532/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491374635161878532/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[æ¯”ç‰¹å¹£æ˜¯å…¨çƒæ€§çš„]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/so4azf/bitcoin_is_global/?score=414&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fso4azf%2Fbitcoin_is_global%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fso4azf%2Fbitcoin_is_global%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/so4azf/bitcoin_is_global/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 12:46:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[æˆ‘å€‘æ€Žéº¼èƒ½èª å¯¦åœ°ç›¸ä¿¡é€™æ¨£ä¸€å€‹è’è¬¬çš„æƒ³æ³•ï¼šä¸€å€‹æœ‰èƒ½åŠ›å…¥ä¾µ10è¬å€‹BTCçš„äººæ±ºå®šå°‡2000å€‹ç§é‘°ä¿å­˜åœ¨......é›²å­˜å„²ä¸­ï¼Ÿåˆå¦‚ï¼Œè¯é‚¦èª¿æŸ¥å±€å¦‚ä½•åŸ·è¡Œæ­·å²ä¸Šæœ€å¤§çš„é‡‘èžæ‰£æŠ¼ï¼Œä»¥ç²å¾—36å„„ç¾Žå…ƒçš„BTCã€‚]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/snxzp1/how_can_we_honestly_believe_the_absurd_notion/?score=341&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsnxzp1%2Fhow_can_we_honestly_believe_the_absurd_notion%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsnxzp1%2Fhow_can_we_honestly_believe_the_absurd_notion%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/snxzp1/how_can_we_honestly_believe_the_absurd_notion/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 12:46:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[å¦‚æžœä½ è¦çŠ¯å¤§éŒ¯ï¼ŒMetamaskæ‡‰è©²è­¦å‘Šä½ ï¼Œå°±åƒä½ çš„åç—…æ¯’è»Ÿä»¶æˆ–ç¶²çµ¡ç€è¦½å™¨æœƒè­¦å‘Šä½ ä¸€æ¨£--é€™èˆ‡é›†ä¸­åŒ–æˆ–åˆ†æ•£åŒ–æ²’æœ‰é—œä¿‚ã€‚]]></title><description><![CDATA[é€™ä¸æ˜¯ä¸€å€‹é—œæ–¼åˆ†æ¬Šæˆ–é›†æ¬Šçš„å•é¡Œã€‚é€™ä¹Ÿæ˜¯
ä¹Ÿä¸åƒ…åƒ…æ˜¯ä¸€å€‹ç°¡å–®çš„ "å¥½ "çš„åŠŸèƒ½ã€‚æƒ³è±¡ä¸€ä¸‹ï¼Œä½ ç€è¦½çš„ç¶²ç«™
æ•…æ„å°‡ä½ çš„I.P.åœ°å€å’Œå…¶ä»–ä¿¡æ¯è³£çµ¦é»‘å®¢å’Œå…¶ä»–
æƒ¡æ„è¡Œçˆ²è€…å¯ä»¥å…¬é–‹çœ‹åˆ°ä½ åœ¨åšä»€éº¼å’Œä½ çš„...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snrvt9/metamask_should_warn_you_if_you_are_about_to_make/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnrvt9%2Fmetamask_should_warn_you_if_you_are_about_to_make%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnrvt9%2Fmetamask_should_warn_you_if_you_are_about_to_make%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snrvt9/metamask_should_warn_you_if_you_are_about_to_make/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 12:46:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This isn&amp;amp;#39;t a question about about decentralization or centralization. This is also more than just a simple nice-to-have feature. Imagine you browse websites that knowingly sell your I.P. address and other information to hackers and other malicious actors can openly see what you&amp;amp;#39;re doing and your physical location on a map. Isn&amp;amp;#39;t that dangerous? Don&amp;amp;#39;t our Anti-virus softwares and web browsers stop us from doing these things? Don&amp;amp;#39;t all windows machines have these installed by default?               &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It feels like this is one of those topics that 5 or 10 years down the road, none of us will be discussing because it&amp;amp;#39;s already been implemented for a long long time. If you guys used the first iterations of the internet where you had to memorize I.P. Addresses because there were no DNS names to get to some places online, then pretty much everyone here would agree that no one would use the internet of the late 80s and early 90s today if it were still the same way.                  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To the people who say, &amp;amp;quot;If you have lots of money in ETH or BTC and you are sending it to an address by mistake, it&amp;amp;#39;s your fuck up and you deserve to lose your money.&amp;amp;quot; You&amp;amp;#39;re missing the point completely. The point is that your antivirus warns you when you are about to make a massive mistake that could lead to something like ransomware, spyware, or trojans getting installed to your PC. I think it would be great to have Metamask fire off an audible warning and a message that says, &amp;amp;quot;The wallet address you are sending funds to is a known contract address and not a hot wallet. The funds you send will not be used by any human being and will be lost forever. Do you wish to continue?&amp;amp;quot; seems fine. Maybe stack it with, something like, &amp;amp;quot;This address is to a known wallet address of an Exchange that suffered a security breach and has ended service to their customers. The funds you send to this wallet address will likely be lost forever.&amp;amp;quot; Not bad...              &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But what if we have someone whose account on an exchange was terminated and then all of the exchanges got together and said, &amp;amp;quot;Let&amp;amp;#39;s make a database of irrecoverable wallet addresses where terminated / irretrievable 0x addresses exist so that users don&amp;amp;#39;t send funds to them by mistake, and let the people at Metamask know this as well.&amp;amp;quot; Sounds like an interesting value proposition.                  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Finally, by improving the way wallets function we are increasing adoption by eliminating one route where users can screw up simply by stopping them from making a mistake and making them double check an address they send funds to.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;                &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;And I almost forgot: To be clear, I am NOT advocating that wallets block transactions at all. If the user is fully aware of what they are doing, then the opus is on them.&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[äººå€‘æƒ³å›žåˆ°éŽåŽ»è³¼è²·BTCï¼Œç„¶è€Œä»–å€‘ç¾åœ¨æ­£åœ¨ç¡è¦ºã€‚]]></title><description><![CDATA[æ¯å€‹äººéƒ½åœ¨è«‡è«–éŒ¯éŽçš„æ©Ÿæœƒï¼Œä½†æœ‰æ™‚æ©Ÿæœƒå°±åœ¨ä»–å€‘é¢å‰ï¼Œä»–å€‘å»æ²’æœ‰åˆ©ç”¨ï¼Œæ²’æœ‰èªè­˜åˆ°ã€‚
æ©Ÿæœƒå°±åœ¨ä»–å€‘é¢å‰ï¼Œä½†ä»–å€‘å»æ²’æœ‰åˆ©ç”¨ï¼Œæ²’æœ‰èªè­˜åˆ°ã€‚
äººå€‘é‚„åœ¨ "åœ¨é€™è£æ’å…¥ä½ æœ€å–œæ­¡çš„ç¡¬å¹£ "ä¸Šç¡è¦ºã€‚å¦‚æžœä½ æƒ³
è²·å…¥BTCæˆ–ETHï¼Œç¾åœ¨å°±åŽ»åšå§! å¦‚æžœä½ æƒ³è²·ADAï¼ŒNANOï¼ŒDOTï¼Œ...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snuhg5/people_wants_to_go_back_in_time_to_buy_btc_yet/?score=314&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnuhg5%2Fpeople_wants_to_go_back_in_time_to_buy_btc_yet%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnuhg5%2Fpeople_wants_to_go_back_in_time_to_buy_btc_yet%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snuhg5/people_wants_to_go_back_in_time_to_buy_btc_yet/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 12:46:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Everyone talks about missed opportunities, but sometimes the opportunities are right in front of them and they fail to take advantage, to recognise them. People are still sleeping on &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;â€insert your favourite coin hereâ€&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;. If you want to buy BTC or ETH, do it now! If you want to buy ADA, NANO, DOT, MONERO, ETH, MATIC, AAVE, ALGO, UNI, LTC or any from the 11,000~ cryptos, do it now !&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sometimes, luck is when opportunity meets preparation. The opportunity of a lifetime has been in front of people for a months if not years now! Many people dismiss crypto because they donâ€™t understand it. Instead of giving an hour of their time to begin learning about the problems that crypto solves.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Stop listening to good olâ€™ banks. They donâ€™t care about you. Be aware, and have clear frame of mind.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Born too late to explore the Earth. Born too early to explore the stars. But born just in time to invest in Cryptocurrency. Donâ€™t hesitate to take opportunities. Itâ€™s your time now !&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[çµ¦æˆ‘çš„è·è˜­è¿½éš¨è€…

ç·Šæ€¥ï¼šç°½ç½²è«‹é¡˜æ›¸ï¼Œè¦æ±‚ç«‹å³å»¢é™¤è·è˜­çš„ç§‘ç¾…ç´ç¥¨ã€‚

1) å¡«å¯«ï¼šå§“åã€é›»å­éƒµä»¶ã€åŸŽå¸‚
2) é€šéŽä½ å°‡æ”¶åˆ°çš„é›»å­éƒµä»¶ç¢ºèª

å·²ç¶“æœ‰80è¬å€‹ç°½åäº†!

æœå‹™å™¨å†æ¬¡ä¸Šç·š
è«‹è½‰ç™¼ðŸ™
https://t.co/2aUGK1VK2A]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491369870889713672/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491369870889713672/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 11:42:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[çˆ†ç‚¸æ€§æ–°èžï¼šæ“šä¿„ç¾…æ–¯ã€Šç”Ÿæ„äººå ±ã€‹å ±é“ï¼Œä¿„ç¾…æ–¯æ”¿åºœå’Œä¸­å¤®éŠ€è¡Œå‰›å‰›å°±åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£é”æˆå”è­°ã€‚

å…©å€‹çµ„ç¹”å°‡æŠŠæ¯”ç‰¹å¹£å’ŒåŠ å¯†è³‡ç”¢ä½œçˆ²è²¨å¹£å°å¾…ã€‚]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491372730901725184/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491372730901725184/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 11:42:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[JUST IN - åŠ æ‹¿å¤§ã€‚è‰¾ä¼¯å¡”çœçœé•·å‚‘æ£®-è‚¯å°¼å®£ä½ˆï¼Œå°‡æ–¼ä»Šæ™šåˆå¤œå–æ¶ˆç–«è‹—è­·ç…§è¨ˆåŠƒã€‚]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491371515085934593/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491371515085934593/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 11:42:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[æ‰¾åˆ°æˆ‘2013å¹´çš„éŒ¢åŒ…]]></title><description><![CDATA[æ‰€ä»¥ç•¶æˆ‘13æ­²çš„æ™‚å€™ï¼Œæˆ‘çž­è§£äº†æ¯”ç‰¹å¹£ä¸¦é–‹å§‹åœ¨æˆ‘çš„éŠæˆ²é›»è…¦ä¸ŠæŒ–ç¤¦ã€‚
é›»è…¦ä¸ŠæŒ–ã€‚ä¸€æ®µæ™‚é–“å¾Œå¤±åŽ»äº†èˆˆè¶£ï¼Œæ¯”ç‰¹å¹£çˆ†ç‚¸äº†ï¼Œæˆ‘æ„Ÿå˜†å¹´è¼•çš„æˆ‘çš„éŒ¯èª¤ã€‚
ç­‰ç­‰

é€šéŽæˆ‘ä»¥å‰çš„è°·æ­Œç¡¬ç›¤ï¼Œæ‰¾åˆ°äº†æˆ‘çš„éŒ¢åŒ…ï¼Œå•é¡Œæ˜¯--æˆ‘å®Œå…¨ä¸çŸ¥é“å¦‚ä½•è¨ªå•å®ƒ/ã€‚
æˆ‘å®Œå…¨ä¸çŸ¥é“å¦‚ä½•è¨ªå•å®ƒ/å¦‚æžœæˆ‘èƒ½è¨ªå•å®ƒã€‚é€™æ˜¯å€‹...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/so8dlp/found_my_wallet_from_2013/?score=504&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fso8dlp%2Ffound_my_wallet_from_2013%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fso8dlp%2Ffound_my_wallet_from_2013%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/so8dlp/found_my_wallet_from_2013/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 10:44:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So when I was 13, I learned about bitcoin and starting mining it on my gaming PC. Lost interest after a while, bitcoin blows up, I lament young meâ€™s error, etc&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Went through my old google drive and found my wallet, problem is - I have absolutely no idea how to access it / if I can access it. Itâ€™s a text file with .aes.json file extension at the end of the title. I know itâ€™s my wallet since thatâ€™s what the document is titled.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Any advice here or is this just a lost cause? I know absolutely nothing about crypto besides surface level knowledge.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit - Rip DMâ€™s&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[å°æ–¼æ¯å€‹ä½¿ç”¨Braveç€è¦½å™¨çš„äººä¾†èªª]]></title><description><![CDATA[ä¸€å€‹æœ¬æœˆç²å¾—12.25å€‹BATçš„äººæœ€è¿‘çš„å¸–å­ç²å¾—äº†ç›¸ç•¶å¤šçš„é—œæ³¨ã€‚
ç‰½å¼•åŠ›ã€‚æˆ‘æ³¨æ„åˆ°ï¼Œè¨±å¤šäººåœ¨è©•è«–ä¸­æåˆ°ä»–å€‘
æ¯å°æ™‚åªæ”¶åˆ°1æˆ–2å€‹æ·»åŠ ã€‚

å¦‚æžœä½ çš„Braveå·²ç¶“æ›´æ–°ï¼Œä½ å¯ä»¥å°Žèˆªåˆ°çŽå‹µè¨­ç½®ï¼ˆåœ¨Braveçš„
çŽå‹µçª—å£ï¼‰ï¼Œä¸¦å¾žé‚£è£...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snh7rs/for_everyone_using_the_brave_browser/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnh7rs%2Ffor_everyone_using_the_brave_browser%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnh7rs%2Ffor_everyone_using_the_brave_browser%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snh7rs/for_everyone_using_the_brave_browser/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 09:32:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Recent post from a person gaining 12.25 BAT this month gained quite some traction. I noticed that many people mentioned in the comments that they are only receiving 1 or 2 adds per hour.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If your Brave is updated you can navigate to Reward Settings (in the Brave Rewards window), and from there click on the icon on the right of Brave Private Ads. This will bring up a menu that lets you specify how many adds per hour you are limited do.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now, I don&amp;amp;#39;t know how it possible to get 12.25 BAT, but I was previously getting close to 1 with being locked to 5 ads per hour. Being locked to 10 should net you close to 2 or even 3 if you are browsing a lot.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Welcome!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ä¿„ç¾…æ–¯å°‡æ‰¿èªåŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£çˆ²ä¸€ç¨®è²¨å¹£å½¢å¼]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/so5z5p/russia_set_to_recognize_crypto_as_a_form_of/?score=447&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fso5z5p%2Frussia_set_to_recognize_crypto_as_a_form_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fso5z5p%2Frussia_set_to_recognize_crypto_as_a_form_of%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/so5z5p/russia_set_to_recognize_crypto_as_a_form_of/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 09:32:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[æˆ‘è®€äº†å‡±è¥¿-ä¼å¾·çš„æ–¹èˆŸæŠ•è³‡å…¬å¸çš„132é  "2022å¹´å¤§æƒ³æ³• "å ±å‘Šã€‚æ‰€ä»¥ä½ ä¸å¿…é€™æ¨£åš]]></title><description><![CDATA[å¦‚æžœä½ ä¸èªè­˜å¥¹ï¼Œå‡±è¥¿-ä¼å¾·æ˜¯ä¸€ä½åŸºé‡‘ç¶“ç†ï¼ˆArk Investï¼‰ï¼Œå¥¹åœ¨2020/21å¹´å› ä¸€ç³»åˆ—éžå¸¸æˆåŠŸçš„æŠ•è³‡/å¸‚å ´æŠ¼æ³¨è€Œå´›èµ·ã€‚
åœ¨ä¸€ç³»åˆ—éžå¸¸æˆåŠŸçš„æŠ•è³‡/å¸‚å ´è³­æ³¨ä¹‹å¾Œï¼Œå¥¹åœ¨2020/21å¹´å¶„éœ²é ­è§’ã€‚

å¥¹æ˜¯é¡›è¦†æ€§æŠ€è¡“çš„å …å®šä¿¡ä»°è€…ã€‚

èªçˆ²æ©Ÿå™¨äººæŠ€è¡“ã€æ˜Žå¤©çš„é›»æ± å’ŒåŸºå› çµ„å­¸ä»¥åŠerm.....ã€‚]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snx7rw/i_read_cathie_woods_ark_invests_132_page_big/?score=338&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnx7rw%2Fi_read_cathie_woods_ark_invests_132_page_big%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnx7rw%2Fi_read_cathie_woods_ark_invests_132_page_big%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snx7rw/i_read_cathie_woods_ark_invests_132_page_big/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 08:35:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you donâ€™t know her, Cathie Wood is a fund manager (Ark Invest) who rose to prominence in 2020/21 after a series of very successful investments/market bets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;She is a strong believer in disruptive technologies.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Think robotics, tomorrowâ€™s batteries and genomics as well as erm.. blockchain technology and is perhaps &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;the most bullish person&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; on crypto.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;She recently predicted that BTC will be worth &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;over $1M by 2030&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, making her perhaps the most bullish person I know.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Allow me to summarize the reportâ€™s highlights on the future of Bitcoin..&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Ark Invest analysts predict that the market capitalization of blockchain technology will reach $49T in 2030.&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thatâ€™s roughly &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;half&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; what the global equities market is worth today ($106T).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cathie Wood predicts that &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;more than half (57%)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; of that market cap will come from Bitcoin alone; believing Bitcoinâ€™s market cap will climb to &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$28T by 2030.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Currently, Bitcoin&amp;amp;#39;s market cap stands at $815B, down from an ATH of around $1.2T.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And this is where she gets her $1M/BTC price point from (more details on that at the end of this post).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;According to Cathie Wood, El Salvadorâ€™s Bitcoin â€œexperimentâ€ is already a resounding success.&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Why?&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; The data &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;speaks volumes.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;# of people in El Salvador with a Bitcoin wallet = &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;3.8 million&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;# of people in El Salvador with a traditional bank account = &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;1.9 million&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The % of eligible citizens with a Bitcoin wallet in El Salvador is 84% as of December 2021, versus 42% with a traditional bank account.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Whatâ€™s more bullish is people are actually using these wallets!&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Bitcoin wallets in El Salvador settled (on average) &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$2M worth of transactions in remittances DAILY&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; as of October 2021.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;On an annual basis, this accounts for roughly &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;12% of ALL remittances sent&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; to El Salvador (total = $6B annually, or &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;2% of El Salvadorâ€™s overall GDP&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Readerâ€™s Note I â€” Remittances are money transfers sent from one party who works abroad to another in their home country (typically family).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;And El Salvador is not alone..&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;2021 was the year that Bitcoinâ€™s annual settlement volume &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;surpassed that of Visaâ€™s.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoinâ€™s total came to a whopping &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$13.1T, or ~120% of Visaâ€™s.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is effectively a &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;5x increase&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; on the previous year ($2.3T in 2020, ~24% of the Visa networkâ€™s).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, is the Bitcoin network becoming more dominated by larger investors with deeper pockets?!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&amp;gt;Well.. probably.&amp;lt;/span&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The average value of each individual transaction in 2021 was $136,555. This is up from $21,590 in 2020, significantly more than the increase in Bitcoinâ€™s price over the same period.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This makes sense as ETFs, countries and companies have all increased their BTC holdings in 2021 and now hold roughly 1.5 million BTC. Or, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;8% of the total circulating supply.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The 5 largest publicly disclosed bitcoin wallets belong to the (1) Grayscale Bitcoin Trust (2) Block One (3) Microstrategy (4) CoinShares and (5) Tesla.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;But what about me, you and the annoying Karen you avoid on the school run?&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Believe it or not, most Bitcoin investors in 2021 were not speculators.&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The number of BTC long term holders has been steadily increasing since 2011, except for a substantial â€œblipâ€ back in 2018. Understandable.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This trend has continued throughout the most recent bull run in 2020/21.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Long term investors now collectively hold &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;13.5m Bitcoin&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, or more than half of all BTC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Readerâ€™s Note II â€” A â€œlong term investorâ€ is defined by Ark Invest as someone who has held their BTC for more than 155 days.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Readerâ€™s Note III â€” Yes, they removed any wallets with â€œdustâ€ BTC from the data.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;So how does Cathie Wood arrive at the $28T BTC market cap by 2030?&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Is she, like all of us, drunk on hopium?&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Iâ€™ll give you the figures and let you make your mind up:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Readerâ€™s Note IV â€” Important For Context..  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Goldâ€™s market capitalization is $10T (2021)  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The global equities market has an overall market capitalization of $106T (2021)  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In their analysis, Ark Invest chose to project BTCâ€™s 2030 market cap using 2021 data rather than â€œ&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;projected&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;â€ 2030 data/guesswork.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now For The Juice:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;BTC will become the new â€œdigital goldâ€ and account for a whopping 50% of goldâ€™s market cap by 2030 â€” or, $5.5T.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;More S&amp;amp;amp;P companies will keep BTC on their balance sheets (like Tesla). Ark Invest estimates 5% of balance sheets will be kept in BTC â€” adding another $4.2T.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Institutions are not far behind and will keep 2.55% of assets in BTC â€” accounting for $4.1T.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;High Net Worth Individuals will dedicate 5% of their portfolios to BTC â€” thatâ€™s another $4.0T right there.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Nation-states will keep 1% of their reserves in BTC â€” providing a further $3.8T in â€œvalueâ€ to the market.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;US Banks will get in on the action too and use BTC for 25% of all inter-bank settlements â€” thatâ€™s another $3.8T.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;BTC will have replaced fiat currencies in emerging markets at a rate of around 10% by 2030 â€” or, $2.8T.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Finally, BTC will account for 50% of all global remittances â€” adding a relatively meagre $0.3T.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&amp;gt;Grand Total = $28.5T (equal to $1.36M/BTC)&amp;lt;/span&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Readerâ€™s Note V â€” For those interested, I personally think some of these numbers are actually conservative especially as (mentioned earlier) theyâ€™re based on 2021 market capitalization rather than â€œprojectedâ€ 2030 market caps.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Obv there is so much more in the report about blockchain tech and DeFi, but I chose to focus on BTC in this post because I, honestly, already doubt anyone will read this considering its length so it doesnâ€™t need to be any longer.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyway, Iâ€™m sorry if I bored you and youâ€™re most welcome if you happened to read and appreciate this post :)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[æˆ‘å€‘åˆé–‹å§‹äº†å°ä¸­åœ‹çš„ç–‘æ…®]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sns6yu/here_we_go_with_the_china_fud_again/?score=319&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsns6yu%2Fhere_we_go_with_the_china_fud_again%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsns6yu%2Fhere_we_go_with_the_china_fud_again%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sns6yu/here_we_go_with_the_china_fud_again/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 06:35:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[æ‹›è˜äººå“¡èªªï¼Œéš¨ç€å·¥äººå€‘é€ƒé›¢è°·æ­Œå’Œäºžé¦¬éœï¼Œè½‰è€ŒæŠ•å‘åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£å’ŒWeb3å‰µæ¥­å…¬å¸ï¼Œç¡…è°·ä¸å†æ˜¯å‰è¡›çš„ç§‘æŠ€å‰æ²¿é™£åœ°ã€‚"ä»–å€‘çš„é£›èºéƒ¨åˆ†æ˜¯çˆ²äº†å„˜æ—©å…Œç¾ä»–å€‘æ‰€èªçˆ²çš„è¡Œæ¥­çš„æœªä¾†ã€‚"]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/so0fg9/silicon_valley_is_no_longer_the_edgy_tech/?score=408&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fso0fg9%2Fsilicon_valley_is_no_longer_the_edgy_tech%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fso0fg9%2Fsilicon_valley_is_no_longer_the_edgy_tech%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/so0fg9/silicon_valley_is_no_longer_the_edgy_tech/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 06:35:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ç¢ºä¿åœ¨è¶…ç´šç¢—å»£å‘Šä¸­å°‹æ‰¾å¾©æ´»ç¯€å½©è›‹ï¼Œé€™å¯èƒ½æ˜¯å€¼å¾—çš„ã€‚]]></title><description><![CDATA[æˆ‘å€‘ä¸€ç›´è½èªªåœ¨å³å°‡åˆ°ä¾†çš„è¶…ç´šç¢—LVIä¸­ï¼Œå°‡æœ‰ä¸€å †å‚³èžä¸­çš„åŠ å¯†å¸‚å ´çš„å•†æ¥­å»£å‘Šã€‚
å‚³èžä¸­ä¾†è‡ªåŠ å¯†å¸‚å ´çš„å»£å‘Šï¼ŒåŒ…æ‹¬ä¾†è‡ªcrypto.com
[https://crypto.com]ï¼Œcoinbaseï¼Œç”šè‡³å¯èƒ½æ˜¯dogecoinã€‚å°æ–¼crypto.com
[https://crypto.com] æœ€æœ‰å¯èƒ½çš„æ˜¯ï¼Œé¦¬ç‰¹-é”è’™å°‡å†æ¬¡å‡ºç¾ã€‚ä½†æ˜¯...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snxksz/make_sure_to_look_for_easter_eggs_during_super/?score=353&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnxksz%2Fmake_sure_to_look_for_easter_eggs_during_super%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnxksz%2Fmake_sure_to_look_for_easter_eggs_during_super%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snxksz/make_sure_to_look_for_easter_eggs_during_super/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 05:38:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We been hearing that the coming  Super Bowl LVI there is going to be a bunch of rumored commercial from the cryptomarket including one from &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://crypto.com&quot;&amp;gt;crypto.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, coinbase and may be even dogecoin .  For &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://crypto.com&quot;&amp;gt;crypto.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; most likely Matt Damon is going to appear again.  But did you know that in the last commercial there was a hidden Easter egg, hidden to the side, below is the image&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/j9tdy8pybog81.png?width=686&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=f528560f443709228ff4478efd79ef796e8f732d&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/j9tdy8pybog81.png?width=686&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=f528560f443709228ff4478efd79ef796e8f732d&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;you see that QR code hidden to the side? Well had you scan that code; it would had taken you to a website which you can register and then get a free airdrop.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyways, this super bow, the entire US is going to be watching and I think speculate that buried in those commercials might be some other hidden easter eggs, may be not QR codes but something else.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I don&amp;amp;#39;t think its going to be much even if there are easter eggs but hey free money and the chance to brag that you found it on your own.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let the hunt begin.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ç¾Žåœ‹å¸æ³•éƒ¨å‰›å‰›æ‰£æŠ¼äº†36å„„ç¾Žå…ƒçš„åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£ï¼Œä¸¦é€®æ•äº†èˆ‡2016å¹´Bitfinexé»‘å®¢æ”»æ“Šæœ‰é—œçš„å…©äººã€‚]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snoqjp/the_us_doj_just_seized_36_billion_in_crypto_and/?score=349&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnoqjp%2Fthe_us_doj_just_seized_36_billion_in_crypto_and%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnoqjp%2Fthe_us_doj_just_seized_36_billion_in_crypto_and%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snoqjp/the_us_doj_just_seized_36_billion_in_crypto_and/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 22:42:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ç¾Žåœ‹å®˜å“¡æŸ¥ç²2016å¹´Bitfinexé»‘å®¢æ”»æ“Šçš„æ¯”ç‰¹å¹£ | è¯é‚¦å®˜å“¡é€±äºŒæŸ¥ç²åƒ¹å€¼ç´„36å„„ç¾Žå…ƒçš„æ¯”ç‰¹å¹£ï¼Œèˆ‡2016å¹´åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£äº¤æ˜“æ‰€Bitfinexè¢«é»‘æœ‰é—œã€‚]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/snosgv/us_officials_seize_bitcoin_from_2016_bitfinex/?score=316&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsnosgv%2Fus_officials_seize_bitcoin_from_2016_bitfinex%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsnosgv%2Fus_officials_seize_bitcoin_from_2016_bitfinex%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/snosgv/us_officials_seize_bitcoin_from_2016_bitfinex/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 22:42:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ç¬¬ä¸‰æ¬¡æ˜¯å€‹å¥½æ©Ÿæœƒï¼Ÿhttps://t.co/tCacirJO9v]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491157645805617152/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1491157645805617152/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 21:40:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Web3/Ethereumç¤¾å€ç›®å‰è¢«ä¸€å ´æ–‡åŒ–æˆ°çˆ­æ‰€åˆ†è£‚ã€‚é€™è£æœ‰ä¸€å€‹æ˜“æ–¼ç†è§£çš„å›žé¡§ã€‚]]></title><description><![CDATA[è‡ªä¸Šé€±æœ«ä»¥ä¾†ï¼Œä»¥å¤ªåŠç¤¾å€å·²ç¶“è¢«ä¸€å ´
å²ç„¡å‰ä¾‹çš„æ–‡åŒ–æˆ°çˆ­ã€‚å…©å€‹é™£ç‡Ÿå·²ç¶“å½¢æˆï¼Œè€Œä¸”æ²’æœ‰è·¡è±¡è¡¨æ˜Ž
ä»–å€‘å¾ˆå¿«å°±æœƒæ‰¾åˆ°å…±åŒé»žã€‚æˆ‘ä¸æœƒç«™åœ¨é€™
å› çˆ²æˆ‘åªæƒ³è®“äººå€‘çž­è§£é€™å€‹å•é¡Œã€‚

é‚£éº¼......åˆ°åº•æ˜¯ä»€éº¼......ï¼Ÿ]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snmrp5/the_web3ethereum_community_is_currently_divided/?score=375&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnmrp5%2Fthe_web3ethereum_community_is_currently_divided%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnmrp5%2Fthe_web3ethereum_community_is_currently_divided%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snmrp5/the_web3ethereum_community_is_currently_divided/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 20:33:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Since last weekend, the Ethereum community has been torn apart by an unprecedented culture war. Two camps have formed, and there is no indication that they will find common ground anytime soon. I will not take side with this post, as I only want to inform people of this issue.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;So... What exactly is going on?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One of the pillars of the Web3 movement is the Ethereum Naming Service (ENS). This is a way to associate a public address with an easy-to-remember address; rather than telling your friend to send ether to you at 0x1234abcd..., for example, you tell them to send that to &amp;amp;quot;yourname.eth&amp;amp;quot;. It may not matter much today, but this protocol is a part of the foundation on which much of Web3 is built.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One of ENS&amp;amp;#39;s most influential developers, Brantly Millegan, has made some very controversial tweets about homosexuality, trans people, masturbation and pornography. Brantly is a practicing Catholic, and he has stated that all of these things are &amp;amp;quot;evil&amp;amp;quot;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;People in the community asked him to withdraw his words and apologize, which he refused.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Why did the situation escalate?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Soon, two camps were formed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On the one hand, those who believe that Brantly can say whatever he wants, since it is his freedom of speech. These people do not necessarily endorse his positions, but they defend his right to express them. They argue that the essence of Web3 is permissionless. In their view, nobody should be cancelled for their personnal beliefs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On the other hand, there are those who believe that Brantly views are dangerous and hurtful to members of the community who are gay, transgender, or who use pornography. They are afraid that, as a public figure in the Web3 community, Brantly will scare away a lot of people with his opinions.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We have all the ingredients for a good old-fashioned &amp;amp;quot;wokeness versus free speech&amp;amp;quot; conflict.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What are the consequences of the dispute?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Brantly was removed from his position by the organization that manages ENS. Some of the &amp;amp;quot;free speech&amp;amp;quot; fringe reacted by selling their ENS tokens, and some even gave up their .eth domain entirely.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On its side, the &amp;amp;quot;woke&amp;amp;quot; fringe hopes that such incidents will not happen again. They are gathered under the name &amp;amp;quot;ENS is for everyone&amp;amp;quot;, and they militate for Web3 to be a safe space for everyone.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What&amp;amp;#39;s next?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I don&amp;amp;#39;t know, and nobody knows. But this first culture war is a great test to determine the values of Web3. Do we want it to be a bastion of free speech, or do we want it to be a welcoming place for everyone? The next few weeks are gonna be interesting, that&amp;amp;#39;s for sure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thanks for reading, and I hope you learned something from me today! What do you think about all this?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT : &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Please be respectful in your comments, the discussion will be of better quality that way.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[åœ¨BTCçˆ²900ç¾Žå…ƒæ™‚å°‡å…¶æ‰€æœ‰è³‡é‡‘æŠ•å…¥åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£çš„å®¶åº­å·²ç¶“æ¬åˆ°äº† "æ¯”ç‰¹å¹£å¤©å ‚ "è‘¡è„ç‰™ï¼Œå› çˆ²é‚£è£æœ‰0%çš„åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£ç¨…ã€‚]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snp0ke/the_family_that_put_all_its_money_into_crypto/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnp0ke%2Fthe_family_that_put_all_its_money_into_crypto%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnp0ke%2Fthe_family_that_put_all_its_money_into_crypto%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snp0ke/the_family_that_put_all_its_money_into_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 20:33:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[èªªæœæˆ‘çš„æœ‹å‹åœ¨100,000ç¾Žå…ƒä¹‹å‰è³¼è²·æ¯”ç‰¹å¹£]]></title><description><![CDATA[" é€™æ˜¯å¾ˆæœ‰å¯èƒ½çš„" ðŸ¤“ä»–çš„æå¤±åæ­£ðŸ˜‚

https://preview.redd.it/ob73r2u0ykg81.png?width=899&format=png&auto=webp&s=508c9bb03143d7ae9eb679f337db10b5e5b5e2ae]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sngeoe/convincing_my_friend_to_buy_bitcoin_before_100000/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsngeoe%2Fconvincing_my_friend_to_buy_bitcoin_before_100000%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsngeoe%2Fconvincing_my_friend_to_buy_bitcoin_before_100000%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/sngeoe/convincing_my_friend_to_buy_bitcoin_before_100000/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 19:32:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot; This is very possible &amp;amp;quot; ðŸ¤“ his loss anyway ðŸ˜‚&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ob73r2u0ykg81.png?width=899&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=508c9bb03143d7ae9eb679f337db10b5e5b5e2ae&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/ob73r2u0ykg81.png?width=899&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=508c9bb03143d7ae9eb679f337db10b5e5b5e2ae&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[åŠ æ‹¿å¤§å¡è»Šå¸æ©Ÿè»ŠéšŠç¹žéŽGoFundMeçš„é™åˆ¶ï¼Œç”¨æ¯”ç‰¹å¹£ç±Œé›†äº†45è¬ç¾Žå…ƒä»¥ä¸Šçš„è³‡é‡‘]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snop25/canadian_trucker_convoy_raises_450000_using/?score=520&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnop25%2Fcanadian_trucker_convoy_raises_450000_using%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnop25%2Fcanadian_trucker_convoy_raises_450000_using%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snop25/canadian_trucker_convoy_raises_450000_using/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 18:40:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[çœŸçš„å—Žï¼Ÿ]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/snflu2/true/?score=317&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsnflu2%2Ftrue%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsnflu2%2Ftrue%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/snflu2/true/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 18:40:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[è©¦åœ–æ“ºè„«æ³•å®šè²¨å¹£é«”ç³»å°±åƒ......ã€‚]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/snobpw/trying_to_get_off_the_fiat_monetary_system_be_like/?score=517&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsnobpw%2Ftrying_to_get_off_the_fiat_monetary_system_be_like%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsnobpw%2Ftrying_to_get_off_the_fiat_monetary_system_be_like%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/snobpw/trying_to_get_off_the_fiat_monetary_system_be_like/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 18:40:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[æœ‰æ²’æœ‰äººï¼Ÿ]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/snfprq/anyone/?score=330&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsnfprq%2Fanyone%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsnfprq%2Fanyone%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/snfprq/anyone/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 17:34:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[å¦‚æžœä½ æƒ³åœ¨æ—¥é–“äº¤æ˜“ä¸­è³ºéŒ¢ï¼Œå…ˆè©¦è©¦é€™å€‹ã€‚]]></title><description><![CDATA[åœ¨ç´™é¢ä¸Šé€²è¡Œæ—¥é–“äº¤æ˜“ï¼Œè‡³å°‘æœ‰ä¸€å€‹æœˆç”šè‡³æ›´é•·æ™‚é–“ã€‚(æ²’æœ‰å¯¦éš›é€²è¡Œ
äº¤æ˜“ï¼‰ã€‚

å¹¾å¹´å‰æˆ‘å¾—åˆ°äº†é€™å€‹å»ºè­°ï¼Œä½†æ²’æœ‰è½é€²åŽ»ï¼Œçµæžœä¸‹è·Œäº†50%ã€‚

é€™è½èµ·ä¾†å¾ˆå¥‡æ€ªï¼Œä½†å®ƒæœƒå‘Šè¨´ä½ é€™æ˜¯å¤šéº¼çš„å›°é›£å’Œä¸å¯é æ¸¬ï¼Œå°¤å…¶æ˜¯åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£ã€‚
å°¤å…¶æ˜¯åŠ å¯†è²¨å¹£ã€‚

å¾žå­—é¢ä¸Šçœ‹ï¼Œä½ å¯ä»¥å¯«ä¸‹æ¯ä¸€ç­†äº¤æ˜“ï¼Œä½ æœƒ...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snle9h/if_you_want_to_make_money_day_trading_try_this/?score=364&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnle9h%2Fif_you_want_to_make_money_day_trading_try_this%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsnle9h%2Fif_you_want_to_make_money_day_trading_try_this%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/snle9h/if_you_want_to_make_money_day_trading_try_this/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 17:34:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Day trade on paper for at least a month or even longer. (Without actually making the trades)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I got this advice a few years ago but didn&amp;amp;#39;t listen and was down 50%.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It sounds odd, but it&amp;amp;#39;ll show you how hard and unpredictable it is, especially with crypto.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Literally write every trade you would have made with your crypto and see if you&amp;amp;#39;re really in the green after at least a month.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This will be a great way to learn you can&amp;amp;#39;t always time the market but without losing a big chunk of your money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m not saying day trading isn&amp;amp;#39;t possible, but make your mistakes on paper first.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>