<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[加密貨幣國外熱門討論]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 23:32:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[律師問題：如果一個假設國家的Trias Politica被打破了怎麼辦？當行政權力授予自己永恆的緊急權力時。當立法權被愚弄或賄賂以通過緊急法律時。當司法權因此被繞過時。是否有法律上的補救措施？https://t.co/b8ZPnG3aFu]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1479217211617198088/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1479217211617198088/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 22:44:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1.6.22: 英國所有成人羣體中，完全接種疫苗者的感染率現在比未接種疫苗者的感染率要高，而且上升得更快。所有年齡段的接種疫苗者和未接種疫苗者都繼續受到感染和傳播--在大多數年齡段，接種疫苗者的感染率更高--使得接種疫苗的護照和強制規定毫無意義。https://t.co/wLXWLkurlf]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1479205638223933446/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1479205638223933446/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 21:46:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[昨天，一個僞裝成投資者的 "發現 "的騙子/洗盤手發了一個帖子，直接射到了這個子的頂部]]></title><description><![CDATA[1月5日，有網友在加密貨幣這裏發了一個關於新的NFT遊戲的帖子
他們 "發現了"。該遊戲在Binance智能鏈上有自己的代幣。


該帖子在被刪除之前就被管理員迅速而正確地刪除了。
但在它登上本子的頭版之前，就被管理員迅速而正確地刪除了。

在...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxfs5n/yesterday_a_scammershiller_who_masqueraded_as_an/?score=307&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxfs5n%2Fyesterday_a_scammershiller_who_masqueraded_as_an%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxfs5n%2Fyesterday_a_scammershiller_who_masqueraded_as_an%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxfs5n/yesterday_a_scammershiller_who_masqueraded_as_an/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 21:45:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On January 5, a user made a post here on cryptocurrency about a new NFT game they “discovered”. The game has its own token on the Binance Smart Chain.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;The post was swiftfully and rightfully deleted by the mods before it could do much damage, but not before it got to the frontpage of this sub.&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In fact, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/fEuukUf.png&quot;&amp;gt;the post made it to the top&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Right off the bat, this was extremely suspicious because:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Upvotes are still hidden which means it’s a very new post&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;It got to the top 8 posts of the sub when it was half an hour old then quickly kept going up from there&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;It only had a few comments and more than ⅓  of them were from the OP&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Normally when a very young post makes it to the top of the frontpage, it has an insane level of engagement and high variety comments from other users gained in a super short time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But this was not the case here.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;I come from a marketing background and know firsthand how easy it is to “hack” social media platforms like reddit to make something go viral artificially.&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Coincidentally a few months ago, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://np.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/pqnd3s/i_did_a_little_digging_on_the_latest_shitcoin/&quot;&amp;gt;I also found a network of paid accounts&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and bot accounts on reddit that crypto scammers use to boost their rugpull posts of new coins (you know the ones with titles like 🚀🚀 Anal Inu Coin 🚀🚀🌕 🌕).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So just from the points above, I was 95% sure it was just a lost rugpuller who probably meant to post it on the other less-moderated crypto subreddits.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But no.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This rugpuller had the audacity to pretend to be a new investor who had just “discovered” an amazing gem, so I wanted to dig a little more.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Checking the user behind the post sealed the deal as a bought-for shiller&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here’s a screenshot of their &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/SkkTfjr&quot;&amp;gt;post history&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/cblIPdB&quot;&amp;gt;comment history&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;More suspicious things pop up here that says: this is 100% not a genuine person and this was not a genuine post:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Account had 0 post activity in 3 years&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Also 0 comment activity in 1 year&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Absolutely no crypto-related content in any comments of posts in the history of the account&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Despite all that, the account comes out of the shadows and suddenly starts making posts about a new crypto game in multiple places.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Let&amp;amp;#39;s look at their post and how they masqueraded as an innocent user who just wanted to share their discovery&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here are &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/TfhgkgH.png&quot;&amp;gt;direct quotes from the post&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; before it was deleted:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;“Hey guys, just wanted to let you all know about this new Crypto Game called &amp;amp;quot;Moonscape&amp;amp;quot;.”&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This first sentence of the post is not the language of someone who just discovered a game. This is the script of someone making a promotional video.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;“It is the first game launched on the Seascape Lighthouse IDO project, but made by a very successful team. Definitely worth checking out and for sure can 100X very quickly.”&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve read a lot of DDs and research pieces on this sub, and the only posts that compliment the devs but don’t give names or examples of what the devs actually accomplished are scam posts.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you look at how genuine newbies post and talk here, they all ask if a project is legit. They don’t confidently guarantee lambos.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;“Moonscape is a resource strategy management #DeFi NFT Game that takes place on a futuristic moon. Players scramble for limited resources to develop their burgeoning cities.”&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The only people who use hashtags in new coin posts are the rugpullers behind the new coin.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;*“The game will be brower based, with phone apps coming later in the year. Direct payment to moonscape token will also be availble in the game at a later date the devs have stated. Please keep an eye out for this one, its going to be masive.”
*
More marketing-derived language.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Besides, if the game hasn’t launched yet how did the user discover it? Lmao&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;“MSCP Token is a BSC token and availble on Pancake swap, but i think the native token is on the Moonriver network. You can use the meter.passport to swap fro m BSC to moonriver which will enable you to stake the coins. I believe staking is around 70% at the moment, and you can take your coins out whenever you want without penalty. Moonriver is part of the Moonbeam network on Kusama I belive.”&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;More language that looks lifted from a brochure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This time they added “I think” and “I believe” because they’re a third party and totally not affiliated with it. They’re 100% impartial and are just guessing things. Sure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;“Id be happy to answer any questions if you have any as well :)”*&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They got their message mixed up here in the end.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What kind of new investor who just discovered a “massive” project is confident enough to take questions? If they know so much, why did they talk about the specifics in the previous section with such uncertainty?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;They also kept up the charade in the comments and had lots of replies to innocent users&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do these sound like they came from someone who’s impartial to the completely new not launched yet project they just discovered?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/9qblSaW.png&quot;&amp;gt;OP sure knows a lot about this game&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; that hasn’t launched yet for someone who’s not involved in it&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Telling people to &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/5k07B43.png&quot;&amp;gt;send you PMs&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; is always a sure fire way to convince them you’re not a scammer yes&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Apparently &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/gCtmbMc.png&quot;&amp;gt;100x returns is realistic and genuine&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It’s honestly hilarious.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It’s like they started with a genius idea to pretend to be a normal person, but abandoned it halfway through their post then went all in on shilling in the comments.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;TLDR&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Scammers, shillers, rugpullers have a network of accounts to boost their posts to the top of subreddits, including here on /cryptocurrency.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Be mindful of the language in the post and look into the user before you believe anything.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[紅色的日子是真正的FOMO，但你們需要控制自己。]]></title><description><![CDATA[價格下降了，而你卻買不到？

你是否感到害怕錯過了一個好的購買機會？

是的，那麼你們應該控制自己。人們會告訴你要買入下跌的股票
他們可能是對的，但你的投資不應該被恐懼心理所驅動。

如果你有一個計劃，就堅持你的計劃。如果你...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxb7hg/red_days_are_the_true_fomo_but_you_need_to/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxb7hg%2Fred_days_are_the_true_fomo_but_you_need_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxb7hg%2Fred_days_are_the_true_fomo_but_you_need_to%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxb7hg/red_days_are_the_true_fomo_but_you_need_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 20:45:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Prices are down, and you can&amp;amp;#39;t buy? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do you feel the fear of missing out a good buying opportunity? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Yeah, then you should control yourselves. People will tell you to buy the dip and they may be right BUT your investments shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t be driven by FOMO. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you have a plan, stick to your plan. If you have money to invest in red times, spread the sell orders and don&amp;amp;#39;t throw too much at the market. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Don&amp;amp;#39;t invest more than you can afford to lose. This is even more true during red days. The opportunity seems very good but you never know the bottom of the dip. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please act rationally and not with your emotions. DCAing doesn&amp;amp;#39;t mean throwing money at dips in hope that the market goes back up. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You don&amp;amp;#39;t need to buy every dip, in the end consistency is more rewarded. Good luck out there!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這到底是怎麼回事？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我觀察股市、加密貨幣市場和貴金屬市場已經5年左右了。
過去5年左右。我總是發現有一件事很吸引人，那就是這些市場一起移動的方式。
最常見的例子是，一個市場上升，另一個市場下降，而第三個市場沒有任何值得注意的地方。
最常見的例子是，一個市場上升，另一個市場下降，而第三個市場沒有任何值得注意的事情。

由於這整個GME...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxefap/wtf_is_going_on/?score=367&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxefap%2Fwtf_is_going_on%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxefap%2Fwtf_is_going_on%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxefap/wtf_is_going_on/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 20:45:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Ive watched the stock market, crypto market, and precious metal market for a the past 5ish years. One thing I always found fascinating is the way the markets move together, most common example, one going up while another goes down and the third not doing anything noteworthy.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Since this whole GME thing last year, I’ve watch the crypto and stock markets move almost in tandem with each other, but metals markets still did their independent thing…until lately. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;All three markets are down and look like they are starting to Synchronize and start moving in tandem. And I will tell you I don’t know what it means but it scares the hell out of me.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我在2022年的目標是達到0.1 BTC]]></title><description><![CDATA[雖然不多，但這是一個誠實的目標。將會堆積起來]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rx2ekf/my_goal_for_2022_is_to_get_to_01_btc/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frx2ekf%2Fmy_goal_for_2022_is_to_get_to_01_btc%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frx2ekf%2Fmy_goal_for_2022_is_to_get_to_01_btc%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rx2ekf/my_goal_for_2022_is_to_get_to_01_btc/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 19:34:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It ain&amp;amp;#39;t much but it&amp;amp;#39;s an honest goal. Gonna stack!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[偉大的重新調整：瞭解我們所處的位置和我們要去的地方]]></title><description><![CDATA[2021年11月10日，比特幣達到了69,000美元左右的高點。在我打字的時候。
目前的價格是42,948美元。但這篇文章不是關於價格的。它是關於
我們所處的位置和我們的方向，從4年的減半到減半的週期來看
週期。

我們幾乎是在下一次減半的中途。

你可能...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rx4tt1/the_great_readjustment_understanding_where_we_are/?score=315&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frx4tt1%2Fthe_great_readjustment_understanding_where_we_are%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frx4tt1%2Fthe_great_readjustment_understanding_where_we_are%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rx4tt1/the_great_readjustment_understanding_where_we_are/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 19:34:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On November 10th, 2021, Bitcoin reached a high around $69,000.  As I type this, the current price is $42,948.  But this post isn&amp;amp;#39;t about the price.  It&amp;amp;#39;s about where we are and where we&amp;amp;#39;re headed, in terms of the 4 year halving-to-halving cycle.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;We&amp;amp;#39;re almost halfway to the next Halving.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You probably know what the halving is.  Let&amp;amp;#39;s talk about the effect the halving has.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Every ten minutes, a miner wins a block reward, and that&amp;amp;#39;s a big deal because block rewards are the only way new Bitcoin is created.  Right now, the block reward is 6.25 BTC.  Thus, every ten minutes, 6.25 BTC is created and awarded to a miner.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In May 2024, the block reward will be cut in half, to 3.125 BTC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That doesn&amp;amp;#39;t sound like a big change unless you&amp;amp;#39;re a miner, but add up the block rewards over time and you&amp;amp;#39;ll see how much of a difference the halving makes on the supply of newly mined coins hitting the market:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;6.25 BTC are mined every ten minutes (roughly).  This is the current block reward.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;6.25 X 6 = 37.5 BTC are mined every hour.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;37.5 X 24 = 900 BTC are mined every day.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;900 X 30 = 27,000 BTC are mined every month.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;27,000 X 4 = 108,000 BTC are mined every four months.  I use four months as a reference point here because it takes around four months for the halving to cause an imbalance of supply and demand, better known as a supply shock.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;The Supply Shock Of 2024:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In May 2024, the halving will cut the block reward in half, from 6.25 BTC down to 3.125 BTC.  Price is where supply meets demand, and the halving cuts the supply of new coins in half.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;By the beginning of fall, 2024, instead of having 108,000 BTC added to the supply since May, only 54,000 will have been added (because The Halving cut the block reward in half).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That decrease is what causes a supply shock.  The supply drops, which means there won&amp;amp;#39;t be enough supply to meet the demand, which means the price will keep rising until demand drops enough to put supply and demand in balance again.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here&amp;amp;#39;s an easy way to understand a supply shock:  Imagine that you have to attend a huge meeting every morning for a week.  Luckily, they provide enough coffee for everybody.  But one day, there&amp;amp;#39;s only half as much coffee.  The supply of coffee was cut in half but the demand is still the same, so there&amp;amp;#39;s not enough.  People are getting pissed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the marketplace, price is set by demand.  When the supply of BTC being sold goes down, the price keeps going up until there isn&amp;amp;#39;t enough demand to buy it at a higher price.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Price is where supply meets demand:  how much is being sold and how much are buyers willing to pay.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But we all know it isn&amp;amp;#39;t that simple in reality.  In 2024, miners will start hoarding coins instead of selling them, because they anticipate higher prices.  This will make the supply shock worse because it will drop the supply of coins being sold even lower.  And rising prices causes hype, which will drive demand even higher, which will push prices even higher.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;But It Ain&amp;amp;#39;t 2024 Yet!&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A typical halving-to-halving four year cycle looks like this:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Halving, followed by around 4 months of hoarding, where people hold on to their coins rather than sell them, anticipating higher prices.  This is followed by a bull run of around a year and a crash that goes on for a few months, which is followed by a roughly 2 year period of readjustment that lasts until the next halving.  I think we&amp;amp;#39;re somewhere between the crash and readjustment phase now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Maybe we&amp;amp;#39;ll see a crash, maybe we won&amp;amp;#39;t.  Institutional money may have disrupted the usual post-bull-run crash, or at least lessened it.  Or not.  Only time will tell.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s easy to feel despair as the price of Bitcoin drops, but I view this as an opportunity.  I think you should too.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just as the last 4 year cycle was the last chance to buy at 4 digit prices, this 4 year cycle may be the last chance to buy at 5 digit prices.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is the time to accumulate.  Buy while you can and hold, because 2024 will be here before you know it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Secure your coins, preferably in a hardware wallet.  Make sure your seed phrase is secured for the long haul.  Have a plan in place for passing on your coins if you die...  just in case.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;P.S.:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If declining prices are causing you anguish, walk away for a while.  Don&amp;amp;#39;t sell, but DO stop checking the price and reading forums and the news if doing so causes you more pain than pleasure.  Take care of your mental health.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;KEEP CALM&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
AND&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
HODL ON&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(Sorry for the edit.  I wrote this rather quickly &amp;amp;amp; I found a typo)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這個人有一種神奇的技能，可以預測你應該去哪裏買更多的比特幣。去吧，HODL]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rxi8g3/this_guy_has_a_magical_skill_to_predict_where_you/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frxi8g3%2Fthis_guy_has_a_magical_skill_to_predict_where_you%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frxi8g3%2Fthis_guy_has_a_magical_skill_to_predict_where_you%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rxi8g3/this_guy_has_a_magical_skill_to_predict_where_you/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 19:34:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[法國總統馬克龍：500萬未接種疫苗的公民是 "非公民"。
加拿大總理特魯多：未接種疫苗的人是 "厭惡女人和amp；種族主義者 "的極端分子。
拜登總統：這種流行病是未接種疫苗者的大流行病。

進步的領導力是否需要妖魔化對方？]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1479094775475179520/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1479094775475179520/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:47:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對@100trillionUSD的採訪現在正在首播! 🚀🚨
關於。
- S2F模型
- 模式的失敗
- 他有爭議的推文
- 推特上的街區
- 經濟戰爭
- 新繁榮
- 離開荷蘭。

在這裏查看他的情況 👉🏻 https://t.co/nWRrUDuGNl https://t.co/YgMZlFjOLN]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1479118366837149697/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1479118366837149697/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:47:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[生物安全監控制度，荷蘭版2022。https://t.co/tcXIgIJznV]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1479116640566476803/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1479116640566476803/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:47:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你準備好爲2022年的整個過程而不顧結果，放棄你的一切了嗎？如果沒有，你可能要重新考慮你的立場。]]></title><description><![CDATA[個人解毒劑；4月份，我問我哥哥是否持有任何加密貨幣。他
他說有，他賣了一些Eth，賺了幾百塊。我告訴他不能賣，只能
持有。他說他是 "機會主義"，"沒有鑽石手"。- 就在
上週我們一起開車，他說'所有...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxa8er/are_you_ready_to_hodl_everything_you_have_for_the/?score=558&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxa8er%2Fare_you_ready_to_hodl_everything_you_have_for_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxa8er%2Fare_you_ready_to_hodl_everything_you_have_for_the%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxa8er/are_you_ready_to_hodl_everything_you_have_for_the/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:47:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Personal antidote; in April I asked my older brother if he held any crypto. He said yes, that he sold some Eth and made a few hundred. I told him no sell only hold. He said he was &amp;amp;#39;opportunistic&amp;amp;#39; and &amp;amp;#39;didn&amp;amp;#39;t have diamond hands&amp;amp;#39;.  - Just last week we were driving in the car together and he said &amp;amp;#39;All my crypto now are ten year holds&amp;amp;#39; and I could have cried out of happiness.       &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Volatility scares people, and we all have to respect that. It will take time for people to come around and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://thumbs.dreamstime.com/b/bitcoin-cryptocurrency-import-big-data-animation-abstract-rainbow-spot-light-background-223802827.jpg&quot;&amp;gt;see this space for all that it holds&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;; from opportunistic cash grabs to apex dollar hedges, from over leveraged scams to the true start of DAOs that one-day might replace Apple.        &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Nuance is key! Consistency requires you to be as ignorant today as you were a year ago (historian Bernard Berenson said that). Are you still the same hodler you were a year ago?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[第四大BTC地址剛剛增加了43,000個BTC! 這個錢包在其歷史上從未出售過任何一個BTC，現在持有價值近5BN的BTC。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxdehv/the_4th_largest_btc_address_just_added_a_massive/?score=501&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxdehv%2Fthe_4th_largest_btc_address_just_added_a_massive%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frxdehv%2Fthe_4th_largest_btc_address_just_added_a_massive%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rxdehv/the_4th_largest_btc_address_just_added_a_massive/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:47:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你看得越近，你看到的越少]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rxcip4/the_closer_you_look_the_less_you_see/?score=1267&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frxcip4%2Fthe_closer_you_look_the_less_you_see%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frxcip4%2Fthe_closer_you_look_the_less_you_see%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rxcip4/the_closer_you_look_the_less_you_see/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:47:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[第三大比特幣鯨魚錢包今天以43.5千美元的價格又增加了179個BTC，總額爲780萬美元。自12月調整以來，鯨魚每天都會買入BTC低於47000美元。自11月以來，鯨魚共買入13,594個BTC，賣出0個。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx5yq5/the_3rd_largest_bitcoin_whale_wallet_added_179/?score=382&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx5yq5%2Fthe_3rd_largest_bitcoin_whale_wallet_added_179%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx5yq5%2Fthe_3rd_largest_bitcoin_whale_wallet_added_179%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx5yq5/the_3rd_largest_bitcoin_whale_wallet_added_179/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 10:32:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特幣今年前5天下跌了10％。]]></title><description><![CDATA[每隔4年就會有一次討厭的熊市。希望堆積一些便宜的衛星終端
年末的時候 💰]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwyn1x/bitcoin_is_down_10_percent_this_year_in_the_first/?score=364&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwyn1x%2Fbitcoin_is_down_10_percent_this_year_in_the_first%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwyn1x%2Fbitcoin_is_down_10_percent_this_year_in_the_first%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwyn1x/bitcoin_is_down_10_percent_this_year_in_the_first/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 08:44:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Every 4 years there’s a nasty bear market.  Looking to stack some cheap sats end of the year time 💰💰💰&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我不可能是唯一一個認爲大多數 "買跌停板 "的人是在胡說八道的人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在你說OP只是生氣，因爲他是在紅色。我現在很好，處於綠色狀態
即使有90%的閃電崩盤我也不在乎，我只投資我可以承受的
我只投資我能夠承受的損失。

每次出現小幅回調時，這個子網站都會被轟炸成
"你買了跌停板嗎？哦，你最好買...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx6zdf/i_cant_be_the_only_one_who_thinks_that_most_of/?score=419&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx6zdf%2Fi_cant_be_the_only_one_who_thinks_that_most_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx6zdf%2Fi_cant_be_the_only_one_who_thinks_that_most_of%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx6zdf/i_cant_be_the_only_one_who_thinks_that_most_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 08:44:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Before you say OP is just mad because he is in the red: I am well in the green and I don&amp;amp;#39;t care even if there is a 90% flash crash, I only invest what I can afford to lose.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Every single time there there is a small correction this sub gets bombarded with &amp;amp;quot;Did you buy the dip? Oh man you better buy the dip!&amp;amp;quot;, &amp;amp;quot;What coins are you guys buying this dip?&amp;amp;quot;, &amp;amp;quot;Yo, bro I wish the dip was 50% so I could buy more&amp;amp;quot;.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If people in this sub bought the dip as much as they claim to in their posts I am pretty positive we would have ran out of some coins in the market. To me these posts are no different than someone commenting &amp;amp;quot;To the moon&amp;amp;quot;,&amp;amp;quot;When Lambo?&amp;amp;quot; or &amp;amp;quot;Nobody knows shit about fuck&amp;amp;quot;. Low effort bullshit that gets spammed over and over again.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Just buy whatever the fuck you want, at whatever price you want.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[過去24小時內7.25億美元的加密貨幣清算!]]></title><description><![CDATA[在過去24小時內，當我們都在等待突破時，7.25億美元的
美元已經被清算了。

上週處於 "極度恐懼 "的4800點。今天，如果我們達到同樣的價格
點，我們都會看漲。

在我的誠實意見中，我知道這是今年相當粗略的開始，但42,500
價格...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx4fje/725_million_in_crypto_liquidation_in_last_24_hours/?score=449&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx4fje%2F725_million_in_crypto_liquidation_in_last_24_hours%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx4fje%2F725_million_in_crypto_liquidation_in_last_24_hours%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx4fje/725_million_in_crypto_liquidation_in_last_24_hours/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 06:48:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In last 24 hours while we all are waiting for a breakout, $725 million US Dollars have been liquidated. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Last week were in &amp;amp;#39;extreme fear&amp;amp;#39; at 48k. 
Today, if we reach the same price point, we all will be bullish.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In my honest opinion,
I know this is quite a rough start to the year, but 42,500 price point might be our bottom. 
For long term, its always going to go up. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This recent acceleration in sell-side momentum is getting BTC closer to a bullish trend reversal.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On days like this one,
When you cant buy a dip, 
Just keep your phone away from you, eyes off your red candle screens, and do something else today.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Come a back after a day or two. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Have a good day everyone!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto使我對金錢着迷，並改變了我的生活。這也是與一個紅色的投資組合。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直打算做一個體面的人，過着體面的生活
並按規則行事。確保我所做的一切是安全的、經過計算的
而且沒有壓力。就這樣蜿蜒而過，然後死去。這就是生活，你能做什麼？
能做什麼。

然後進入加密貨幣。

我今年29歲，一直在半...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwvpye/crypto_has_made_me_obsessed_about_money_and/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwvpye%2Fcrypto_has_made_me_obsessed_about_money_and%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwvpye%2Fcrypto_has_made_me_obsessed_about_money_and%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwvpye/crypto_has_made_me_obsessed_about_money_and/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 06:48:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I always planned on going through life being a decent man making a decent living and playing by the rules. Making sure everything I did was safe and calculated and non stressful. Just meander through and die. Such is life and what can you do about it. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then enter crypto. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m 29 and have been semi successful. I’ve always been happy with where I was and never super stressed out about anything. Get the 8-5 M-F job. Log off at 5 every day. Go to the gym. Play some videogames. Got married. Was happy. Figured everything would work out as long as I played by the system. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But man has crypto lit a fire under my ass. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve never been super on top of money. Spent it wisely, got a house early. Been ok with it. But after crypto I researched everything constantly. I consolidated old 401ks. Opened an IRA, maxed out my current 401k match. Sold my house because I had a place to be rent free for as long as I needed for a new house and it wasn’t the best neighborhood to be in. Made a nice return on proceeds. Was able to have a dream wedding from it. Invested a good amount of safe money into crypto. Got a crypto.com card for rewards. Got another simple credit card. Boosted my credit from 680 to 720. Did much better at work since I had new motivation and got raises and promotions from. Love working OT because thats more money to have and invest. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Is my portfolio in the red? Again, yes lol. But I don’t care. Playing the long game and getting all my other finances in order has been part of the journey. Couldn’t be happier with where I am at in life now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你不能把它換回法幣，你還會買加密貨幣嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[今天早些時候，我看到有人在這裏評論說，他們絕不會出售他們持有的一些
幣--這沒什麼好奇怪的，每天都有人這麼說。
但這讓我想到：如果你永遠不能把你的加密貨幣賣給法幣，那麼
人們還會買它嗎？

這是一個思想實驗。在這個...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwq3mg/would_you_still_buy_crypto_if_you_couldnt/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwq3mg%2Fwould_you_still_buy_crypto_if_you_couldnt%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwq3mg%2Fwould_you_still_buy_crypto_if_you_couldnt%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwq3mg/would_you_still_buy_crypto_if_you_couldnt/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 05:33:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Earlier today, I saw someone on here commenting that they would &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;never&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; sell some coin they held - nothing too unusual, there are people saying that every day. But it got me thinking: if you &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;could&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; never sell your crypto for fiat, would people still buy it?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;This is a thought experiment.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; In this scenario, you couldn&amp;amp;#39;t exchange crypto for fiat, ever - but it&amp;amp;#39;s not just that exchanges wouldn&amp;amp;#39;t offer it, there would be no loophole (&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;edit: so also no crypto credit/debit cards&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;) for it. You, for some reason, could not find someone to privately sell your coin to for fiat. In this hypothetical world, everything would be the same as now - you could buy crypto with fiat, you could use crypto for their use cases, and you could even use crypto to buy stuff in the few places that enable it - but you could not get fiat for it. This means, you would either have to have a use case for crypto that isn&amp;amp;#39;t &amp;amp;quot;getting more money&amp;amp;quot;, or you would have to speculate on more adoption and more merchants accepting crypto in the future.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Would you still invest in crypto? I&amp;amp;#39;ll be honest: I&amp;amp;#39;m in this to make more fiat, if I couldn&amp;amp;#39;t exhange crypto for fiat I would not invest. What about you?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[然而，價值超過666,000,000的頭寸再次從市場上被抹去。]]></title><description><![CDATA[然而，價值超過650,000,000美元的頭寸再次從市場上被抹去。

其中大部分是多頭頭寸。

在過去24小時內，有175,705名交易員被清算。

最大的單個清算訂單發生在Bitmex - XBTUSD價值10.00萬美元
(該死！)

有趣的是，這一次大多數的...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwyti0/yet_again_over_666000000_worth_of_positions_were/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwyti0%2Fyet_again_over_666000000_worth_of_positions_were%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwyti0%2Fyet_again_over_666000000_worth_of_positions_were%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwyti0/yet_again_over_666000000_worth_of_positions_were/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 05:33:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Yet again over $650,000,000 worth of positions were wiped from the market.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Most of them were long positions.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the past 24 hours, 175,705 traders were liquidated.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The largest single liquidation order happened on Bitmex - XBTUSD value $10.00M (damn!)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Interestingly this time around majority of positions wiped were on Okex and not on Binance. Are Binance users getting smarter?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please remember that trading with leverage is extremely risky and you should not do it unless you are extremely experienced.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/9huz09mq5y981.png?width=1533&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=a58d01efc98a99199a3c047a63732de07661e413&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/9huz09mq5y981.png?width=1533&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=a58d01efc98a99199a3c047a63732de07661e413&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["還有人興奮嗎！？" 不，我沒有。這很糟糕，我毫不介意地說。]]></title><description><![CDATA[它需要幾周的時間在排行榜上慢慢攀升，然後在幾個小時內
我們又回到了幾個月前的位置？是的，這很糟糕。一個事實是
事實上，加密貨幣只是一些富人的遊戲，在美聯儲威脅性的東西出現的一瞬間，他們就會跳出來。
美聯儲的威脅性事件發生時，他們就會跳出來，這很糟糕。事實上，...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwywij/anybody_else_excited_no_im_not_this_sucks_and_i/?score=466&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwywij%2Fanybody_else_excited_no_im_not_this_sucks_and_i%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwywij%2Fanybody_else_excited_no_im_not_this_sucks_and_i%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwywij/anybody_else_excited_no_im_not_this_sucks_and_i/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It takes weeks upon weeks to slowly climb in the charts, then within a few hours it we&amp;amp;#39;re right back to where we were months ago?  Yeah, that blows.  The fact that crypto is just some game for rich people to dip out of the microsecond something threatening from the Fed happens sucks.  The fact that people bought only to see things dip like crazy sucks.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And most importantly - all the people who are curious about crypto, and want to learn more and get in, but then see the prospect of losing 15% of their investment in a couple of hours and avoid crypto like the plague, THAT FUCKIN SUCKS.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sure, buy the dip if you&amp;amp;#39;ve got money, make your trades, come here and make your post assuring everyone everything will be ok and act like we&amp;amp;#39;re all idiots who can&amp;amp;#39;t see you&amp;amp;#39;re just assuring yourself more than anyone.  I&amp;amp;#39;m not impressed anymore.  It&amp;amp;#39;s fine for all of us to be bummed about this, and it would be great if this subreddit was a place that didn&amp;amp;#39;t make anyone who felt that way feel like some kind of stupid investor for having those feelings.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;edit&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;:  alright I&amp;amp;#39;m disabling inbox replies now.  Nothing new being said, my responses are clear, and there&amp;amp;#39;s now countless comments doing exactly the very thing I called out.  All I&amp;amp;#39;ll say is if you&amp;amp;#39;re feeling bummed today, you&amp;amp;#39;re not stupid, you&amp;amp;#39;re not a bad investor, and it &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;absolutely does not mean you should leave crypto.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;  It&amp;amp;#39;s a normal reaction and having that feeling isn&amp;amp;#39;t the same as throwing in the towel and giving up.  Peace&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["德國的銀行告訴客戶將他們的錢帶到其他地方，因爲客戶必須支付負利息"。沒問題，我想我們會把錢帶到加密貨幣上。]]></title><description><![CDATA[德國的銀行已經開始向客戶收取負利息，這意味着
他們想讓你付給他們錢，以換取你把錢存放在一個賬戶裏。

不是開玩笑，他們真的告訴他們的客戶把錢帶到其他地方。
[https://www.wsj.com/articles/banks-in-germany-tell-customers...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwvac8/banks_in_germany_tell_customers_to_take_their/?score=362&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwvac8%2Fbanks_in_germany_tell_customers_to_take_their%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwvac8%2Fbanks_in_germany_tell_customers_to_take_their%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwvac8/banks_in_germany_tell_customers_to_take_their/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Banks in Germany have started charging customers negative interest, meaning that they want you to pay them in exchange for you storing your money in an account.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;No joke, they literally &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wsj.com/articles/banks-in-germany-tell-customers-to-take-deposits-elsewhere-11614594601&quot;&amp;gt;tell their customers to take their money elsewhere&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Of course, in reality they still want to be in control of your money, but now even charge you for giving them this privilege.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;No problem, guess we take our money somewhere else. You can earn more than 10% interest on holding some stablecoin, or you hold any other Crypto, like Ethereum, which has outperformed even the highest rallying traditional markets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If banks really want to be in control of our money, they better be ready to pay for it, or we move our money to Crypto (or literally anywhere else). This basically a scam on older people who are not aware where to store their money elsewhere.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你不能處理好50%的傾銷，你就不配得到500%的泵...。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你不能處理好50%的拋售，你就不配得到500%的抽水...。

幾年前，人們用這句話（插入例如x%）來形容恐慌性的帖子。

由於我們今天看到了一些波動，我開始看到恐慌性的
幾年前，這裏的一些老手說過一些話，以保持下巴和...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx0ati/if_you_cant_handle_the_50_dump_you_dont_deserve/?score=773&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx0ati%2Fif_you_cant_handle_the_50_dump_you_dont_deserve%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frx0ati%2Fif_you_cant_handle_the_50_dump_you_dont_deserve%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rx0ati/if_you_cant_handle_the_50_dump_you_dont_deserve/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you can’t handle the 50% dump you don’t deserve the 500% pump…&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Words (insert eg x% )that was used years ago as the go to for panic posts- &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Since we are seeing a bit of volatility today and I’m starting to see panic posts some words from veterans here from years ago to keep the chin up and HODL strong. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The market tend to have a bullwhip effect vs normal stock market nowadays so any move is exponentially larger. Part of the risk and excitement of being in the crypt. If you haven’t been here long (most people here have got into the crypt the last 4 months) this is part of the game and likely will be for a time. This is good as this also gives the gainz over time more than traditional markets. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The market is more mature than years gone by but the volatility is still there albeit less pronounced eg 80% drop in 2hrs - keep it simple (dont over trade)and HODL in what you believe in and may the gwei be with you….&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;PS this is something that has been part of crypto since the early days that hardens one to a new level of apathy and diamond hands the real test comes in when suicide lines come in at the post 30% drops to 80% drops. Again only have skin in the game in what you believe and make sure it’s quality bags!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在你的硬幣崩潰時賣出是非常愚蠢的。]]></title><description><![CDATA[隨着最近的暴跌，我相信有很多人在賣，但這對我來說沒有任何意義。
對我來說沒有任何意義，因爲如果你買的是可靠的幣，而不是一些昨天剛出來的低
幣，它們都會回升，你就會忘記這次暴跌。
忘記這次崩潰。

比特幣崩潰到28000，但又爬了回來...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwyvgy/selling_when_your_coin_crashes_is_plain_stupid/?score=442&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwyvgy%2Fselling_when_your_coin_crashes_is_plain_stupid%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwyvgy%2Fselling_when_your_coin_crashes_is_plain_stupid%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwyvgy/selling_when_your_coin_crashes_is_plain_stupid/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With the recent crash I&amp;amp;#39;m sure there are a lot of people selling, but it doesn&amp;amp;#39;t make any sense to me as if you&amp;amp;#39;ve bought reliable coins, and not some low marketcap coin that came out yesterday, they will all climb back up and you&amp;amp;#39;ll forget about this crash.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin crashed to 28k but climbed back up to 69K, isn&amp;amp;#39;t that a proof that it always does? There have been so many crashes like this one and it will pass and everyone will forget about it. Not only that but Bitcoin will break its ATH again this year, that much is obvious.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The reason you&amp;amp;#39;re down is not because your coin failed, the whole market failed so why sell if you believe in it? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So if you&amp;amp;#39;re thinking about selling, especially at a loss, I&amp;amp;#39;d advise you to be patient and hold as there&amp;amp;#39;s no point to it and you&amp;amp;#39;ll only lose money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Algorand的創始人Silvio Micali因發明零知識（ZK）證明而獲得圖靈獎]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwwx6x/silvio_micali_founder_of_algorand_won_the_turing/?score=417&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwwx6x%2Fsilvio_micali_founder_of_algorand_won_the_turing%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwwx6x%2Fsilvio_micali_founder_of_algorand_won_the_turing%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwwx6x/silvio_micali_founder_of_algorand_won_the_turing/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wahoo... 新年BTC銷售!]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwy1jn/wahoo_new_years_btc_sale/?score=490&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwy1jn%2Fwahoo_new_years_btc_sale%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwy1jn%2Fwahoo_new_years_btc_sale%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwy1jn/wahoo_new_years_btc_sale/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 04:34:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cryptoland，這是真實的，令人厭惡的，它是加密貨幣一切問題的實際表現。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這裏是密碼區，只是要警告你，你不會再有10分鐘的時間了。
看完這段視頻後，你就再也回不去了。

https://youtu.be/jf3ajS5me78

對於那些不想看視頻的人來說，這裏有一個關鍵點。密碼區是
玄幻世界的實際表現。由兩個腦殘的幻想家創建
來向你推銷...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwj21h/cryptoland_this_is_real_its_disgusting_and_its_a/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwj21h%2Fcryptoland_this_is_real_its_disgusting_and_its_a%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwj21h%2Fcryptoland_this_is_real_its_disgusting_and_its_a%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwj21h/cryptoland_this_is_real_its_disgusting_and_its_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:48:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is cryptoland, just be warned you won’t get the 10 minutes back after watching this video. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/jf3ajS5me78&quot;&amp;gt;https://youtu.be/jf3ajS5me78&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For those who did not want to watch the video here is the rub. Cryptoland is the physical manifestation of the metaverse. Created by two brain dead visionaries to sell you yet again more worthless NFTs and tokens to equate to real land on a private island only for crypto visionaries to work, live, and play.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can buy a 1 acre plot of real land to build a real house on, workout on a beachside crypto themed gym, eat at a crypto themed restaurant and bar. But what else? A ultra exclusive night club that is a members only club on a members only island than only special NFT holders can get into.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cryptoland is designed for the new lifestyle of “digital nomads” who spend their lives in hotels and glued to charts on their phones then create content with quality TA about how what coin can go up, down, or sideways. The best part is there is a whole island of these assholes!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I think I’m going to be sick…&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我剛剛把我所有的積蓄都投進了比特幣，我不知道該作何感想。]]></title><description><![CDATA[一些背景信息，我來自一個新的第三世界國家（黎巴嫩）。
我存了730美元，沒有工作，23歲，我剛剛把700美元投進了BTC，我很興奮但也很緊張。
興奮而又緊張，我絕不會虧本賣出，我願意在虧本前自殺。
但我不知道，我的胃裏有蝴蝶。

插入...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwnj33/i_just_threw_all_my_savings_into_bitcoin_and_idk/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwnj33%2Fi_just_threw_all_my_savings_into_bitcoin_and_idk%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwnj33%2Fi_just_threw_all_my_savings_into_bitcoin_and_idk%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwnj33/i_just_threw_all_my_savings_into_bitcoin_and_idk/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:33:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some background information, im from a newly 3rd world country ( Lebanon) and ive saved 730$, dont have a job and im 23, i just threw a 700$ into btc and im excited yet nervous, i would never sell at a loss, I&amp;amp;#39;d kill my self before taking a loss but idk i have butterflies in my stomach.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Insert motivational quotes here xD.
What do you think? Is it foolish from me? But i had to buy this dip...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Looping智能錢包現在可以在iOS的L2上免費激活。]]></title><description><![CDATA[更新你的iOS應用程序，它將讓你完全免費激活L2錢包，因爲
費用會轉給Loopring。

然後你可以通過L2網絡中的朋友添加資金，或通過RAMP法幣通道購買
來資助L2錢包。

爲了擁有完整的功能（社會恢復，L1資金等），你需要...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwluuk/looping_smart_wallet_is_now_free_to_activate_on/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwluuk%2Flooping_smart_wallet_is_now_free_to_activate_on%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwluuk%2Flooping_smart_wallet_is_now_free_to_activate_on%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwluuk/looping_smart_wallet_is_now_free_to_activate_on/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:33:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Update your iOS app, it will let you activate the L2 wallet completely free as the fee gets passed onto Loopring.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You can then add funds via L2 networked friends or buy via the RAMP fiat on-ramp to fund the L2 Wallet.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To have full functionality (social recovery, L1 funds etc) you’ll need to activate the L1 wallet which will of course incur a gas fee so be cautious of the current Eth gas fee. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The main draw of the L2 Wallet atm is access to DEX/AMM on L2 w/very cheap transfer fees. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Apparently the Android free L2 Wallet deploy will come soon, I assume in the next day as they can push it to Android basically any time whereas iOS has to get approved.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你聽過的最好的比特幣名言是什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA["他們的無知就是你的機會。" -邁克爾-賽勒

這句話是我最喜歡的，肯定是向貝索斯的名言致敬]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rweo0a/whats_the_best_bitcoin_quote_you_have_ever_heard/?score=318&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frweo0a%2Fwhats_the_best_bitcoin_quote_you_have_ever_heard%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frweo0a%2Fwhats_the_best_bitcoin_quote_you_have_ever_heard%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rweo0a/whats_the_best_bitcoin_quote_you_have_ever_heard/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:33:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;Their ignorance is your opportunity.&amp;amp;quot; -Michael Saylor&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That one is my favorite- surely an homage to Bezos famous quote&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[妻子&amp; Crypto]]></title><description><![CDATA[在另一個帖子中，我看到無數的用戶說，如果加密貨幣突然間
變成0美元，他們的妻子會和他們離婚，帶走孩子，等等。這怎麼會
這怎麼行呢？

如果你有一些你投資的生意，而它變成了垃圾，你的家人會放棄你嗎？
家人會放棄你嗎？

你是不是用你妻子的錢...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwo2sy/wives_crypto/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwo2sy%2Fwives_crypto%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwo2sy%2Fwives_crypto%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwo2sy/wives_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:33:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In another post, I read countless users saying that if crypto all of a sudden went to $0, their wives would divorce them, take the kids, etc etc. How does that work? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you have some business that you invested in, and it goes to crap, does the family give up on you? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Are you using you wife&amp;amp;#39;s money to buy crypto and your kids aren&amp;amp;#39;t eating because of it?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Well, not at all like that here at home. I invested in Crypto, but I invested in crypto with MY OWN MONEY, if it goes to zero, it&amp;amp;#39;s my bad, not hers. She works and earns her money too, buys her shoes and dresses and I don&amp;amp;#39;t stick my nose in, it&amp;amp;#39;s her money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As long as our house expenses are covered where each one pays half of them, then the spare money we can do whatever we want because it&amp;amp;#39;s our money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For context, I live in Portugal (Europe), for cultural reasons, things might work differently in your country. Not saying I&amp;amp;#39;m right and you are wrong, just putting different lifestyles in perspective.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How does it work at your place? Does your family have a say in your personal expenses?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[零知識證明的解釋就像你是5歲的孩子一樣]]></title><description><![CDATA[孩子們好!

所以，你對加密貨幣感興趣，而且你聽說過那些
所謂的 "零知識證明"（ZK），這些項目包括Loopring、zkSync
和StarkWare。

現在你想知道：什麼是零知識證明，爲什麼它們如此重要？
重要？好消息，冠軍，我在這裏爲你提供...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwpfkx/zeroknowledge_proof_explained_like_you_are_5/?score=358&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwpfkx%2Fzeroknowledge_proof_explained_like_you_are_5%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwpfkx%2Fzeroknowledge_proof_explained_like_you_are_5%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwpfkx/zeroknowledge_proof_explained_like_you_are_5/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 22:33:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hi kids!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, you&amp;amp;#39;re interested in cryptocurrencies, and you&amp;amp;#39;ve heard about those so-called &amp;amp;quot;zero-knowledge proofs&amp;amp;quot; (ZK) used by projects such as Loopring, zkSync and StarkWare.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now you&amp;amp;#39;re wondering : what are zero-knowledge proofs and why are they so important? Good news, champ, I am here for you!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let&amp;amp;#39;s say I found a cave with two distinct entrances, Left and Right. The two entrances are connected by a corridor, but a dragon prevents anyone from passing through the corridor. To make the dragon let you through, you need a magic stone. I have this magic stone, and I want to prove to you that I have it, but I don&amp;amp;#39;t want to show it to you, and I don&amp;amp;#39;t want to tell my secret to anyone but you.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is how it works. You close your eyes while I enter the cave, without telling you if I chose the Left or Right entrance. You open your eyes again, then ask me to come out on a particular side and I do so. You close your eyes, I go back into the cave, and we repeat the experience 100 times.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If I have the magic stone, the dragon will let me through everytime and I can leave the cave through the entrance you tell me, 100 times out of 100. But if I don&amp;amp;#39;t have the stone, every other time I won&amp;amp;#39;t be able to get out through the chosen entrance - statistically, I will only have the good answer 50% of the time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;So by using this method, I will prove to you that I have the magic stone, without ever showing it to you&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Moreover, you will not be able to prove to anyone else that I have the stone, since an outside observer could always think that we have arranged it together in advance.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is what is called a zero-knowledge proof. In cryptocurrencies, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;the magic stone is the private key&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. Zero-knowledge proofs are used to show to a validator that you are indeed in possession of the private key, without revealing said private keys to the validator, and without letting the rest of the world know you have the key.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thank you for listening to my story. I hope you had fun today, my little friends!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有誰經歷過這種情況？我把比特幣的事情告訴了我的同事，他對比特幣作爲一種通貨膨脹的對沖工具非常着迷。第二天，他帶着一堆狗屎幣回來了，但沒有比特幣。]]></title><description><![CDATA[他說他下載了Coinbase併購買了一些Youtuber推薦的隨機硬幣。
建議的。我問他是否買了任何比特幣，他說 "沒有，太貴了。
昂貴"。

🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rws5ye/anyone_else_experience_this_told_my_friend_at/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frws5ye%2Fanyone_else_experience_this_told_my_friend_at%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frws5ye%2Fanyone_else_experience_this_told_my_friend_at%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rws5ye/anyone_else_experience_this_told_my_friend_at/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 21:32:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;He said he downloaded Coinbase and bought a bunch of random coins some youtuber suggested. I asked him if he bought any Bitcoin, he said &amp;amp;quot;nope, it was too expensive&amp;amp;quot;. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦🤦&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[抬起頭來，注意安全。我剛剛失去了BTC，因爲有惡意軟件侵入了我的剪貼板[Windows]]]></title><description><![CDATA[我剛剛損失了大量的BTC（至少對我來說，我只能保存
~100美元/月）。我把我最後購買的BTC（sats，真的）放在我的交易所裏。
想把它們轉移到我在手機上使用的（軟件）錢包。所以我
在一個安全的記事本應用程序上覆制/粘貼地址，該應用程序與...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwlkd0/heads_up_and_be_safe_i_just_lost_btc_because_of/?score=331&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwlkd0%2Fheads_up_and_be_safe_i_just_lost_btc_because_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwlkd0%2Fheads_up_and_be_safe_i_just_lost_btc_because_of%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwlkd0/heads_up_and_be_safe_i_just_lost_btc_because_of/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 21:32:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I just lost a significant amount of BTC (to me at least, I can only save ~100$/month). I had my last BTC (sats, really) purchases sitting in my exchange and wanted to move them to my (software) wallet that I use on my phone. So I copied/pasted it the address on a secure notepad app that syncs with PC, then checked that the address shown on my PC matched the wallet address. It did, so that&amp;amp;#39;s cool.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So on the PC I copied/pasted it on the address box for the withdrawal at my exchange, it was shown as a valid address and I proceeded with the transaction. WRONG!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I sat there waiting for my funds to appear on my wallet but they never did. Transaction was shown as completed on the exchange and then I got alarmed. Started to write an email to my exchange&amp;amp;#39;s support team and then it clicked.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I wanted to say that the destination address was &amp;amp;#39;X&amp;amp;#39; but somehow it was being shown as &amp;amp;#39;Y&amp;amp;#39; on the transaction history. But every time I tried to paste my address it was changing right before my eyes. So my email was looking like &amp;amp;lt;&amp;amp;lt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;This is mi destination address: &amp;amp;#39;Y&amp;amp;#39; // This is the address shown on the transacion history: &amp;amp;#39;Y&amp;amp;#39;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;gt;&amp;amp;gt;. Now, my notepad app was clearly showing that the adddress I was trying to copy was most definitely not &amp;amp;#39;Y&amp;amp;#39;, so something was up.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyway, at that point I deleted the email, no need to bother some support dude because of something that was looking more and more like a royal fuck up.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And then there it is, there was some malware on my PC that was actively seeking BTC addresses and switching them to something similar but a different address alltoghether from whoever scammer made the damned thing. I clearly fucked up by not realizing that, and now&amp;amp;#39;s too late.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Malwarebytes was quick to find and delete the thing and now the computer&amp;amp;#39;s clean again (just like my exchange account, haha. FUCK.)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Be safe out there and double check or triple check everything when doing a transaction. I didn&amp;amp;#39;t realize  at the time so I&amp;amp;#39;m an idiot, but maybe you won&amp;amp;#39;t have to be.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;---&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TL;DR&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s malware out there reading your clipboard to find BTC addresses, and when you try to copy/paste it will paste a similar address from the scammer. I didn&amp;amp;#39;t realize so I&amp;amp;#39;m an idiot, but maybe you won&amp;amp;#39;t have to be.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;---&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT: Okay, thanks for the awards and all. I read the comments but was lazy to reply to each one individually.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;1- My PC wasn&amp;amp;#39;t as infested as some of you may think, I actually clean installed windows 11 like 3 weeks ago FFS. I will reformat it again on the weekend, no worries there. The fucking antivirus did find the culprit, though. After deleting the files and restarting the PC, clipboard was behaving correctly again (I checked a shit ton of times).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;2- &amp;amp;#39;A secure notepad app that syncs&amp;amp;#39; was just to make it easier to explain. It was Bitwarden, using the note entry options. It&amp;amp;#39;s a password manager so it is indeed secure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;3- Mac / Linux people... Let&amp;amp;#39;s just not go there, I don&amp;amp;#39;t care about OS master race. Windows is a great fit for what I use it and all other OS have their flaws too.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;4- Hardware wallet option is something that I&amp;amp;#39;m always considering, I just fear loosing it, TBH. 2-stage transactions seems like a good enough compromise to me for the time being.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;5- Software wallet on my phone gets uninstalled after each deposit, because I agree that it&amp;amp;#39;s not a great thing to carry around. Then whenever I want to transfer again I re-download it and use the seed phrase to access my stuff.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;6- Now let&amp;amp;#39;s be clear, I know that evrything&amp;amp;#39;s my fault, here. For what is worth, the address was very similar (first letters were the exact same), and was given as a valid address by the exchange so i trusted it more than I should have, but i did not check the complete string and that&amp;amp;#39;s on me. I&amp;amp;#39;m a bit of a newbie, but not a complete idiot, it&amp;amp;#39;s just that I plain hadn&amp;amp;#39;t heard about this particular scam before (hence why I wrote it to alert any other newbie that could find the info useful).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;7- To the people thinking that this was an ad and I didn&amp;amp;#39;t just lose my money... I wish it was so, I truly truly do. Imagine if those fuckers were paying me, too. Ah... Wouldn&amp;amp;#39;t that be nice? &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anyway, you can&amp;amp;#39;t trust your clipboard, there&amp;amp;#39;s a lesson learned.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;m a few steps back and it kinda sucks, but I&amp;amp;#39;ll go back to stacking sats.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Airbnb將實施加密貨幣支付]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwn5a8/airbnb_to_implement_crypto_payments/?score=399&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwn5a8%2Fairbnb_to_implement_crypto_payments%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Frwn5a8%2Fairbnb_to_implement_crypto_payments%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/rwn5a8/airbnb_to_implement_crypto_payments/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 20:37:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我希望我在投資加密貨幣時能早些做的事情]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好! 今天是我第一次進行加密貨幣交易的週年紀念日! 我的
我第一次購買的是以太坊，從那時起，我就一直在學習。
學習之旅。

我後來學到了很多東西，而不是我希望的那樣，所以這裏有一些東西
我希望我早一點做的事情，當...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwjwly/things_i_wish_i_did_earlier_when_investing_in/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwjwly%2Fthings_i_wish_i_did_earlier_when_investing_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwjwly%2Fthings_i_wish_i_did_earlier_when_investing_in%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwjwly/things_i_wish_i_did_earlier_when_investing_in/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 18:47:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hi everyone! Today marks the anniversary of my first ever crypto transaction! My first purchase was of Ethereum, and since then it has been nothing else but a learning journey.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There were a lot of things I learnt later than what I wished, so here are a few of the things I wish I did earlier when investing in crypto:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Keeping track of transactions&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: when I first bought crypto, I invested X amount of fiat without keeping track of how much I have put into it. Later, I discovered the portfolio trackers. Some good examples are the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://delta.app/en&quot;&amp;gt;Delta App&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coinmarketcap.com/&quot;&amp;gt;CoinMarketCap&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; portfolio tool. I rather input the transaction manually after making them, as I don&amp;amp;#39;t really like giving API keys to 3rd parties.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Opening a Vault for Moons&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: easily the worst mistake I have ever done. I never knew the existence of moons until they, well, mooned. I always use my PC or laptop for Reddit and never seen the Vault menu, and when I found out about I felt so stupid as I was quite active in this sub when I first started. Open your Vault!! It is literally free crypto for your posts - please focus on quality!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Having Native Wallets&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: this isn&amp;amp;#39;t a mistake, but more of a &amp;amp;quot;help the ecosystem&amp;amp;quot; kind of thing. What I must recommend though is to keep all your assets away from exchanges. A system failure, hacking attack or just bankruptcy can be the end of your funds, so keep your coins in an external wallet. I started with &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.exodus.com/&quot;&amp;gt;Exodus Wallet&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, as it has the most assets and allows staking for interest rewards. With time, I migrated to native wallets (wallets made for a single network in particular) and around 80% of my assets are secured with a Ledger Nano X (hardware wallet, not hackable!).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Don&amp;amp;#39;t stick to one exchange&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: not all exchanges have all the coins you will want. Not all exchanges have the same features and most importantly, not all have the same fees. what exchanges do I recommend? I personally use &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://Crypto.com&quot;&amp;gt;Crypto.com&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kraken.com/&quot;&amp;gt;Kraken&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. Of course, each one to their own and geographical restrictions may apply to some exchanges.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Don&amp;amp;#39;t do stupid things that can cause you headaches&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: what I mean with this is, do not add 5 bank accounts to your fiat withdrawal addresses, don&amp;amp;#39;t deposit fiat from 4 different banks in 3 different countries, 2 credit cards and 4 debit cards. Focus on 1 and 1. One card. One bank account. Work yourself around that and it will help you massively. I have seen so many issues with people with locked accounts due to having to verify details etc. that can just be solved by this. I never had a single issue using &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.revolut.com/&quot;&amp;gt;Revolut&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; as my bank account and the virtual card as my means of payment if i use this. Also, all bank deposits are allowed to exchanges from them (EU Customer). KYC! Just do it. The government knows all about you anyways, so don&amp;amp;#39;t worry. You are happy to give your bank details, name, surname, card number away but not a selfie of yourself? The big exchanges have great privacy and security measures, don&amp;amp;#39;t worry!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Find Rewards. There are A LOT OF THEM!&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: Crypto is a baby. A volatile baby, but a baby nonetheless. Everything is new! DeFi projects can offer 100%+ APY by staking your coins, projects with PoS networks offer some really good interest by just hodling their coin and a lot of platforms offer interest in stablecoins and other tokens. Personally, I use one of the VISA Cards that CDC offer. It earns me cashback, free services and lets be honest, looks cool af!&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Lastly but most importantly, ENJOY&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;: Don&amp;amp;#39;t look at the chart every day and worry. Yes I look at my portfolio every day but just to see if it is a good moment to buy or not. I never worry. If you are a day trader, then yes. A hodler, then hodl. You are here for the long run. Enjoy the experience, the learning and the communities (apart from &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/r/bitcoin&quot;&amp;gt;r/bitcoin&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; - that&amp;amp;#39;s a cult). &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hopefully this helps newbies a bit more, and makes it easier to start up! Have a great year everyone.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你的altcoin剛剛升值了嗎？很好! 現在賣掉15%的包。把剩下的錢留給下一次升空，或者用你的新收益買入下一次下跌的機會。這是一個簡單的經驗法則，以確保你總是在獲取利潤]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們很容易陷入 "哦，不，我不應該賣掉整袋東西，因爲...... "的困境。
如果它漲得更多怎麼辦！" 該死的，你想持有是對的。

但這是一個賺錢的遊戲，如果這是你的目標，你需要賣出
進入欣喜狀態

當你看到你的硬幣有兩位數的收益時，...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwcosl/did_your_altcoin_just_moon_great_now_sell_15_of/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwcosl%2Fdid_your_altcoin_just_moon_great_now_sell_15_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwcosl%2Fdid_your_altcoin_just_moon_great_now_sell_15_of%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwcosl/did_your_altcoin_just_moon_great_now_sell_15_of/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 16:38:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s so easy to get stuck on, &amp;amp;quot;oh no, I shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t sell the whole bag because what if it goes up more!&amp;amp;quot; And dammit, you&amp;amp;#39;re right to wanna hold. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But this is a game of making money, and if that&amp;amp;#39;s your goal you need to &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;sell into euphoria&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When you&amp;amp;#39;re seeing double digit percent gains on your coin, it&amp;amp;#39;s time to make that trade and sell a little bit of the bag. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s usually a nice dip afterwards and you&amp;amp;#39;ll be glad you&amp;amp;#39;ve got the powder to burn. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And if there&amp;amp;#39;s not a dip afterwards, you&amp;amp;#39;ve got 85% of your original bag to decide to hold or sell. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Finally, if the coin truly tanks afterwards then, you have some USDC that&amp;amp;#39;s much more tradable than your ElonCumRocket. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s truly a win-win-win&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NFTs不會毀掉電腦遊戲，貪婪的遊戲公司會利用NFTs毀掉電腦遊戲]]></title><description><![CDATA[正如標題所說，最近在遊戲分論壇上有一個帖子，稱
聲稱NFTs將進一步毀掉電腦遊戲，就像微交易一樣
那樣。

然而，我不同意這種說法。如果NFTs出現在DnD中，他們將是一個
合法的中立力量，他們不是善或惡，他們是......]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwlo57/nfts_wont_ruin_computer_games_greedy_game/?score=505&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwlo57%2Fnfts_wont_ruin_computer_games_greedy_game%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwlo57%2Fnfts_wont_ruin_computer_games_greedy_game%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwlo57/nfts_wont_ruin_computer_games_greedy_game/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 14:33:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As the title says, there was a post recently in the gaming subreddit that was claiming that NFTs will ruin computer gaming further just like microtransactions did.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, I disagree with that statement. If NFTs were in DnD they would be a lawful neutral force, they are not good or evil they are just a tool and being a transparent and open tool it makes them more easy to keep track of.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If anything NFTs should provide more consumer protection for digital game downloads than the present model of Microsoft being all like &amp;amp;quot;trust me bra, we got this&amp;amp;quot; until one day they just remove the game from the store and leave no public evidence that you ever owned it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, I also 100% guarantee that game companies are going to use this to further monetise the market for pointless crap cosmetics and strip even more out of a game to sell back to the player later.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But people shouldn&amp;amp;#39;t hate the technology, that&amp;amp;#39;s like hating the internet because game companies use the internet to download microtransactions, it really makes no sense. Hate the companies and hate the people buying their garbage.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[要誠實。你買了哪種硬幣，只是因爲它在這裏或twitter或其他地方被兜售，而沒有對它進行研究？]]></title><description><![CDATA[你見過正在或已經被不停地推銷的錢幣嗎？Ehem ERG
ALGO LRC

大家總是說要自己研究，但我們都知道，有些時候
當我們懶得去做這個繁瑣的投資部分時，我們就會想，啊？
去它的，有什麼可能出錯，就把...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwhxvb/be_honest_which_coins_did_you_buy_just_because_it/?score=362&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwhxvb%2Fbe_honest_which_coins_did_you_buy_just_because_it%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwhxvb%2Fbe_honest_which_coins_did_you_buy_just_because_it%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwhxvb/be_honest_which_coins_did_you_buy_just_because_it/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 13:37:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Have you ever seen coins that are being or have been shilled nonstop? &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Ehem&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; ERG ALGO LRC&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Everyone always say DO YOUR OWN RESEARCH, but we all know that there are times when we are too lazy to do this tedious part of investment and we&amp;amp;#39;re like &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;ahh fuck it, what could possibly go wrong&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; and just put in money.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So which projects or coins have you bought without doing prior research and just went in head first? Was it successful? Did it fail horribly? How were you convinced to buy it just because? Was it the sheer volume of the people shilling? Did you read something informative that enticed you to buy it?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: ok that&amp;amp;#39;s a lot of people&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[資產按其S2F比率和市場價值排隊，只是巧合還是有意義的模式？請注意，目前的BTC集羣（2020-2024年，右上角的藍點）已經填滿了一半。https://t.co/2A05HERwoY]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1478701553800335363/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1478701553800335363/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 12:48:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[現在發生的事情。Airbnb可能很快增加對加密貨幣支付的支持]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwgmna/happening_now_airbnb_could_soon_add_support_for/?score=357&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwgmna%2Fhappening_now_airbnb_could_soon_add_support_for%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwgmna%2Fhappening_now_airbnb_could_soon_add_support_for%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwgmna/happening_now_airbnb_could_soon_add_support_for/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 12:48:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[人類的進步是以卡達舍夫尺度來衡量的；#比特幣加速了能源網的建設，爲未來提供動力。https://t.co/hLe9XLp8IW]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1478656462947762177/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1478656462947762177/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 11:37:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是唯一一個從未在Coinbase遇到過問題的人嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我每天都看到無數關於Coinbase對人們來說是多麼糟糕的帖子。
他們的Coinbase賬戶被黑了，他們被騙了，Coinbase的支持人員不願意
他們的賬戶被黑了，他們被騙了，Coinbase的支持不給他們回話，等等。

我從去年年初開始使用Coinbase。我做了一次性投資，每週
循環投資，每月循環投資，...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwcou2/am_i_the_only_one_that_has_never_had_a_problem/?score=333&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwcou2%2Fam_i_the_only_one_that_has_never_had_a_problem%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwcou2%2Fam_i_the_only_one_that_has_never_had_a_problem%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwcou2/am_i_the_only_one_that_has_never_had_a_problem/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 11:37:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I see countless posts everyday about how Coinbase has been terrible for people. Their Coinbase account got hacked, they got scammed, Coinbase support won’t get back to them, etc…&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I started with Coinbase early last year. I did lumpsum investments, weekly recurring investments, monthly recurring, staking, Coinbase earn, conversions, literally everything you can do on Coinbase (besides sell) and have never ever had one issue. I mean, I’m not out here throwing money at memecoins but I’d say I’m using Coinbase the way it is supposed to be used and what they promise. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve more than tripled what I put in, and do not have a single complaint about it. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Is there anyone else that is completely satisfied with Coinbase? I can’t help but think, looking at all these posts, that a lot of the problems people are running into are user error, but maybe I’m the exception?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[需要一個勇敢的人說出真相。@Bobscartoons是一個勇敢的、深具同情心的人。
https://t.co/NRfaqmIzAr]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1478662379005259776/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1478662379005259776/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 10:36:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特幣可能達到10萬美元並超過黃金的市場份額。高盛公司：比特幣可能達到10萬美元並超過黃金市場份額]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwbnby/bitcoin_could_reach_100k_and_overtake_golds/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwbnby%2Fbitcoin_could_reach_100k_and_overtake_golds%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frwbnby%2Fbitcoin_could_reach_100k_and_overtake_golds%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rwbnby/bitcoin_could_reach_100k_and_overtake_golds/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 10:36:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不要像你的父母一樣... 現在就進行投資，這樣你的孩子就可以帶着錢長大，成爲你一直討厭的傻逼。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我從事加密貨幣有一段時間了，但我還沒有發財。
除了價格波動外，我還注意到，有很多人正在進入加密貨幣。
如果不是投資，就是玩NFT遊戲，或者用它來買東西，在某個地方打折。
在達拉斯小牛隊體育場等地方打折買東西，......]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw3vsz/dont_be_like_your_parents_invest_now_so_your_kids/?score=307&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw3vsz%2Fdont_be_like_your_parents_invest_now_so_your_kids%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw3vsz%2Fdont_be_like_your_parents_invest_now_so_your_kids%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw3vsz/dont_be_like_your_parents_invest_now_so_your_kids/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 08:38:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ve been in crypto for a while and no im not rich yet. but what i been noticing besides the price flux lol, is the amount of people that is getting into crypto as a whole. if its not investing its NFT games, or using it to buy something at a discount at somewhere like the Dallas Mavericks stadium, or people are just seeing ads or companies that produce products they use, get into it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;the other day on the train i seen many train carts with AVAX (Avalanche blockchain) ads all over the inside of the train cart in NYC ( you can imagine the excitement i felt lol) , i also seen ads for Upland ( a crypto real estate game)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;this is our chance to really get invested and wait for things to get better. I know there&amp;amp;#39;s a chance the market will collapse in a spectacle of people pulling their hair out and jumping out windows, but with the amount of institutions and big companies getting involved, i doubt it. the amount of users they will bring on to what ever networks they decide to work with will def help the case.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;every time the internet upgrades a good handful of people get rich, and yes alot of people lose money also ( but those are the impatient people or the people who put in too much and end up having to pull out )&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;even look at this video from after skool is all about crypto. ( mainly ether and bitcoin ) but they are a youtube channel that makes videos about mental health and life&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;VIDEO: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qGHMyxYSa58&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qGHMyxYSa58&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;if they are making videos about it, i know this is def not going anywhere and who ever chooses the best chains to invest in will change their life for the better or worse if you only want hookers and cocaine... your choice and youre money&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;So for the love of MONEY,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; just DYOR and Invest&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;HODEL&amp;amp;gt; PROFIT&amp;amp;gt; CREATE&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[三星將與氣候解決方案平臺Veritree一起種植200萬棵樹，該平臺使用Cardano來驗證和跟蹤重新造林過程的每一步。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rvvt2w/samsung_to_plant_2_million_trees_with_climate/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frvvt2w%2Fsamsung_to_plant_2_million_trees_with_climate%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frvvt2w%2Fsamsung_to_plant_2_million_trees_with_climate%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rvvt2w/samsung_to_plant_2_million_trees_with_climate/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 07:38:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在播出幾個月後，馬特-達蒙的加密貨幣廣告突然得到一堆負面關注。推特上的巨頭們似乎對他們錯過的收益感到不滿]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw5s4p/after_being_on_the_air_for_months_the_matt_damon/?score=314&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw5s4p%2Fafter_being_on_the_air_for_months_the_matt_damon%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw5s4p%2Fafter_being_on_the_air_for_months_the_matt_damon%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw5s4p/after_being_on_the_air_for_months_the_matt_damon/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 05:38:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Algorand治理分配明細--50,000筆交易只需花費50ALGO]]></title><description><![CDATA[那些報名參加第一輪治理的人將已經收到他們的
獎勵了。

50,000筆交易只用了20分鐘，價值1億美元的ALGO
分發。總的交易費用爲50ALGO。

現在無論你是否有一袋ALGO，它的好處是可以看到什麼是...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw4j5a/algorand_governance_distribution_breakdown_50000/?score=313&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw4j5a%2Falgorand_governance_distribution_breakdown_50000%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Frw4j5a%2Falgorand_governance_distribution_breakdown_50000%2F</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/rw4j5a/algorand_governance_distribution_breakdown_50000/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 05:38:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Those that signed up for the first round of governance will have received their rewards now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;50,000 transactions took just 20 minutes, with $100 million worth of ALGO distributed. The total transaction fee costing 50 ALGO. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now whether you have a bag of ALGO or not, its good to see what is possible with crypto and can only be seen as a positive for us all.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For those that aren&amp;amp;#39;t aware, the rewards were around 3.5% for the 3 month locked period - that&amp;amp;#39;s 14.75%APR. Again, this is only another positive for us all. Its well above inflation and considerably more than any bank would offer in a standard savings account. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The deadline for the second round of Governance is the 6th January, so if you&amp;amp;#39;re thinking about locking it in until the end of March you&amp;amp;#39;ve got a couple of days left (depending where you are in the world).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>