<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[加密貨幣國外熱門討論]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 09:20:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[加密貨幣的初學者指南]]></title><description><![CDATA[什麼是區塊鏈？

它是一個 "不可變的賬本"。想想看，它就像一本住在天上的書。
每當有什麼變化時，它就會用神奇的墨水寫下來，當墨水乾了之後。
永遠不會改變。而這些書有成千上萬的副本，都是在同一時間被更新。
在同一時間更新。如果有一天...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s41z1x/a_beginners_guide_to_cryptocurrency/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs41z1x%2Fa_beginners_guide_to_cryptocurrency%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs41z1x%2Fa_beginners_guide_to_cryptocurrency%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s41z1x/a_beginners_guide_to_cryptocurrency/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 08:35:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What is a blockchain?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is an “immutable ledger.” Think about it like a book that lives in the sky. Every time something changes, its written down with magic ink, that when dries, never changes. And there are thousands of copies of these books, all getting updated at the same time. If one is ever messed with, the other books would wipe out the problem and replace it with the correct entry.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;(Tedtalk – Blockchain Massively simplified)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mbcg.io/vision?pgid=kn921drf-2058f817-4ebc-4c29-8430-a667933ff044&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.mbcg.io/vision?pgid=kn921drf-2058f817-4ebc-4c29-8430-a667933ff044&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What is proof of Work?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;First generation crypto currency worked of the concept of Poof of work. There, it is a race to solve a complicated math puzzle, and perform the block write operation. And as a reward get coin. “Mining.” Mining is slow. Bitcoin can only do 7 transactions a minute.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Of the thousands and thousands of machines out there racing to win the next block, only 1 at a time wins. That means the others have literally wasted their energy via compute CPU and GPU cycles. Bitcoin used more energy than Argentina last year.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
But its not all bad. POW is still the oldest and most battle tested consensus algorithm, and many ague more secure because of it. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/p/proof-work.asp&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/p/proof-work.asp&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-56012952&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-56012952&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What is proof of Stake?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Proof of Stake works on different types of newly developed “Consensus” algorithms. Ouroboros protocol, created by IHOK and Cardano, along with a team of PHDs and mathematicians, is the first of its kind. They created a secure “lottery” consensus mechanism to “elect” the next “slot leader” to write the block. Here each Stake pool can get a chance to be elected by winning the lottery. Each Ada coin represents 1 lottery ticket. When you delegate to the pool, you give that pool your ticket, not your coin. If the pool wins, you get the reward along with everyone in the pool, and the operator. Because there is no more complicated math puzzle, and no more computers racing to solve the puzzle, its much much faster, and much much cheaper. Cardano nodes can be run on Raspberry Pi.. A lot of nodes out there run on Solar energy. It’s so good, Ethereum, who is proof of work currently, is moving to this model as part of their ETH 2.0 migration. Hopefully this summer with the &amp;amp;quot;merge.&amp;amp;quot; In efforts to reduce gas fees and energy concerns. Pokodot created its own Consensus algorithm. Called Grandpa. Tezos has its Emmy+, and the list goes on. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Each other their own way of doing things. But “gen 3” is not Proof of work.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What you should remember is that for both POW, POS, and others, they are all a means of incentivizing the actual people that run the computers hosting the blockchain code. Without them, there is no “decentralized network of immutable ledgers.” Which is because that’s just fancy talk for machines running our code to support the blockchain. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/p/proof-stake-pos.asp&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/p/proof-stake-pos.asp&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cardano.org/ouroboros/&quot;&amp;gt;https://cardano.org/ouroboros/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://wiki.polkadot.network/docs/en/learn-consensus&quot;&amp;gt;https://wiki.polkadot.network/docs/en/learn-consensus&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://ethereum.org/en/developers/docs/consensus-mechanisms/pos/&quot;&amp;gt;https://ethereum.org/en/developers/docs/consensus-mechanisms/pos/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://wiki.tezosagora.org/learn/baking/proofofstake/consensus&quot;&amp;gt;https://wiki.tezosagora.org/learn/baking/proofofstake/consensus&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What is Market Cap and coin supply and why should we care?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Market Capitalization is equal to Price of Coin times Supply of Coin. That is, it. But very important.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;BITCOIN has a fixed supply. It is not all mined yet. Not until 2140. But it does have a finite amount, 21 Million.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here is why you can see a 65K or even 100K bitcoin, but you’ll probably never see a 100 dollar DOGE, or even a 30 Dollar Ada (not soon anyway)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Currently there are  18,929,200 BTC out there at a cost of 43,087.16.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That means, the market cap is 43,087.16 x 18,929,200  = 815,605,469,072 (815B)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cardano, has a fixed coin supply as well. But it is 45 Billion. There are currently 33,526,814,681. So you see the max is 2500x more. Likewise, with 130B DOGE vs 18M BTC - it’s ~6700X more. DogeCoin also makes 10,000 new coins a minute.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At a price is 1.26 that means the market cap for Cardano is 1.26 X 33,526,814,681 = 42,243,786,498.06 (42B)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You’ll need 136B market cap to reach a 1-dollar DOGE in the next year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;132,670,764,300 + ((10,000*60*24*351) = 137,725,164,300 (Supply of DOGE in 1 year from now)&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
137,725,164,300 * 1 = 137,725,164,300&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;You&amp;amp;#39;ll need an almost 1 Trillion Market Cap for Cardano to hit 3032,127,627,594 * 30 = 963,828,827,820&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To give you some reference. Here is the Market cap of some big names.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Visa – 499B&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Adobe – 250B&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Amazon – 1.7T&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It’s very confusing because every coin has their own supply. Their own way of creating coins and at what cadence. Some even “burn” coins. So, know what yours does and how it works.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bitpanda.com/academy/en/lessons/what-is-market-capitalisation-market-cap-and-why-does-it-matter/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.bitpanda.com/academy/en/lessons/what-is-market-capitalisation-market-cap-and-why-does-it-matter/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://coinmarketcap.com/&quot;&amp;gt;https://coinmarketcap.com/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/tech/cryptocurrency-burning-can-it-manage-inflation/#:%7E:text=Coin%20burning%20is%20the%20process,according%20to%20the%20Motley%20Fool&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.investopedia.com/tech/cryptocurrency-burning-can-it-manage-inflation/#:~:text=Coin%20burning%20is%20the%20process,according%20to%20the%20Motley%20Fool&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://companiesmarketcap.com/visa/marketcap/&quot;&amp;gt;https://companiesmarketcap.com/visa/marketcap/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://companiesmarketcap.com/adobe/marketcap/&quot;&amp;gt;https://companiesmarketcap.com/adobe/marketcap/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://companiesmarketcap.com/amazon/marketcap/&quot;&amp;gt;https://companiesmarketcap.com/amazon/marketcap/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;How can I “get in early?”&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;First. We are all early. You might not have gotten in on the first floor, but we’re only halfway up the stairs to the second flight.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Global wealth is estimated at 1 quadrillion. All the Market Cap in crypto is at 2.05 Trillion. That’s only 0.21% of the world’s wealth.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When looking for “what could be the next big thing” find something with a low market cap, regardless of coin price, that has a strong chance of doing well because of team and tech, the two Ts.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also ask yourself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What are these coins use cases?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Who is their target audience for adoption?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Who is funding them?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Who is their team building it? What is their history?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Do they have a good plan?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://river.com/learn/how-much-worlds-money-in-bitcoin/#:%7E:text=Global%20wealth%20is%20estimated%20at,represents%200.09%25%20of%20global%20wealth&quot;&amp;gt;https://river.com/learn/how-much-worlds-money-in-bitcoin/#:~:text=Global%20wealth%20is%20estimated%20at,represents%200.09%25%20of%20global%20wealth&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What are your goals?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto is really split into 4 worlds.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Day traders, H.O.D.L.’ers, Whales, and weak hands.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Day traders realize that this market is very volatile, now, and historically. Good ones, can capitalize on quick gains by buying low and selling high, waiting for a dip, then buying back in, and selling high again, cyclically.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then there are those that “Hold On for Dear Life.” These people tend to find something they really are passionate about, and never sell. They keep buying. If they see their coin dips, below at what they bought it at, and have some extra funds, they buy more, to &amp;amp;quot;Average Down.&amp;amp;quot; Or Dollar cost average (DCA) by buying a set amount on a regular cadence. They only “take profit” buy selling a small portion when price is really high.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Whales, are investors that come in with millions and billions of dollars. They often “test” the market buy either buying or dumping millions and billions in hopes to manipulate the market to their advantage. If you’re reading this, you’re probably not in this category, but you should know they exist and effect this marketplace.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Then there are “weak hands.” Do not pick this one. These people buy high and sell low. They only invest based on emotion, and nothing else. When things start going bad, they panic, and sell at a loss. Its much better to let your coin go to .000000001 cents, and just hold on to it in the hopes of a rally years later, then it is to ever sell at a loss. Never do this. Never.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Each has its own risks and rewards.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Day trading can rack up dollars quick, but you can lose them just as quick. And there are tax implicates with trades. Some unknown, and constantly changing.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;HODL, might take years, but if you do, the chance of your Return on Invest improves significantly in crypto.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Pick what works best for you but have a plan.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptocurrencyfacts.com/hodling-vs-trading-for-new-cryptocurrency-investors/&quot;&amp;gt;https://cryptocurrencyfacts.com/hodling-vs-trading-for-new-cryptocurrency-investors/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What are things to look out for?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Do your own research&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. There are now more then 4K types of crypto currencies. You can create your own in about 30 minutes with the right free tools.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The mortality rate of new coins is super high this year. Lots of people trying to do Pump and Dumps.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There is nothing in life that goes up for no reason, if it does, it’s a Ponzi scheme.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://lifehacker.com/how-to-create-your-own-cryptocurrency-1825337462&quot;&amp;gt;https://lifehacker.com/how-to-create-your-own-cryptocurrency-1825337462&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.financialexpress.com/market/rip-cryptocurrencies-number-of-dead-coins-up-35-over-last-year-tally-nears-2000-mark/2226169/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.financialexpress.com/market/rip-cryptocurrencies-number-of-dead-coins-up-35-over-last-year-tally-nears-2000-mark/2226169/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://bravenewcoin.com/insights/how-to-identify-a-crypto-pump-and-dump-scheme&quot;&amp;gt;https://bravenewcoin.com/insights/how-to-identify-a-crypto-pump-and-dump-scheme&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What is the difference between storing on an exchange or in a wallet?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A lot.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;First, you must remember what the dream of crypto is really offering.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Its offering a way for us to break away from banks. Forever.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Centralized banks that can print money, is a problem. Blockchain solves this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But not if the new bank ends up being Binace or Coinbase. In fact, keeping your coin in exchanges puts us all at risk of market manipulation by them.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;When a certain 1 person or group owns too many nodes, they can make choices that would benefit them. The attack vector is called a 51% attack or sybil attack.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Today however, you need exchanges to on ramp and off ramp FIAT. FIAT money is government-issued currency that is not backed by a physical commodity, such as gold or silver.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But it will not be like that forever. Chains like ADA and DOT will be interoperable with legacy banks and will eventually cut out exchanges.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Personally, I despise BNB coin and binace. They already take high fees, and now they want the control and the rewards too. Coinbase isn’t much better. Again though, a necessary evil, for now.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But more important than the “dream” is that they can be hacked.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They are a website. Not a blockchain. They hold the keys to your wallet, and let you use them with a weak password and no mfa if you like. Its literally like storing your money in a bank. So know your bank. Good thing, like a bank, SOME, are federally insured up to a certain amount. But some are not, and people have lost millions and billions in the past this way.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Lastly, there is the notification of “passive income” and “interest.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With POS systems, delegators are incentivized to “stake” their coin by earning interest.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With POW systems, like bitcoin, you’d have to stand up your own machine, configure it, and let it use your energy in your house. With withs like Cardano Ada, and ETH 2.0, you can now pull your coin off the exchange, put it in a wallet, delegate to a pool, and earn interest. All while maintaining full control of your coins.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://academy.binance.com/en/articles/sybil-attacks-explained&quot;&amp;gt;https://academy.binance.com/en/articles/sybil-attacks-explained&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/f/fiatmoney.asp&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/f/fiatmoney.asp&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/hack-binance-cryptocurrency-exchange/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.wired.com/story/hack-binance-cryptocurrency-exchange/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://help.coinbase.com/en/coinbase/other-topics/legal-policies/how-is-coinbase-insured&quot;&amp;gt;https://help.coinbase.com/en/coinbase/other-topics/legal-policies/how-is-coinbase-insured&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1jiWH6Up0pPNRssCkMFw4drLRQjKVGsQtGAArITgqABE/edit?usp=sharing&quot;&amp;gt;https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1jiWH6Up0pPNRssCkMFw4drLRQjKVGsQtGAArITgqABE/edit?usp=sharing&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What are Smart Contracts? (This one will blow your mind if you are a developer)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;First let us start with what most people say.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“Smart contracts are self-executing contracts with the terms of the agreement between buyer and seller being directly written into lines of code.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Which is true for sure. It helps build trust and removes the cumbersome third party “trusted agent” like a bank.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But what smart contracts really are is “ANY Code” that can be written to a blockchain and NEVER be changed, forever.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;ANY CODE. You can write your own coins and put them into the block. It happens a lot.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Games, sure, put in the chain. Check out CryptoKitties.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the future ALL business will be blockchain businesses. Every transaction, every process in the building and distribution, will be written to a magic book that can’t be messed with.. Ever..&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/s/smart-contracts.asp&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/s/smart-contracts.asp&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dappuniversity.com/articles/code-your-own-cryptocurrency-on-ethereum&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.dappuniversity.com/articles/code-your-own-cryptocurrency-on-ethereum&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cryptokitties.co/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.cryptokitties.co/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What are NFTs?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;NonFungible Tokens is metadata attached to an asset. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The metadata is things like who created it, and when. Along with the most important piece the link to the asset. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The asset is what most people think of when they talk about NFTs.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Its a digital file. Like a jpg or a mov file.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
But its not stored in the blockchain like most assume.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Instead they are stored, most often, in IPFS storage.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
IPFS is very cool, but its not blockchain, and thus not &amp;amp;quot;immutable.&amp;amp;quot; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So what’s the big deal? I can upload a gif to the internet today.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The big deal is twofold.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;First, you are not uploading anything to the “internet.” That whole thing we call the internet is flawed. Tracked, centralized, monitored, and gated.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What you are doing is creating an EARLY entry, in a book that will never change for the rest of time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Let us sit and think about that for a second.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;De Beers is going to have to get new slogan. “A &amp;lt;del&amp;gt;diamond&amp;lt;/del&amp;gt; NFT is forever”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Right now, it is some awful GIF of a dogecoin. But it is not what it is. It is what it represents.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It is the next chapter in Art history. What is created will last longer than the Mona Lisa. Someday you will have blockchain archaeologist that comb though chains.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Plus, taking away the cool factor, they create a place that you can now prove you did it first.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Artist could upload lyrics as an NFT, and later sell them, without the fear their art might be stolen before a contract is in place. People could attach their house deed to a chain, and ever again dispute who owns the land after a conflict.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Besides gaming, NFTs are frequently used to sell a wide range of virtual collectibles, including NBA virtual trading cards, music, digital images, video clips and even virtual real estate in &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://decentraland.org/&quot;&amp;gt;Decentraland&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, a virtual world.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That of course is the rosier outlook on NFTs.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Unfortunately, in practice there are many gaps today.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The first I already mentioned. The asset is not stored in the blockchain.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
What that means is that the IPFS provider could &amp;amp;quot;unpin&amp;amp;quot; your asset, and if its not saved anywhere else, you&amp;amp;#39;ll end up with an NFT that has metadata that points to a url that has nothing there.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The second problem, is that there are thousands of blockchains. People can take your asset, because its publicly pined, and then go create an NFT on another blockchain, and then claim theirs is in fact the original. You&amp;amp;#39;d have to check every chain that supports NFTs to ensure it was in fact the first first.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Or people have taken hard artwork, like paintings, and then minted and sold them as NFTs. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/22310188/nft-explainer-what-is-blockchain-crypto-art-faq&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.theverge.com/22310188/nft-explainer-what-is-blockchain-crypto-art-faq&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://theconversation.com/how-nonfungible-tokens-work-and-where-they-get-their-value-a-cryptocurrency-expert-explains-nfts-157489#:%7E:text=Besides%20gaming%2C%20NFTs%20are%20frequently,in%20Decentraland%2C%20a%20virtual%20world&quot;&amp;gt;https://theconversation.com/how-nonfungible-tokens-work-and-where-they-get-their-value-a-cryptocurrency-expert-explains-nfts-157489#:~:text=Besides%20gaming%2C%20NFTs%20are%20frequently,in%20Decentraland%2C%20a%20virtual%20world&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://hyperallergic.com/702309/artists-say-plagiarized-nfts-are-plaguing-their-community/&quot;&amp;gt;https://hyperallergic.com/702309/artists-say-plagiarized-nfts-are-plaguing-their-community/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Terminology?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;HODL = Hold On for Dear Life&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Hopium  =  Represents the belief that the situation will someday improve.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
FOMO = Fear of Missing Out&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
FUD = Fear, Uncertainty, and Doubt&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Bear/Bearish =  &amp;amp;quot;Bears&amp;amp;quot; believe that an asset, for example a digital currency, will decline in value.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
Bull/Bullish =  If a trader believes that an asset will rise in value, he or she is a &amp;amp;quot;bull.&amp;amp;quot; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://fintechmagazine.com/financial-services-finserv/140-blockchain-and-crypto-words-ultimate-z-glossary&quot;&amp;gt;https://fintechmagazine.com/financial-services-finserv/140-blockchain-and-crypto-words-ultimate-z-glossary&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Who the hell are you?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Who me? &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;I’m not a finical advisor&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. I work for a major software company as my full-time job, and manage Microsoft Active Directory and Azure AD. 😊I do however love the idea of blockchain, and what it can bring to the world. I also am a cofounder of Mirai Blockchain Group. A small team of industry professionals that have come together to support reputable chains and provide education to those looking to gain knowledge. We mange Stake Pools, for Cardano, and possible other chains in the future, like ETH. Delegate to our pool today and we can grow together! &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;MBCG&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Pool&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Find us on the web: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://mbcg.io/&quot;&amp;gt;https://mbcg.io&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Follow on Reddit for other great content! And follow on Linkedin: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/company/mirai-blockchain-group&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.linkedin.com/company/mirai-blockchain-group&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你讓索拉納負責倒下，卻假裝和諧號什麼都沒發生，你就是一個絕望的僞君子。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不持有任何SOL或ONE，我也不打算這樣做（至少不是很快），但我
但我知道，這個組織的大多數人都害怕索拉納，害怕到他們一直在散佈謠言。
以至於他們一直試圖散佈虛假信息，好像這部分人真的有任何影響力一樣。
你真的認爲5k的支持率會有字面意義上的......]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4adpl/if_you_hold_solana_accountable_for_going_down_but/?score=326&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4adpl%2Fif_you_hold_solana_accountable_for_going_down_but%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4adpl%2Fif_you_hold_solana_accountable_for_going_down_but%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4adpl/if_you_hold_solana_accountable_for_going_down_but/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 08:35:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I don’t hold any SOL or ONE and I don’t plan to do it (at least not soon) but I know that the majority of this sub is scared of Solana, so scared that they’re trying to spread FUD all the time, as if this sub actually has any influence on the market (you really think 5k upvotes will have literally any effect on the market?)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If one posts “LUL Solana is so garbage Ethereum never went down” for when Solana went down, but then post “it’s no big deal stuff happens” for when Harmony went down, that’s just desperate hypocritical behavior. Either hold them both accountable for the same problem, or don’t hold either accountable. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It’s easy to pass on circle-jerking sub and shilling random coins on this sub, but this one is just too sad and disgusting to look over imo.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[國會將就比特幣的能源使用舉行聽證會....oh boy....，這將帶來什麼樣的妖魔化、蠱惑人心和錯誤信息？？]]></title><description><![CDATA[國會宣佈就比特幣的能源使用舉行聽證會 - CryptoShameless
[https://cryptoshameless.com/2022/01/congress-announces-hearing-on-bitcoins-energy-use/]

所以聽證會從下週四，1月20日開始。誰會成爲國會山下的一個完全
在這些聽證會上，誰會成爲國會山的傻瓜？有多少...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s43xq7/congress_to_have_hearing_on_bitcoins_energy_useoh/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs43xq7%2Fcongress_to_have_hearing_on_bitcoins_energy_useoh%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs43xq7%2Fcongress_to_have_hearing_on_bitcoins_energy_useoh%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s43xq7/congress_to_have_hearing_on_bitcoins_energy_useoh/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 05:38:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptoshameless.com/2022/01/congress-announces-hearing-on-bitcoins-energy-use/&quot;&amp;gt;Congress Announces Hearing on Bitcoin’s Energy Use - CryptoShameless&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So the hearing starts next Thursday, Jan 20th.  Who&amp;amp;#39;s going to be the complete fool up there on capitol hill during these hearings?  How much just total idiocy will Maxine Waters show?  How about Brad Sherman?  Pick your favorite idiotic politician!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉不會接受DOGE....，這是現實，假裝能夠在特斯拉商店購買一些玩具或皮帶扣（835 DOGE）與實際採用是一回事，充其量是虛僞的。真正的採用=能夠使用DOGE購買S型車或網絡卡車。]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，像往常一樣，DOGE的月亮男孩對彌賽亞-伊隆發佈他的一個
毫無意義的推文......宣佈Telsa實際上不接受
DOGE作爲任何特斯拉車輛的付款。

以下是特斯拉將接受DOGE的內容。

> 特斯拉公司（TSLA.O）將接受基於備忘錄的...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4871s/tesla_will_not_be_accepting_doge_thats_the/?score=486&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4871s%2Ftesla_will_not_be_accepting_doge_thats_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4871s%2Ftesla_will_not_be_accepting_doge_thats_the%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4871s/tesla_will_not_be_accepting_doge_thats_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 04:52:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So as usual the DOGE moon boys are ecstatic that Messiah Elon posted one of his pointless tweets... to announce that Telsa would effectively NOT be accepting DOGE as payment for any Tesla vehicles.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here&amp;amp;#39;s what Tesla &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;will&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; be accepting DOGE for:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Tesla Inc (TSLA.O) will accept meme-based cryptocurrency dogecoin as payment for its &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;merchandise&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; such as the &amp;amp;quot;Giga Texas&amp;amp;quot; belt buckle and mini models of electric vehicles, Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk said in a tweet on Friday.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In other words, you can buy a few Tesla toys and a belt buckle like this one (835 DOGE):&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://shop.tesla.com/product/giga-texas-belt-buckle?sku=1758879-00-A&quot;&amp;gt;https://shop.tesla.com/product/giga-texas-belt-buckle?sku=1758879-00-A&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;DOGE had a predictable and modest 20% gain following the non news &amp;amp;#39;news&amp;amp;#39;, which probably enabled Elon to lighten his bags yet again.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/technology/tesla-merchandise-buyable-using-dogecoin-musk-says-tweet-2022-01-14/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.reuters.com/technology/tesla-merchandise-buyable-using-dogecoin-musk-says-tweet-2022-01-14/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To see that this really is becoming a joke, the EXACT SAME news was reported on the EXACT SAME DAY last month (14th December):
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/musk-says-tesla-will-accept-dogecoin-merchandise-2021-12-14/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.reuters.com/markets/us/musk-says-tesla-will-accept-dogecoin-merchandise-2021-12-14/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[維基百科編輯投票決定不將NFT列爲藝術，引發了加密貨幣社區的憤怒]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s44fhb/wikipedia_editors_have_voted_not_to_classify_nfts/?score=356&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs44fhb%2Fwikipedia_editors_have_voted_not_to_classify_nfts%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs44fhb%2Fwikipedia_editors_have_voted_not_to_classify_nfts%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s44fhb/wikipedia_editors_have_voted_not_to_classify_nfts/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 04:52:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特幣可能在今年年底前成爲湯加的法定貨幣]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3nwqc/bitcoin_could_become_legal_tender_in_tonga_by_the/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3nwqc%2Fbitcoin_could_become_legal_tender_in_tonga_by_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3nwqc%2Fbitcoin_could_become_legal_tender_in_tonga_by_the%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3nwqc/bitcoin_could_become_legal_tender_in_tonga_by_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 02:31:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你會選擇每年有保障的5萬美元的工資，直到死亡，還是現在就選擇100萬美元的加密貨幣。]]></title><description><![CDATA[假設你救了這個老人的命，他變成了有錢人，但他也喜歡和人玩，所以作爲禮物，他給了你一個禮物。
他也喜歡和人玩，所以作爲禮物，他給你提供了每年5萬美元的工資，直到你死爲止，但條件是你不能將其投資。
50,000美元，直到你死，條件是你不能投資任何東西，或
100萬美元在任何你想要的加密貨幣中，不能...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4268h/would_you_take_a_guaranteed_50000_a_year_salary/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4268h%2Fwould_you_take_a_guaranteed_50000_a_year_salary%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs4268h%2Fwould_you_take_a_guaranteed_50000_a_year_salary%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s4268h/would_you_take_a_guaranteed_50000_a_year_salary/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 02:31:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So let&amp;amp;#39;s say you saved this old man&amp;amp;#39;s life and he turned out to be rich but he also likes to play with people so as a gift he offers you a yearly salary of $50,000 until you die with the condition that you cannot invest any of it, or $1,000,000 in any crypto currency you want that cannot be withdrawn for a minimum of five years.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;$50,000 would have to be spent fully every year.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;$1,000,000 in crypto could not be moved for five years.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Of you choose the one million in crypto, which one would you choose?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我開了一家出租私人飛機的公司，接受BTC 🙌。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我靠着從軍隊退休後的一點收入，已經環遊世界5年了。
從軍隊退休後，我在南美遇到了一個了不起的女人。

我們剛剛開了一傢俬人包機公司（她已經在這個領域工作了6年）。
6年了）。而且我們很自豪地接受BTC。

我曾經看到，在...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s3xhfl/i_opened_a_company_that_rents_private_planes_and/?score=338&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs3xhfl%2Fi_opened_a_company_that_rents_private_planes_and%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs3xhfl%2Fi_opened_a_company_that_rents_private_planes_and%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s3xhfl/i_opened_a_company_that_rents_private_planes_and/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 01:46:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I have been traveling the world for 5 years on a small income from my medical retirement from the military and met an amazing woman in South America. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We just opened a private charter jet company (she has been working in this space for 6 years). And we proudly accept BTC. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I once saw the power in using crypto when I paid for part of my stay at a hotel in Colombia where my payment hit their account in minutes. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The banking system is too slow. And they have too much power over our money. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I will be having meetings with other brokers and charter jet providers about accepting Bitcoin too. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto is the revolution this world needs and I love to be a part of this movement in a small way.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Loopring - 深入探討]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，夥計們，我是Spragg，我在YouTube（SpraggTalksMoney）上對各種不同的硬幣/代幣進行了深入的研究。
我想既然我已經爲我的視頻寫好了腳本，那麼我也會在這裏發佈摘要。
我想既然我已經爲我的視頻寫了腳本，我也會在這裏發佈摘要。

如果有人對未總結的完整版本感興趣，鏈接是...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3zv3b/loopring_a_deep_dive/?score=320&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3zv3b%2Floopring_a_deep_dive%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3zv3b%2Floopring_a_deep_dive%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3zv3b/loopring_a_deep_dive/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 00:32:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hey guys, Im Spragg, I do deep dives into various different coins/tokens on youtube (SpraggTalksMoney), I thought since I’ve already written the scripts for my video anyway I’d post the summary on here too.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If anyone’s interested in the full un-summarized version the link is here: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/j5cEdmAeICU&quot;&amp;gt;https://youtu.be/j5cEdmAeICU&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Preface&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the top 40 tokens ranked by market cap only 6 aren’t on Ethereum, with those being on the Binance smart chain, but this makes sense, if you were opening a shop in real life, you’d want to do it where the people are, and not in the middle of the countryside. Ethereum, while long maintaining it’s position as the largest smart contract chain does have its problems, those being gas fees and congestion.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This means that while anything built on Ethereum gets the benefits of decentralisation and security, it inherits those problems too.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;DEXs are in my opinion though are some of the most important aspects to the free trade of crypto, allowing for swapping between any on chain, or wrapped asset, but if you wanted to perform a trade on uniswap now you’d be paying well over $150 in fees.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And this is where loopring comes in, aiming to not only solve these existing problems and provide a completely new take on how DEX’s should function.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Foundation&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Like a lot of the current markets most promising protocols, Loopring, created by Daniel Wang an ex google software engineer, first appeared in the form of an ICO in the 2017 bull run raising 45 million. Unfortunately, Daniel and his team are based in Shanghai, and as we all know China loves to flip flop on their crypto regulation, coming out with new laws outlawing ICO’s forcing the Loopring Foundation to refund most of the funds earnt. However, from the ICO there was 20k Ethereum not refunded, which at the time was worth around 7.5 million, and with this they forged on with the creation of the Loopring protocol.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Unlike a lot of projects in the crypto space that start their marketing extremely early to try and hook investors sometimes before the product even has a working first version, Looping’s focus was on creating the product and then letting it sell itself. Arguably had the market not become so crowded with people almost acting like salesmen trying to shove any half-baked crypto project down people’s throats this strategy probably would’ve worked.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This isn’t to say that the company isn’t starting to move towards providing a greater feature set such as Ethereum virtual machine compatibility but given how tight lipped they’ve been on the topic shows that they don’t want this to dominate the narrative of what the platform actually currently does.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Loopring Protocol&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Loopring aims to give anyone the tools to build their own DEX but without needing to go through any of the problems in actually starting a DEX, Loopring is to decentralised exchanges what the Tendermint SDK is to Proof of stake. Its certainly not the only way to do it, but it cuts out a large portion of the groundwork required.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At the core of Loopring is a Zero Knowledge Proof rollup layer built on top of the Ethereum base chain, since not many people know what this actually is or entails, I thought Id briefly explain it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Zero Knowledge proof is not unique to crypto, it in fact pre-dates it by over 25 years, and is a cryptographic protocol that allows a party to prove that a statement is true to a recipient party, what makes it significant though is that the recipient party doesn’t need to be privy to any potentially secret information that goes into proving the statement.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Think of it like a magic trick, if a magician said he could predict the suit and number of a card we will draw from a deck of cards, and then proceeds to do it and get it right, we can assume that it wasn’t just sheer luck, and that he can in fact do what he says he can, but we as the second party have no idea how the trick was done.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So when we apply this to crypto we get the ability to prove to the base chain that something happening on a side chain or layer 2 is verifiably true, which as we all know is extremely important in a trustless environment like a blockchain.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So now we move onto the rollup part, on the base chain, in this case Ethereum, a transaction is a single monetary transfer from a to b, this means that to process 100 transfers, you need 100 transactions.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A much more efficient way of doing this would be to process 100 transfers and put them all through at once under a single transaction. The problem with doing this however is the blockchain can only verify the transaction and not data within the event log of the transaction and so in this case it would assume the 100 transactions are all invalid and reject them unless it could be proven otherwise.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, to combine this all together, a zkRollup works by performing transactions off chain, and then submitting them back to the main chain as a single transaction with the proof required to confirm that what happened off chain still conforms to the base chain’s rules, and that they’re all valid transactions so that the base chain can process them accordingly as though it had done the work itself.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This technology is what Loopring uses along with Relayers to allow anyone to create a DEX and keep gas fees low.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;At the core of everything is the loopring relayer. The relayer is in charge of virtually everything in the ecosystem, from generating the proofs, building blocks, matching orderbooks and more.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The loopring protocol will work with any relayer, however there is currently a single canonical relayer being used which is run by the Loopring foundation, now I do have some concerns about this which I will, as usual, cover at the end, but all you need to know is that the Loopring protocol is entirely non-custodial.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Token Supply and Distribution&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There’s currently 1.2 billion LRC in circulation, which is 100 million less than the max supply of 1.3 billion which is due to the fact that a portion of the supply has been burnt.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Any operation the loopring protocol will incur a fee, same as performing any action on the blockchain, in the case of Loopring this is just 0.3% of the transaction value, where 0.2% is returned to the liquidity providers as incentive and 0.1% goes to the loopring DAO.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The use of the LRC value held by the Loopring DAO is voted on, with the options for its use being grants to incentivize partnerships, impermanent loss protection, liquidity incentives on top of the 0.2% fee, and then finally burning LRC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Concerns&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Firstly, despite the protocol being Relayer agnostic, that is to say that anyone can build a relayer and start to perform network actions, the only current Relayer operated by the Loopring foundation. This unfortunately does mean that there’s a centralised aspect to the network as it currently stands.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now, hopefully I’ve done a good enough job of explaining why this isn’t an immediate red flag for the platform, given that the entire point is to be non-custodial and have layers on layers of protocol specifics to ensure that control is always entirely in the user’s hands, I just personally don’t like the fact that the security of an investment into LRC would depend on the Loopring foundation upkeeping that relayer.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And my second concern is to do with marketting.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As it stands currently loopring has $450m locked within the contract, which for a project sitting at 2.1 billion market cap is lower than I would’ve expected. Take Curve for example, which is sitting only 100 million dollars higher in market cap but has over 20 billion dollars locked by it’s contract on Ethereum alone.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This on its own might not be cause for concern but the DEX created by the Loopring foundation was born out of being unable to secure partners to build their own DEX’s and show off the platform. This to me shows that for the platform to survive, more of an emphasis needs to be placed on getting the protocol out into the wider DeFi audience and not just within the retail space where it currently seems to be sitting.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對市場來說是個好消息。USDC在以太坊上的供應量首次超過了競爭對手USDT的供應量]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3y8av/good_news_for_the_market_usdcs_supply_on_ethereum/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3y8av%2Fgood_news_for_the_market_usdcs_supply_on_ethereum%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3y8av%2Fgood_news_for_the_market_usdcs_supply_on_ethereum%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3y8av/good_news_for_the_market_usdcs_supply_on_ethereum/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 23:40:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[[OC]蘋果股票在2021年沒有超過比特幣的表現]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s40bf0/oc_apple_stock_did_not_outperform_bitcoin_in_2021/?score=347&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs40bf0%2Foc_apple_stock_did_not_outperform_bitcoin_in_2021%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs40bf0%2Foc_apple_stock_did_not_outperform_bitcoin_in_2021%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s40bf0/oc_apple_stock_did_not_outperform_bitcoin_in_2021/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 23:40:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[6年前的這一天，比特幣開發者Mike Hearn宣佈比特幣失敗了，並賣掉了他所有的比特幣。當時的匯率是430美元。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3tnxb/on_this_day_6_years_ago_bitcoin_developer_mike/?score=318&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3tnxb%2Fon_this_day_6_years_ago_bitcoin_developer_mike%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3tnxb%2Fon_this_day_6_years_ago_bitcoin_developer_mike%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3tnxb/on_this_day_6_years_ago_bitcoin_developer_mike/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 22:32:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特幣將於今年年底在湯加成爲法定貨幣]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s3sdy3/bitcoin_set_to_be_legal_tender_in_tonga_by_end_of/?score=304&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs3sdy3%2Fbitcoin_set_to_be_legal_tender_in_tonga_by_end_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs3sdy3%2Fbitcoin_set_to_be_legal_tender_in_tonga_by_end_of%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s3sdy3/bitcoin_set_to_be_legal_tender_in_tonga_by_end_of/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 21:44:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特幣是數字黃金。歷史即使不重演，也會押韻的。"6102號行政命令 "來了!]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://preview.redd.it/i5o29ekxmnb81.png?width=700&format=png&auto=webp&s=c25fe2c48eec3268d3b9c99dd34fb083e286ea25

美國國稅局今年早些時候透露，它在本財政年度已經扣押了35億美元。
2021年。據報道，美國政府今年已經扣押了170,000%以上的
今年的加密貨幣...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s3saqk/bitcoin_is_digital_gold_history_if_not_repeats/?score=322&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs3saqk%2Fbitcoin_is_digital_gold_history_if_not_repeats%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs3saqk%2Fbitcoin_is_digital_gold_history_if_not_repeats%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s3saqk/bitcoin_is_digital_gold_history_if_not_repeats/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 19:38:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/i5o29ekxmnb81.png?width=700&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=c25fe2c48eec3268d3b9c99dd34fb083e286ea25&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/i5o29ekxmnb81.png?width=700&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=c25fe2c48eec3268d3b9c99dd34fb083e286ea25&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;The  IRS revealed earlier this year that it has seized $3.5 billion in the  fiscal year 2021. According to reports, the US government has seized  170,000% more cryptocurrency this year than it did in 2019. Jarod  Koopman, director of the Internal Revenue Service&amp;amp;#39;s cybercrime unit&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://news.coincu.com/47346-us-seized-1700x-more-cryptocurrency/&quot;&amp;gt;https://news.coincu.com/47346-us-seized-1700x-more-cryptocurrency/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;--------------------------------------------------------------&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Executive Order 6102&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; is an &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Executive_order_(United_States&quot;&amp;gt;executive order&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;) signed on April 5, 1933, by &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/US_President&quot;&amp;gt;US President&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Franklin_D._Roosevelt&quot;&amp;gt;Franklin D. Roosevelt&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;amp;quot;forbidding the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hoarding_(economics&quot;&amp;gt;hoarding&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;) of &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gold_coin&quot;&amp;gt;gold coin&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gold_bullion&quot;&amp;gt;gold bullion&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gold_certificates&quot;&amp;gt;gold certificates&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; within the continental United States.&amp;amp;quot; The executive order was made under the authority of the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trading_with_the_Enemy_Act_of_1917&quot;&amp;gt;Trading with the Enemy Act of 1917&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, as amended by the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Emergency_Banking_Act&quot;&amp;gt;Emergency Banking Act&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; in March 1933.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The stated reason for the order was that hard times had caused &amp;amp;quot;hoarding&amp;amp;quot; of gold, stalling economic growth and worsening the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Great_Depression&quot;&amp;gt;depression&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; as the US was then using  the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gold_standard&quot;&amp;gt;gold standard&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for its currency.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Presidential_Proclamation&quot;&amp;gt;Presidential Proclamation&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikisource.org/wiki/Proclamation_2039&quot;&amp;gt;2039&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;  that forbade the hoarding &amp;amp;#39;of gold or silver coin or bullion or  currency&amp;amp;#39;, under penalty of $10,000 and/or up to five to ten years  imprisonment.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[只是想和你們分享我的數字貨幣的實物藝術。興奮地看到加密貨幣（尤其是比特幣）的長期前景以及它對世界的影響。藝術作品完全由筆和一些金箔完成。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s38ctb/just_wanted_to_share_my_physical_art_of_a_digital/?score=305&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs38ctb%2Fjust_wanted_to_share_my_physical_art_of_a_digital%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs38ctb%2Fjust_wanted_to_share_my_physical_art_of_a_digital%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s38ctb/just_wanted_to_share_my_physical_art_of_a_digital/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 19:38:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[最新採訪@100trillionUSD! 
我們討論。
 - 2021年#比特幣爲何錯過10萬美元
 - 2021年B計劃最驚訝的是什麼
 - 2022年B計劃最擔心的是什麼
 - 利率上升，通貨膨脹 
 - 股票風險溢價
 - 他的比特幣&amp; S2F起源故事

https://t.co/xdYePMtfTj https://t.co/2iMV3wZQ5L]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1482052060891815936/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1482052060891815936/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 18:44:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[和諧"（ONE）已經停機，我討厭它。]]></title><description><![CDATA[從今天早上開始，和諧網絡再次陷入停頓。見
https://explorer.harmony.one/blocks/shard/0 爲證。我非常矛盾
我對這件事的感受。從2021年初開始，我一直是ONE的支持者和粉絲。
的支持者和粉絲，我對未來感到非常興奮，因爲神奇的DApps是...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3nknw/harmony_one_is_down_and_i_hate_it/?score=303&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3nknw%2Fharmony_one_is_down_and_i_hate_it%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3nknw%2Fharmony_one_is_down_and_i_hate_it%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3nknw/harmony_one_is_down_and_i_hate_it/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 18:44:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As of this morning, the Harmony network grinded to a halt yet again. See &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://explorer.harmony.one/blocks/shard/0&quot;&amp;gt;https://explorer.harmony.one/blocks/shard/0&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for proof. I&amp;amp;#39;m super conflicted on how I feel about this. I have been a ONE supporter and fan from early 2021 onward, and I&amp;amp;#39;m super excited for the future since amazing dApps are being built on it as we speak. It seems so odd that they have dozens of people working on development, but somehow they can&amp;amp;#39;t figure out how to handle their RPC or prevent/fix spam attacks on the network.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The main reason I&amp;amp;#39;m going to stick around is the amazing group of people and developers that are in this space. The developer of &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://fuzz.fi&quot;&amp;gt;fuzz.fi&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; decided to run his own RPC and there&amp;amp;#39;s a couple of other groups/people as well that try to support the Harmony Ecosystem in any way they can.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Props to the people that are working on this 24/7, but it&amp;amp;#39;s time to grow up and fix stuff. We&amp;amp;#39;re a Top50 coin now, time to move forward, onwards and upwards!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[非常看好BAT! 在Brave上運行的廣告活動的數量正在大規模增長!]]></title><description><![CDATA[最新的數字詳細說明了目前正在全球範圍內進行的廣告活動的數量
目前在Brave上運行的廣告活動數量是驚人的!

今天，有5525個廣告活動正在有效地運行，並被用戶看到!

這些數字是一個新的...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3qy01/very_bullish_for_bat_the_amount_of_ad_campaigns/?score=340&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3qy01%2Fvery_bullish_for_bat_the_amount_of_ad_campaigns%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3qy01%2Fvery_bullish_for_bat_the_amount_of_ad_campaigns%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3qy01/very_bullish_for_bat_the_amount_of_ad_campaigns/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 17:35:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The newest numbers detailing the amount of ad campaigns that are currently running on Brave worldwide are staggering!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Today there are 5525 campaigns effectively running and being seen by the users!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;These number is a new ATH!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/h4fzamv48nb81.png?width=720&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=398e4817bbbf0c7b7e821fa30e710c2930005165&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/h4fzamv48nb81.png?width=720&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=398e4817bbbf0c7b7e821fa30e710c2930005165&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The increase of campaigns is massive: on this day in 2021 there were 1359 campaigns running.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This means a plus of over 300% in one year!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Calculated for half a year, taking the 14th of June 2021 as the day, we see 4085 campaigns.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Which in turn gives us a growth of over 35% in 6 month!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Of course not all the regions have the same amount of ads shown. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;the top 10 regions are as following:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/gsxkcgjg8nb81.jpg?width=1030&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=6d3aacaa3133c0de75773268e33d6ed876b1aead&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/gsxkcgjg8nb81.jpg?width=1030&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=6d3aacaa3133c0de75773268e33d6ed876b1aead&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To find out how many and what ads are being shown in your region, visit  &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://sampson.codes/brave/ads/my_region/&quot;&amp;gt;Brave Ads in My Region (sampson.codes)&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; .&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To see examples of ads run around the world, visit  &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://brave.photos/&quot;&amp;gt;Home - Brave browser sponsored image archive&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Ad campaigns are bought with BAT or the any other currency, which will be exchanged to BAT by Brave. Brave in turn will redistribute the earned BAT as rewards to the users.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The digital ad industry today is worth hundreds of billions, and will grow to a trillion+ dollar industry this decade.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Those numbers are really bullish for the future of Brave and its token BAT, and i feel like the future is really bright for this project!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[r/CryptoCurrency Predictions Tournament ]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3v6wh/rcryptocurrency_predictions_tournament/?score=2114&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3v6wh%2Frcryptocurrency_predictions_tournament%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3v6wh%2Frcryptocurrency_predictions_tournament%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3v6wh/rcryptocurrency_predictions_tournament/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 16:36:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[里約熱內盧市長將把市財政的1%投資於比特幣]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s3r10q/rio_de_janeiros_mayor_to_invest_1_of_the_citys/?score=540&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs3r10q%2Frio_de_janeiros_mayor_to_invest_1_of_the_citys%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs3r10q%2Frio_de_janeiros_mayor_to_invest_1_of_the_citys%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s3r10q/rio_de_janeiros_mayor_to_invest_1_of_the_citys/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 15:39:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我不想這麼說，但很多較新的加密貨幣投資者不是在投資，而是在賭博。]]></title><description><![CDATA[大多數新手認爲，加密貨幣是可以讓你一夜暴富的東西。
他們最終在 "月球 "之前投資於低市值幣。當然
他們中的一些人可能有潛力給你帶來巨大的回報，但很多
人最終完全忽視了風險......]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3qrsk/i_hate_to_say_it_but_a_lot_of_the_newer_crypto/?score=377&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3qrsk%2Fi_hate_to_say_it_but_a_lot_of_the_newer_crypto%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3qrsk%2Fi_hate_to_say_it_but_a_lot_of_the_newer_crypto%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3qrsk/i_hate_to_say_it_but_a_lot_of_the_newer_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 13:39:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Most newbies think that Crypto is something that will make you rich overnight, and they end up investing in low market cap coins before they &amp;amp;quot;moon&amp;amp;quot;. Of course a few of them might have the potential to give you great returns, but a lot of people completely end up ignoring the risk factor. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;CryptoMoonShots vs &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/r/Cryptocurrency&quot;&amp;gt;r/Cryptocurrency&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/azvhoo2o3nb81.png?width=1099&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d6668d709c5ff7f2f82bd1a4ef1ce276700af48d&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/azvhoo2o3nb81.png?width=1099&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d6668d709c5ff7f2f82bd1a4ef1ce276700af48d&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The CryptoMoonShots subreddit has even started to outpace the Cryptocurrency subreddit in terms of growth. It is a terrible thing to see considering the vast majority of the cryptocurrencies advertised there there are complete scam projects. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Don&amp;amp;#39;t get me wrong. Some low market coins do have great utility and great future potential, but when you start going lower into the low millions or hundreds of thousands, the risk far outweighs their benefits.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you are new to Crypto, the best thing you can do in Crypto is DCA and accumulate larger projects for the long term. Crypto is not the stock market, and deviating away from trusted projects or trying to rely on technical analysis is very risky.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TLDR: Unfortunately a lot of the newbies that are joining Crypto are completely ignoring even top 100 coins and are choosing to put their money in these shady &amp;amp;quot;get rich quick&amp;amp;quot; schemes which is nothing short of gambling.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[霹靂：巴西里約熱內盧市將把該市1%的儲備金分配給#比特幣 😎]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1481944405418332168/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1481944405418332168/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 12:54:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[什麼是 "gamma"，爲什麼#btc用戶應該理解期權理論中的希臘語？

https://t.co/Hat6xtZ8l4]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1481931850465656834/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1481931850465656834/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 12:54:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爆炸性新聞：比特幣案件繼續成倍增加。Segwit變體現在最常見。專家警告說，新的Taproot變體將在未來幾年成倍增長。"根本沒有辦法阻止它！" https://t.co/VtKm69uJwY]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1481959250251464706/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1481959250251464706/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 12:54:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[衛生部長已經得出結論，不再需要Covid認證，因爲Omicron浪潮緩解了https://t.co/LVE4ay5a7W]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1481931586685779969/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1481931586685779969/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 12:54:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[*U.K.將在本月放棄Covid通行證：時報]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1481927731495550980/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1481927731495550980/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 10:40:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特斯拉將接受Dogecoin!]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3k0si/tesla_to_accept_dogecoin/?score=328&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3k0si%2Ftesla_to_accept_dogecoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3k0si%2Ftesla_to_accept_dogecoin%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3k0si/tesla_to_accept_dogecoin/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 10:40:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[EMA預示着，在危機的這一時刻，Omicron成爲中心舞臺，補充管理將被撤回。 幾乎所有的案件都被掃除，使得任何額外的訂閱計劃都變得過時。https://t.co/XPvXkUpPZO]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1481924131343974402/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1481924131343974402/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 09:47:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[另一個僅有0.000072%的網絡比特幣礦工贏得了6.25個比特幣的區塊獎勵，價值27.3萬美元! 這是一週內第二次發生這種情況，每次的概率都是1/400,000。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s342nd/another_solo_bitcoin_miner_with_just_0000072_of/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs342nd%2Fanother_solo_bitcoin_miner_with_just_0000072_of%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs342nd%2Fanother_solo_bitcoin_miner_with_just_0000072_of%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s342nd/another_solo_bitcoin_miner_with_just_0000072_of/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 08:39:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑞波公司律師指責SEC故意拖延訴訟]]></title><description><![CDATA[瑞波（XRP）陣營的頂級律師之一Stuart Alderoty最近在Twitter上抨擊了美國證券交易委員會（SEC）。
在Twitter上對美國證券交易委員會（SEC）進行了抨擊。
根據Alderoty的說法，SEC會故意拖延他們與瑞波公司之間的訴訟
儘可能地拖延他們與瑞波公司之間的訴訟。



瑞波公司...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s35m78/ripple_lawyer_accuses_sec_of_intentional_delay/?score=308&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs35m78%2Fripple_lawyer_accuses_sec_of_intentional_delay%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs35m78%2Fripple_lawyer_accuses_sec_of_intentional_delay%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s35m78/ripple_lawyer_accuses_sec_of_intentional_delay/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 08:39:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;One of the top lawyers in the Ripple (XRP) camp, Stuart Alderoty, recently lashed out at the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) on Twitter. According to Alderoty, the SEC would deliberately try to delay the lawsuit between themselves and Ripple as long as possible.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Ripple lawsuit&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Ripple, meanwhile, has been embroiled in an infamous lawsuit with the US SEC for over a year. The SEC accuses Ripple of selling securities in the past without the necessary licenses. At the moment, Ripple is hopeful that the lawsuit will soon come to an end and the judge will finally issue a ruling. However, Alderoty lashed out at the SEC on Twitter. He believes that the SEC does not want the court case to end any time soon.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/jisowqdswhb81.png?width=498&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=4e9c680ce369d60ff1003268f0fa06d86912468a&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/jisowqdswhb81.png?width=498&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=4e9c680ce369d60ff1003268f0fa06d86912468a&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Gary Gensler&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In the series of Twitter messages, Alderoty responds to a message from SEC Chairman Gary Gensler. Gensler revealed why, in his opinion, enforcement of rules is one of the SEC&amp;amp;#39;s most important tasks. Soccer without referees would turn into an unfair occupation in no time according to Gensler. If teams don&amp;amp;#39;t have to worry about penalties and enforcement of the rules, things will go wrong. The same goes for the markets, according to Gensler. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/dmwxeixuwhb81.png?width=509&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=0ef5caa037c3fe6e1f067f0eed849ae04b274c14&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/dmwxeixuwhb81.png?width=509&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=0ef5caa037c3fe6e1f067f0eed849ae04b274c14&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Alderoty argues that the SEC is guilty of &amp;amp;quot;regulation by enforcement.&amp;amp;quot; That by simply initiating a lawsuit against an entity they are trying to control certain markets. This is also why, according to Alderoty, the SEC does not seem to be in any particular hurry in the lawsuit.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Ripple&amp;amp;#39;s CEO, Brad Garlinghouse, still seemed convinced in November of last year that the lawsuit will end this year. In addition, he is hopeful that the judge&amp;amp;#39;s ruling will also be in Ripple&amp;amp;#39;s favor.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[儘管我不願意承認，但反月球的農民可能有一個觀點。]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，在花了幾個月的時間在這個子上，看到人們
抱怨月球農民和不斷的轉帖，我終於不得不同意
同意同樣的東西確實被反覆張貼。我按 "新 "分類，因爲
想閱讀和評論全新的帖子，現在我已經...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3fwib/as_much_as_i_hate_to_admit_it_the_anti_moon/?score=331&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3fwib%2Fas_much_as_i_hate_to_admit_it_the_anti_moon%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3fwib%2Fas_much_as_i_hate_to_admit_it_the_anti_moon%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3fwib/as_much_as_i_hate_to_admit_it_the_anti_moon/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 07:32:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So After Spending time on this sub for a couple of months and seeing people complain about moon farmers and constant repost, I am finally going to have to agree that the same thing does get posted over and over again. I sort by New due to wanting to read and comment on brand new post and I have now seen this  post about Kim kardashian and Floyd Maywether getting sued over some crypto scam posted Dozens of times if not hundreds. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I would like to state up front that I am in favor of moon farming but feel like a little bit of effort should be put in, not just constantly posting news articles that have already been posted. I am not asking for much, just a quick search to see if its been posted ten times in the last hour already. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Is there a solution to this? Perhaps&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But I dont have any answers or the power to make any changes on this sub, I just wanted to let you guys know that Kim and Floyd are getting sued and its crypto related.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now that everybody knows this, please stop posting the same articles over and over and I will give every post after mine that is not a news article an award until I run out of my Reddit coins.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thank you for attending my Rant, and may you be blessed with awards and moons in this difficult time.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Edit: I&amp;amp;#39;ve been awarding every new post, but I had to skip the anti ALGO post because I&amp;amp;#39;m pro ALGO and Silvio would get mad at me.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特幣哈希率已經達到183 Exahash，創歷史新高。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s34fbd/bitcoin_hash_rate_has_reached_183_exahash_a_new/?score=310&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs34fbd%2Fbitcoin_hash_rate_has_reached_183_exahash_a_new%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs34fbd%2Fbitcoin_hash_rate_has_reached_183_exahash_a_new%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s34fbd/bitcoin_hash_rate_has_reached_183_exahash_a_new/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 05:40:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[富達公司是世界上最大的資產管理公司之一，管理着4.9萬億美元的資產。他們這樣寫道。]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 我們也認爲這裏有非常高風險的博弈理論在起作用，即如果
> 比特幣的應用增加，今天確保一些比特幣的國家將
> 在競爭中會比他們的同行更有優勢。因此，即使其他
> 國家不相信這個投資理論或採用...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3fzes/fidelity_is_one_of_the_largest_asset_managers_in/?score=358&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3fzes%2Ffidelity_is_one_of_the_largest_asset_managers_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3fzes%2Ffidelity_is_one_of_the_largest_asset_managers_in%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3fzes/fidelity_is_one_of_the_largest_asset_managers_in/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 04:49:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We also think there is very high stakes game theory at play here, whereby if bitcoin adoption increases, the countries that secure some bitcoin today will be better off competitively than their peers. Therefore, even if other countries do not believe in the investment thesis or adoption of bitcoin, they will be forced to acquire some as a form of insurance. In other words, a small cost can be paid today as a hedge compared to a potentially much larger cost years in the future. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;We therefore wouldn&amp;amp;#39;t be surprised to see other sovereign nation states acquire bitcoin in 2022 and perhaps even see a central bank make an acquisition.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fidelitydigitalassets.com/articles/2021-trends-impact&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.fidelitydigitalassets.com/articles/2021-trends-impact&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我昨天被騙了，因爲我去年做了一件事。一個關於錢包聯繫的教訓。]]></title><description><![CDATA[幾個月前，當我剛接觸加密貨幣時，我把我的Metamask錢包連接到一個網站上
來提取一些資金。實際上，我這樣做了幾次，都沒有問題。它
它似乎和任何交易所一樣可靠 - 煎餅交換，1英寸，uniswap，raydium。
等等。

當我使用它時，該網站甚至被Haze crypto驗證過...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s2tpmx/i_got_scammed_yesterday_from_something_that_i_did/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs2tpmx%2Fi_got_scammed_yesterday_from_something_that_i_did%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs2tpmx%2Fi_got_scammed_yesterday_from_something_that_i_did%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=true</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s2tpmx/i_got_scammed_yesterday_from_something_that_i_did/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 04:49:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Months ago, when I was new to crypto, I connected my Metamask wallet to a site  to withdraw some funds. I did this a few times actually without  issues. It seemed as reliable as any exchange - pancake swap, 1inch,  uniswap,  raydium, etc...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The site was even verified by Haze crypto when I used it months ago, but it has since been updated and now warns of the site as a scam. I&amp;amp;#39;m unsure if  I&amp;amp;#39;m allowed to post the name of the exchange site, a mod can tell me if its ok. I actually hadn&amp;amp;#39;t even used the site this year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The scammers were patient. They waited until the wallet had more funds in it than it did when first connected. Around $1400 BUSD worth.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How did it happen?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I found the transaction on bscscan and traced the wallet address back to the exchange site. I remembered using it once last year, but not much more. So I decided to create another wallet and conducted some tiny transactions to try to figure out how the scam worked.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is what I believe happened.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The wallet was connected to the exchange like any other. The exchange was audited and seemed legit. I performed tiny transaction of some BUSD and the approval request from Metamask appeared. Looking carefully, I noticed that the approval button was designed to approve THREE (3) transactions. One was the transacrtion I had made, but one of the other transactions was &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;an authorisation for the exchange to withdraw up to $100000000 BUSD!&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What the hell? I never noticed a transaction like that before. I checked my main Metamask and found the same type of authorisation last year. Shit. Somehow hidden among normal transactions I had approved a request to allow this exchange to withdraw funds whenever they fucking wanted. All they had to do was watch my wallet transactions and determine a point when they thought I currently had a lot more money than usual stored.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How to prevent in the future?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Naturally, I was concerned that I had conducted similar type transaction approval requests in the past, so I started to research how to check who/what else has access to my wallet. I fortunately fopund nothing else of concern. But I wanted to share how to check it for yourselves.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Firstly, Make sure that existing connected sites are accurate.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Anything   you don&amp;amp;#39;t use anymore, or worse, don&amp;amp;#39;t recognise should be immediately   removed. This is easy to do. Open your wallet, click the three dots  and  select &amp;amp;#39;connected sites&amp;amp;#39;, browse through the list and revoke  anything  that you don&amp;amp;#39;t want.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Secondly, revoke any tokens. This is likely something very few people do.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;And this is how I got scammed.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For Ethereum Mainnet/Binance Smart Chain, visit the site token checker on ethscan/bscscan. Enter your ETH/BSC wallet address and browse though the list. Revoke anything you no longer use.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;EDIT:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Thank you to all the people who DMd and thanked me for alerting them to the issue of token approval. Some people said they found dozens of connected sites and tokens that they hadn&amp;amp;#39;t touched in a very long time. I&amp;amp;#39;m grateful some people found my experience beneficial.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The mod said it was ok to post a screenshot. See below. The issue that I was trying to raise was not so much the site itself, but the ability for most sites to connect your token with unlimited access.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/a9hrz7obtfb81.png?width=720&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e88d709d37ca3e3fe22ef7686ecdc038e7bc1392&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/a9hrz7obtfb81.png?width=720&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e88d709d37ca3e3fe22ef7686ecdc038e7bc1392&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我討厭Facebook（一家以操縱隱私而聞名的公司）進入加密貨幣市場（一個依靠隱私而繁榮的市場）的事實。]]></title><description><![CDATA[或至少曾經依靠隱私而繁榮，現在幾乎所有集中式交易所都有KYC這樣的東西。
幾乎每個集中式交易所都有KYC這樣的東西。

但是，仍然沒有一個集中式交易所會像Facebook的Meta那樣糟糕。

我鄙視他們。他們竊取我們的私人信息，賣給公司做廣告
定向。

看着市場如何...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3exuk/i_hate_the_fact_that_facebook_a_company_known_for/?score=365&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3exuk%2Fi_hate_the_fact_that_facebook_a_company_known_for%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs3exuk%2Fi_hate_the_fact_that_facebook_a_company_known_for%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s3exuk/i_hate_the_fact_that_facebook_a_company_known_for/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 04:49:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Or at least used to thrive off of privacy now that there are things like KYC on almost every centralized exchange.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But still, no centralized exchange will ever be as bad as Facebook’s Meta.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I despise them. They steal our private info to sell to companies for ad targeting.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Watch how the market will start getting littered with ads (even ones unrelated to crypto) once Meta starts monopolizing the crypto space.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I think the only way to avoid this would be through allowing publishers to motorize without ads through users’ processing power. Networks like Gather are already doing that so lets hope this swerves away companies like Facebook and Google.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我投資]]></title><description><![CDATA[我18歲，從事一份我討厭的快餐工作。開始投資每筆50美元
發薪。你認爲這夠嗎？太少了嗎？有什麼建議或提示給
的建議或提示？]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s3awze/i_invested/?score=336&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs3awze%2Fi_invested%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs3awze%2Fi_invested%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s3awze/i_invested/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 04:49:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m 18 years old, working a fast food job I hate. Started investing $50 every paycheck. Do you think this is enough? Too little? Any suggestions or tips for someone new to bitcoin?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[歷史上最大的事件之一剛剛發生，沒有人注意到。]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://investor.ncr.com/news-releases/news-release-details/ncr-completes-acquisition-cryptocurrency-leader-libertyx



NCR公司是美國曆史上最具統治力的財富500強上市公司之一。
美國曆史上最主要的上市公司之一。他們自1925年以來一直在紐約證券交易所上市交易，價值數十億美元。
他們是美國最受歡迎的公司之一。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s3fpwd/one_of_the_biggest_events_in_history_has_just/?score=817&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs3fpwd%2Fone_of_the_biggest_events_in_history_has_just%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs3fpwd%2Fone_of_the_biggest_events_in_history_has_just%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s3fpwd/one_of_the_biggest_events_in_history_has_just/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 04:49:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://investor.ncr.com/news-releases/news-release-details/ncr-completes-acquisition-cryptocurrency-leader-libertyx&quot;&amp;gt;https://investor.ncr.com/news-releases/news-release-details/ncr-completes-acquisition-cryptocurrency-leader-libertyx&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;NCR Corp. is one of the most dominate publicly traded fortune 500 companies in US history.  They have been traded on the NYSE since 1925 and are worth billions. They are the company behind practically every cash register and self check out kiosk in the world. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Walmart, McDonalds, Starbucks, Home Depot, Wendy&amp;amp;#39;s - name a mega business and NCR runs the cash register software for it.  Basically the entire global retail and hospitality industries use NCR. They now plan to offer Bitcoin on all of these devices.  Bitcoin payments, bitcoin custody, bitcoin exchange - literally everywhere. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Hyperbitcoinization is imminent and we haven&amp;amp;#39;t heard a word about it in the media. Spread the word lads - it&amp;amp;#39;s happening!!!!!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Polygon宣佈，其期待已久的倫敦硬分叉，將在1月18日前啓動MATIC代幣的燃燒。]]></title><description><![CDATA[昨天，Polygon公司宣佈，它期待已久的EIP-1559升級將在1月18日（大約8點）之前進行。
將於1月18日（UTC時間上午8點左右）進行。這次升級將改變
以太坊網絡上的整個收費市場運作，因爲它將會帶來一個
離散的費用基礎，而不是支付給...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s328qt/polygon_has_announced_that_its_long_awaited/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs328qt%2Fpolygon_has_announced_that_its_long_awaited%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs328qt%2Fpolygon_has_announced_that_its_long_awaited%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s328qt/polygon_has_announced_that_its_long_awaited/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 03:37:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Yesterday, Polygon has announced that it’s long awaited EIP-1559 upgrade is set to take place by January 18 (about 8a.m UTC). This upgrade is set to change the entire fee market operations on the Ethereum network, as it will be bringing a discrete fee base that is burned instead of being paid to the miners, and an elimination to the first-price auction mechanism.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This upgrade won’t be having a direct impact on the gas fees, but it will be allowing the users to estimate the costs better.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Another main impact of this upgrade is that it’ll be having a deflationary impact on MATIC. Since Polygon’s total supply of tokens is fixed at 10 billion, the reduction of the token number will be having a direct deflationary impact on the asset. A we know, 0.27% of the total supply will be burned annually, which means 27 million MATIC. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This upgrade is going to have a positive impact on the dApps users, as they’ll be enjoying even lower fees, and developers will be receiving a boost as well. Not to forget that the EIP 1559 will also minimize the number of spam transactions and the network congestion. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Finally, will this upgrade have a direct impact on MATIC’s price?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[VISA報告稱25%的公司希望在2022年前接受比特幣和加密貨幣支付]]></title><description><![CDATA[比特幣（BTC）等加密貨幣的採用已經在順利進行。
然而，來自Visa的研究
[https://www.reuters.com/technology/quarter-small-businesses-across-nine-countries-plan-offer-crypto-payments-visa-2022-01-12/]
的研究顯示，2022年主流加密貨幣的發展前景更加廣闊。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s35hya/visa_reports_25_of_companies_want_to_accept/?score=312&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs35hya%2Fvisa_reports_25_of_companies_want_to_accept%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs35hya%2Fvisa_reports_25_of_companies_want_to_accept%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s35hya/visa_reports_25_of_companies_want_to_accept/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 01:44:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Adoption of cryptocurrencies such as bitcoin (BTC) is already well underway. However, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/technology/quarter-small-businesses-across-nine-countries-plan-offer-crypto-payments-visa-2022-01-12/&quot;&amp;gt;research from Visa&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; shows that 2022 has even more in store for mainstream crypto adoption. In fact, a whopping 25% of small businesses in 9 different countries plan to start accepting crypto payments this year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Companies exceed consumer expectations&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The survey was conducted among 2,250 small businesses in 9 different countries. These are the United States, Canada, Brazil, Singapore, Germany, Ireland, Russia, the United Arab Emirates and Hong Kong. Also, 1,000 Americans and 500 residents in each country were asked for their opinions. In doing so, the survey covers almost all continents and provides a nice picture of the average sentiment worldwide.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Visa reports that 25% of these 2,250 businesses plan to accept crypto payments by 2022. This is while among consumers, only 13% expect companies to do so. Jeni Mundy, global head of merchant sales at Visa, states that more trust seems to be emerging:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;I think more people are more confident in crypto,&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Interest in crypto especially outside North America&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Furthermore, the survey revealed that it is mainly companies outside North America that are interested in accepting crypto payments. In North America, only 19% (US) and 8% (Canada) say they have these plans. In the United Arab Emirates, Singapore, Hong Kong and Brazil, the percentage is as high as 30%. Even companies that do not want to accept crypto this year may change tack later. Indeed, the survey also shows that three-quarters of companies believe that expanding payment options is &amp;amp;quot;fundamental&amp;amp;quot; to their business growth. Mundy argues that it is a &amp;amp;quot;natural evolution&amp;amp;quot; to accept crypto over time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Visa happy with results&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The results will be music to Visa&amp;amp;#39;s ears. After all, the payments giant is betting big on crypto. Last year, for example, it launched a crypto consulting service. In addition, the company made a promise to continue supporting crypto.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美聯儲不公平地將懷俄明州的加密銀行拒之門外，並說如果我們開始批准加密銀行，很快就會有幾百家了 ! 美聯儲認爲這足以阻止申請!]]></title><description><![CDATA[要建立一個加密銀行，公司需要從當地政府獲得SDPI許可證，然後在美聯儲開立一個主賬戶。
然後在美聯儲開立一個主賬戶，以便與中央銀行安排付款，並與其他金融機構進行結算。
中央銀行，並與其他金融機構進行結算。

Kraken和Avanti是活躍在加密貨幣業務中的兩個實體，它們都是...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s2ybyc/federal_reserve_unfairly_shutting_out_wyomings/?score=317&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs2ybyc%2Ffederal_reserve_unfairly_shutting_out_wyomings%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs2ybyc%2Ffederal_reserve_unfairly_shutting_out_wyomings%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s2ybyc/federal_reserve_unfairly_shutting_out_wyomings/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 21:38:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To established a Crypto Bank,a company needs SDPI charter from the local authorities then a master account with Federal Reserve to arrange payments with Central Bank and to conduct settlements with other financial institutions. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Kraken and Avanti are two entities active in Crypto business ,both have received permission under Wyoming law to become Special Purpose Depository Institutions(SDPI)-a new type of financial entity that can transact in Crypto while also performing traditional banking services. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After receiving SDPI charter from authorities,next step is to require a master account at Federal Reserve to arrange payments with Central Bank and conduct settlements with other financial institutions.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But here comes the main problem, Federal Reserve blocked the applications to open the master account without any legitimate reasons.Not only this, Federal Reserve sat on SDPI applications for more than a year and has been slow to communicate with Crypto Banks on why the whole process is taking so much time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Fed Chair Jerome Powell defending the FED&amp;amp;#39;s decision to block Crypto Banks with this statement &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;if we start granting these, there will be a couple hundred of them soon.They are hugely precedential, which is why I am taking my time on this&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Even though Mr. Jerome Powell agreed that there are good arguments for treating them as eligible to receive accounts.Just because it&amp;amp;#39;s &amp;amp;quot;Crypto Bank&amp;amp;quot; they can&amp;amp;#39;t get the permission for master account.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And people think authorities are now realizing the potential of Crypto and ready to accept it as a part of financial system.They are just saying nice words so that their public image remain intact, and their actions are in the direction to stop Crypto at any cost. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Source :
&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://decrypt.co/90186/powell-lummis-spdi-kraken-wyoming&quot;&amp;gt;https://decrypt.co/90186/powell-lummis-spdi-kraken-wyoming&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[摩根大通&amp;高盛在2018年的崩盤中被曝是比特幣的最大買家，他們公開&amp;面地抨擊比特幣是一個騙局&amp;。如果一個億萬富翁想要的東西，就像《鯊魚坦克》中的神奇先生一樣，他們會否定/唾棄它，讓你廉價出售給他們。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s2ijsa/jp_morgan_goldman_sachs_exposed_as_being_the/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs2ijsa%2Fjp_morgan_goldman_sachs_exposed_as_being_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs2ijsa%2Fjp_morgan_goldman_sachs_exposed_as_being_the%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s2ijsa/jp_morgan_goldman_sachs_exposed_as_being_the/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 21:38:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[伊麗莎白-沃倫的前工作人員在投資10美元后對一項Defi協議提起了訴訟。而且沒有人意識到或可能意識到，這10美元的鉅額投資是爲了提起訴訟而故意的。這裏沒有任何線索可供聯繫。]]></title><description><![CDATA[一個名叫肯特的小夥子在一個名爲 "PoolTogether "的協議中投資了10美元，該協議
該協議本質上是將儲蓄過程遊戲化，爲他們提供機會，從收集的資金產生的利息中贏得獎勵。
從收集的資金所產生的利息中獲得獎勵。

這裏需要注意的一點是--他是沃倫參議員在2020年期間的團隊的一部分。
總統選舉]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s35jr7/elizabeth_warrens_ex_staffer_has_filed_a_lawsuit/?score=317&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs35jr7%2Felizabeth_warrens_ex_staffer_has_filed_a_lawsuit%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs35jr7%2Felizabeth_warrens_ex_staffer_has_filed_a_lawsuit%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s35jr7/elizabeth_warrens_ex_staffer_has_filed_a_lawsuit/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 20:32:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A chap named Kent had invested $10 in a protocol called &amp;amp;#39;PoolTogether&amp;amp;#39; which essentially gamifies the process of saving by offering them a chance to win awards from the interest generated by collected funds.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A point to note here is- he was a part of Sen. Warren&amp;amp;#39;s team during 2020 presidential elections and that in the lawsuit he&amp;amp;#39;s described as someone who&amp;amp;#39;s gravely concerned at the prospective use of the cryptocurrency. His &amp;amp;#39;very legitimate&amp;amp;#39; concerns are about climte change and crypto&amp;amp;#39;s role in it, bad rug pulls, subversion of laws set by the society and so on.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The lawsuit in itself is not concerning but when you connect the dots on who filed the lawsuit and the purpose behind it- you see that this is but a malicious attempt of ridiculing crypto by only emphasizing a small proportion of use case. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A complete bullshittery continues still&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[哈薩克斯坦並沒有決定 "突然關閉採礦"。他們封鎖了互聯網連接，因爲他們正處於內戰的邊緣......]]></title><description><![CDATA[令人驚訝的是，你需要互聯網來進行加密貨幣......



我是一個生活在黎巴嫩的人（這個國家正處於政治、經濟和社會崩潰的邊緣）。
我可以告訴你，只有一個以自我爲中心的混蛋纔會關注正在發生的事情。
纔會看到哈薩克斯坦發生的事情而只想到比特幣。



他們有很多...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s33a70/kazakhstan_didnt_decide_to_suddenly_shut_off/?score=326&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs33a70%2Fkazakhstan_didnt_decide_to_suddenly_shut_off%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs33a70%2Fkazakhstan_didnt_decide_to_suddenly_shut_off%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s33a70/kazakhstan_didnt_decide_to_suddenly_shut_off/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 20:32:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And surprise you need internet for crypto…&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Coming from a person living in Lebanon (a country on the verge of political, economical, and civil collapse) I can tell you that only a self centered asshole will look at what&amp;amp;#39;s going on Kazakhstan and just think of Bitcoin.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;They&amp;amp;#39;re having much bigger problems than mining, I can assure you that.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And if you really want to bring crypto into it, this might be the chance for alts to finally decouple from BTC.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It’s slowly but surely happening and I already bought some DeFi alts like Curve cause I think its the best DeFi project and some BitDAO considering how much they’ve been investing in the DeFi space recently.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Many are the time that BTC has ruined an uptrend cause it went down 0.01%. So this might actually be good for the market long term if you care about is crypto in this humanitarian disaster…&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我正在挖掘有關比特幣價格預測的舊帖子和文章，我發現這個帖子非常有趣。]]></title><description><![CDATA[注：該文章（下面的鏈接）發表於2019年9月，在5個月前
Covid崩潰的前5個月。當時的價格約爲10 000美元。作者稱。

 * 每枚比特幣的價格將在不早於2021年和不晚於2028年達到100 000美元。
   不晚於2028年。2028年後，價格將永遠不會低於100 000美元。
 *...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s2zvsa/i_am_digging_through_old_posts_and_articles_with/?score=370&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs2zvsa%2Fi_am_digging_through_old_posts_and_articles_with%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs2zvsa%2Fi_am_digging_through_old_posts_and_articles_with%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s2zvsa/i_am_digging_through_old_posts_and_articles_with/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 18:37:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Note: The Article (link below) was published in September 2019, 5 months before the Covid Crash. The Price was around 10 000 USD. The Author called:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;the price will reach $100 000 per bitcoin no earlier than 2021 and no  later than 2028. After 2028, the price will never drop below $100 000 &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;the price will reach $1 000 000 per bitcoin no earlier than 2028 and no  later than 2037. After 2037, the price will never drop below $100 000 &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/xqyoezqxzfb81.png?width=1269&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=916afd35285d21d4946683ef8a6798c17056da3e&quot;&amp;gt;I added todays Price in Black and the Covid Crash in Red. The Green Line marks the low of 2041 of 1.8 Million Doller per 1 Bitcoin&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Take a look at the Logarithmic Chart from Today:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/g2eakl6whgb81.png?width=1050&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=77cc4a267dec9b303fc26c79f56e86b86edfe166&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/g2eakl6whgb81.png?width=1050&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=77cc4a267dec9b303fc26c79f56e86b86edfe166&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Price hit the Top of the Loga Channel in July 2011, Dec 2013 and the Dec 2017. From a historical perspective we can say that it needs around 4 years to hit the top. If this repeats, we will hit around 150.000 within the next months. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The Article has some other nice calculations, take the deep dive:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sauce: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/quantodian-publications/bitcoins-natural-long-term-power-law-corridor-of-growth-649d0e9b3c94&quot;&amp;gt;https://medium.com/quantodian-publications/bitcoins-natural-long-term-power-law-corridor-of-growth-649d0e9b3c94&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[每個人都認爲加密貨幣是被操縱的，因爲沒有監管。但有些人多年來一直在操縱股票市場，沒有人阻止他們]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s2wpaa/everyone_thinks_crypto_are_manipulated_because/?score=325&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs2wpaa%2Feveryone_thinks_crypto_are_manipulated_because%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs2wpaa%2Feveryone_thinks_crypto_are_manipulated_because%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s2wpaa/everyone_thinks_crypto_are_manipulated_because/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 16:53:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我在2018年1月1日買了1千美元的十大加密貨幣（四年報告）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[試驗 - 追蹤2018年十大加密貨幣 - 四年報告 - 漲幅+34
[https://preview.redd.it/dzzes3g8ngb81.png?width=666&format=png&auto=webp&s=4e29ebda29cda106029c3f762a91b8b7d815d509]

在這裏找到包含所有表格的完整博文
[https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s30bsi/i_bought_1k_of_the_top_10_cryptos_on_january_1st/?score=1008&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs30bsi%2Fi_bought_1k_of_the_top_10_cryptos_on_january_1st%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs30bsi%2Fi_bought_1k_of_the_top_10_cryptos_on_january_1st%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s30bsi/i_bought_1k_of_the_top_10_cryptos_on_january_1st/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 16:53:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/dzzes3g8ngb81.png?width=666&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=4e29ebda29cda106029c3f762a91b8b7d815d509&quot;&amp;gt;EXPERIMENT – Tracking 2018 Top Ten Cryptocurrencies – FOUR YEAR REPORT – UP +34&amp;amp;#37;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Find the full blog post with all the tables&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-48&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Welcome to your monthly no-shill data dump: Here&amp;amp;#39;s the FOUR YEAR REPORT for the 2018 Top Ten Experiment featuring &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BTC, XRP, ETH, BCH, ADA, LTC, NEM, DASH, IOTA,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Stellar.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;tl;dr&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What&amp;amp;#39;s this all about?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; I purchased $100 of each of Top 10 Cryptos in Jan. 2018, haven&amp;amp;#39;t sold or traded, reporting every single month for four years. Did the same in 2019, 2020, 2021, and more recently, the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/announcing-top-10-2022/&quot;&amp;gt;2022 Top Ten a few weeks ago&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Learn more about the history and rules of the Experiments&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/about/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Snapshots taken on the 1st of each month.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;December&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Highlights:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; A bloody, all-red month&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Overall since Jan. 2018:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ETH&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; solidly in the lead, followed by &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BTC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ADA.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;  After briefly pulling ahead earlier in the year, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;the 2018 Top Ten are now significantly underperforming the S&amp;amp;amp;P 500&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; over the same time period.  Q: So, big crypto fail, right?&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A: Only if I stopped after the first year.  The &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;2018+2019+2020+2021 Combined Top Ten Portfolios are returning 406%, much, much better than traditional markets over the same time period (&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;fancy new chart at the very bottom of the post).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Some exciting new changes for&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/announcing-top-10-2022/&quot;&amp;gt;2022&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;!&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;I&amp;amp;#39;ll focus on 2022 Top Ten Portfolio reports + one other portfolio on a rotating basis (down to two reports per month)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Incorporated Decentralized Finance (DeFi) for the first time. &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Factoring in stablecoin gains:  In past years, I have not included the ROI that is possible with stables in the monthly reports.  This year, I will detail ways to build on the $100 of USDC in the 2022 portfolio and gamify it a bit: my goal is to outperform as many as the other cryptos in the 2022 Top Ten Portfolio as possible (simple if it turns out to be a bear year, a bit more challenging if the 2022 market moons).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Giveaways: Who doesn’t love a good old fashioned giveaway? I’ll be giving away crypto during the year, either through Twitter, Reddit, or my email list. I’m still figuring out the details, but aim to give away around $100 a month in crypto.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Friendly competition: I will compare my homemade 2022 Top Ten Crypto Index Fund Experiment to a Total Crypto Market Cap Index Token ($TCAP &amp;lt;a href=&quot;/r/TotalCryptoMarketCap&quot;&amp;gt;r/TotalCryptoMarketCap&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;) to see which one outperforms.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And here we go!!!!!!!!!!!!!!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Four Year Report – UP 34%&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/c3c6wlctpgb81.jpg?width=1056&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=380248b14486edaa5749fba7a390198bf81260a0&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/c3c6wlctpgb81.jpg?width=1056&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=380248b14486edaa5749fba7a390198bf81260a0&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Welcome to the four year report!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The 2018 Top Ten Crypto Index Fund Portfolio is &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BTC, XRP, ETH, BCH, ADA, LTC, IOTA, NEM, Dash,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Stellar&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;December highlights for the 2018 Top Ten Portfolio:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;100% red month&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;IOTA&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; falls the least, only down -4% (on news that staking on the Firefly wallet will yield two cryptos, Assembly and Shimmer).&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ETH&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; maintains a solid overall lead, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BTC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; in second place, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ADA&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; in third.  Three coins in the green since January 2018.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;After four years, the 2018 Portfolio is +34%, behind the S&amp;amp;amp;P 500’s ROI over the same time period.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;December Ranking and Dropouts&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here’s a look at the movement in ranks since January 2018:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/ulc9dwgvpgb81.jpg?width=412&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=2eadc9a98ec75b726cef37af7cb716fddf3126db&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/ulc9dwgvpgb81.jpg?width=412&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=2eadc9a98ec75b726cef37af7cb716fddf3126db&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Top Ten dropouts since January 2018:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; After four years of the 2018 Top Ten Experiment, only 40% of the cryptos that &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-ten-month-one/&quot;&amp;gt;started in the Top Ten&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; have remained.  &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;NEM, Dash, Stellar, Bitcoin Cash, IOTA&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Litecoin&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; have been replaced by &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Binance Coin, Tether&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;DOT, SOL&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;LUNA&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;USDC.  NEM&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; looks like it wants to be the first to drop out of the Top 100.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;December Winners and Losers&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;December Winners&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; –  &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;IOTA&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; outperformed the pack, dropping only -4% this month. 100% of the cryptos in the red.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;December Losers&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; –   Losing nearly a third of its value, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Litecoin&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; fell the most, down -30%. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;NEM&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; followed &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;LTC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, dropping -27% in December.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Tally of Monthly Winners and Losers&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After four years, here’s a tally of the monthly winners and losers over the life of the 2018 Top Ten Experiment. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/lisz7rgxpgb81.jpg?width=411&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=cbf41f94e9716f0140f3a7dfff3f655fa9d21a59&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/lisz7rgxpgb81.jpg?width=411&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=cbf41f94e9716f0140f3a7dfff3f655fa9d21a59&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With 11, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Bitcoin&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; has two more monthly wins than second place &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Cardano&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.  &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;NEM&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; has finished last place most often (12 months out of 48).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Bitcoin&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; is still the only cryptocurrency that hasn’t yet lost a month since January 2018 (although it has come very close a couple of times).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Overall Update –  2021 ends with a whimper. After four years, ETH in first place, and Dash and NEM tied for worst overall performance.&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After reaching an All Time High (+72%) in &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-46&quot;&amp;gt;October&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, the 2018 Top Ten Portfolio continued to lose value.  After four years of holding these cryptos, only 3 out of the 10 cryptos are in the green: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BTC,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ETH,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ADA.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Overall, first place &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ETH&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; (+413%) is well ahead of &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BTC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; (+257%) and third place &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ADA&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; (+99%).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The initial $100 invested in first place &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;ETH&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; four years ago?  It’s worth $515 today.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;DASH&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;NEM&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; are virtually tied at the bottom, both down over -86% since &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-ten-month-one/&quot;&amp;gt;January 2018&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;  The initial $100 invested in each four ago is worth about $13 today.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Total Market Cap for the entire cryptocurrency sector:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/mldnsr7zpgb81.png?width=582&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d82435bc0e39657707f2143fb5dd1951f6ddcfd1&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/mldnsr7zpgb81.png?width=582&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=d82435bc0e39657707f2143fb5dd1951f6ddcfd1&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;End of December 2021 market cap: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$2,211,626,655,207&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The total crypto market dropped significantly in December.  Crypto as a sector is still up +285% since &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-ten-month-one/&quot;&amp;gt;January 2018&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There was no easy way to achieve this at the time, but if you were able to capture the entire crypto market since New Year’s Day 2018, you’d be doing much, much better than the Experiment’s Top Ten approach (+34%), the return of the S&amp;amp;amp;P (+78%) over the same period of time, and nine of the individual cryptos within the 2018 Top Ten (except for &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Ethereum)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto Market Cap Low Point in the 2018 Top Ten Crypto Index Experiment: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$114B in&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-ten-month-thirteen/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;January 2019&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto Market Cap High Point in the 2018 Top Ten Crypto Index Experiment: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$2.65T in&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-46/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;October 2021&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Bitcoin dominance:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/qygnx0a0qgb81.png?width=487&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=567958cf7214839fa7befa749d61125dade6a9a8&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/qygnx0a0qgb81.png?width=487&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=567958cf7214839fa7befa749d61125dade6a9a8&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BitDom&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; declined a bit in December, ending the month at 40.2%.  When looking at the entire four year 2018 Experiment time frame, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BTC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; dominance is near the low end.  For context:   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Low Point in the 2018 Top Ten Crypto Index Experiment: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-ten-month-one&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;33% in January 2018&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;High Point in the 2018 Top Ten Crypto Index Experiment: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-ten-month-twenty/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;70.5% in August 2019&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Overall return on $1,000 investment since January 1st, 2018: &amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/cxtd9lb1qgb81.jpg?width=339&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=25b3da0034194812e2b66f977450fff1555b48fb&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/cxtd9lb1qgb81.jpg?width=339&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=25b3da0034194812e2b66f977450fff1555b48fb&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The 2018 Top Ten Portfolio lost $325 in December.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If I decided to cash out the 2018 Top Ten Experiment today, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;the $1000 initial investment would be worth $1,341&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, up 34% from &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-ten-month-one/&quot;&amp;gt;January 2018&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Green is unfamiliar territory for the 2018 Top Ten Portfolio and a recent development.  Over the first four years of the 2018 Index Fund Experiment, thirty-eight months have been in the red, with only ten months of green.  And all ten of the green months have come in 2021. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here’s a look at the ROI over the life of the experiment, month by month, since the beginning of the 2018 Experiment four years ago:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/cbumx113qgb81.jpg?width=654&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=7bba9861143359ff6b70ff0ca8e6ba75de5d00d6&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/cbumx113qgb81.jpg?width=654&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=7bba9861143359ff6b70ff0ca8e6ba75de5d00d6&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The all time high for this portfolio is &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-46&quot;&amp;gt;October 2021&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; (+72%).  The lowest point was in January 2019 when the 2018 Top Ten Portfolio was down &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-ten-month-thirteen/&quot;&amp;gt;-88%&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.   &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Remember: no one can predict the value of any crypto tomorrow, let alone next month or next year.  The 2018 Top Ten Crypto Portfolio was down -88% after one year, -80% after two years, -25% after three years.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Combining the 2018, 2019, 2020, and 2021 Top Ten Crypto Portfolios&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Alright, that’s that for the 2018 Top Ten Crypto Index Fund Experiment recap.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But I didn’t stop the Experiment in 2018:  I invested another $1000 in the &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;2019&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;2020,&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;2021&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Top Ten Cryptos as well (&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;(and, just announced,&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/announcing-top-10-2022/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;again in 2022&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;!)&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.  How are the other Crypto Index Fund Experiments doing?    &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-48&quot;&amp;gt;2018 Top Ten Experiment&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;: up +34% (total value $1,341)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2019-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-36&quot;&amp;gt;2019 Top Ten Experiment:&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; up +504% (total value $6,044)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2020-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-24&quot;&amp;gt;2020 Top Ten Experiment&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;: up +795% (total value $8,951)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2021-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-12&quot;&amp;gt;2021 Top Ten Experiment&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;: up +292% (total value $3,921)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So overall? Taking the four portfolios together, here’s the bottom bottom bottom &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;bottom&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; line: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;After a $4,000 investment in the 2018, 2019, 2020, and 2021 Top Ten Cryptocurrencies,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; the combined portfolios are worth &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$20,257&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; ($1,341 + $6,044 + $8,951 + $3,921).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;That’s up +406%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; on the combined portfolios, &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;down from&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-47&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;last month’s all time high&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; for the combined Top Ten Index Fund Experiments.  Here’s the combined monthly ROI since I started tracking the metric in January 2020:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/xcl80o35qgb81.jpg?width=511&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e2cd4923360a5492259faf606b3649c893fd4b16&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/xcl80o35qgb81.jpg?width=511&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=e2cd4923360a5492259faf606b3649c893fd4b16&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;That’s a +406% gain by investing $1k in whichever cryptos happened to be in the Top Ten on January 1st (including stablecoins) for four years in a row.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Comparison to S&amp;amp;amp;P 500:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m also tracking the S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 as part of the Experiment to have a comparison point with other popular investments options.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/3uss07c8qgb81.png?width=582&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=3e68ae4c88a82ff35b70538ec11dd137e83447e2&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/3uss07c8qgb81.png?width=582&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=3e68ae4c88a82ff35b70538ec11dd137e83447e2&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;After four years: the S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 is up +78% since January 2018, so the initial $1k investment into crypto on &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-ten-month-one/&quot;&amp;gt;January 1st, 2018&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; would be worth $1,780 had it been redirected to the S&amp;amp;amp;P.  That’s more than double the +34% return of the 2018 Top Ten Crypto Portfolio over the same period of time.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Taking the same invest-$1,000-on-January-1st-of-each-year approach with the S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 that I’ve been documenting through the Top Ten Crypto Experiments, the yields are the following:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2018 = $1,780 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2019 = $1,900 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2020 = $1,480 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2021 = $1,270 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Taken together, here’s the bottom bottom bottom &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;bottom&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; line for a similar approach with the S&amp;amp;amp;P: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;After four $1,000 investments into an S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 index fund in January 2018, 2019, 2020, and 2021, my portfolio would be worth $6,430&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; ($1,780 + $1,900 + $1,480 + $1,270)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That is up &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+61%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-ten-month-one/&quot;&amp;gt;since January 2018&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; compared to a &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+406%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; gain of the combined Top Ten Crypto Experiment Portfolios.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here’s a fancy new chart showing the four year ROI comparison between a Top Ten Crypto approach and the S&amp;amp;amp;P as per the rules of the Top Ten Experiments: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/gnkxsud9qgb81.png?width=575&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=3f94a09a11a36620fca7b8630d615420049141b2&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/gnkxsud9qgb81.png?width=575&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=3f94a09a11a36620fca7b8630d615420049141b2&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Conclusion:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Many thanks to the long-time Experiment followers, appreciate you taking the time to follow along over the years.  For those just getting into crypto, welcome! I hope these reports can somehow give you a taste of what you may be in for as you begin your crypto adventures.  Buckle up, think long term, don’t invest what you can’t afford to lose, and try to enjoy the ride! Feel free to reach out with any questions and stay tuned for monthly progress reports. Keep an eye out for my parallel projects where I repeat the experiment, purchasing another $1000 ($100 each) of new sets of Top Ten cryptos as of &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2019-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-36&quot;&amp;gt;January 1st, 2019&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2020-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-24&quot;&amp;gt;January 1st, 2020&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2021-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-12&quot;&amp;gt;January 1st, 2021&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, and most recently, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/announcing-top-10-2022/&quot;&amp;gt;January 1st, 2022&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我相信，CRO終於提供了普通人進入加密貨幣所需要的東西，即簡單、真實的使用方法。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想指出的是，我不是在推銷CRO，我有一袋很小的CRO，甚至不夠他們的借記卡的第一層。
甚至不足以獲得他們借記卡的第一層。我還想補充的是，他們
他們遠非完美，他們的應用程序慢得令人髮指，我討厭我不得不用手機而不是電腦。
用手機而不是臺式機，這兩件事都讓我......]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s2xcou/i_do_believe_that_cro_has_finally_delivered_what/?score=335&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs2xcou%2Fi_do_believe_that_cro_has_finally_delivered_what%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fs2xcou%2Fi_do_believe_that_cro_has_finally_delivered_what%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/s2xcou/i_do_believe_that_cro_has_finally_delivered_what/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 15:43:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I want to point out that I&amp;amp;#39;m not shilling CRO, I have a tiny bag of it, not even enough to get the first tier of their debit card. I also want to add that they are far from perfect, their app is so ridiculously slow and I hate that I have to use a mobile phone instead of a desktop, both drive me mad. Also I know it&amp;amp;#39;s not decentralised so a lot of the crypto &amp;amp;#39;purists&amp;amp;#39; are not going to like it (even though no crypto coin where you can just buy a controlling quantity with the only limitation being having enough money was never truly decentralised in my opinion).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That said I think they have structured their business model perfectly towards the average person:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;1) You need to have almost zero knowledge to buy CRO and stake it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;2) Their pre paid debit card is the best bridge I&amp;amp;#39;ve seen so far between fiat and crypto, you just spend your fiat and get crypto in return. It doesn&amp;amp;#39;t require all the world&amp;amp;#39;s companies to change their payment systems and pricing structure. Everything stays in fiat and the user gets the reward. Also it looks super cool and makes people want to show it off.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;3) Their daily missions encourage a repeating $20 daily DCA which is perfect for teaching new investors to put in gradually and repeatedly rather than dumping a 4/5 digit lump sum all in on one price point, often near ATHs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;4) They offer decent staking rewards although you do need a large bag of CRO to access it which I feel is a bit off-putting.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;5) They are doing real marketing, buying stadiums and paying Matt Damon to be in their adverts. Compare that to someone like LRC who also have a fait on ramp and wallet system and their marketing consists of a guy posting laser eye memes on twitter and discord and saying things like &amp;amp;quot;WAGMI&amp;amp;quot;. I know Matt Damon was just paid to be in an advert but I still trust any company that can actually afford to hire him far more than a company that cannot / will not spend that money.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;6) The coin price point is something that retail can understand, it&amp;amp;#39;s not a scary large number like BTC but it&amp;amp;#39;s also not 6 0s after a decimal like a lot of shitcoins.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;7) Their model is built around buying and holding their coin for other rewards which is, again, great at teaching retail to HODL rather than the only means of value to try and sell at a higher price point that pretty much the rest of the crypto market exists on.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[它正在發生! 另一個國家可以使用比特幣作爲貨幣；這次是組成湯加王國的160多個島嶼。https://t.co/A6aJgrnARj]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1481619064703307780/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1481619064703307780/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 13:45:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[富達公司是世界上最大的資產管理公司之一，管理着4.9萬億美元的資產。今天他們這樣寫道。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s2wow7/fidelity_is_one_of_the_largest_asset_managers_in/?score=609&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs2wow7%2Ffidelity_is_one_of_the_largest_asset_managers_in%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs2wow7%2Ffidelity_is_one_of_the_largest_asset_managers_in%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s2wow7/fidelity_is_one_of_the_largest_asset_managers_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 13:45:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如何觀察比特幣價格？我發現一開始很難觀察加密貨幣的趨勢，因爲金融的非可視性。所以我決定爲像我這樣的人創建Crypto Stars - Market Tutorial手機應用程序。你怎麼看，是否值得繼續開發這樣的應用程序？]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s2w0e6/how_do_you_watch_the_bitcoin_price_i_found_its/?score=307&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs2w0e6%2Fhow_do_you_watch_the_bitcoin_price_i_found_its%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fs2w0e6%2Fhow_do_you_watch_the_bitcoin_price_i_found_its%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/s2w0e6/how_do_you_watch_the_bitcoin_price_i_found_its/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 13:45:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>