<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[加密貨幣國外熱門討論]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览关于加密货币的国外热门讨论]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 08:32:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[剛剛從槓桿交易中賺了1.1美元。現在問我任何問題。]]></title><description><![CDATA[是的，我做了這個子裏所有人都害怕的事情。我做了
別人都做不到的事情。我對某一硬幣進行了25倍的投資，並賺取了
1.1美元的巨大利潤。現在我終於可以在我的簡歷中加入專業的槓桿交易員了
我終於可以在我的簡歷上加上專業的槓桿交易員，並申請在一些錯誤的銀行工作，然後去一個...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szkgsr/just_made_11_off_leverage_trading_ask_me_anything/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszkgsr%2Fjust_made_11_off_leverage_trading_ask_me_anything%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszkgsr%2Fjust_made_11_off_leverage_trading_ask_me_anything%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szkgsr/just_made_11_off_leverage_trading_ask_me_anything/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 07:36:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Yes, I did the thing that everyone here in this sub is afraid of. I did the thing that no one else could. I went 25x into a certain coin and made an enormous 1.1$ profit. Now I can finally add professional leverage trader to my resume and apply for a job at some bug bank then go to a government organization, from there I will start my political career and in a few months be senator, after that I will make a crypto legal tender law as it should be and try do pass it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Sounds good right?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But no joke had some amazing timing. Selling 3min before the dumb and making that profit. Oh leverage really is the safest thing ever.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But don&amp;amp;#39;t worry I will obviously remember you all after becoming president.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[俄羅斯開始轟炸烏克蘭全境]]></title><description><![CDATA[俄羅斯在日出時開始轟炸烏克蘭各地的薄弱點。所以這
這意味着現在在該國有一場全面的戰爭。這也意味着全世界
供應鏈的進一步短缺、戰爭的努力，以及未知的整體波動所造成的經濟緊張。
未知因素造成的整體波動。

提醒加密貨幣新...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t02blf/russia_started_bombing_all_over_ukraine_double/?score=327&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft02blf%2Frussia_started_bombing_all_over_ukraine_double%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Ft02blf%2Frussia_started_bombing_all_over_ukraine_double%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/t02blf/russia_started_bombing_all_over_ukraine_double/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 07:36:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Russia started bombing weak spots all around Ukraine during sunrise. So that means there is a full scale war now in the country. That also means worldwide economic tensions caused by further supply chain shortages, war effort, and overall volatility from the unknown.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A reminder for crypto new comers who are getting absolutely pantsed and turned around right now. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Selling at a loss historically makes no sense. Overtime crypto and the overall stock market and real estate. It all bounces back.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Time in the market over timing it. Instead of thinking you know what’s gonna happen. Just buy some here and there. And in 2025 maybe we we all be better off for it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;All of that being said I’m so sorry if you live in Ukraine I cannot even imagine being a smaller country being brutally attacked by a large and vicious neighbor with no remorse.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Fight if you want, escape if you can. Russia kills civilians and supporters of anything western. Just a week ago the US exposed a list of Ukrainians Russians were to kill and put in camps after an invasion.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Please don’t think it cannot happen. Be safe and be smart. Fight hard the Russians are just people.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Crypto.com有點糟糕。]]></title><description><![CDATA[目前在Reddit上有很多CDC的粉絲，所以這篇文章會被降權到無聲無息，可能很多人都看不到。
變得默默無聞，可能沒有多少人看到，但我還是想談談我的
經驗。

我大約20天前開始使用他們，每天購買大約20美元的
每天購買大約20美元的加密貨幣來耕種他們的戰利品箱，加上...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szk86n/cryptocom_kinda_sucks/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszk86n%2Fcryptocom_kinda_sucks%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszk86n%2Fcryptocom_kinda_sucks%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szk86n/cryptocom_kinda_sucks/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 05:38:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There’s a lot of CDC fanboys on Reddit at the moment so this will get downvoted into obscurity and probably not seen by many, but I want to talk about my experience anyway. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I started using them about 20 days ago and have been buying around $20 usd of crypto per day to farm their loot boxes, plus around $1500 worth of CRO to hold. There are no fees for the first 30 days so I thought I’d just spread out some buys and see what I get in loot box rewards. So far….like $11 worth of CRO. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In this time I have had three instance where I needed to contact customer service. While it was easy to get in touch with customer service, not one has ever actually fixed the problem. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The first two problems were relatively minor. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I didn’t get the loot box diamonds for a large order I made. I tried to use the support function, still never got them. Honestly, I don’t care that much. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;My NFT account and password won’t work. It constantly says my password is incorrect, even though it is 100% correct. I even reset the password, and it still won’t work. I contacted support and we just kept going in loops. It was almost like that scene from Idiocracy where they talk about plants and electrolytes. I wasn’t sure if I wanted to get into NFTs, but I did want to browse. I’ll just not get into NFTs now, no big deal. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The real issue….&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ol&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;I spent $500 yesterday for some crypto on the dip. The app glitches out, I get a “transaction cancelled” once the app starts working again, receive no cryto, but I was still charged $500. My banks has confirmed in their system and in Visa that the transaction was approved on their end and the money is at CDC. CDC support is non existent here. They say it isn’t in my transaction history however I sure as hell got charged for it.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ol&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;While talking to my bank the gentleman I was speaking with said the day before he had the exact same call come in about crypto.com charging people but not delivering the goods. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cdc needs to get their shit together if they are looking for mass adoption to happen through them. I’m assuming I’ll get my $500 back in a few days, but even if I  do I missed an opportunity to buy at a target price because their system isn’t 100% functional. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Maybe they should have spent some of that Matt and Lebron money ensuring their systems work properly.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[歐盟計劃禁止比特幣和工作證明加密貨幣]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以，這剛剛發生。
https://www.btc-echo.de/news/bitcoin-spd-gruene-und-linke-fordern-verbot-in-der-eu-135678/

自動翻譯。

夯實加密貨幣監管。歐洲議會希望禁止
提供基於 "環境不可持續 "的加密貨幣服務。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/szm39a/european_union_plans_to_forbid_bitcoin_and_proof/?score=328&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fszm39a%2Feuropean_union_plans_to_forbid_bitcoin_and_proof%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fszm39a%2Feuropean_union_plans_to_forbid_bitcoin_and_proof%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/szm39a/european_union_plans_to_forbid_bitcoin_and_proof/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 04:30:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, this just happened: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.btc-echo.de/news/bitcoin-spd-gruene-und-linke-fordern-verbot-in-der-eu-135678/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.btc-echo.de/news/bitcoin-spd-gruene-und-linke-fordern-verbot-in-der-eu-135678/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Automated Translation:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Cramming crypto regulation. The European Parliament wants to prohibit the provision of crypto services based on &amp;amp;quot;environmentally unsustainable consensus mechanisms&amp;amp;quot; in its MiCA guidelines. This is according to a final compromise proposal from the responsible Committee on Economic and Monetary Affairs (ECON), which is available to BTC-ECHO. De facto, this could mean the end for proof-of-work-based cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin from January 1, 2025 in the European Union. The final decision on the draft is to be made in Parliament on February 28.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Stefan Berger told BTC-ECHO that he believes it is &amp;amp;quot;very likely&amp;amp;quot; that the proposal will go through. As Chairman of the ECON Committee, he is largely responsible for the design of the MiCA Directive on the regulation of cryptocurrencies in the European Parliament. The advance of the Bitcoin ban had thereby the SPD, Greens and Left energetically demanded, said the CDU politician in an interview with BTC-ECHO.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The parliamentary groups of the Christian Democrats, right-wing conservatives and liberals would have vehemently resisted the inclusion of the ban in the negotiations. In the end, the Social Democrats, Greens and Left threatened to otherwise withhold their approval of the MiCA draft, according to reports. Previously, SPD politician Joachim Schuster had already publicly called for a bitcoin ban. Green Party European politician Sven Giegold also spoke to BTC-ECHO in favor of illegalization.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The vote next Monday will be followed by a trilogue between the EU Commission, the Parliament and the member states, at the end of which the Commission will be tasked with evaluating the Parliament&amp;amp;#39;s proposal. The decision on this should be expected before the end of this year. In the October 2020 draft, the Commission opposed a bitcoin ban.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin clause is &amp;amp;quot;fatal&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Federal Finance Minister Christian Lindner did not want to comment on the impending bitcoin ban to BTC-ECHO. Frank Schäffler (FDP), member of the Budget Committee of the Bundestag, considers the new proposal of the EU Parliament &amp;amp;quot;fatal&amp;amp;quot;. He already called for changes to the MiCA guidelines last year.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I assume and also expect that the German government and the lead finance minister Christian Lindner will prevent this.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Robert Kopic of the industry association Blockchain for Europe also sees the potential for the clause to &amp;amp;quot;put Europe at a disadvantage.&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is a point that would put Europe, along with its green miners, at a disadvantage and would solely lead to them migrating abroad and Europe losing geopolitical access to Bitcoin.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The economic disadvantages of a Bitcoin ban are therefore obvious. A fact that the EU Commission will also take into account in its MiCA assessment, says Stefan Berger. What the final decision will ultimately look like is uncertain at this point.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[墨西哥參議員堅信比特幣在墨西哥應該是合法的]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/szizur/mexican_senator_is_convinced_that_bitcoin_should/?score=310&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fszizur%2Fmexican_senator_is_convinced_that_bitcoin_should%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fszizur%2Fmexican_senator_is_convinced_that_bitcoin_should%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/szizur/mexican_senator_is_convinced_that_bitcoin_should/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:18:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有人剛花了204個ETH（55.3萬美元）的交易費去造幣廠做NFTs]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szqe20/someone_just_spent_204_eth_553k_in_transaction/?score=319&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszqe20%2Fsomeone_just_spent_204_eth_553k_in_transaction%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszqe20%2Fsomeone_just_spent_204_eth_553k_in_transaction%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szqe20/someone_just_spent_204_eth_553k_in_transaction/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:18:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特幣是 "自由測試"]]></title><description><![CDATA[任何政治家、政黨或政府如果反對或甚至是
對比特幣的自我監管是反自由和反民主的。
期間。

抱怨環境問題，洗錢的可能性，等等，只是
誤導性的。不要上當。這個測試很簡單。這個測試...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/szh7rk/bitcoin_is_the_freedom_test/?score=306&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fszh7rk%2Fbitcoin_is_the_freedom_test%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fszh7rk%2Fbitcoin_is_the_freedom_test%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/szh7rk/bitcoin_is_the_freedom_test/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 01:22:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Any politician, political party, or government that is against or even ambivalent about self-custody of bitcoin is anti-freedom and anti-democracy. Period.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Whining about environmental concerns, money laundering potential, etc is just misdirection. Don&amp;amp;#39;t fall for it. This test is simple. This test is accurate.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you are going to vote, make sure you know where your candidate or party of choice stands on this issue.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If there are no candidates/parties who pass the test where you live, you know the system is rigged and you need to either a) demand better options or b) exit the system you are in.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[人們聲稱持有是最容易的事情。但僅僅在幾個紅色的月後就恐慌了。持有是不容易的，如果你做到了，那就恭喜你。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在加密貨幣中說得最多的一件事是HODL。許多人都在談論這個策略如何
戰略是最簡單的事情，通過長期持有，他們將很容易賺取
一噸的利潤。但這些人也只是被加密貨幣的一些短期波動所嚇倒的人。
短期的加密貨幣運動。

特別是在這種情況下。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szoeqp/people_claiming_that_holding_is_the_easiest_thing/?score=360&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszoeqp%2Fpeople_claiming_that_holding_is_the_easiest_thing%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszoeqp%2Fpeople_claiming_that_holding_is_the_easiest_thing%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szoeqp/people_claiming_that_holding_is_the_easiest_thing/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 01:22:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The one thing that is said the most in crypto is HODL. Many talk about how this strategy is the easiest thing and by holding rly long-term they will easily make a ton of profit. But those are also just the people that get shacked out by some short-term movement in crypto. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Especially during such few months people forget their strategy and just panic. Knowing what you are doing is the most powerful thing ever. And you don&amp;amp;#39;t rly do that if you through your whole strategy apart at the first sign of danger. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So even if you may think that holding is easy and too default. It&amp;amp;#39;s not like that. If it woukd have been that easy then the thousands of people that bought crypto during the very beginning would be billionaires by now. Being able to hold on to your crypto and prevent sell pressure is indeed a major achievement.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[7年後追憶Coinbase CEO...]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/szrf5j/remembering_coinbase_ceo_7_years_later/?score=473&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fszrf5j%2Fremembering_coinbase_ceo_7_years_later%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fszrf5j%2Fremembering_coinbase_ceo_7_years_later%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/szrf5j/remembering_coinbase_ceo_7_years_later/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 01:22:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特魯多撤銷《緊急狀態法》，渥太華抗議活動結束]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szth6f/trudeau_revokes_emergencies_act_as_ottawa_protest/?score=607&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszth6f%2Ftrudeau_revokes_emergencies_act_as_ottawa_protest%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszth6f%2Ftrudeau_revokes_emergencies_act_as_ottawa_protest%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szth6f/trudeau_revokes_emergencies_act_as_ottawa_protest/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 01:22:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[XRP不能被踢出市值前十名，無論市場發生什麼FUD：熊或SEC都不能殺死它...... 這就像該死的 "終結者"...。還有誰對此感到好笑/不解？]]></title><description><![CDATA[夥計，我記得這個子在20年12月的時候，出現了那麼多的備忘錄，有那個
在葬禮上和xR(I)P一起在墓碑旁大笑的那個傢伙。整個加密貨幣
twitter都瘋了。"XRP將在1月底前跌出前十名
'21'..."

"中心化 "的廢話終於出了門，...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sznpv1/xrp_cant_be_kicked_out_of_top_10_by_market_cap_no/?score=360&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsznpv1%2Fxrp_cant_be_kicked_out_of_top_10_by_market_cap_no%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsznpv1%2Fxrp_cant_be_kicked_out_of_top_10_by_market_cap_no%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sznpv1/xrp_cant_be_kicked_out_of_top_10_by_market_cap_no/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 01:22:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Man, I remember this sub back in December &amp;amp;#39;20, so many memes appearing with that dude laughing at the funeral near the tombstone with xR(I)P. The entire crypto twitter going wild: &amp;amp;quot;XRP gonna drop out of top ten by the end of January &amp;amp;#39;21&amp;amp;#39;...&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The &amp;amp;quot;centralized&amp;amp;quot; crap finally going out of the door, good riddance etc. etc. Meanwhile we still have centralized crap like BNB and Solana also in the top 10 that make XRP Ledger look like the most decentralized thing since Bitcoin...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now, you all wonder, ok dude but where&amp;amp;#39;s the joke(s), you had me with that comedy flair.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Well, yeah, HODL my milk cause those nipples need a refill but I have the feeling that in the end the joke is on us.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Once the headlines read: &amp;amp;quot;Ripple beats SEC&amp;amp;quot; that XRP shitcoin is gonna go 2x-5x from current prices and the unimaginable (that turned out to be real at least once in the past) flipping FUD (XRP over ETH) will be a thing again...&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這家德國保險公司稱公開數據太低&amp;提到了道德......這爲保險業的其他公司效仿提供了掩護&amp;他們會的。新聞流的海嘯對宣傳者來說將是無法控制的。

2/23/2022 堤壩破裂之日！https://t.co/EUf7OFqsea]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1496629828572827650/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1496629828572827650/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 23:36:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我如何清洗我的比特幣？]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以我已經堆積了幾年了，幾乎只通過
Coinbase。由於最近美國和加拿大都在嘗試監管，我
我希望我的加密貨幣是真正匿名的。我應該如何將我的比特幣
從我現在的錢包轉移到一個非kyc交易所，這樣我就可以 "洗 "了。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/szm0ac/how_do_i_wash_my_bitcoin/?score=360&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fszm0ac%2Fhow_do_i_wash_my_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fszm0ac%2Fhow_do_i_wash_my_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/szm0ac/how_do_i_wash_my_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 23:34:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So I’ve been stacking for a couple years now, pretty much only buying through Coinbase. With the recent attempts of regulation in both the US and Canada, I want my crypto to be truly anonymous. How should I go about moving my Bitcoin from my current wallet to a non-kyc exchange so that I can “wash” it? Should I transfer to USDC first? I know if I cash it out and re-enter, that will probably trigger the IRS and that’s the last thing I want. Any and all advice is welcome.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[加州提出接受比特幣納稅的法案]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szixf5/california_introduces_bill_to_accept_bitcoin_for/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszixf5%2Fcalifornia_introduces_bill_to_accept_bitcoin_for%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszixf5%2Fcalifornia_introduces_bill_to_accept_bitcoin_for%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szixf5/california_introduces_bill_to_accept_bitcoin_for/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 22:42:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[現實檢查：不要指望進入比特幣成爲一個百萬富翁。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們都看到了 "100k EOY "的影響者是如何在我們進入2022年時被幹掉的。

即使如此，如果比特幣達到10萬，那也只是2倍，這是非常令人印象深刻的。
不要誤會我的意思，但這還不足以讓你成爲百萬富翁。

你看到的大多數人在加密貨幣領域賺了這麼多錢，基本上...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sziozv/reality_check_dont_go_into_bitcoin_expecting_to/?score=351&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsziozv%2Freality_check_dont_go_into_bitcoin_expecting_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsziozv%2Freality_check_dont_go_into_bitcoin_expecting_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sziozv/reality_check_dont_go_into_bitcoin_expecting_to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 21:38:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;We’ve all seen how the “100k EOY” influencers got rekt as we entered 2022.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Even still, if Bitcoin reaches 100k that’s only 2x which is super impressive don’t get me wrong, but its not enough to make you a millionaire.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Most people you see who made this much money in the crypto space basically got lucky investing in start ups that boomed.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Some end up being scams and rug pulls, other prove to be a great investment.
A trusted launchpad like Binance or even SolanaPrime since it has insurance backing would decrease those chances of scams a lot though.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bottom line is. Bitcoin is a very cool and safe investment. I love it. But if you want fast profits, you’re looking in the wrong place.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我在2022年1月1日買了1千美元的十大加密貨幣（JAN Update/Month 1）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[試驗 - 追蹤2022年10大加密貨幣 - 第一個月 - 下跌-24%。
[https://preview.redd.it/llcfnowpllj81.png?width=666&format=png&auto=webp&s=4d72f368169047684e5d86e400f26521c8984887]

在這裏找到包含所有表格的完整博文
[https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2022-top-10...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szjzc3/i_bought_1k_of_the_top_10_cryptos_on_january_1st/?score=322&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszjzc3%2Fi_bought_1k_of_the_top_10_cryptos_on_january_1st%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszjzc3%2Fi_bought_1k_of_the_top_10_cryptos_on_january_1st%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szjzc3/i_bought_1k_of_the_top_10_cryptos_on_january_1st/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 19:34:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/llcfnowpllj81.png?width=666&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=4d72f368169047684e5d86e400f26521c8984887&quot;&amp;gt;EXPERIMENT - Tracking Top 10 Cryptos Of 2022 - Month One – Down -24&amp;amp;#37;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Find the full blog post with all the tables&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2022-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-1/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Welcome to your monthly no-shill data dump: Here&amp;amp;#39;s the very &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;first monthly report for the 2022 Top Ten Experiment&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; featuring &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BTC, ETH, BNB, SOL, ADA, USDC, XRP, LUNA, DOT, and AVAX.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;tl;dr&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;What&amp;amp;#39;s this all about?&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; I purchased $100 of each of Top 10 Cryptos in Jan. 2018, haven&amp;amp;#39;t sold or traded, reporting monthly for over four years. Did the same in 2019, 2020, 2021, and 2022. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Learn more about the history and rules of the Experiments&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/about/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;.  Learn more about the new features in the 2022 Top Ten Experiment&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/announcing-top-10-2022/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Snapshots taken on the 1st of each month.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;January Highlights:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Bloody month, all in red except the stable. &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;New features:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; easy +11% on &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;USDC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptex.finance/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TCAP&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; takes the first round in my friendly TCAP vs. Top Ten comparison &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;2018+2019+2020+2021+2022 Combined Top Ten Portfolios are returning 224%.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Month One – Down -24%&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/qvj2yi1jmlj81.jpg?width=1048&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=1727944b3ef4d416d75106a10d61f40c49d27c06&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/qvj2yi1jmlj81.jpg?width=1048&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=1727944b3ef4d416d75106a10d61f40c49d27c06&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Welcome to the first monthly update of the brand new 2022 Top Ten Crypto Index Fund Experiment!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If you want more details on how/where I purchased these cryptos or have any general questions on the Experiment as a whole, feel free to check out my &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/announcing-top-10-2022/21/&quot;&amp;gt;announcement post&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, otherwise, let’s jump in to the first update. Let’s go!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The 2022 Top Ten Crypto Index Fund Portfolio is &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BTC, ETH, BNB, Solana, ADA, USDC, XRP, LUNA, DOT, AVAX&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;January highlights for the 2022 Top Ten Portfolio:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;A rough start for the  2022 Top Ten Portfolio, down nearly one quarter by the end of January.  &amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;USDC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; is the only crypto in the green&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;Traditional markets drop as well, but not nearly as much as crypto&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;January Ranking and Dropouts&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here’s a look at the movement in the ranks one month into the 2022 Top Ten Index Fund Experiment:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/twzj7sm9nlj81.jpg?width=232&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=20b23b5a47188681a52dc58bcd3afb010ea237c4&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/twzj7sm9nlj81.jpg?width=232&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=20b23b5a47188681a52dc58bcd3afb010ea237c4&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A bit of internal shuffling, but not a whole lot of movement in January.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;January Winners and Losers&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;January Winners&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; – Since crypto was down this month, an easy victory for &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;USDC.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; Plus I was able to make about +16% on bonuses and interest (more on that below).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;January Losers&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; –  &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;LUNA&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; got hammered in January, losing about -41% of its value.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Overall Update – Bloody start to 2022: 90% of Top Ten in the red.&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2021-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-1/&quot;&amp;gt;In stark contrast to January 2021,&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; this year is off to a very shaky start.  Never a good sign when first place for the month is a stablecoin (&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;USDC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;LUNA&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; is at the bottom, down -41% in one month.  The initial $100 invested in &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;LUNA&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; thirty days ago is worth $59 today.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Factoring in USDC Gains&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;New feature this year!&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; – In past years, I have not included the ROI that is possible with stablecoins in the monthly reports. These days, there are many ways to earn ROI using stables alone.  I figure this may be especially interesting this year, depending on how the crypto market performs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For the 2022 Top Ten Experiment, I will detail ways to build on the $100 &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;USDC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, starting with the most straightforward strategies.  As we go along in the year, I will share increasingly advanced methods to increase &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;USDC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. My goal of this little side quest will be to beat the ROI of as many of the non-stablecoin cryptos in the Experiment as possible. A simple task if 2022 ends up being a bear year, a bit more difficult if the crypto market moons.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;January&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; – One of the easiest methods to capitalize on stables (or any crypto for that matter) is to take advantage of sign up bonuses of different platforms, many of which can be triggered with a small initial investment.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As detailed in the &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/announcing-top-10-2022/&quot;&amp;gt;2022 Top Ten Index Fund Announcement&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; post, I purchased the $100 of &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;USDC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; through BlockFi.  I signed up using a promo code and received $10 in &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BTC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, which I immediately converted to &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;USDC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;.  These codes are everywhere online (or just ask a friend).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Since the BlockFi Interest Account (BIA) is also paying 8.75% APY on stablecoins, the current running total on the $100 initial &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;USDC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; purchase is: &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$110.64&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/yyuwcf7hnlj81.jpg?width=739&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=1007b85cb5b4683535ac651a02d1650b6f939aff&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/yyuwcf7hnlj81.jpg?width=739&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=1007b85cb5b4683535ac651a02d1650b6f939aff&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There is another BlockFi promo code where you are able to receive $15 in &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BTC&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; on $100, but this bonus can take up to three months.  Going for the $15 bonus might make more sense once you’ve received bonuses from other platforms.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Something to be aware of:&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; US-based BlockFi customers are not currently allowed to add funds to a BIA due to American regulations.  BlockFi is currently in the SEC registration process to offer interest through BlockFi Yield, which will replace BIAs. Bonuses are still valid.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;2022 Top Ten Portfolio vs. Total Crypto Market Cap Token (TCAP)&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Another new feature this year!&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; – The first Top Ten Crypto Experiment was started on 1 January 2018 in an attempt to capture the gains of the entire market. Much has changed in the last four+ years, including innovative Decentralized Finance (DeFi) projects that have created index tokens to capture segments of the crypto market (DeFi, the Metaverse, Blue Chips, etc.) instead of manually buying coins and tokens, like I do for my Experiments.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A project of particular interest to the Top Ten Experiments is the Total Crypto Market Cap (&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://cryptex.finance/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TCAP&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;) token, created by Cryptex, which tracks the entire crypto market – exactly what my Top Ten Portfolios have been trying to recreate from the start.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I thought it would be interesting to compare my homemade 2022 Top Ten Crypto Index Fund Experiment to the &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TCAP&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; token for a bit of a friendly competition. Here’s the question I’ll be tracking this year: &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;would I have been better off with $1,000 of TCAP instead of going through the effort of creating a homemade $1,000 Top Ten Index Fund?&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;January:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With most of crypto in the red, both the &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TCAP&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; token and the 2022 Top Ten Portfolio got hit hard, down -20% and -24% respectively.  In the end, Round 1 goes to Cryptex’s &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;TCAP&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; token.  Visual below:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/p3uearnjnlj81.jpg?width=484&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=738d98736f3a6029dbb15e5a1929b1d5e42151aa&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/p3uearnjnlj81.jpg?width=484&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=738d98736f3a6029dbb15e5a1929b1d5e42151aa&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Bitcoin Dominance:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;BitDom started 2022 at 40.2% and ticked up one percentage point in January, ending the month at 41.2%.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/uc3z66etnlj81.png?width=522&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=dd051ace1772b0f5608de8bff64cc7314316f663&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/uc3z66etnlj81.png?width=522&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=dd051ace1772b0f5608de8bff64cc7314316f663&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For those just getting into crypto, it’s worth paying attention to the &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Bitcoin&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; dominance figure, as it signals the appetite for altcoins vs. &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;BTC.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Overall return on $1,000 investment since January 1st, 2022:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/mrjy6uiunlj81.jpg?width=306&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=4a6d040271cea873b6a7bca5682ba606925c834d&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/mrjy6uiunlj81.jpg?width=306&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=4a6d040271cea873b6a7bca5682ba606925c834d&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Unlike the 2021 Top Ten Experiment (&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2021-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-1/&quot;&amp;gt;which was up +51% in its first month&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;), the 2022 Portfolio is off to a rough start: the initial $1000 investment on New Year’s Day 2022 is now worth &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$762&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;, down -24%. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Combining the 2018, 2019, 2020, 2021, and 2022 Top Ten Crypto Portfolios&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So, where do we stand if we combine five years of the Top Ten Crypto Index Fund Experiments?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-49&quot;&amp;gt;2018 Top Ten Experiment&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;: up +4% (total value $1,035)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;2019 Top Ten Experiment: up +364% (total value $4,639)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;2020 Top Ten Experiment: up +577% (total value $6,766)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;2021 Top Ten Experiment: up +201% (total value $3,009)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2022-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-1/&quot;&amp;gt;2022 Top Ten Experiment:&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; down -25% (total value $747)&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Taking the five portfolios together, here’s the bottom bottom bottom bottom &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;bottom&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; line: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;After a $5,000 investment in the 2018, 2019, 2020, 2021, and 2022 Top Ten Cryptocurrencies,&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; the combined portfolios are worth &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;$16,196.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That’s &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;up +224&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; on the combined portfolios.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;For context, that is &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;way up from one year ago&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; (+127%) but &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;way&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;down from&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2021-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-11/&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;November’s all time high of +553%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.  To get a sense of the entire journey, here’s the combined monthly ROI since I started tracking the metric in January 2020:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/93uwa8x4olj81.png?width=600&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=c160172bb1cdce15a83767eaff9cbc4730e92f9c&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/93uwa8x4olj81.png?width=600&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=c160172bb1cdce15a83767eaff9cbc4730e92f9c&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;That’s a +224% gain by buying $1k of the cryptos that happened to be in the Top Ten (including stablecoins) on January 1st, 2018, 2019, 2020, 2021, and 2022.&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Comparison to S&amp;amp;amp;P 500&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’m also tracking the S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 as part of my Experiment to have a comparison point to traditional markets.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/josk699aolj81.png?width=538&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=bbd42eea95b9e2135f90387f21819961d16597f6&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/josk699aolj81.png?width=538&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=bbd42eea95b9e2135f90387f21819961d16597f6&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 is down -5% so far in 2022, so the initial $1k investment into crypto on New Year’s Day would be worth $950 had it been redirected to the S&amp;amp;amp;P.  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Taking the same invest-$1,000-on-January-1st-of-each-year approach with the S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 that I’ve been documenting through the Top Ten Crypto Experiments, the yields are the following:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2018 = $1,700 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2019 = $1,810 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2020 = $1,410 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2021 = $1,210 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;$1000 investment in S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 on January 1st, 2022 = $950 today&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Taken together, here’s the bottom bottom bottom bottom &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;bottom&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; line for a similar approach with the S&amp;amp;amp;P: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;After five $1,000 investments into an S&amp;amp;amp;P 500 index fund in January 2018, 2019, 2020, 2021, and 2022 my portfolio would be worth $7,080.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;That is up &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+42%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-ten-month-one/&quot;&amp;gt;since January 2018&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; compared to a &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;+224%&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; gain of the combined Top Ten Crypto Experiment Portfolios.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here’s a fancy new chart showing a combined ROI comparison between a Top Ten Crypto approach and the S&amp;amp;amp;P as per the rules of the Top Ten Experiments: &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/22hpx3tcolj81.png?width=575&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9635b15d1b0cb9622b54327bd23e472252f06004&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/22hpx3tcolj81.png?width=575&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9635b15d1b0cb9622b54327bd23e472252f06004&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h2&amp;gt;Conclusion:&amp;lt;/h2&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;To the long time followers of the Top Ten Experiments, thank you so much for sticking around so long. For those just getting into crypto, I hope these reports will help prepare you for the highs and lows that await on your crypto adventures.  Buckle up, go with the flow, think long term, don’t invest what you can’t afford to lose, and most importantly, try to enjoy the ride!  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A reporting note: I’ll focus on 2022 Top Ten Portfolio reports + one other portfolio on a rotating basis this year, so expect only two reports from me per month.  This month’s extended report was on the 2018 Top Ten Portfolio, which is almost back down to break even point.  Read all the gory details&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-49&quot;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;here&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Feel free to reach out with any questions and stay tuned for progress reports. Keep an eye out for my parallel projects tracking the Top Ten cryptos as of &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2018-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-49&quot;&amp;gt;January 1st, 2018&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; (the OG Experiment), &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2019-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-36&quot;&amp;gt;January 1st, 2019&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/tracking-2020-top-10-cryptocurrencies-month-24&quot;&amp;gt;January 1st, 2020&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, and most recently, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://toptencryptoindexfund.com/announcing-top-10-2022/&quot;&amp;gt;January 1st, 2022&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[隱性貨幣對我來說絕對毀了股票。]]></title><description><![CDATA[隱性貨幣絕對破壞了我的動機，甚至看我的股票組合。

在加密貨幣之前，我是一個主要的股票和期權投資者，購買高
買入AT&T這樣的高股息貴族股票，然後每當有一個相對穩定的資產的價格上升時，就賣出覆蓋式看漲期權。
然後在一個相對穩定的資產的價格上升時賣出套期保值。10%的紅利加上...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szb56a/crypto_has_absolutely_ruined_stocks_for_me/?score=317&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszb56a%2Fcrypto_has_absolutely_ruined_stocks_for_me%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszb56a%2Fcrypto_has_absolutely_ruined_stocks_for_me%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szb56a/crypto_has_absolutely_ruined_stocks_for_me/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 18:36:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto has absolutely destroyed my incentive to even look at my stock portfolio. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Before crypto I was a major stocks and options investor, who bought high dividend aristocrats like AT&amp;amp;amp;T, then sold covered calls whenever there was an uptick in price on a relatively stable asset. 10% dividends plus options premiums made me drool like you wouldn’t believe. I did put spreads to buy stocks I believed in, iron condors during low volatility phases, the works. I made enough to put a down payment on a house through slow methodical management of my portfolio, while hedging and making money off premiums rather than gambling. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Now I yoloswag into new defi protocols like Mmf and darkcrypto, and consistently make 200-700% APR like nobody’s business, even while gaining appreciation on my coins. I still monitor risk and stay away from shitcoins, but I’m constantly yield farming protocols that have gained some traction, and go ham into new protocols that check the boxes for me. 100$ per day from yields on only 10k invested is common now, even during the recent downturn, where before 10k invested meant $100 per MONTH. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It’s absolutely RUINED stocks for me. I went from daily management of my portfolio on fidelity, schwab, and even Robinhood, and have since transferred all of my non-retirement stocks into m1finance (which auto rebalances and DCAs) and look at it once a week at best. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What a ride it’s been. Even as the market tumbled, I’m happily plugging away at the different yield farming opportunities, and While I do have the occasional loss on a protocol that I miscalculated the fall, the winners have made up for the rare loss 10x over. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As I get older and need more stability, I’m sure I’ll return, but as it is, crypto is my roller coaster, and stocks are the teacup ride that you’re forced to go on because your niece can’t go on any other ride. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TL;DR: crypto defi return (and loss) potentials blow all stock plays out of the water, and is my crack cocaine.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一些好的'OL比特幣公關👍]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/szjzbb/some_good_ol_bitcoin_pr/?score=313&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fszjzbb%2Fsome_good_ol_bitcoin_pr%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fszjzbb%2Fsome_good_ol_bitcoin_pr%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/szjzbb/some_good_ol_bitcoin_pr/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 18:36:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[前SEC官員預測SEC將輸掉對瑞波的訴訟]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szeysa/sec_will_lose_lawsuit_against_ripple_former_sec/?score=373&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszeysa%2Fsec_will_lose_lawsuit_against_ripple_former_sec%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fszeysa%2Fsec_will_lose_lawsuit_against_ripple_former_sec%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/szeysa/sec_will_lose_lawsuit_against_ripple_former_sec/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 14:34:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我來到比特幣是爲了收益，但我將爲革命而留下來。我將對CBDC說不!]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/szayax/i_came_to_bitcoin_for_the_gains_but_i_will_stay/?score=377&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fszayax%2Fi_came_to_bitcoin_for_the_gains_but_i_will_stay%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fszayax%2Fi_came_to_bitcoin_for_the_gains_but_i_will_stay%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/szayax/i_came_to_bitcoin_for_the_gains_but_i_will_stay/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 13:32:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不存在任何有關的問題，也不存在任何有關的問題 https://t.co/xLAlHFRprh]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1496426028310355968/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1496426028310355968/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 10:40:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hey @JustinTrudeau 👹....Are we allowed to help people pay for groceries who had had had their bank accounts frozen? 

還是說這將使我們成爲合作者，並使我們的賬戶也被凍結？

以前從未在獨裁國家生活過，所以不清楚所有的後勤工作🤔。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1496419227045093380/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1496419227045093380/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 09:40:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[好吧，這是個漫長而艱難的過程，但我終於成爲了一個完整的投幣者！"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直在儘可能多地買入下跌的股票，最終達到了擁有1
BTC。現在是擁有2個的下一個目標。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/syplbh/well_it_has_been_a_long_hard_slog_but_i_am/?score=309&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsyplbh%2Fwell_it_has_been_a_long_hard_slog_but_i_am%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsyplbh%2Fwell_it_has_been_a_long_hard_slog_but_i_am%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/syplbh/well_it_has_been_a_long_hard_slog_but_i_am/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 08:44:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Been buying the dips as much as I could and finally reached my goal of owning 1 BTC.   Now on the the next goal of owning 2.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[市場是紅色的，你的投資是下降的，所以把你的注意力從損失上移開，來享受一局神之解鎖。]]></title><description><![CDATA[> Gods Unchained是一款區塊鏈交易卡牌遊戲，它採用了《爐石傳說》的一些最佳功能。
> 爐石傳說》的特點，但有一個獨特的法力系統和一個原創的青睞
> 的功能。它允許你賺取卡片和飾品，然後你可以在
>市場上出售。NFTs存儲在以太坊和...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sz48hw/the_market_is_red_your_investments_are_down_so/?score=321&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsz48hw%2Fthe_market_is_red_your_investments_are_down_so%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsz48hw%2Fthe_market_is_red_your_investments_are_down_so%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sz48hw/the_market_is_red_your_investments_are_down_so/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 07:31:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;blockquote&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Gods Unchained is a blockchain trading card game that &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;takes some of the best features from&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;Hearthstone,&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;but has a unique mana system and an original favor feature&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;. It allows you to earn cards and trinkets, which you can then sell on the marketplace. NFTs are stored on the &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Ethereum&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Immutable-X&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; blockchains. The game is available only for &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Windows.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/blockquote&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Take this time to earn some NFT&amp;amp;#39;s in the form of Trading cards that are going up in value and at the same time enjoy playing a game to distract yourself from the crypto winter before us.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Gods Unchained is a play to earn game, completely free to play and advance at your own pace.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know some of you think NFT&amp;amp;#39;s are stupid but they work great for a trading card games, you actually own your cards and can easily sell, trade and buy cards on the Immutable-X market place.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;you can start playing today and start earning cards today.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Roadmap&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/4iy9twlufhj81.png?width=1110&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=4449f6206dba529b220cf9e58eaf927e40f2fd04&quot;&amp;gt;https://trello.com/b/GpDgnYPZ/gods-unchained-roadmap&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;Mobile coming soon&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h3&amp;gt;What can we expect to see from the game?&amp;lt;/h3&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There’s a lot to come with the game, but in order not to ruin the gaming experience achieved through the likes of future expansion sets (e.g. new NFT card sets, we can’t disclose many details. But here’s a high-level overview of what we’re working on.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Mobile game release:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; We have an internal team designing and building out a mobile version of Gods Unchained to ease the barrier of entry by allowing the game to be played on the go. Our first touchstone is to get a playable alpha out this year. Our hope is to deliver the first access to our players in the first half of next year, with a wider alpha sometime in the second half of the year.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Expanding the game:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; We have a heap of new cards coming out early this year with a refresh of our main card set: the Core set (a set is a collection of cards). We also have brand new NFT expansion sets in the works, alongside new game functionalities, items, and modes. To tie these developments all together, the team is also hard at work improving the new player onboarding experience. This will make it easier for anyone and everyone to join Gods Unchained and get playing.&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/0aoaq5tahhj81.png?width=603&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=8563d6d8e0cc6727bcd944d6647cb6d572ece69e&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/0aoaq5tahhj81.png?width=603&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=8563d6d8e0cc6727bcd944d6647cb6d572ece69e&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/akyq6d7chhj81.jpg?width=289&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=3e0c731f0a722a7e70c7db92818608ac9ec5553f&quot;&amp;gt;https://godsunchained.com/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;It&amp;amp;#39;s Time to Duel!&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/r746l1aphhj81.gif&quot;&amp;gt;https://i.redd.it/r746l1aphhj81.gif&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If any of you decide to play and are up for a challenge let me know, Direct challenges are available and it would be fun to play some of you on this sub.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;TLDR: play Gods Unchained to distract yourself during crypto winter.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[只是爲了好玩，我做了一個預測比特幣價格的程序]]></title><description><![CDATA[我很無聊，想寫一個python程序，我決定寫一個
一個預測比特幣的程序。

它的工作原理是，它查看過去N天的價格圖（通過不同的N值循環），然後試圖找到摩根的時間。
不同的N值），然後試圖找到過去最相似的價格模式的時間
在過去發生的價格...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sz29b9/just_for_fun_i_made_a_program_that_predicts_the/?score=342&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsz29b9%2Fjust_for_fun_i_made_a_program_that_predicts_the%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsz29b9%2Fjust_for_fun_i_made_a_program_that_predicts_the%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sz29b9/just_for_fun_i_made_a_program_that_predicts_the/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 06:39:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I was bored trying to think of a python program to write and I decided to write a bitcoin predicting program.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;How it works is it looks at the price graph for the last N (cycling through different values of N) days then tries to find the time the most similar pattern in price occurred in the past to the current pattern, then predicts the price based on what happened after that previous pattern occurred.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is probably worthless and won&amp;amp;#39;t be an accurate reflection of the future price at all, but just for fun, here&amp;amp;#39;s what it says about the next few years of bitcoin.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;It says that the current pattern we&amp;amp;#39;re in is reminiscent of 2018-01-06.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;On the graph, the left side of the green line is the recent price history (red line) and historical price history from 2018-01-06 (blue line), and right of the green line, the future price (red line) is modelled after the price history from 2018. The y-axis numbers on the left are the recent/future price and the y-axis numbers on the right are the historical prices from 2018.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;90-day prediction:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Graph: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/gyQu523.png&quot;&amp;gt;https://i.imgur.com/gyQu523.png&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Peak: 2022-02-24 $41,030.37&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bottom: 2022-04-19 $24,538.98&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Final: 2022-05-21 $34,227.86&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;1-year prediction:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Graph: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/1MZjLFX.png&quot;&amp;gt;https://i.imgur.com/1MZjLFX.png&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Peak: 2022-02-24 $41,030.37&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bottom: 2022-10-06 $13,340.72&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Final: 2023-02-20 $22,262.68&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;(just under) 3-year prediction:&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; (falls just short of 3 years, I think because it doesn&amp;amp;#39;t have enough data)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Graph: &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/m76ks2c.png&quot;&amp;gt;https://i.imgur.com/m76ks2c.png&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Peak: 2025-08-30 $282,899.62&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bottom: 2022-10-06 $13,340.72&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Final: 2025-12-13 $155,385.66&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So there you have it. Just a bit of entertainment. Don&amp;amp;#39;t go investing based on this. I&amp;amp;#39;m gonna keep track and see how successful its predictions were.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美聯儲官員被禁止交易!]]></title><description><![CDATA[正如你可能已經看到的那樣，在過去的幾天裏，有一個頭條新聞在互聯網上流傳。
互聯網。美聯儲官員被禁止交易股票、債券和
加密貨幣。

很明顯，有許多人抱怨，許多人認爲這應該在很久以前就開始實施。
很久以前就推出了。

我個人認爲...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sysldq/fed_officials_banned_from_trading/?score=301&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsysldq%2Ffed_officials_banned_from_trading%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsysldq%2Ffed_officials_banned_from_trading%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sysldq/fed_officials_banned_from_trading/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 05:34:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;As you&amp;amp;#39;ve probably seen the last days, there has been a headline going around the internet: FED officials are banned from trading stocks, bonds and also cryptocurrencies. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Obviously there were many complaints and many that thought this should have been introduced long time ago.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I personally think it&amp;amp;#39;s a good decision, as they are the ones who have a word in the way the economy is going, so it wouldn&amp;amp;#39;t be fair if they were allowed to trade prior to their own decisions (unfair advantage). &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Also, last year there were controversies regarding some positions traded by them right before the COVID measures to help the economy.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What&amp;amp;#39;s your opinion? 
Tell me in the comments below.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這就是加密圈被大衆接受所需要的保護：英國警方將價值540萬美元的加密貨幣返還給世界各地的詐騙受害者]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://news.bitcoin.com/uk-police-return-5-4-million-to-cryptocurrency-fraud-victims/

與加密貨幣有關的騙局層出不窮，而媒體也試圖將其吹得天花亂墜。
所以這些騙局已經成爲我們進步的一個主要絆腳石。
爲我們的進步。

上面的文章談到了如何...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/syhnnc/this_is_the_kind_of_protection_the_cryptosphere/?score=302&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsyhnnc%2Fthis_is_the_kind_of_protection_the_cryptosphere%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsyhnnc%2Fthis_is_the_kind_of_protection_the_cryptosphere%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/syhnnc/this_is_the_kind_of_protection_the_cryptosphere/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 05:34:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://news.bitcoin.com/uk-police-return-5-4-million-to-cryptocurrency-fraud-victims/&quot;&amp;gt;https://news.bitcoin.com/uk-police-return-5-4-million-to-cryptocurrency-fraud-victims/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Crypto related scams are a dime a dozen and the media also attempts to blow up every single one of em so that these scams have become a major stumbling block for our progress.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The article above talks about how the Greater Manchester Police seized $5.4Mil of crypto from a scam that spannes the globe and are now returning it to the victims who come from places like Europe, China, Australia, HK, UK and the US.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Theres $10Mil more that they plan to recover still and distribute among the 150 or so victims. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I dont know how they did or how they located the victims but i assume having a permanent public ledger that keeps track of all expenses may have helped!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Seeing something like this amidst all the Canadian anti-crypto dicktatorship and Indian taxation issues gives me hope that it may indeed be possible to clamp down on crypto scams. Now if only the politicians would take note.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Does anyone know if the UK has any specific crypto protection laws or are crypto crimes regulated just like other financial crimes?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[60%的商家希望在一年內接受加密貨幣。報告顯示，60%的商家希望在一年內接受加密貨幣]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/syyr08/60_of_merchants_want_to_accept_crypto_within_a/?score=307&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsyyr08%2F60_of_merchants_want_to_accept_crypto_within_a%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsyyr08%2F60_of_merchants_want_to_accept_crypto_within_a%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/syyr08/60_of_merchants_want_to_accept_crypto_within_a/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 04:43:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[著名的色情明星詐騙她的社區，帶着150萬美元跑路了]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sz5e78/famous_porn_star_scams_her_community_runs_away/?score=453&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsz5e78%2Ffamous_porn_star_scams_her_community_runs_away%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsz5e78%2Ffamous_porn_star_scams_her_community_runs_away%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sz5e78/famous_porn_star_scams_her_community_runs_away/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 04:43:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[比特幣錢包製造商收到加拿大 "凍結 "錢包的命令]]></title><description><![CDATA[加拿大的情況對加密貨幣社區來說很有意思。也就是說，它
它顯示了政府是如何處理像比特幣（BTC）這樣的加密貨幣的。
試圖奪取財政資源。而在最近幾天，它
很明顯，加拿大當局並不確定該怎麼做...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/syx42w/bitcoin_wallet_maker_gets_order_from_canada_to/?score=331&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsyx42w%2Fbitcoin_wallet_maker_gets_order_from_canada_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsyx42w%2Fbitcoin_wallet_maker_gets_order_from_canada_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/syx42w/bitcoin_wallet_maker_gets_order_from_canada_to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 03:34:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The situation in Canada is interesting for the crypto community. Namely, it shows how a government deals with cryptocurrencies like bitcoin (BTC) in a situation where it is trying to seize financial resources. And in recent days it became clear that Canadian authorities are not so sure what to do with it!&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Canada is on the heels of truckers and supporters&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;In Canada, a large group of truckers protested for a long time by blocking cities, border crossings and bridges with their trucks. The action could count on quite some support in Canada and worldwide. The truckers received many donations, also in the form of crypto. After Prime Minister Justin Trudeau activated the controversial and draconian Emergencies Act, authorities were able to freeze bank accounts and obtain data without the intervention of a judge. This is to deal with the support and consequences of the protest.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Freezing Bitcoin Wallets&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;So in recent days there have been plenty of articles in crypto news about how Canadian authorities are going after the truckers. But remarkably, they don&amp;amp;#39;t seem to fully understand how crypto works. Nunchuk, a wallet developer recently received an order from the Ontario Superior Court of Justice to &amp;amp;quot;freeze&amp;amp;quot; bitcoin wallets of truckers and &amp;amp;quot;release data.&amp;amp;quot; Such actions are obviously impossible for a wallet developer. In a response, Nunchuk let the court know:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;&amp;amp;quot;We do not collect user identification information other than email addresses. We also do not have keys. Therefore, we cannot &amp;amp;quot;freeze&amp;amp;quot; our users&amp;amp;#39; assets. We cannot &amp;amp;quot;prevent&amp;amp;quot; them from being moved. We have no knowledge of &amp;amp;quot;the existence, nature, value and location&amp;amp;quot; of our users&amp;amp;#39; assets. This is by design.&amp;amp;quot;&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/v6gyr02lzfj81.png?width=588&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=2efad357efd1325441c51876beedd8ad958bbd34&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/v6gyr02lzfj81.png?width=588&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=2efad357efd1325441c51876beedd8ad958bbd34&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If one has bitcoin in one&amp;amp;#39;s own wallet, no one can access it unless they have access to the private key. Keep this private key safe at all times and do not share it with anyone.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你們中的大多數人爲了未來的利潤買了NFT，最終會被卡住。證明我錯了]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道NFT不僅僅是JPG。

我知道有些NFT是藝術。

我知道傳統藝術也可能是無用的。

我知道有些人從中賺了大錢。

但他們中的大多數只是對未來收益的空頭承諾。

不像購買加密貨幣，你可以真正出售或支付...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sz0fgu/most_of_you_who_bought_nfts_for_future_profits/?score=466&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsz0fgu%2Fmost_of_you_who_bought_nfts_for_future_profits%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsz0fgu%2Fmost_of_you_who_bought_nfts_for_future_profits%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sz0fgu/most_of_you_who_bought_nfts_for_future_profits/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 02:08:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know that NFTs are not just JPGs.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know some NFTs are art.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know that traditional art could be useless as well.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I know that some people made good money from that. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;But most of them are just empty promises for future gains.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Unlike buying cryptocurrency which you can actually sell or pay with (and it&amp;amp;#39;s value will likely increase), you&amp;amp;#39;ll end up stuck with a quickly deprecating asset that depends on hype.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Prove me wrong.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Won&amp;amp;#39;t most of those who spent their crypto on NFTs end up with nothing? 
Is it that different from regular collectables?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[女子在加密貨幣戀情騙局中失去39萬美元的遺產]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sys37m/woman_loses_390000_of_inheritance_in_crypto/?score=313&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsys37m%2Fwoman_loses_390000_of_inheritance_in_crypto%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsys37m%2Fwoman_loses_390000_of_inheritance_in_crypto%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sys37m/woman_loses_390000_of_inheritance_in_crypto/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 02:08:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[做好心理準備。]]></title><description><![CDATA[隨着俄羅斯對烏克蘭的持續入侵，美國和歐盟正在對俄羅斯實施金融
對俄羅斯實施金融制裁，並將從本質上試圖將其排除在國際經濟之外。
國際經濟。我認爲俄羅斯對此的反應是非常明顯的。
他們將擁抱比特幣，以便他們的...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/syrx06/be_mentally_ready/?score=364&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsyrx06%2Fbe_mentally_ready%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsyrx06%2Fbe_mentally_ready%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/syrx06/be_mentally_ready/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:58:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;With Russia&amp;amp;#39;s ongoing invasion of Ukraine, the U.S and EU are imposing financial sanctions on Russia and will essentially attempt to exclude them from the international economy. I think Russia&amp;amp;#39;s response to this is pretty obvious and telegraphed, they are going to embrace Bitcoin so that their oligarchs and members of government can continue to transact internationally. Hopefully their citizens are also allowed to use it without too much regulation, but not holding my breath. We&amp;amp;#39;ve already seen the draft bill of this, and now more than ever they have a justification to accelerate this. I don&amp;amp;#39;t know whether it happens in the next three weeks or next six month, but it appears to me that the course is set. Putin has been yearning to invade Ukraine ever since 2014, but the financial sanctions that would ensue were probably enough of a deterrent. Up until now. Putin now has an alternative, and he seems to have gained enough confidence in Bitcoin&amp;amp;#39;s decentralized and uncensorable attributes to use it to circumvent the international dollar system.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The reason for this post is to remind people that if/when Russia does this, you might want to reconsider how open you are in public about being a Bitcoiner.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;If Russia adopts Bitcoin, the legacy media and politicians are going to very quickly shape and pressure public opinion into believing that Bitcoin is to blame for Russia&amp;amp;#39;s sudden immunity to financial sanctions. They will call it a dictator&amp;amp;#39;s weapon and the reason why their financial warfare tactics are no longer effective. It could even get so bad as to a minority of media claiming that Bitcoiners are colluding with the Russian state. Stuff like &amp;amp;quot;The only reason why you own Bitcoin is to transact with the Russian state&amp;amp;quot; or &amp;amp;quot; Anyone promoting Bitcoin is promoting Russia&amp;amp;quot;. (Writing these easy to predict quips makes me feel physically sick).&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I personally have nothing but hatred and disgust for Vladimir Putin. He has shown on countless occasions that he is a psychopathic tyrant who uses force to coerce millions of people in doing things that are beneficial to him and detrimental to them. He is a net negative for humanity.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;However, Bitcoin is a neutral technology that is available to all. To dictators and freedom fighters alike. What each person decides to do with that tool is fully their responsibility and has nothing to do with the tool itself. For example, if it &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.themoscowtimes.com/2021/02/11/russian-opposition-finds-refuge-in-bitcoin-a72907&quot;&amp;gt;weren&amp;amp;#39;t for Bitcoin, there would not be any political opposition in Russia in the first place&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. Just as Putin can benefit by adopting Bitcoin, he can also be tremendously harmed by it.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Bitcoin is apolitical. I know that everyone in this sub understands this. But the majority of people do not.   And I&amp;amp;#39;m afraid that the topic of Bitcoin is about to get disgustingly politicized. If this is the case (I really hope I&amp;amp;#39;m wrong), then you might want to reconsider how open you are about being a Bitcoiner.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The decision will be 100% yours. Some will be defiant and brave enough to take on the senseless criticism heads on. Others will prefer to self-censor to avoid the emotionally draining societal pressure. Every person will know for themselves what the best course of action depending on their unique set of circumstances.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Be mindful that full scale social and political ostracization can be mentally very, very tough.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;All I&amp;amp;#39;m saying is to that it´s probably a good idea to decide ahead of time how you are going to act in case this likely scenario does indeed play out. This way you can minimize any regret.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;And, I can only hope that this amazing community will continue to be a refuge for divergent and politically alienated people. Whatever you decide to do, I feel confident in saying that Bitcoiners will keep on having each other´s back.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[喬-羅根播客｜比特幣正在顛覆權力階層，就像印刷術的發明一樣｜精英們正在用CBDC、疫苗護照和社會信用體系進行補償。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/syud95/joe_rogan_podcast_bitcoin_is_disrupting_power/?score=459&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsyud95%2Fjoe_rogan_podcast_bitcoin_is_disrupting_power%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsyud95%2Fjoe_rogan_podcast_bitcoin_is_disrupting_power%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/syud95/joe_rogan_podcast_bitcoin_is_disrupting_power/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:58:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[加密貨幣億萬富翁並不看重價格下跌。普通投資者纔是。"泰勒-溫克艾沃斯（Tyler Winklevoss）在他的推特賬戶上說："我非常看好加密貨幣，我已經好幾周沒有查看價格了。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/syqb8z/crypto_billionaires_arent_watching_price_drop/?score=326&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsyqb8z%2Fcrypto_billionaires_arent_watching_price_drop%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsyqb8z%2Fcrypto_billionaires_arent_watching_price_drop%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/syqb8z/crypto_billionaires_arent_watching_price_drop/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:36:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有人在instagram上冒充維塔利克，這是個騙局]]></title><description><![CDATA[IG上有一個名爲 "buterin_official "的賬戶，擁有100萬粉絲
正在通過INSTAGRAM的付費廣告宣傳一個騙局。

我重複一遍。


100萬名追隨者



我不能相信這通過了instagram的廣告...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/syunqu/someone_is_impersonating_vitalik_on_instagram_its/?score=315&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsyunqu%2Fsomeone_is_impersonating_vitalik_on_instagram_its%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsyunqu%2Fsomeone_is_impersonating_vitalik_on_instagram_its%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/syunqu/someone_is_impersonating_vitalik_on_instagram_its/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:36:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;There&amp;amp;#39;s an account on IG called &amp;amp;quot;buterin_official&amp;amp;quot; with &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;1 MILLION FOLLOWERS&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; that&amp;amp;#39;s promoting a scam THROUGH INSTAGRAM PAID ADS&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I repeat:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;1 MILLION FOLLOWERS&amp;lt;/h1&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;#x200B;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/g7kl0dbpgfj81.png?width=339&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=87122ff239a73253b1552bf45777ed8654a43aa5&quot;&amp;gt;I can&amp;amp;#39;t believe this passed the instagram ads process&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Vitalik &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;has no IG&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; and he didn&amp;amp;#39;t mention anything about this on his official page nor his verified twitter account.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The image is fake and the &amp;amp;quot;send 1 ETH get back 2&amp;amp;quot; is a scam older than the universe, don&amp;amp;#39;t fall for that crap please&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Here is the real image:&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/7zkfppbxgfj81.jpg?width=1136&amp;amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=9f2128cdaec63b26933cdecf769136eba7a0be2c&quot;&amp;gt;Original image&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Spread the word, let&amp;amp;#39;s end this kind of bullshit that only delegitimizes crypto&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Report the accounts &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/buterin_official/?hl=es&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.instagram.com/buterin_official/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/vitalikether/&quot;&amp;gt;https://www.instagram.com/vitalikether/&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在最近的加密貨幣市場下跌期間，幾個新幣已經滑入它們的 "買入區"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[一家領先的加密貨幣分析公司表示，最近的加密貨幣市場下跌使
將四種altcoins置於理想的購買範圍內。

根據Santiment的數據，1英寸（1INCH）
[https://swapzone.io/currencies/1inch?utm_source=reddit&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=promo]。
Loopring...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sypyqs/several_altcoins_have_slipped_into_their_buy/?score=397&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsypyqs%2Fseveral_altcoins_have_slipped_into_their_buy%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsypyqs%2Fseveral_altcoins_have_slipped_into_their_buy%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sypyqs/several_altcoins_have_slipped_into_their_buy/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 19:36:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;A leading crypto analytics firm says that the latest crypto market dip has placed four altcoins in the ideal buying range.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;According to Santiment, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://swapzone.io/currencies/1inch?utm_source=reddit&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=social&amp;amp;amp;utm_campaign=promo&quot;&amp;gt;1inch (1INCH)&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://swapzone.io/currencies/loopring?utm_source=reddit&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=social&amp;amp;amp;utm_campaign=promo&quot;&amp;gt;Loopring (LRC)&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://swapzone.io/currencies/ren?utm_source=reddit&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=social&amp;amp;amp;utm_campaign=promo&quot;&amp;gt;Ren Protocol (REN)&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; and The &amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://swapzone.io/currencies/sand?utm_source=reddit&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=social&amp;amp;amp;utm_campaign=promo&quot;&amp;gt;Sandbox (SAND)&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;are all in “buy the dip” territory.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
What do you think about it, have you heard of these projects, what&amp;amp;#39;s more important would you invest in them?  &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/skebuc59iej81.png?width=3840&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=3d0704850c0436904aa0eb3faf7e9282d704796b&quot;&amp;gt;https://preview.redd.it/skebuc59iej81.png?width=3840&amp;amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;amp;s=3d0704850c0436904aa0eb3faf7e9282d704796b&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[雷-達里奧。將最多2%的投資組合分配給比特幣是合理的]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sylx16/ray_dalio_allocating_up_to_2_of_your_portfolio_to/?score=330&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsylx16%2Fray_dalio_allocating_up_to_2_of_your_portfolio_to%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsylx16%2Fray_dalio_allocating_up_to_2_of_your_portfolio_to%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sylx16/ray_dalio_allocating_up_to_2_of_your_portfolio_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 18:31:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[這哥們在區塊鏈上做了一個替代Reddit。瘋狂]]></title><description><![CDATA[幾天前，我無意中發現了這個人，這讓我很震驚。
令人震驚。 

名爲Esteban Abaora的開發者開發了一個無服務器、無管理和
的替代方案，它將在區塊鏈系統上運行。
(它實際上將使用 "基於公鑰的尋址 "和一個區塊鏈系統。]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/syp7q6/this_dude_made_an_alternative_reddit_on_a/?score=551&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsyp7q6%2Fthis_dude_made_an_alternative_reddit_on_a%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsyp7q6%2Fthis_dude_made_an_alternative_reddit_on_a%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/syp7q6/this_dude_made_an_alternative_reddit_on_a/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 18:31:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;I’ve accidentally found out about this guy a few days ago and it’s quite mind blowing. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Developer called Esteban Abaora has developed a serverless, adminless and decentralized Reddit alternative that will run on a blockchain kind of system (&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; it will actually use &amp;amp;quot;public key based addressing&amp;amp;quot; and a peer-to-peer pubsub network.&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;)&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Pretty crazy stuff right?!&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Developer believes that this design would solve the problems of a serverless, adminless decentralized Reddit alternative. It would allow unlimited amounts of subplebbits, users, posts, comments and votes. This is achieved by not caring about the order or availability of old data. It would allow users to post for free using an identical Reddit interface. It would allow subplebbit owners to moderate spam semi-automatically using their own captcha service over peer-to-peer pubsub. It would allow for all features that make Reddit addictive: upvotes, replies, notifications, awards, and a chance to make the &amp;amp;quot;front page&amp;amp;quot;. &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Finally, it would allow the Plebbit client developers to serve an unlimited amount of users, without any server, legal, advertising or moderation infrastructure.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/plebbit/whitepaper/discussions/2&quot;&amp;gt;https://github.com/plebbit/whitepaper/discussions/2&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What do you think? Im really surprised by the way he is planning this to work. Its neither DAG nor traditional blockchain. I&amp;amp;#39;m intrigued. Now your posts could live on forever! &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[部長說，自採用比特幣以來，薩爾瓦多的旅遊業增長了30%。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/syp0p8/tourism_in_el_salvador_up_30_since_bitcoin/?score=480&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsyp0p8%2Ftourism_in_el_salvador_up_30_since_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsyp0p8%2Ftourism_in_el_salvador_up_30_since_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/syp0p8/tourism_in_el_salvador_up_30_since_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 18:31:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[色情女演員拉娜-羅德斯顯然在她的NFT項目啓動後放棄了。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/syimeo/porn_actress_lana_rhoades_apparently_abandons_her/?score=352&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsyimeo%2Fporn_actress_lana_rhoades_apparently_abandons_her%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsyimeo%2Fporn_actress_lana_rhoades_apparently_abandons_her%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/syimeo/porn_actress_lana_rhoades_apparently_abandons_her/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 16:52:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[繼科羅拉多州之後，加州將允許用比特幣支付政府服務費用]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sybah4/after_colorado_california_to_allow_bitcoin/?score=310&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsybah4%2Fafter_colorado_california_to_allow_bitcoin%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsybah4%2Fafter_colorado_california_to_allow_bitcoin%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sybah4/after_colorado_california_to_allow_bitcoin/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 15:34:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一位藝術家炸燬了一輛價值25萬美元的蘭博基尼以抗議加密貨幣文化]]></title><description><![CDATA[一位名叫Shl0ms的藝術家炸燬了一輛價值25萬美元的蘭博基尼，以抗議加密貨幣
文化。
這位藝術家說："這項技術是非常有前途的，有許多我們可以用它來做的好事。
我們可以用它做很多好事，但也有很多可怕的事情正在發生。
用它來做。

Shl0ms說他選擇炸燬一輛蘭博，因爲它...]]></description><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sybsvu/an_artist_blew_up_a_250000_lamborghini_to_protest/?score=311&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsybsvu%2Fan_artist_blew_up_a_250000_lamborghini_to_protest%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FCryptoCurrency%2Fcomments%2Fsybsvu%2Fan_artist_blew_up_a_250000_lamborghini_to_protest%2F&amp;channel=CryptoCurrency&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/sybsvu/an_artist_blew_up_a_250000_lamborghini_to_protest/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 15:34:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&amp;lt;!-- SC_OFF --&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;An artist, Shl0ms, blew up a $250,000 Lamborghini to protest against crypto culture.&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;
The artist said, “This technology is incredibly promising, there are so many good things we can do with it but there are so many terrible things being done with it,” &amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Shl0ms said he chose blow up a Lambo because it “is a pretty potent representation of people simply engaging with crypto because it’s a way for them to make money off other people as quickly as possible.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;

&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;What do you think? Is this a reflection of crypto culture? Or a publicity stunt for the artist?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;!-- SC_ON --&amp;gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不要忘記]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/syn565/dont_forget/?score=406&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsyn565%2Fdont_forget%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsyn565%2Fdont_forget%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/syn565/dont_forget/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 15:34:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[專業人士的投資技巧]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/synba2/investing_tips_from_a_pro/?score=395&amp;original_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsynba2%2Finvesting_tips_from_a_pro%2F&amp;discuss_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2FBitcoin%2Fcomments%2Fsynba2%2Finvesting_tips_from_a_pro%2F&amp;channel=Bitcoin&amp;sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/reddit/r/Bitcoin/comments/synba2/investing_tips_from_a_pro/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 14:37:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我的荷蘭朋友@mylegacykit（假幣僞造和訴訟的第一來源）被停了微博。

你可以在他的新賬戶上關注他。@Arthur_van_Pelt https://t.co/fGDlQ9TkUd]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1496056082673848323/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1496056082673848323/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 12:51:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[[新帖]比特幣是西方世界需要的自由技術

"數百萬人爲了利潤而來，但爲了革命而留下。比特幣以一種獨特的方式教授經濟學、個人理財、數學、哲學、地緣政治、以及更多。

https://t.co/wIfMLSj1WC]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1496061390343352320/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1496061390343352320/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 12:51:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爆炸性新聞是Moderna和輝瑞的股票價格下跌，不是因爲VAERS，或DMED，甚至是被推翻的FOI 75暫停令--而是由於保險數據--金錢交易--人們正在出售。]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1496062813923590145/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1496062813923590145/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 12:51:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["備忘錄#比特幣債券"

首先他們無視你，然後他們嘲笑你... https://t.co/JiNdoJJpYN]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1496059537081700352/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1496059537081700352/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 12:51:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[木偶大師。https://t.co/ZhVax3fpeb]]></title><link>https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1496064744574398465/?sensitive=false</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://crypto.buzzing.cc/zh-Hant/tweet/1496064744574398465/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 12:51:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>